<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364383817160-1</Id><Topic><Title>Wow $321,665 Limo Bill for Joe Biden and Obama closes White House Tours &amp; Kids Easter Egg Hunt</Title><Username>vensh_u</Username><Timestamp>1364326114030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:28:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe Bidens Tax Payer Paid $500,000 a Nite Hotel Room in Paris Joe Bidens Tax Payer Paid $500,000 a Nite Hotel Room in Paris Democrats Fleecing the Taxpayer daily. Wow $321,665 Limo Bill for Joe Biden.</Msg><Username>badgermma_5555</Username><Timestamp>1364383817160</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 07:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364384183499-2</Id><Topic><Title>BEYONCE dedicates new song to Obama -♫♪ ♫ ♫♪ Yes Barack Your a Big Spender $$$ ♫ ♪♫♪ ♫ ♫♪ ♫ ♪ and liar to ♫♪ ♫</Title><Username>maxwizard66675</Username><Timestamp>1364301204131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 08:33:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bought the record as a wedding gift. Oh well. Hope they like it. Gay guy who is getting married if Gay Marriage Oked by courts.</Msg><Username>badgermma_5555</Username><Timestamp>1364384183499</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 07:36:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364384294530-3</Id><Topic><Title>"Joe Legal" and "Jose Illegal"</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1364350722917</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 22:18:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So that is why Obama raised my taxes on Jan.1, 2013 and now wants the GOP to give him another tax increase. Hell No obama must Go and Joe Illegal with him.</Msg><Username>badgermma_5555</Username><Timestamp>1364384294530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 07:38:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364384451752-4</Id><Topic><Title>2013 Pinocchio Award goes to Obama again for lying more than any President in History</Title><Username>maxwizard66675</Username><Timestamp>1364302041407</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 08:47:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Clinton or John Edwards will give Obama the 2013 Pinocchio Award. LOL!</Msg><Username>badgermma_5555</Username><Timestamp>1364384451752</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 07:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364384613982-5</Id><Topic><Title>juniorsclassmate_5 YOU CAN POST AGAIN WHEN I SAY YOU CAN</Title><Username>maxwizard66675</Username><Timestamp>1364302469562</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>juniorsclassmate_ remember no posting lies or You will be run off the Board Again. God is watching and keeping score.</Msg><Username>badgermma_5555</Username><Timestamp>1364384613982</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 07:43:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364386230205-6</Id><Title>Expect flash crash of 15% (single day decline)</Title><Msg>This is 2007 on steroids. California housing bubble back, etc.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1364386230205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:10:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364387040357-7</Id><Topic><Title>LIBERAL DEMOCRAT PROFESSOR KILLS SELF AFTER CAUGHT MOLESTING YOUNG CHILDREN</Title><Username>unemployed_obama_youth</Username><Timestamp>1364354611869</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 23:23:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hell, liberal or bagger, makes no difference to me whether or not he kills himself. I just wish that Rep. Mark Foley (R-Fla.) would have done the same too. Don't you?</Msg><Username>triglicons</Username><Timestamp>1364387040357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364387369821-8</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>vincent.middleton</Username><Timestamp>1362511286358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 14:21:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>meynterrence</Username><Timestamp>1364387369821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:29:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364387441169-9</Id><Title>I AM ABOUT READY TO DO SOMETHING YOU REPUBLICAN BAGGERS HAVE FAILED TO DO IN YEARS...</Title><Msg>Jump in the shower, put on some nice clean clothes, and spend the day out-of-doors with friends. Remember those days back in "ought one" when you had a partial life before Bush made you whackos hole up in your basements and trailers with those "color coded duct tape plastic around the windows and doors" days??? What a bunch of old naive dumbazz losers!</Msg><Username>triglicons</Username><Timestamp>1364387441169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364387996768-10</Id><Topic><Title>I AM ABOUT READY TO DO SOMETHING YOU REPUBLICAN BAGGERS HAVE FAILED TO DO IN YEARS...</Title><Username>triglicons</Username><Timestamp>1364387441169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:30:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good morning jr. what a fn loser. you should just try to keep one ID and stick with it child. Ignore for the board idiot stalker.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364387996768</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364388094660-11</Id><Topic><Title>Expect flash crash of 15% (single day decline)</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1364386230205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think CA is about to go bankrupt. many other states will follow. the EU is the least of our worries. I think cal alone is a bigger economy than most of the EU.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364388094660</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364388434858-12</Id><Topic><Title>Wow $321,665 Limo Bill for Joe Biden and Obama closes White House Tours &amp; Kids Easter Egg Hunt</Title><Username>vensh_u</Username><Timestamp>1364326114030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:28:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>every time obama flys his family and dogs in each of their own air force one jests it cost million. manchelles hair appointments cost us millions along with sending the oldest daughter and all her friends with 25 SS agents to mexico cost millions. obama wants to hurt the children. he spends their money keeps them out of WH and aborts them. obviously obama has a war on children!</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364388434858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364389088739-13</Id><Title>not a peep from obama al and jesse</Title><Msg>about white baby shot by black kids! the true racists are the ones calling racism, never a peep when it goes the other way. creepy dividers using their own poison of sterotyping to divide. americans need to stand up to these racists and call them out on their stunts. they dont want to eliminate it they want to nurture it.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364389088739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:58:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364389211827-14</Id><Title>I don't like Palin's communist positions</Title><Msg>Whether the rest of America had a clue to what exactly she was babbling about is doubtful. So a quick summary of what is going on in the 49th state is probably necessary. State government is stinking rich up here thanks to the Palin-championed oil tax, but oil production has been steadily falling since her brief stint in office. Some now argue the ever-decreasing flow threatens to shorten the life of operation for the trans-Alaska oil pipeline -- the 800-mile conduit that carries crude from the Arctic oil fields to Prince William Sound, where the oil is transported on tanker ships to the Lower 48. Continued pipeline operation is vital to the state because the taxes, royalties and fees on the crude flowing through the pipe fund about 90 percent of state government in Alaska, which likes to think of itself as the "owner state," as much of the oil sits on state lands. It is this "owner state" idea Palin flaunted before CPAC. It is a radical concept born of the Communist Manifesto, which argued that workers should own the means of production instead of being mere cogs in the machinery of businesses driven by individuals -- the so-called "bourgeoisie." "By bourgeoisie is meant the class of modern capitalists, owners of the means of social production and employers of wage labour," Karl Marx and Frederick Engels observed in 1848. Back then, the "bourgeoisie" were what Palin now calls the "crony capitalists," the people with the financial resources and political connections to make things happen. The bourgeoisie/crony capitalists contrasted with the "proletariat," who Marx and Engels described simply as "the class of modern wage labourers who, having no means of production of their own, are reduced to selling their labour power in order to live."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364389211827</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:00:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364389216849-15</Id><Topic><Title>A woman makes a choice A bad one</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364388565853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jr I see you keep posting all I see "Post hidden because you ignored this user" I put you on ignore idiot so stop wasting your time loser. get a job. I am not your dad go find him somewhere else little pet.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364389216849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:00:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364389304832-16</Id><Topic><Title>A woman makes a choice A bad one</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364388565853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>idiot! a fertilized zygote is a contingent human being. honestly your denial about what is living inside a woman's womb is absurd! what do you think it is, a pumpkin?</Msg><Username>dumbpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364389304832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:01:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364389577029-17</Id><Topic><Title>A woman makes a choice A bad one</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364388565853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah,,, changing the topic when confronted with what's living inside a woman's womb. Interesting! So by your changing the topic, you admit you are wrong about this, eh? And</Msg><Username>dumbpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364389577029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:06:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364390193677-18</Id><Topic><Title>A woman makes a choice A bad one</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364388565853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>talking about chickens? I'm talking about human life here!</Msg><Username>dumbpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364390193677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364390368807-19</Id><Title>I don't think anyone should have the legal right to end the life of a human being who has no say in the matter</Title><Msg>yeah, it's legal to do so right now. but as we know from our country's history, laws have not always been just! for example: Jim Crow Laws, 3/5ths compromise, etc...</Msg><Username>dumbpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364390368807</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:19:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364390767889-20</Id><Topic><Title>not a peep from obama al and jesse</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364389088739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:58:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah dead, you see they already arrested the guys that did it, no real need to protest when justice is being done now is there?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364390767889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:26:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364391565014-21</Id><Topic><Title>I AM ABOUT READY TO DO SOMETHING YOU REPUBLICAN BAGGERS HAVE FAILED TO DO IN YEARS...</Title><Username>triglicons</Username><Timestamp>1364387441169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:30:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What? You have friends?? I think not!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>aaaa99999999999999999</Username><Timestamp>1364391565014</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:39:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364391695039-22</Id><Title>Dumbivans supper</Title><Msg>Dumb posted last night about dining on "filet minion' !! LOLOLOLOLOLOL This is a guy who says he goes on fancy vacations and loves to dine in high end restaurants but he cant spell " filet mignon"' LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL EFFING HILARIOUS!!!! Today he's dining on his foot!!!!!HEEHEEHEEHEEHEEHEEHEE</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364391695039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:41:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364391710329-23</Id><Title>we need to cut off the welfare communist Red states</Title><Msg>In Hale County, Alabama, 1 in 4 working-age adults is on disability. On the day government checks come in every month, banks stay open late, Main Street fills up with cars, and anybody looking to unload an old TV or armchair has a yard sale. Sonny Ryan, a retired judge in town, didn't hear disability cases in his courtroom. But the subject came up often. He described one exchange he had with a man who was on disability but looked healthy. "Just out of curiosity, what is your disability?" the judge asked from the bench. "I have high blood pressure," the man said. "So do I," the judge said. "What else?" "I have diabetes." "So do I."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364391710329</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:41:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364393796395-24</Id><Topic><Title>Expect flash crash of 15% (single day decline)</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1364386230205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Calif. governor claims the budget problems are solved. They are using trick accounting to hide 20 billion+ deficits in that state. In fact, many local governments are about to go bankrupt. Too much debt burden world wide.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1364393796395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:16:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364395683609-25</Id><Topic><Title>we need to cut off the welfare communist Red states</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364391710329</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:41:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cali is in the biggest hole dyp shyyt.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364395683609</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:48:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364395700430-26</Id><Topic><Title>we need to cut off the welfare communist Red states</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364391710329</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:41:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>let us start there.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364395700430</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364395842716-27</Id><Title>dumb calls itself dumb</Title><Msg>bwahahahahahahahaha him and barney need to get obamas dyck out of there mouths...ignore for the ignorant maggo id. fn loser, needs to get a job and stop whining.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364395842716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:50:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364395930777-28</Id><Title>Affordable HC act</Title><Msg>BWAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA liberals are fn idiots. they love being lied too. at least billy was better at it.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364395930777</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364396217732-29</Id><Title>Faux outrage</Title><Msg>Fox Freaks: 'Jim Carrey Has Killed More People Than All the Rifles Combined' Posted: 26 Mar 2013 05:00 PM PDT Fox Freaks: 'Jim Carrey Has Killed More People Than All the Rifles Combined' Fox faux outrage has been in overdrive since the release of a comedy video by actor Jim Carrey ("Cold Dead Hand") yesterday. Carrey's spoof of the NRA and Charlton Heston had The Five spitting nails, with Greg Gutfeld leading the charge, calling Carrey "a pathetic, sad, little freak" and "a modern bigot", among other epithets. GUTFELD: “He is the most pathetic tool on the face of the earth. And I hope his career is dead, and he ends up sleeping in a car the way his life began. This video only made me want to go out and only buy a gun. He thinks this is biting satire and going after rural America and a dead man. Let’s talk about Charlton Heston. Charlton Heston was one of the first actors to be behind the civil rights movement and march. What did this jackass Jim Carrey do? He was behind the anti-vaccine panic. There are what, 165,000 people that died from measles last year, according to the World Health Organization.” “Jim Carrey has killed more people than all the rifles combined,” Gutfeld continued. “He is a dirty, stinking coward. He is a moral coward. He did a video attacking rural America. But he wouldn’t do video about gangs, which kills way more people with handguns — he wouldn’t do that because he is worried about his career. Such a pathetic, sad, little freak. He is a jiberring mess. He is a modern bigot, he is a modern bigot. He is a bottomless pit of insecurity and the desire for acceptance is why he is doing this, because he knows in his heart he is a fraud.” Dana Perino chirped in that Carrey was attacking rural America, while Eric Bolling saw it as self-promotion. Token liberal Bob Beckel wondered why "a foreigner" (Jim Carrey is Canadian) was commenting at all. And on and on it went. This is just one of several more versio</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1364396217732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:56:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364396236401-30</Id><Topic><Title>opsie</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364395641983</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:47:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh no!</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364396236401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:57:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364396600304-31</Id><Topic><Title>Affordable HC act</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364395930777</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>opsie, lied to again.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364396600304</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 11:03:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364396661948-32</Id><Topic><Title>Affordable HC act</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364395930777</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bush did it bwahahahahahahahahahaha fn idiots deserve what they are about to get handed to them from the snake oil sales man.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364396661948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 11:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364396732810-33</Id><Title>liberals mentality</Title><Msg>better all americans suffer then just one or two.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364396732810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 11:05:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364396786647-34</Id><Topic><Title>not a peep from obama al and jesse</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364389088739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:58:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>where is al and jeese! obama could that have been your son?</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364396786647</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 11:06:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364397000475-35</Id><Title>FACT!</Title><Msg>obama bankrupted america. 7 trillion is an almost double nat debt still have 3 years to go. think about all that debt with borrow rates lowest in american history. imagine if they went up just 1%. children are already poor before they are born. fed also has 4 trillion he will need to dump from balance sheets. this gets real bad. hopfully like billy obama can keep pumping the bubble and pass the problem to the next guy...it is the liberals way.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364397000475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 11:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364397321489-36</Id><Title>jr worships me I bet it cant not post a reply to my every comment</Title><Msg>BWHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA i is my little pet...watch as it hangs on my EVERY word. waiting all day for me to post so it can say something BWAHAHAHAHAHAHA, sounds like someone needs a job :(</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364397321489</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 11:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364397523114-37</Id><Topic><Title>remember when harry reid exploited marines that were killed</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364397468837</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 11:17:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>to bad harry cant just change its id.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364397523114</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 11:18:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364397852477-38</Id><Title>2% tax increase for middle class</Title><Msg>higher Food HC and school. just what the middle class needed. BWHAHAHAHAHA so I guess all that fair share obama was spewing was just a bunch of lies...he just wanted their votes. now they are getting hammered by his policies. dont forget who lowered your taxes middle class. yep good old w had your back after all.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364397852477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364399432660-39</Id><Topic><Title>Secret CSCO Info Revealed</Title><Username>willson_ethan</Username><Timestamp>1363607782953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 07:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for share</Msg><Username>liamsmith380</Username><Timestamp>1364399432660</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 11:50:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364399575763-40</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbivans supper</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364391695039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:41:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where's dumbivan??LOLOLOL Eating his " filet minion"LOLOLOLOL Funny he calls others dumb red necks or Texans when they make a boo-boo. He runs away and hides when he does it. HEEHEEHEEHEEHEEHEE Its spelled " FILET MIGNON" you effing dummy. LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364399575763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 11:52:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364401482408-41</Id><Topic><Title>Faux outrage</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1364396217732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like gfo once again shows its ignorance and lack of intelligence. Maybe it's the libTARD brainwashing. Even Bob, the 5's only Democrat was perplexed by Carrey's attack on Heston. FYI you IDIOT, Heston was one of the FEW in Hollywood when he was young who SPOKE OUT for civil rights when it was not a popular thing to do. Carrey was attacking a dead guy and that was the rub you ignorant lowlife.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1364401482408</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 12:24:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364401681390-42</Id><Title>THE DEMS HOPE FOR HOMEO MARRIAGE and a GAYOBAMA DYNASTY IS</Title><Msg>ABOUT AS SAFE AS money in a Cypress bank. KOKSUCKERS</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364401681390</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 12:28:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364402307418-43</Id><Title>MAGOO, I DUB THEE SODOMITESUZY</Title><Msg>your new id and much more accurate and descriptive of you than your other ids</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364402307418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 12:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364402402614-44</Id><Topic><Title>THE DEMS HOPE FOR HOMEO MARRIAGE and a GAYOBAMA DYNASTY IS</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364401681390</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 12:28:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are a bigot, a racist, your posts make that clear junior5</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364402402614</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 12:40:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364403643429-45</Id><Topic><Title>MAGOO, I DUB THEE SODOMITESUZY</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364402307418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 12:38:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He wont use his dumbivan id for awhile. That one is in hiding.LOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364403643429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:00:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364403992707-46</Id><Topic><Title>MAGOO, I DUB THEE SODOMITESUZY</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364402307418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 12:38:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, he is caught with over-using his junior5 id right now. That's his "attack id", but really he comes across as a big sissy no matter what id he tries to hide behind, a sissy is a sissy by any other id LOL!!</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364403992707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:06:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364404202079-47</Id><Title>SEVENTEEN YEARS AGO SLICK WILLY SIGNED THE DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE ACT</Title><Msg>now he repudiates his own law. What a confused mutherfuhker he is</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364404202079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:10:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364404378213-48</Id><Topic><Title>SEVENTEEN YEARS AGO SLICK WILLY SIGNED THE DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE ACT</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364404202079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:10:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dont you know that was pop then. see liberals do whatever it is that the media tells them. they dont have a moral compass they let the masses tell them what is moral. just like dopey saying debt ceiling raises are unethical now it is unethical to not do it. no direction just following the heard.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364404378213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:12:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364404381818-49</Id><Topic><Title>SEVENTEEN YEARS AGO SLICK WILLY SIGNED THE DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE ACT</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364404202079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:10:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He and Hillary are " evolving ". They are are getting ready for 2016. And the libs will suck it up.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1364404381818</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364404897323-50</Id><Topic><Title>Want To See A List Of "OUTED" Republicans, How About Republican Pedophiles?</Title><Username>the.word999</Username><Timestamp>1364318933065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 13:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sodomitesuzy, sodomy violates the law. Please get help you creep.</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364404897323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:21:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364405396903-51</Id><Topic><Title>teabilly dope ROTF!!</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364403936892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee Louis if you're going to the Hill why are you parking illegally two miles away? The distance between the Capitol, at one end of the National Mall, and the Lincoln Memorial at the other, is 2 miles. That’s a long walk for most people.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364405396903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:29:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364405545325-52</Id><Topic><Title>Faux outrage</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1364396217732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tea billies are to funny, notice FAUX news had nothing to say about Carrey's position just personal attacks, just like the billies on this board</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364405545325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:32:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364405585685-53</Id><Topic><Title>SEVENTEEN YEARS AGO SLICK WILLY SIGNED THE DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE ACT</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364404202079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:10:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes a dem "evolves" a GOP flips hahahahahahaha fn liberals use words. all they do is talk expect misery and opposite results. enjoy that tax middle class. guess dopey was just flapping his blue lips when he said the same thing over and over and over. not a peep since elections. come on dopey where is all the tax the rich tough talk?</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364405585685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:33:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364405813818-54</Id><Topic><Title>Faux outrage</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1364396217732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny I can't find any links between Carrey and the anti-vaccine movement, funny maybe FAUX confused him with Michelle Bachmann, LOL oh and tea billies, there are no liberals on any FAUX programs, there are some tea billies that pretend to play the part in order to make liberals look more stupid then tea billies</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364405813818</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:36:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364406135806-55</Id><Title>they are turning up everywhere tea billies, time to panic, LOL</Title><Msg>NBC newscaster Jenna Wolfe made her own headlines Wednesday when she came out publicly with partner Stephanie Gosk and announced they’re having a baby. The Today show's Sunday anchor said she and Gosk, a foreign correspondent at NBC, have been together three years, plan to wed and embarked on “Operation Baby” in December. “My girlfriend, Stephanie Gosk, and I are expecting a baby girl the end of August,” Wolfe, 39, wrote in the debut post for her new pregnancy blog. “We felt like we wanted to share our adventures with a wide-eyed, little person,” she blogged. “The more we talked about it, the better the idea seemed.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364406135806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:42:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364407023442-56</Id><Topic><Title>Show Me The Money! CSCO Style!</Title><Username>fise.more</Username><Timestamp>1364398045103</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 11:27:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow amazing report, impressive...</Msg><Username>anniyygom</Username><Timestamp>1364407023442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364407048606-57</Id><Topic><Title>A woman makes a choice A bad one</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364388565853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chickens?</Msg><Username>dumbpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364407048606</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:57:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364407405722-58</Id><Title>BammyCare = The Fall of the Democrap Party</Title><Msg>15-35% instant cost of living increase, waiting in lines and filling out multiple pages of paperwork to have a mole removed, cancer patience denied chemo therapy... It's already started in some areas. Nice going Oblunder, you're doin' a heck of a job reshaping Amerika...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364407405722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:03:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364407648276-59</Id><Topic><Title>THE DEMS HOPE FOR HOMEO MARRIAGE and a GAYOBAMA DYNASTY IS</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364401681390</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 12:28:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so did you pick out your bridal gown yet sodomitesuzy?? LOL!</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364407648276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:07:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364407798970-60</Id><Topic><Title>BammyCare = The Fall of the Democrap Party</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364407405722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:03:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Olosercare is a huge fuhking nightmare and blight on this nation that will take us to 3rd world status</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364407798970</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:09:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364407869958-61</Id><Topic><Title>BammyCare = The Fall of the Democrap Party</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364407405722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:03:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is that what's going on in the pretend rabbit hole, LOL meanwhile in the real world 8 million children get to stay on their parents insurance, 46 million people have access to healthcare, 150,000 children live every year that would have died.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364407869958</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:11:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364408555812-62</Id><Title>It isn't clear why tea billies are so opposed to gay marriage</Title><Msg>except for their outright hatred for anyone that isn't exactly like them</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364408555812</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:22:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364408746430-63</Id><Topic><Title>BammyCare = The Fall of the Democrap Party</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364407405722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:03:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"cancer patience" are those people with cancer that don't mind waiting in line? carrik show of her second grade education almost daily</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364408746430</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:25:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364409088902-64</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbivans supper</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364391695039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:41:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So how was that "filet minion "last night,Dumbphony? LOLOLOLOLOL You go to all those fancy restaurants and never saw " filet mignon " on the menu at least one time? HEEHEEHEEHEEHEEHEE Busted yourself again you phony lying bastid!! HEEHEEHEEHEEHEE</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364409088902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:31:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364409148068-65</Id><Title>JUNIOR5/MAGOO,ETC HATES US "BREEDERS" AS THEY CALL US HETEROS</Title><Msg>they envy the fact that we can make babies the RIGHT way, no surrogates needed LOL!!! They despise that their sodomite kind would die out in a generation if the creeps didn't "recruit" by grooming and molesting little boys and girls. They are shameless reprobates who are hellbound!</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364409148068</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:32:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364409388689-66</Id><Topic><Title>JUNIOR5/MAGOO,ETC HATES US "BREEDERS" AS THEY CALL US HETEROS</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364409148068</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:32:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>word!!!</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1364409388689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364409402521-67</Id><Topic><Title>JUNIOR5/MAGOO,ETC HATES US "BREEDERS" AS THEY CALL US HETEROS</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364409148068</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:32:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior loves licking little boys tricycle seats .Says they are yummy and gives him a woody!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364409402521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:36:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364409574067-68</Id><Topic><Title>'cancer patience denied chemo therapy' ROTF!!</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364409462982</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:37:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you gotta admit it's pretty funny reading her #$%$ posts, one has to wonder if she is for real, or if she is a liberal just trying to make conservatives look stupid.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364409574067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:39:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364409609316-69</Id><Title>OBAMA ADMIN. ARBITRARILY REFUSES TO DEFEND DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE</Title><Msg>act before the SCOTUS! Once again he has violated his presidential oath to defend the laws of this land! The last time was on deporting illegals. This POS is NO president, he is a TRAITOR and should be arrested and tried on the grounds of TREASON!</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1364409609316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:40:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364409699808-70</Id><Topic><Title>'cancer patience denied chemo therapy' ROTF!!</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364409462982</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:37:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Filet Minion"!!!! LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL Wonder if Dumb is a #$%$ from Texas??LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364409699808</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364409729138-71</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ADMIN. ARBITRARILY REFUSES TO DEFEND DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1364409609316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:40:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why do you want Obama to defend a law that violates the Constitution, I thought all you tea billies loved the Constitution.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364409729138</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:42:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364409887616-72</Id><Topic><Title>'cancer patience denied chemo therapy' ROTF!!</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364409462982</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:37:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm starting to lose my patient with you carey, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364409887616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364409948308-73</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ADMIN. ARBITRARILY REFUSES TO DEFEND DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1364409609316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:40:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that LAW was brought into being by his hero/fellow demcrap Slick Willie LMAO! AND it has never been ruled "unconstitutional" you lying POS</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1364409948308</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364410037413-74</Id><Topic><Title>A woman makes a choice A bad one</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364388565853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your basic ignorance is not surprising but the depth is.... Sperm, released at the point of 'wacking off' are not zygote. Fertilized egg, fertilized by sperm is the zygote that becomes the next human being. Women ovulate monthly. If not fertilized, that egg is flushed. Abortion is murder. America has destroyed 50 million babies...very sad. We will suffer, and are now suffering, because of this choice.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1364410037413</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:47:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364410040395-75</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ADMIN. ARBITRARILY REFUSES TO DEFEND DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1364409609316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:40:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will be this week or next</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364410040395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:47:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364410151763-76</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ADMIN. ARBITRARILY REFUSES TO DEFEND DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1364409609316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:40:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL shows what you know mowron, the ruling won't be until JUNE!</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1364410151763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364410222034-77</Id><Title>THERE IS NO 'GAY MARRIAGE'...sort of like 'dark-light', or 'dry water'....</Title><Msg>In a parallel, disturbed universe, gay marriage may exist. It cannot exist in this one! Gay is pathology, as is adultery, arrogance, cruelty, lying and deceit. Defining 'lying' as 'alternate truth telling' does not change the pathology. No harmony, no peace, no joy....no sustenance in that #$%$ relationship. Just fact.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1364410222034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364410241518-78</Id><Topic><Title>'cancer patience denied chemo therapy' ROTF!!</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364409462982</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:37:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't give Junior his anal leakage problem.That happened from his disgusting sexual practices with winos behind the Greyhound bus station.LOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364410241518</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:50:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364411069253-79</Id><Topic><Title>'cancer patience denied chemo therapy' ROTF!!</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364409462982</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:37:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>denied it because he didn't have the patient to wait around, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364411069253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:04:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364411425587-80</Id><Title>LETS SAY AS THE HOMEODEMS WANT, THE WHOLE COUNTRY, OR MOST OF</Title><Msg>IT BECOMES HOMEOS! So where do they get their future perverts from? What keeps their twisted lifestyle alive then? As it is now, if homeomarriage is made "legal", it, as with abortion, will only assist in furthering undermining and diminishing the U.S. population and taxpayer base. Their godless philosophy therefore will be allowed to impoverish (further) and destroy this country in mere decades.</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1364411425587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364411628189-81</Id><Title>LMAO----Bill O'Reilly Supports Gay Marriage.</Title><Msg>On Fox News Tuesday he tells "bible thumpers" to keep their nose out of other peoples business"</Msg><Username>times_x</Username><Timestamp>1364411628189</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364411684048-82</Id><Topic><Title>BammyCare = The Fall of the Democrap Party</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364407405722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:03:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROMNEY LANDSLIDE????</Msg><Username>times_x</Username><Timestamp>1364411684048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:14:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364411758526-83</Id><Topic><Title>LETS SAY AS THE HOMEODEMS WANT, THE WHOLE COUNTRY, OR MOST OF</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1364411425587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:10:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so answer the question DOOFUS! If they get their way, where do the new taxpayers come from to support the eldderly, the disabled, those in POVERTY, etc. etc. Where does the money come from to build the bridges and roads, maintain a military, police, fire departments, ETC!? You fools are short-sighted just as with Abortion and how it has devastated the taxbase! Few people = fewer taxes!</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1364411758526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:15:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364411824121-84</Id><Title>Remember Baggers Telling Us For 4 Straight Years...."Anybody Can Beat The Marxist Muslum"?</Title><Msg>ROMNEY LANDSLIDE.......... WOWZA!!!!</Msg><Username>times_x</Username><Timestamp>1364411824121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:17:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364411952088-85</Id><Title>BREAKING: It's Now Being Confirmed Drstone Has terminal Cancer!</Title><Msg>We can only pray he goes quick.....painfully...but quick.</Msg><Username>newt_gringitch</Username><Timestamp>1364411952088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364412137105-86</Id><Topic><Title>SEVENTEEN YEARS AGO SLICK WILLY SIGNED THE DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE ACT</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364404202079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:10:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>12 years ago Bush told everyone Iraq had WMD's 8 years later he admitted that they didn't. What a confused American killing mutherfuhker he is.</Msg><Username>times_x</Username><Timestamp>1364412137105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:22:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364412237186-87</Id><Title>Cisco dividend?</Title><Msg>Where has csco's dividend gone? Seems an announcement is appropriate if there is going to be one this quarter.</Msg><Username>tppfan</Username><Timestamp>1364412237186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:23:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364412301122-88</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: It's Now Being Confirmed Drstone Has terminal Cancer!</Title><Username>newt_gringitch</Username><Timestamp>1364411952088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FTS-- I want that lying KOCHsucker to go really really slow and watch himself being ate up right before his own eyes in the mirror. Like the majority of Republican posters we can all assume he's one huge fatfaahkur that will take some time for it to consume him.</Msg><Username>times_x</Username><Timestamp>1364412301122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:25:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364412440371-89</Id><Topic><Title>LETS SAY AS THE HOMEODEMS WANT, THE WHOLE COUNTRY, OR MOST OF</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1364411425587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:10:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>right on....the dems as usual do not think things through, they just jump onboard with what they think will get them votes somehow. They could care less about this nation, they are all traitors and faygs</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1364412440371</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:27:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364412518654-90</Id><Topic><Title>SEVENTEEN YEARS AGO SLICK WILLY SIGNED THE DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE ACT</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364404202079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:10:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Hillary runs in 2016 maybe we'll see all the Youtube videos of her talking about Saddam's WMDs . We might even know what happened at Benghazi by then.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1364412518654</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:28:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364412571276-91</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ADMIN. ARBITRARILY REFUSES TO DEFEND DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1364409609316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:40:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Relax everyone. John Roberts is just going to say that gay marriage is a tax</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1364412571276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364412600207-92</Id><Topic><Title>SEVENTEEN YEARS AGO SLICK WILLY SIGNED THE DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE ACT</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364404202079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:10:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>actually you lie again magoo/timesx POS. W never later said there were no WMDs in Iraq, 100s were found when we enteref it. Now GFU sissy!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1364412600207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:30:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364413228154-93</Id><Title>Did Mark Kelly falsify Form 4473</Title><Msg>He attempted to purchase a gun for political purposes. So should he go to prison? I say yes. Is he mentally disturb for such an act? I say yes. These zealots should be prosecuted for falsifying government documents.</Msg><Username>kashkow</Username><Timestamp>1364413228154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364413574292-94</Id><Topic><Title>Did Mark Kelly falsify Form 4473</Title><Username>kashkow</Username><Timestamp>1364413228154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:40:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After what he and his wife have gone through,it's understandable why he did what he did. If it was wrong, he deserves a break.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1364413574292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364413601250-95</Id><Topic><Title>SEVENTEEN YEARS AGO SLICK WILLY SIGNED THE DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE ACT</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364404202079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:10:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>actually you lie again magoo/timesx POS W never later said there were no WMD's in Iraq 100's were found when we enteref. now GFU sissy! ********************************************************************************** If I were you jay I'd do a web search before you continue on with your ignorance. In fact, I know how much that you old dudes enjoy fetching your quotes and spin from the website YouTube you can actually witness for yourself George W. Bush admitting that they NOW realize that Saddam Hussien had no WMD's and had actually destroyed them after the first gulf war in compliance with U.N resolutions. Don't take it from me, Bush is the one that said it himself. So was he lying then when he said that there were or is he lying now? If you have a compelling argument with actual proof from some credible source other than some blogger I will gladly read what you have with an open mind. What's your source?</Msg><Username>ee_degree</Username><Timestamp>1364413601250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:46:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364413634570-96</Id><Topic><Title>Show Me The Money! CSCO Style!</Title><Username>fise.more</Username><Timestamp>1364398045103</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 11:27:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy, hold and get rich!</Msg><Username>bbakeerke</Username><Timestamp>1364413634570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364414101337-97</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbivans supper</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364391695039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:41:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Magoo loves to make fun of others typos and misspellings.Funny that somebody nailed him for his bad spelling.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1364414101337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:55:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364414479326-98</Id><Topic><Title>SEVENTEEN YEARS AGO SLICK WILLY SIGNED THE DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE ACT</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364404202079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:10:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>crickets</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364414479326</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:01:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364414520601-99</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbivans supper</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364391695039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:41:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>food stamps buy a lot these days.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364414520601</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364414659934-100</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbivans supper</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364391695039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 09:41:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>remember when he lashed out and said it makes more in a day then i will make in my whole life...hahahahahahahahahahahahahaha then he tells us he does not pay any taxes because it is rich.hahahahahahahahahahahahah fn idiot aka magoo jr is on ignore.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364414659934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:04:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364415246662-101</Id><Topic><Title>Show Me The Money! CSCO Style!</Title><Username>fise.more</Username><Timestamp>1364398045103</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 11:27:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very impressive!!</Msg><Username>angelpz31</Username><Timestamp>1364415246662</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:14:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364415271636-102</Id><Title>Little hope seen for millions priced out of health overhaul</Title><Msg>opsie....obama sticks it to the middle class again. bwhahahahahahahahahahaha.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364415271636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:14:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364415502467-103</Id><Title>LAZY BUM OBAMAS HAVEHAD OVER A MONTH OF VACATION ALREADY IN 2013</Title><Msg>costing millions in taxpayer dollars, just as I predicted he would do in a 2nd term. Look for much more where that came from. FIRE the slug!</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1364415502467</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:18:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364415525727-104</Id><Topic><Title>A woman makes a choice A bad one</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364388565853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what is worse we will now be forced to pay for it. i dont agree with murder but have to pay for it. sick fn sick. liberals have no morals. cumbaya everyone has rights but an innocent child has none. if he /she makes it passed abortion it gets obamas 50k worth of debt. obamas secret war on children.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364415525727</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:18:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364415584949-105</Id><Topic><Title>A woman makes a choice A bad one</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364388565853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 08:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>look the magoojr bumb id running out of ids. ignore idiot! fn loser needs a job.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364415584949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:19:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364415711731-106</Id><Title>maxine waters said sequester will cost america 180 million jobs</Title><Msg>ROTFLOL, these are the liberal heros.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364415711731</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:21:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364415749482-107</Id><Topic><Title>SEVENTEEN YEARS AGO SLICK WILLY SIGNED THE DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE ACT</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364404202079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:10:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>exactly wonka. The dems are lying Sacks o shet. Troops reported finding 100s of WMDS when they entered Iraq that contained yellow cake and others with nerve gas and poison.</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1364415749482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:22:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364415869518-108</Id><Topic><Title>SEVENTEEN YEARS AGO SLICK WILLY SIGNED THE DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE ACT</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364404202079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:10:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slick once again eats his own words now and proves that he as a rapist is lower than a POS</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1364415869518</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:24:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364416320385-109</Id><Topic><Title>Little hope seen for millions priced out of health overhaul</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364415271636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:14:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they will "haf ta" learn. nancy did say we have to pass it to know what is in it. surprise...have fun middle class, this should help you hahahahahahahaha fn idiots.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364416320385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:32:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364416551616-110</Id><Title>remember when obama said rich "haf ta" pay their fair share</Title><Msg>ROTFLOL.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364416551616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:35:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364416732655-111</Id><Title>obama's affordable HC</Title><Msg>ROTFLOL</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364416732655</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:38:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364416981346-112</Id><Title>remember when billy clinton kept lying to us</Title><Msg>Liberals made him their hero. they hang on his every word like he is a god. they love being lied to. ROTFLOL.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364416981346</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:43:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364417045723-113</Id><Topic><Title>BammyCare = The Fall of the Democrap Party</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364407405722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:03:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no one will be able to afford his affordable HC.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364417045723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:44:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364417288712-114</Id><Topic><Title>BammyCare = The Fall of the Democrap Party</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364407405722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:03:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they will have to learn they passed it so now they will have to learn what in it. did you know almost 20% of what was in the bill that paid for it has already been stripped out by dems. so now we as a nation cant pay for it either. get it passed then take out the clauses that pay for it. dems will be crying for higher taxes 75% rates on everyone soon. have fun. it took abe the republican 8 years to free the slaves and dopey only 5 to make us all slaves again.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364417288712</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:48:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364417364371-115</Id><Topic><Title>remember when obama said rich "haf ta" pay their fair share</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364416551616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>crickets now.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364417364371</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:49:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364417416473-116</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco dividend?</Title><Username>tppfan</Username><Timestamp>1364412237186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:23:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They paid the last one a month early (Dec. of 2012 instead of Jan. of 2013) so it would be taxed at a lower rate. Still it looks like they are delinquent if they are going to stay on schedule and pay one around April 25. Generally takes at least a month from declaration to record date to payment.</Msg><Username>rlb799</Username><Timestamp>1364417416473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:50:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364417444622-117</Id><Title>next year liberals will be throwing eggs at obama</Title><Msg>wait they will feel the pain of 8 years in imaginary land where ideals that seem warm and fuzzy never happen and only bring about more pain.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1364417444622</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 16:50:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364418340608-118</Id><Title>Remember Dumb complimenting his wife</Title><Msg>Said " Dear,that filet minion was great!!!!!!" LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL Then his wife said. "Wow, you are a stupid fk. "</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364418340608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 17:05:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364419110644-119</Id><Topic><Title>SEVENTEEN YEARS AGO SLICK WILLY SIGNED THE DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE ACT</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1364404202079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 13:10:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course there were no WMD's even Bush joked about not finding any, but reality doesn't have a place in the Tea Billies imaginary reality, LOL w poll supports that theory. The poll, constructed by Dartmouth government professor Benjamin Valentino and conducted by YouGov from April 26 to May 2, found that fully 63 percent of Republican respondents still believed that Iraq had weapons of mass destruction when the U.S. invaded in 2003. By contrast, 27 percent of independents and 15 percent of Democrats shared that view. Jim Lobe, chief of the Inter Press Service's Washington bureau, reported the finding in his blog on Wednesday. The Bush administration's insistence that the Iraqi government had weapons of mass destruction and might give them to terrorists was a key selling point in its campaign to take the country to war. It turned out to be untrue. Debate continues over whether former President George W. Bush and Vice President #$%$ Cheney, and other top officials knew there were no WMD, but intentionally deceived the American people and Congress because they were intent on attacking Iraq for less palatable reasons -- or whether they managed to convince themselves that it was true using cherry-picked intelligence. There is no reality-based argument that Iraq actually had WMD, after extensive searches found none, but this is hardly the first time many Americans have been certain of something that simply wasn't true. A Washington Post poll in September 2003 found that nearly 70 percent of all Americans were convinced that Saddam Hussein was personally involved in the 9/11 terrorist attacks -- even though he was not. Bush, Cheney and others consistently linked al Qaeda to Hussein in speeches they gave in the run-up to war, and the media rarely pushed back. But neither Bush nor Cheney continued to claim that there were actual WMDs in Iraq once the searches came up empty -- although they both continued to insist that Saddam had the "capability" to produce them.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364419110644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 17:18:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364419263905-120</Id><Title>carey get's mad and lashes out when she post stupid things</Title><Msg>like "cancer patience" are those people with cancer that don't mind waiting in line? carrik show of her second grade education almost daily</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364419263905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 17:21:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364419592749-121</Id><Title>tea billies so stupid they think Iraq had WMD's</Title><Msg>believe the earth is flat believe it is 6,000 years old believe the sun goes around the earth don't believe in evolution believe Sarah Palin is smart LOL you can't make up how stupid these people are!!!</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364419592749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 17:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364420367150-122</Id><Topic><Title>remember when carey said the bible was written in english?</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364419953628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 17:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The governor of Texas, Mr. Rick Perry, (who wants to abolish three Federal Offices, the Department of Education, {the second one he wants to abolish I forgot} and the third one he wants to abolish HE forgot), when asked if The Bible should also be taught in Spanish replied, “if English was good enough for Jesus, then it’s good enough for me." Tea billies are dumb as stones</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364420367150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 17:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364420564174-123</Id><Title>looks like it must be meal time</Title><Msg>at the nursing home, Ivan and Carey aren't posting</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364420564174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 17:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364425126423-124</Id><Topic><Title>Secret CSCO Info Revealed</Title><Username>willson_ethan</Username><Timestamp>1363607782953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 07:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>news like dreams</Msg><Username>tomsmith172</Username><Timestamp>1364425126423</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 18:58:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364426524724-125</Id><Topic><Title>tea billies so stupid they think Iraq had WMD's</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364419592749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 17:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I always wondered what a teabilly was. Sounds like a racial slur. It's almost like a ni88er joke like we told when we were kids.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364426524724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 19:22:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364426665387-126</Id><Title>GLOBAL WARMING CAUSES MORE SNOW, BLIZZARDS, FREEZING AND ICE..</Title><Msg>Global warming makes it colder. Water dries you off And when is really dark and you need to see something, we liberal Democrats turn off the lights. Gun control stops violent deaths.......................knife control, stick control, rock control, brick control, broken bottle control, car control, baseball bat control, also reduces violent deaths... Abortion reduces violent deaths..murdering 50,000,000 babies reduces murder....said the Democrat.........</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1364426665387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 19:24:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364426720277-127</Id><Topic><Title>dumb ivan shorted NFLX at 177 today</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1362685800218</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 14:50:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So how is that working out for you?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364426720277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 19:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364426969847-128</Id><Topic><Title>GLOBAL WARMING CAUSES MORE SNOW, BLIZZARDS, FREEZING AND ICE..</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1364426665387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 19:24:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have tried to tell you guys, the actual theoretical research behind Global Warming is VALID. The problem is practice and procedure. The earth is warming up, and the sea level is rising. When the ocean rises an inch in twenty years, it's probably not a good idea to run around screaming "The sky is falling." It might be time to develop real solutions to a potential problem. Dems just want to tax the air and let chicken little figure out what to do about it later.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364426969847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 19:29:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364427260132-129</Id><Topic><Title>tea billies so stupid they think Iraq had WMD's</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364419592749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 17:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bet most teapartiers can spell " mignon ". LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364427260132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 19:34:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364427584266-130</Id><Topic><Title>remember when carey said the bible was written in english?</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364419953628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 17:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I must be winning. The Magoo ids are ganging up on me and lying too!!!!LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL Have no interest in the bible or who wrote it. Come up with a different lie, Junior.HEEHEEHEHEEHEEHEEHEE</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364427584266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 19:39:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364427596385-131</Id><Topic><Title>tea billies so stupid they think Iraq had WMD's</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364419592749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 17:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ivan gets a stiffie when one of the teaparty members makes a boo boo. Classic stereotyping and bigotry. Like a black person never really was a stupid as the ni*88er jokes made them out to be?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364427596385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 19:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364427714456-132</Id><Topic><Title>looks like it must be meal time</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364420564174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 17:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sure post a lot like Junior!!!!LOLOLOLOLOOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364427714456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 19:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364427801020-133</Id><Topic><Title>looks like it must be meal time</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364420564174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 17:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only the part of being stupid and bigoted. Otherwise, they seem like two different people.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364427801020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 19:43:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364428101100-134</Id><Topic><Title>looks like it must be meal time</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364420564174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 17:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah,the nurse bit is standard Junior. The cretin has a limited vocabulary and education. Uses many of the same phrases,slurs,and insults in all his ids.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364428101100</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 19:48:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364428829576-135</Id><Topic><Title>dumb ivan shorted NFLX at 177 today</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1362685800218</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 14:50:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well didn't short it today, but did short it at 177, not working out that well but still think it might make money, course it's only a half of one percent position, did you go long ACAS at 7 when I told you, or HZO at 10? Funny you don't ask about those?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364428829576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:00:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364429168030-136</Id><Topic><Title>dumb ivan shorted NFLX at 177 today</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1362685800218</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 14:50:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know you aren't Junior. He would be marking my KOL fiasco. You didn't mention ACAS on this board at 7.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364429168030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:06:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364429327025-137</Id><Topic><Title>dumb ivan shorted NFLX at 177 today</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1362685800218</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 14:50:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I still own DOG at 31.20, too. Not bad for a 2 month short position in the Great Obama market of 2013.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364429327025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:08:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364429493606-138</Id><Topic><Title>Local Airport Closures Cause GOPers Sequestration Anxiety</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364428923504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The sequester bill was written by Jack Lew and his staff.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1364429493606</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364429621276-139</Id><Topic><Title>Local Airport Closures Cause GOPers Sequestration Anxiety</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364428923504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eventually, the Obama appointees will figure out how to manage a budget, and reopen them. Until then, we can probably laugh at the Democrat finger pointing circle jerk.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364429621276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364429799048-140</Id><Topic><Title>Local Airport Closures Cause GOPers Sequestration Anxiety</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364428923504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans offered to make changes in the bill so Obama could have some leeway in how the cuts were implemented.Obama turned them down.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1364429799048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:16:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364429818024-141</Id><Topic><Title>Local Airport Closures Cause GOPers Sequestration Anxiety</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364428923504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>remember in the real world when 174 republicans voted for sequestration in the house and 95 Dems did, LOL now the GOPERS that voted for it say it's not their fault, to funny how the GOPERS continue to double down on how stupid their base is and keep winning, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364429818024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:16:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364430006507-142</Id><Topic><Title>Local Airport Closures Cause GOPers Sequestration Anxiety</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364428923504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know what they say? "Rome wasn't built in a day" The forensic accountants are still working on figuring out why it collapsed.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364430006507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:20:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364430032127-143</Id><Topic><Title>Local Airport Closures Cause GOPers Sequestration Anxiety</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364428923504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not a liar like you,pal. I know what I'm talking about,unlike you. I have no time for your silly games.Welcome to ignore.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1364430032127</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:20:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364430070691-144</Id><Topic><Title>Local Airport Closures Cause GOPers Sequestration Anxiety</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364428923504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah I remember that, you're right, the GOP said these cuts are painful, we will mandate that cuts have to be made and you can determine where to make them, then we can blame you for the cuts cause we don't want to vote on what to cut, LOL funny how the GOP is willing to give up its constitutional responsibilities as long as they can blame Obama , LOL\ funny how the tea billies believe in the constitution, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364430070691</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364430378655-145</Id><Topic><Title>Local Airport Closures Cause GOPers Sequestration Anxiety</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364428923504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not a liar like you,pal. I know what I'm talking about,unlike you. I have no time for your silly games.Welcome to ignore. translated from tea billie rabbit hole to the real world You have exposed me for the idiot I am, I can't refute the obvious so I will ignore you.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364430378655</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:26:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364430831144-146</Id><Topic><Title>Local Airport Closures Cause GOPers Sequestration Anxiety</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364428923504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forgot to switch ids,didn't you,pal. Or did you want me to read it so you used dumb instead of Junior ??</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1364430831144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:33:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364431042540-147</Id><Topic><Title>Local Airport Closures Cause GOPers Sequestration Anxiety</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364428923504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I only post under one id pinhead, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431042540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:37:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364431156817-148</Id><Title>Thank God the NRA protects guys like this so they can buy weapons</Title><Msg>of course if the tea billies had IQ's over 70 it wouldn't happen would it. Two days after the January 2011 shooting, Randy Loughner told a group of F.B.I. and sheriff’s investigators that he had grown so worried about his son’s odd behavior in the months since Jared had been forced to withdraw from a community college because of campus officials’ fears about the safety of staff and students that he had begun to keep his son in at night by rendering his Chevrolet Nova inoperable. But, Randy Loughner told the investigators, he had not done so before the morning of the attack, when his son drove away at 6 a.m. to secretly buy ammunition for the Glock he had purchased at a local sporting goods store about six weeks before. When his son returned home a couple of hours later, Randy Loughner said, he questioned him about what he was carrying in his backpack, which prompted Jared Loughner to turn and run, eventually fleeing into the desert. About two hours later, he had apparently used some of that ammunition, emptying a 33-round magazine in about 19 seconds, and killing, among others, a federal judge and a 9-year-old girl and seriously wounding Ms. Giffords, who was shot in the head at close range. In her interviews with law enforcement officials, Amy Loughner described her son as a “loner” who talked to himself. She said she had insisted that he be tested for drugs because she believed he was using methamphetamine despite his denials. She told Pima County sheriff’s detectives that she and her husband had taken a shotgun away from their son in the months before the shooting and told him he needed to get psychological help. “Sometimes you’d hear him in his room, like, having conversations,” Ms. Loughner said about her son during an interview with investigators. “And sometimes he would look like he was having a conversation with someone right there. Be talking to someone. I don’t know how to explain it. I don’t.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431156817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:39:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364431265297-149</Id><Topic><Title>Local Airport Closures Cause GOPers Sequestration Anxiety</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364428923504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You post under a lot of ids. Dumb. Everyone here knows it. BTW,are you having filet mInion again tonight?/LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL How EFFING STUPID!!!!HEEHEEHEEHEE</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364431265297</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364431404234-150</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God the NRA protects guys like this so they can buy weapons</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431156817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FILET MINION!!!!!!LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL Stupidest post ever!!!!!!HEHEEHEEHEEHEEHEE How did it taste, you effing moron.LOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1364431404234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:43:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364431662259-151</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God the NRA protects guys like this so they can buy weapons</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431156817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>idiots agree it would be foolish to deny Jason his second amendments rights, it is better to have thousands killed a year at a cost to taxpayers of a trillion dollars plus, better that then deny a psycho a gun of course you have to agree probably 25% of all gun nuts are psycho, so naturally they don't want background checks</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431662259</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364431929626-152</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God the NRA protects guys like this so they can buy weapons</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431156817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The question La Pierre asked was; "How is a universal background check not a registration issue?" Do people who don't actually want to buy a gun go down to get background checks?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364431929626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:52:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364432245871-153</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God the NRA protects guys like this so they can buy weapons</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431156817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Truest me. Most of us would prefer that Junior got a "universal" background check before he could purchase a toothpick.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364432245871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364432541141-154</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God the NRA protects guys like this so they can buy weapons</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431156817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical elitist leftist. Like Stalin, would rather filet and barbeque the minions than acknowledge their gripes.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364432541141</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:02:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364432674309-155</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God the NRA protects guys like this so they can buy weapons</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431156817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>does anyone that owns a car not register it? Why do we require car registrations but not guns? oh yeah killers don't want to get caught</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364432674309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:04:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364433019173-156</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God the NRA protects guys like this so they can buy weapons</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431156817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try to sell it, beotch! Don't call it a "background check" if it is a registration.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364433019173</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:10:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364433766018-157</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God the NRA protects guys like this so they can buy weapons</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431156817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems Dumb changed his focus from assault weapons to registration.Funny . Maybe he should e-mail Harry Reid and ask what happened.LOL Remember when dumb was saying "We are coming for your guns".LOL Didn't happen.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1364433766018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:22:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364433773224-158</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God the NRA protects guys like this so they can buy weapons</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431156817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just make the background checks universal. As in, idiots like you could kill yourself getting obese and ugly from buying a 32 ounce soda, so you need a freaking background check.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364433773224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:22:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364434123433-159</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God the NRA protects guys like this so they can buy weapons</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431156817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well it is simply a background check so jason and his kind can't kill dozens of innocent people, but you are right it will hopefully lead to a registration, seems kind of silly you can't fish without registering, can't drive a car without registration, can't hunt without registration, but it's fine to buy an assault weapon and kill 50 people without even a background check, I don't think you are a #$%$ so you must agree</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364434123433</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:28:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364434204876-160</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God the NRA protects guys like this so they can buy weapons</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431156817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jason could kill without a gun. Are you really that stupid?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364434204876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:30:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364434457860-161</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God the NRA protects guys like this so they can buy weapons</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431156817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Japan actually banned guns, and their suicide rate is double the suicide rate in America. jason can kill himself without a gun. Australia introduced gun control and the murder rate decreased almost equal to the simultaneous decrease in America. Jason can kill without guns.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364434457860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364434675725-162</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God the NRA protects guys like this so they can buy weapons</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364431156817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 20:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb just reads the DNC talking points and posts what moveon dot org tells him to post.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364434675725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:37:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364436011965-163</Id><Topic><Title>How do the poor and welfare folks pay for obamacare? Terrorists say they pay = LIES</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364434711120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:38:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The poor pay for it. They need to use more foodstamps to buy groceries. It's called "trickle down socialism." The more free government services cost, the more food stamps the government needs to print.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364436011965</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 22:00:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364436826256-164</Id><Topic><Title>How do the poor and welfare folks pay for obamacare? Terrorists say they pay = LIES</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364434711120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:38:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's not socialist enough. A real socialist would create phony work programs for the lazy bums and moochers. He just gives away food stamps without making work.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364436826256</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 22:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364437253851-165</Id><Topic><Title>How do the poor and welfare folks pay for obamacare? Terrorists say they pay = LIES</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364434711120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:38:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agree</Msg><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1364437253851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 22:20:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364437862009-166</Id><Topic><Title>51 percent of REPUBS age 18-45 in favor of same sex marriage!</Title><Username>allnewmagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1364437693914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 22:28:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you care? Are you gay?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364437862009</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 22:31:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364438772767-167</Id><Topic><Title>51 percent of REPUBS age 18-45 in favor of same sex marriage!</Title><Username>allnewmagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1364437693914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 22:28:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, many republicans favor same-sex unions which are equivalent to marriage without using the "marriage" word which was delegated to "holy matrimony" in the Bible. Why all of you drama qu*e*e*ns are having trouble with the legal nuance is not really our problem.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364438772767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 22:46:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364439238264-168</Id><Topic><Title>51 percent of REPUBS age 18-45 in favor of same sex marriage!</Title><Username>allnewmagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1364437693914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 22:28:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will end up being a total non-issue after the Dems win. They will cut the "marriage benefits" out of the tax code, and even single people will get "equal rights." Fools.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364439238264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 22:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364439940782-169</Id><Topic><Title>51 percent of REPUBS age 18-45 in favor of same sex marriage!</Title><Username>allnewmagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1364437693914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 22:28:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's kind of funny. A single guy works for a living, and for some reason, he doesn't need any pre-natal care coverage in his health care, but has to pay just as much as everyone else for it. "Equal rights?"</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364439940782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 23:05:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364442857376-170</Id><Topic><Title>Why Hillary Clinton will never be President. ________ EVER! _______________!!!!</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364441752459</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 23:35:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She will most definitely be our next president. The only one who has a prayer of defeating her is Mr. Biden</Msg><Username>jen.co44</Username><Timestamp>1364442857376</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 23:54:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364442982108-171</Id><Topic><Title>51 percent of REPUBS age 18-45 in favor of same sex marriage!</Title><Username>allnewmagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1364437693914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 22:28:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You just need to do a qu*e*e*ry on Google to find it.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364442982108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 23:56:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364443165167-172</Id><Topic><Title>allnewmagoo6 • Stop spreading your gay lies on CSCO Board.</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364441715384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 23:35:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Would God approval of gay marriage." I asked, but he said "no comment." Well, he actually didn't answer. For some reason he stopped talking to me after he told me the Bible isn't true.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364443165167</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 23:59:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>