<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373174380281-1</Id><Topic><Title>Just Checking</Title><Username>miraclary</Username><Timestamp>1373152134820</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 19:08:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not a chance!</Msg><Username>jog49</Username><Timestamp>1373174380281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 01:19:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373199361814-2</Id><Topic><Title>GWBUSH A VETERAN HERO, OBAMA AN ILLEGAL ALIEN AND DRAFTDODGER OCCUPIER OF THE WHITE HOUSE</Title><Username>gwbush_is_a_patriot</Username><Timestamp>1373136402551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 14:46:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush may have seemed larger than life for eight years, but he left a surprisingly thin legacy. Take his legislative agenda. No Child Left Behind is now widely unpopular among both liberals and conservatives—so unpopular that Congress has spent the past five years assiduously avoiding a vote to reauthorize it. His tax cuts expired in 2010 and are now little more than a political football. His own party wants to repeal key provisions of Sarbanes-Oxley. The Supreme Court has effectively gutted campaign finance reform. On the foreign policy front, his wars are widely viewed as expensive failures. And he was never able to get so much as a vote on Social Security privatization or immigration reform. That doesn't leave much. Pretty much all that's left is the PATRIOT Act and the Medicare prescription drug bill. That's not much for eight years. Beyond that, neither party wants anything to do with him. It's not surprising that Democrats still think of him as the Frat Boy President, one of the worst of all time, but what is surprising is that Republicans largely agree. And speaking of draft-dodgers, Bush and his ebtire cabinet , cept for Rummy, were draft-dodgers. What a legacy, historians will line up at his grave waiting to take a leak on it.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1373199361814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 08:16:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373201335698-3</Id><Title>We love the FISA court....</Title><Msg>FISA Court Has Only Rejected 10 Of 20,909 Spying Requests: One Congressman Has A Solution July 5th, 2013 10:24 am Jason Sattler When the Federal Bureau of Investigation and National Security Agency want to spy on American citizens, they go to the court created by the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act (FISA). And more than 99.9 percent of the time, the court says “yes.” Between 2001 and 2012, the court heard 20,909 surveillance and property search warrants and rejected just 10. “Almost 1,000 of the approved requests required modification, and 26 were withdrawn by the government before a ruling,” writes Bloomberg‘s Ezra Klein. “That’s a startling win rate for the government.” Why is this court so extraordinarily compliant with the government’s wishes? All of the judges are nominated by one man — Chief Justice John Roberts. The effect of this is predictable, writes Klein: The FISA court is composed of federal judges. All are appointed by the same man. All but one hail from the same political party. And unlike judges in normal courts, FISA judges don’t hear opposing testimony or feel pressure from colleagues or the public to moderate their rulings. Under these circumstances, group polarization is almost a certainty.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1373201335698</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 08:48:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373215934137-4</Id><Topic><Title>Just Checking</Title><Username>miraclary</Username><Timestamp>1373152134820</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 19:08:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U outta U flocking mind monkey boy. U only voted for Obama because he said he was a jib, you racist bee*yitch! Rasmussen poll convincing shows BLACKS ARE MORE RACIST THAN WHITES!!! Junior turns everything into a racist guilt trip. That's how blacks have gotten free handouts, easy mortgages, affirmative action, continuous cradle to grave buttt wiping for 40 years. America is turning into Detroit. The parasites are killing the host. Exterminate the rioting monkeys. Drone them.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1373215934137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 12:52:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373221011334-5</Id><Topic><Title>Who ya gonna believe?</Title><Username>fss13</Username><Timestamp>1373135327024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 14:28:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i believe that zimmrman hunted down a unarmed teenager and is desperate to avoid punishment</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmate1</Username><Timestamp>1373221011334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 14:16:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373221037506-6</Id><Topic><Title>Who ya gonna believe?</Title><Username>fss13</Username><Timestamp>1373135327024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 14:28:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lynch whitey ROTF!! you poor old victim you lol!!!!</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmate1</Username><Timestamp>1373221037506</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 14:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373223327497-7</Id><Title>benghazzi ROTF!! IRS ROTF!! and now snowdon is a republican</Title><Msg>gop=cowards and losers</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmate1</Username><Timestamp>1373223327497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 14:55:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373223393361-8</Id><Topic><Title>Who ya gonna believe?</Title><Username>fss13</Username><Timestamp>1373135327024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 14:28:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't believe Obama. Junior and Al Sharpton need to put in jail for inciting race riots.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1373223393361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 14:56:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373223491454-9</Id><Topic><Title>Who ya gonna believe?</Title><Username>fss13</Username><Timestamp>1373135327024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 14:28:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zim was a volunteer protecting his neighborhood from a outside invader high on weed and Purple Drank due to a number or recent house break-ins, typical crimes of drug addicts.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1373223491454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 14:58:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373225254099-10</Id><Topic><Title>NEW GALLOP POLL SHOWS DEMOCRATS ARE UNPATRIOTIC AND DESPISE THE USA WHILE REPUBLICANS ARE VERY PATRIOTIC</Title><Username>the_lochnesss_monster</Username><Timestamp>1372960567250</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:56:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's easy to spot someone who voted for John Kerry -- they wear Crocs. The IMF may slash its global growth forecast for the second time this year due to concerns about emerging markets. We're going to new all time highs babee!!!! BUY BUY BUY</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1373225254099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 15:27:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373225340387-11</Id><Topic><Title>PURPLE DRANK</Title><Username>deeperharbor</Username><Timestamp>1373058475061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 17:07:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trayvon was a wasted angry jig. We are all equal. We can all use the N word. Thanks Chris Rock.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1373225340387</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 15:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373225575920-12</Id><Topic><Title>GWBUSH A VETERAN HERO, OBAMA AN ILLEGAL ALIEN AND DRAFTDODGER OCCUPIER OF THE WHITE HOUSE</Title><Username>gwbush_is_a_patriot</Username><Timestamp>1373136402551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 14:46:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, that's it, Bush was a veteran war hero!! And Obama is a draft dodger LMAO!!! You aren't even bright enough to realize Obama was to young to even register for the draft. And whatever happened to those detectives Trump sent to Hawaii, and the trip Sheriff Joe took there as well looking for Obama's birth certificate? And on a personal note, let me ask you this.....Have you even been abducted by any alien spacecraft and probed...and do they still visit you from time to time? Thanks for sharing.</Msg><Username>dsorne50</Username><Timestamp>1373225575920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 15:32:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373228826605-13</Id><Topic><Title>GWBUSH A VETERAN HERO, OBAMA AN ILLEGAL ALIEN AND DRAFTDODGER OCCUPIER OF THE WHITE HOUSE</Title><Username>gwbush_is_a_patriot</Username><Timestamp>1373136402551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 14:46:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why didn't Barry go to see his brother George Obama while he was in Africa? Aren't they related?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1373228826605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 16:27:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373229012597-14</Id><Title>EGYPT... MILLIONS and MILLIONS OF REASONS TO OUTLAW ISLAM !!!</Title><Msg>OUTLAW ISLAM IN AMERICA and restore Liberty and privacy NOW !!!</Msg><Username>black911operator</Username><Timestamp>1373229012597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 16:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373229118408-15</Id><Title>ASIANA CRASH is a message from DEMS saying, We don't want your future independent Repulican</Title><Msg>Anchor babies !!!</Msg><Username>black911operator</Username><Timestamp>1373229118408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 16:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373235463604-16</Id><Topic><Title>GWBUSH A VETERAN HERO, OBAMA AN ILLEGAL ALIEN AND DRAFTDODGER OCCUPIER OF THE WHITE HOUSE</Title><Username>gwbush_is_a_patriot</Username><Timestamp>1373136402551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 14:46:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama was required to register for the draft. Just because you come here and post a bald face lie does not make your lie true. I understand why Obama refused to register for the draft. His illegal alien status would be exposed because he didn't have photoshop available at that time to manufacture a bogus birth certificate.</Msg><Username>keating_5_john_mccain_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1373235463604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 18:17:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373235624251-17</Id><Topic><Title>GWBUSH A VETERAN HERO, OBAMA AN ILLEGAL ALIEN AND DRAFTDODGER OCCUPIER OF THE WHITE HOUSE</Title><Username>gwbush_is_a_patriot</Username><Timestamp>1373136402551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 14:46:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No Child Left Behind was ONLY unpopular among union democrat 'teachers' all of whom are incompetent and fail to teach and didn't want to be held accountable for their extremely poor job performance. Most of these democrat union 'teachers' cant even pass the tests that the kids are required to pass and most of these democrat union 'teachers' only excel at pedofilia.</Msg><Username>keating_5_john_mccain_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1373235624251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 18:20:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373236550480-18</Id><Title>Democrat Hero Jerry Bruckheimer Could Lose $150 Million on the Lone Ranger Movie</Title><Msg>Democrat Hero Jerry Bruckheimer Could Lose $150 Million on the Lone Ranger Movie. Everybody must run to the theaters and buy tickets because Jerry Bruckheimer is one the the big donors the the democrat party and we must do our part to help Jerry.</Msg><Username>pic_n_save_democrat</Username><Timestamp>1373236550480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 18:35:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373236821662-19</Id><Title>POLICE CHIEF KILLED WITH MACHINE GUNS OBAMA SUPPLIED TO MEXICAN DRUG CARTELS</Title><Msg>POLICE CHIEF KILLED WITH MACHINE GUNS OBAMA SUPPLIED TO MEXICAN DRUG CARTELS. Isn't Obama a conspirator in this crime??? Isn't that a high crime (felony)???</Msg><Username>obama_bp_oil_spill_horror</Username><Timestamp>1373236821662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 18:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373237334043-20</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Hero Jerry Bruckheimer Could Lose $150 Million on the Lone Ranger Movie</Title><Username>pic_n_save_democrat</Username><Timestamp>1373236550480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 18:35:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I routinely boycott movies by hollywood left wingers.</Msg><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1373237334043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 18:48:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373238028120-21</Id><Title>Fourth Of July Violence In Chicago</Title><Msg>Homicide Rate Passes 200 After Long Holiday Weekend Of Shootings</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1373238028120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 19:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373240701097-22</Id><Title>LOL just scrolled back through the last few days</Title><Msg>LOL shut in Deadpainting aka Ivan, aks artie posted all through the long weekend, how sad to be a shut in full of hatred</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1373240701097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 19:45:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373240962718-23</Id><Title>tea billies overdosing on derp</Title><Msg>How much does the evidence change your belief? That depends on three things. It depends on A) how different the evidence is from your prior, B) how strong the evidence is, and C) how strong your prior is... When those people keep broadcasting their priors to the world again and again after every new piece of evidence comes out, it gets very annoying. After every article comes out about a new solar technology breakthrough, or a new cost drop, they'll just repeat "Solar will never be cost-competitive." That is unhelpful and uninformative, since they're just restating their priors over and over. Thus, it is annoying. Guys, we know what you think already. English has no word for "the constant, repetitive reiteration of strong priors". Yet it is a well-known phenomenon in the world of punditry, debate, and public affairs. On Twitter, we call it "derp". Which is to say, a policy commentator is "derpy" when his or her (usually his) prior assumptions about the world are so unwarrantedly strong that he is unswayable by evidence. Derpers have a faith-based approach to policy. Derp is a problem in political debates always and everywhere, but these days it is especially epidemic on the right. Derp is what leads conservatives to insist that hard money is a good idea even as it wrecks the economies of southern Europe; that tax rate cuts are the key to economic growth from any economic and policy baseline; or that Mitt Romney will win the election even when the clear consensus of the polls is that he is behind.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1373240962718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 19:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373241984642-24</Id><Title>funny watching the ultra conservative Brooks take the GOP to task</Title><Msg>According to Brooks, GOP opposition was intellectually weak if one took into account the Congressional Budget Office’s calculations. “You know, I’ve seen a lot of intellectually weak cases in this town,” Brooks said. “I’ve rarely seen as intellectually a weak case as the case against the Senate immigration bill. The Republicans say they want to reduce illegal immigration. The Congressional Budget Office says the Senate bill will reduce it by a third to half. They say they want economic growth. All the top conservative economists say it’ll produce economic growth. They say they want to reduce the debt. The CBO says it will reduce the debt. All the big major objectives the Republicans stand for, the Senate immigration bill will do. And so, the other things they’re talking about are secondary and tertiary issues. Whether we get 86 percent border protection or 90 percent — compared to the big things this bill does, they’re miniscule.” Hello, it's the tea billlie's of course it's intellectually weak. These people are uneducated morons.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1373241984642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 20:06:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373243283783-25</Id><Topic><Title>LOL just scrolled back through the last few days</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1373240701097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 19:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>edy was home with her nurse</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmate1</Username><Timestamp>1373243283783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 20:28:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373244405213-26</Id><Title>OBAMA'S SON TRAYVON WAS HIGH ON DRUGS? WHA WHA WHAAAAT?</Title><Msg>how can this be? Because we all know Obanama would never ever ever use drugs</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1373244405213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373244445246-27</Id><Topic><Title>PRO-ABORTION DEMOCRAT ACTIVISTS CHANT "HAIL SATAN", TELL TX LEGISLATOR "I HOPE YOUR DAUGHTER IS RAPED"</Title><Username>janet_napalitano_is_ugly</Username><Timestamp>1372959583082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:39:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"End of times," "end of days",fundamentalist fools have been saying it for decades, what a crock, of bull. All this homage to unseen supernatural deities is the mythological nonsense of men since the dawn of mankind. Satin , the invisible boggy man for bad adults. A god, any god;the invisible rewarder for good adults,utter mythological nonsense. It can be proven throughout the ages, Man has always created his god or gods, but a god, any god; has never been proven to have created man. Now if man chooses to believe in some deity to give himself an aid to persevere threw his daily ordeals, good; then his beliefs have served their purpose. However, those beliefs are no verification of the existence of any godly deity.... Can I get an Amen!</Msg><Username>fss13</Username><Timestamp>1373244445246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 20:47:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373244543739-28</Id><Topic><Title>A LEFT ON "HOT MIC" CATCHES EVIL OBAMA ON JULY 4TH!</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1373083085546</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 23:58:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree! Obama would most certainly talk like this with hisnigga lingo street talk</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1373244543739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 20:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373245478046-29</Id><Topic><Title>LOL just scrolled back through the last few days</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1373240701097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 19:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you been smoking, boy? My last post before this one was Jul 6, 2013 6:36 PM</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1373245478046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373246241414-30</Id><Topic><Title>LOL just scrolled back through the last few days</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1373240701097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 19:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your profile fits a midget, or a guy with a very small peter. You have to post things than make you feel big.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1373246241414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373246286362-31</Id><Topic><Title>LOL just scrolled back through the last few days</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1373240701097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 19:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ivan everyone knows about your multiple I.D.'s your not talking to tea billies here</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1373246286362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:18:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373246781319-32</Id><Topic><Title>PRO-ABORTION DEMOCRAT ACTIVISTS CHANT "HAIL SATAN", TELL TX LEGISLATOR "I HOPE YOUR DAUGHTER IS RAPED"</Title><Username>janet_napalitano_is_ugly</Username><Timestamp>1372959583082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:39:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since ANTI-ABORTION seems to be the rally point the of conservatives let me just reiterate. Nowhere on this planet is a fetus legally, or medically, recognized as a "baby". Not even in Texas. Gov. Perry would propose a change in "Texas" law to conflict with federal law, which is as rational as his proposal last year; to have Texas remove itself from the union of the united states, for economic reasons. Mr Perry, Seems to me this nation fought a "civil war" to prevent states from seceding from the union once before when, back then; the "Republic of Texas" wanted only their own way... Listen up America, Pro choice, learn to live with it, it's the law of the land.</Msg><Username>fss13</Username><Timestamp>1373246781319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373247161610-33</Id><Topic><Title>LOL just scrolled back through the last few days</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1373240701097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 19:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said I have more than one Id and you said my ID was posting all weekend. Wrong one two counts, little boy.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1373247161610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373248511605-34</Id><Topic><Title>JUNIOR WISHING YOU THE BEST IN YOUR AIDS STRUGGLE</Title><Username>deeperharbor</Username><Timestamp>1373246218705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:16:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dude, ain't junior the little maggot who hangs out on this board 24-7. What a creepy perv he is</Msg><Username>thestrangeloner</Username><Timestamp>1373248511605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373249006831-35</Id><Topic><Title>JUNIOR WISHING YOU THE BEST IN YOUR AIDS STRUGGLE</Title><Username>deeperharbor</Username><Timestamp>1373246218705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:16:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ivan makes up another id, The strange loner, 1 post member, since july 7th, Ivan, aka Dead, aka artie we all know it's you, why not stand behind your own opinions. Posting the same opinion under multiple id's doesn't make your opinion any stronger. but if it makes you feel better as a shut in I guess it doesn't really hurt anyone else, go for it loser</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1373249006831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 22:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373250156531-36</Id><Topic><Title>JUNIOR WISHING YOU THE BEST IN YOUR AIDS STRUGGLE</Title><Username>deeperharbor</Username><Timestamp>1373246218705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:16:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hi dumbjunior! No, wrong again dickbreath, I am not Ivan, etc.</Msg><Username>thestrangeloner</Username><Timestamp>1373250156531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 22:22:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373250387361-37</Id><Topic><Title>JUNIOR WISHING YOU THE BEST IN YOUR AIDS STRUGGLE</Title><Username>deeperharbor</Username><Timestamp>1373246218705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:16:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He sucked so much at the downlowclub they had rush it to the hospital!</Msg><Username>shwdl</Username><Timestamp>1373250387361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 22:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373250562750-38</Id><Title>EGPYTIAN PROTESTORS CARRYING SIGNS TELLING OBAMA TO</Title><Msg>fuckoff on tv now, they don't want his muzubrothahoods runnin thangs</Msg><Username>thestrangeloner</Username><Timestamp>1373250562750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 22:29:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373250640508-39</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Hero Jerry Bruckheimer Could Lose $150 Million on the Lone Ranger Movie</Title><Username>pic_n_save_democrat</Username><Timestamp>1373236550480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 18:35:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope all liberals bite the dust!</Msg><Username>shwdl</Username><Timestamp>1373250640508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 22:30:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373252261449-40</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Hero Jerry Bruckheimer Could Lose $150 Million on the Lone Ranger Movie</Title><Username>pic_n_save_democrat</Username><Timestamp>1373236550480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 18:35:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stock are going over 1700 soon. Get in now. Prepare for blastoff.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1373252261449</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 22:57:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373252344123-41</Id><Topic><Title>JUNIOR WISHING YOU THE BEST IN YOUR AIDS STRUGGLE</Title><Username>deeperharbor</Username><Timestamp>1373246218705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:16:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior is a racist bas*tid clown. He knows everything yet he knows nothing. Typical Obama voter.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1373252344123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 22:59:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373252421383-42</Id><Topic><Title>JUNIOR WISHING YOU THE BEST IN YOUR AIDS STRUGGLE</Title><Username>deeperharbor</Username><Timestamp>1373246218705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:16:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is a algo that monitors stock chat boards for Obama bashing. The more you bash Obama the higher the stock market goes. The rich get richer.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1373252421383</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:00:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373252623868-43</Id><Title>UFC #$%$ ANDERSON SILVA DEFEATED BY WHITE CHRIS WEIDMAN IN</Title><Msg>vegas tonight, a hook to the jaw. Take that cocky Brazilian #$%$</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1373252623868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:03:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373252742788-44</Id><Topic><Title>JUNIOR WISHING YOU THE BEST IN YOUR AIDS STRUGGLE</Title><Username>deeperharbor</Username><Timestamp>1373246218705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:16:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yoonur is a piece of inner city trash</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1373252742788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373255110202-45</Id><Topic><Title>POLICE CHIEF KILLED WITH MACHINE GUNS OBAMA SUPPLIED TO MEXICAN DRUG CARTELS</Title><Username>obama_bp_oil_spill_horror</Username><Timestamp>1373236821662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 18:40:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Answer: No and no.</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1373255110202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>