<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363667221233-1</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA PROMISED NO NEW TAXES ON THOSE MAKING $250,000 OR</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363474249635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 18:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I LIKE! AHHHHHHAHAHAHAHAHA! Obama danigarinchief! One skilless monkey!</Msg><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1363667221233</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363690718067-2</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO starting to move higher!</Title><Username>lucadobson</Username><Timestamp>1362659226270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 07:27:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very nice article</Msg><Username>steele_john</Username><Timestamp>1363690718067</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 06:58:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363693461174-3</Id><Title>REPUBS, U REALLY BELIEVE CHANGING YOUR CONVENTION DATE &amp; ELIMINATING DEBATES GOING TO MAKE YOUR HATED PLATFORM LIKED?</Title><Msg>REPUBS, U REALLY BELIEVE CHANGING YOUR CONVENTION DATE &amp; ELIMINATING DEBATES GOING TO MAKE YOUR HATED PLATFORM LIKED? I CAN'T STOP LAUGHING... maybe that will bring back the women, minority, student, gay, hispanic, asian votes that they have lost</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1363693461174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:44:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363693498183-4</Id><Title>Ted Cruz, Marco Rubio- NEW GOP PLATFORM- appeal to CUBAN and WHITE AMERICANS ONLY</Title><Msg>see if that works for ya !</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1363693498183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:44:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363693570371-5</Id><Topic><Title>wonka, it is obama's fault that yahoo is censoring you//////ROTF!</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363643339754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 17:48:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dddddd</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1363693570371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363693663035-6</Id><Title>Priebus: GOP has room for Pro-Gay Senator Rob Portman</Title><Msg>Priebus: GOP has room for Pro-Gay Senator Rob Portman republican gueers finally coming out of the closet..... wowza!!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1363693663035</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:47:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363693712092-7</Id><Title>Lazy Obama stop Golfing and do your job you utter failure as President.</Title><Msg>The plan submitted by Senate Budget Chairman Patty Murray contrasts sharply. While we appreciate that the Senate actually produced a budget for the first time in four years, it is a huge disappointment. The budget submitted by Senate Democrats calls for $1.5 trillion in higher taxes, trillions more in new spending, and does absolutely nothing to address the broken entitlement system our country is facing. Senator Murray has no plan to ever balance the budget, and instead does the exact opposite - increasing spending and adding an additional $7 trillion to the national debt. Overall, Murray’s plan is very dangerous for Americans and our economy as a whole. Continuing out-of-control spending means raising taxes on you, at a time when many Americans can’t afford more tax increases. To not cut spending is irresponsible, but to not even mention it is pure insanity. We wish the Senate Democrats had put more serious effort into addressing the real problems we face.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363693712092</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:48:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363693778647-8</Id><Title>Thanks Ryan &amp; GOP for a balanced Budget. so where is Obama's?</Title><Msg>On Tuesday, the Securities and Exchange Commission charged the fiscally irresponsible state government for misleading bond investors about the health of its public pension system. The Land of Lincoln’s elected officials have been piling up mountains of pension debt for years and refusing to pay it off. In fact, Illinois currently owes $192 billion in unfunded pension liabilities over the past few decades thanks to its legislature’s long history of shortchanging pension payments. While the spendthrift politicians were caught this time around, it’s not the only trick they have up their sleeve. Governor Pat Quinn has been rubbing elbows with the Obama Administration in an effort to secure a federal bailout. Just last year in his state budget, the governor wrote“significant long-term improvements will come only from … seeking a federal guarantee of the debt.”That’s right, Illinois’s officials are scheming to shift their self-incurred debts onto the backs of taxpayers like you. Sadly, Illinois is just one of many states that may be interested in swindling federal taxpayers. Other states like California and New York have also nearly bankrupted their public pensions and may be looking for a bailout courtesy of Uncle Sam. Fortunately, some fiscally responsible statesmen from the unlikeliest places are taking a stand against this thievery before it takes place. Senator Mark Kirk of Illinois is poised to reintroduce his No States Bailouts Resolution, requiring states as sovereign entities to retain responsibility for the debts they have racked up. ++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++ The plan submitted by Senate Budget Chairman Patty Murray contrasts sharply. While we appreciate that the Senate actually produced a budget for the first time in four years, it is a huge disappointment. The budget submitted by Senate Democrats calls for $1.5 trillion in higher taxes, trillions more in new spending, and does absolutely nothing to address the broken entitlement system our country is facing. Senator Murray has no plan to ever balance the budget, and instead does the exact opposite - increasing spending and adding an additional $7 trillion to the national debt. Overall, Murray’s plan is very dangerous for Americans and our economy as a whole. Continuing out-of-control spending means raising taxes on you, at a time when many Americans can’t afford more tax increases. To not cut spending is irresponsible, but to not even mention it is pure insanity. We wish the Senate Democrats had put more serious effort into addressing the real problems we face. Rep. Ryan Unveils GOP's $4.6T Plan to Cut the Deficit and Obama after 4 years still has not made a Budget yet. USA Today On Tuesday, House Budget Committee Chairman Paul Ryan "unveiled a budget...that would balance the nation's books in 10 years without raising taxes but by eliminating President Obama's health care law, revamping Medicare for future retirees and creating just two tax brackets for individuals - 10% and 25%." USA Today says the House is "scheduled to approve Ryan's budget next week," but "the conservative blueprint stands no chance of gaining traction with Senate Democrats or Obama." Nevertheless, USA Today describes Ryan's budget as a "starting point for renewed debate about how to balance the budget."</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363693778647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:49:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363693847488-9</Id><Title>President Obama American families cannot spend more than Mom &amp; Dad make in a year or they go bankrupt.</Title><Msg>President Obama American families cannot spend more than Mom &amp; Dad make in a year or they go bankrupt. Look what happened to Greece mr.obama you spending fool. Stop using that Maxine Waters fuzzy ghetto math and balance the US budget. We the people demand it and do not want to be the next Greece. Did you fail math at Harvard and High School?</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363693847488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363693875155-10</Id><Title>Wow! It is true that since the GOP took over Congress with huge victory in Nov. 2010 the stock market has hit new highs</Title><Msg>Wow! It is true that since the GOP took over Congress with huge victory in Nov. 2010 the stock market has hit new highs. Funny how when a spending fool liberal president like radical obama is horse collared Wall Street likes it. Now all you flaming liberal tree hugging termite go find a new place to post your baloney. Keep up the pressure on Obama the deficit sending fool off all times.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363693875155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363693923894-11</Id><Title>Leave it to GOP to come up with a solution for the mess that America is now in economically.</Title><Msg>Leave it to GOP to come up with a solution for the mess that America is now in economically. I bought a bird feeder. I hung it on my back porch and filled it with seed. What a beauty of a bird feeder it was, as I filled it lovingly with seed. Within a week we had hundreds of bird taking advantage of the continuous flow of free and easily accessible food. But then the birds started building nests in the boards of the patio, above the table, and next to the barbecue. Then came the poop. It was everywhere: on the patio tile, the chairs, and the table everywhere! Then some of the birds turned mean. They would dive bomb me and try to peck me even though I had fed them out of my own pocket. And others birds were boisterous and loud. They sat on the feeder and squawked and screamed at all hours of the day and night and demanded that I fill it when it got low on food. After a while, I couldn't even sit on my own back porch anymore. So I took down the bird feeder and in three days the birds were gone. I cleaned up their mess and took down the many nests they had built all over the patio. Soon, the back yard was like it used to be quiet, serene and no one demanding their rights to a free meal. Now let's see. Our government gives out free food, subsidized housing, free medical care and free education, and allows anyone born here to be an automatic citizen. Then the illegal’s came by the tens of thousands. Suddenly our taxes went up to pay for free services; small apartments are housing 5 families; you have to wait 6 hours to be seen by an emergency room doctor; your child's second grade class is behind other schools because over half the class doesn't speak English. Corn Flakes now come in a bilingual box; I have to ‘press one ' to hear my bank talk to me in English, and people waving flags other than 'Old Glory' are squawking and screaming in the streets, demanding more rights and free liberties. Just my opinion, but maybe it's time for the government to take down.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363693923894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363693956262-12</Id><Title>It’s hard to think of a president that has been more of an Epic Failure than President Obama</Title><Msg>It’s hard to think of a president that has been more of an Epic Failure than President Obama. Even Carter is glad this guy came along, so at least he knows he is no longer the worst president ever. Here is just a short list of Obama’s Failures: 1. Hawaii is in Asia 2. Passing on the keystone pipeline. 3. Touts a Green Energy Company as exemplary that fails a year later. 4. Using the Gulf Oil Spill to promote Green Energy – instead of cleaning it up. 5. Thinking the Tea Party is a passing fad – or that they are racists. 6. Pulling out of Iraq with no clear victory over insurgent forces. 7. Trying to re-write history through speeches – with inaccurate information (i.e. Statue of Liberty) 8. Getting a Nobel Prize for being the most ineffective President in the history of the United States, though some say it was for his pigment. 9. Putting all legislation on the Internet for five days before it comes to a vote. 10. Returning the bust of Churchill to the Brits. 11. Giving a collection of DVDs to the British PM. 12. Denying the notion of American Exceptionalism. 13. Promising to close Gitmo — failing to do so. 14. Securing the Olympics for Chicago in 2016. 15. Naming numerous Communists/Socialists/Progressives to his various Czar positions and then watching them scurry for cover when Beck begins to call them out, forcing them to resign. 16. Government races for NJ, VA and the Senate Seat in Mass. 17. The midterm elections, which Obama himself called a shellacking. 18. Prediction that stimulus would ensure that unemployment doesn’t exceed 8%. 19. Bowing to just about everybody. 20. Proposing amnesty for illegal aliens to increase the population of voters for Democrat elections. 21. He said, I have visited 57 states. Now there is just 1 left to visit. 22. Obama to Medvedev…give me space I will have more flexibility after my election.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363693956262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363694060458-13</Id><Title>THE STIMULUS Obama wasted on Union thugs &amp; Big Bank crooks.</Title><Msg>THE STIMULUS Obama wasted on Union thugs &amp; Big Bank crooks. Obama's Stimulus Failed To Keep Unemployment Below 8 Percent as Obama Promised Obama's $825 Billion Stimulus Failed To Keep The Unemployment Rate Below The 8 Percent And Is Nowhere Close To The 6 Percent They Predicted It Would Be At By Now. Instead, Since The Stimulus Was Passed, The Unemployment Rate Has Increased From 8.2 Percent To 8.5 Percent And Has Remained Above 8 Percent For A Post-WWII Record 35 Straight Months. The Unemployment Rate Peaked At 10.1 Percent In October 2009…</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363694060458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:54:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363694089139-14</Id><Title>Obamacare the US job killer.</Title><Msg>Obamacare the US job killer. On CBS' "60 Minutes", Obama Called His Health Care Package One Of His Major Accomplishments CBS’ Steve Kroft:"Why do you think you deserve to be reelected? What have you accomplished?" President Obama:"Not only saving this country from a great depression, not only saving the auto industry, but putting in place a system in which we're going to start lowering health care costs and you're never going to go bankrupt because you get sick or somebody in your family gets sick." (CBS' "60 Minutes," 12/11/11) Yet ObamaCare Has Failed To Make Health Insurance More Affordable PROMISE: Obama Promised His Plan "Would Save The Average Family $2,500 On Their Premiums." (Sen. Barack Obama, Remarks Of Senator Barack Obama's Plan To Fight For Working Families And Take On Special Interests In Washington, Indianapolis, IN, 6/20/08) FAILURE: FactCheck.org: ObamaCare Is Actually Making Health Care “Less Affordable.” “At the moment, the new law is making health care slightly less affordable. Independent health care experts say the law has caused some insurance premiums to rise. As we wrote in October, the new law has caused about a 1 percent to 3 percent increase in health insurance premiums for employer-sponsored family plans because of requirements for increased benefits. Last year's premium increases cast even more doubt on another promise the president has made -- that the health care law would 'lower premiums by up to $2,500 for a typical family per year.’”</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363694089139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:54:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363694112816-15</Id><Title>GREEN JOBS are another Obama utter failure. Most companies he funded are bankrupt now.</Title><Msg>GREEN JOBS are another Obama utter failure. Most companies he funded are bankrupt now. "The Obama Administration Has Managed The Nearly Impossible Feat Of Turning Energy Policy Into A Money Loser, Pouring Taxpayer Dollars Into Green-Energy Busts Like Solyndra."(Editorial, "The Non-Green Job Boom," The Wall Street Journal, 11/28/11) Obama Predicted His Investments In Green Energy Would Create 5 Million Jobs PROMISE: In 2008, Then-Senator Obama Claimed His Investments In Green Energy Would Create 5 Million New Jobs. OBAMA: "And I'll invest $150 billion over the next decade in affordable, renewable sources of energy -- wind power, and solar power, and the next generation of biofuels -- an investment that will lead to new industries and 5 million new jobs that pay well and can't be outsourced."(Sen. Barack Obama, Acceptance Speech Remarks At The Democratic National Convention, Denver, CO, 8/28/08) FAILURE: The Failure Of Obama's Green Jobs Programs “Gets More Embarrassing By The Day.”“The green jobs subsidy story gets more embarrassing by the day. Three years ago President Obama promised that by the end of the decade America would have five million green jobs, but so far some $90 billion in government spending has delivered very few.”</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363694112816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:55:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363694171603-16</Id><Title>HOME FORECLOSURES under Obama as President</Title><Msg>HOME FORECLOSURES under Obama as President PROMISE: President Obama Promised That His Housing Program Would Prevent 7 To 9 Million Families From Foreclosure. "And we will pursue the housing plan I'm outlining today. And through this plan, we will help between 7 and 9 million families restructure or refinance their mortgages so they can afford--avoid foreclosure." (President Barack Obama, Remarks On The Home Mortgage Industry In Mesa, Arizona, 2/18/09) FAILURE: Obama Has Only Helped 1.7 Million Avoid Foreclosure Of The 9 Million Homeowners He Promised. "President Obama pledged at the beginning of his term to boost the nation's crippled housing market and help as many as 9 million homeowners avoid losing their homes to foreclosure. Nearly three years later, it hasn't worked out. Obama has spent just $2.4 billion of the $50 billion he promised. The initiatives he announced have helped 1.7 million people."</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363694171603</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:56:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363694221224-17</Id><Title>OBAMA DEFICIT SPENDING THE US BANKRUPT just like Greece is now.</Title><Msg>OBAMA DEFICIT SPENDING THE US BANKRUPT Obama Promised To Cut The Deficit In Half, But Has Failed To Even Present A Plan That Would Bring The Deficit To Those Levels PROMISE: Obama Pledged To Cut The Deficit In Half By The End Of His First Term. OBAMA:”And that's why today I'm pledging to cut the deficit we inherited by half by the end of my first term in office." (President Barack Obama, Remarks At The Fiscal Responsibility Summit, Washington, D.C., 2/23/09) “President Barack Obama Plans To Cut The U.S. Budget Deficit To $533 Billion By The End Of His First Term ...” (Hans Nichols, "Obama Plans To Reduce Budget Deficit To $533 Billion By 2013," Bloomberg, 2/21/09) One White House Official Told Politico "We'll Cut It At Least In Half.""Under White House projections, this year's inherited budget deficit of $1.3 trillion will be cut to $533 billion by fiscal year 2013, the end of the first term. ‘So we'll cut it at least in half,’ the official said." (Mike Allen, "Obama Vows To Cut Huge Deficit In Half," Politico, 2/22/09) FAILURE: Even If Every Part Of Obama's Deficit Reduction Proposal Was Enacted, The Deficit At The End Of His First Term Would Still Be $1.33 Trillion, Over Double What He Promised. (“The President's Plan For Economic Growth And Deficit Reduction; Table S-3,” Office Of Management And Budget, 9/19/11)</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363694221224</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:57:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363694629464-18</Id><Topic><Title>Priebus: GOP has room for Pro-Gay Senator Rob Portman</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1363693663035</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:47:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tttt</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1363694629464</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:03:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363694638358-19</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz, Marco Rubio- NEW GOP PLATFORM- appeal to CUBAN and WHITE AMERICANS ONLY</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1363693498183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:44:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>iiii</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1363694638358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363694650594-20</Id><Topic><Title>REPUBS, U REALLY BELIEVE CHANGING YOUR CONVENTION DATE &amp; ELIMINATING DEBATES GOING TO MAKE YOUR HATED PLATFORM LIKED?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1363693461174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:44:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tttt</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1363694650594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:04:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363694779490-21</Id><Topic><Title>drstone gets thrown off the GE board again? him and his vensh_1 alias?</Title><Username>carey50fairy</Username><Timestamp>1363177402658</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 08:23:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ttttt</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1363694779490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:06:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363695674435-22</Id><Topic><Title>Leave it to GOP to come up with a solution for the mess that America is now in economically.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363693923894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:52:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you GOP.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363695674435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:21:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363695760420-23</Id><Topic><Title>drstone gets thrown off the GE board again? him and his vensh_1 alias?</Title><Username>carey50fairy</Username><Timestamp>1363177402658</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 08:23:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dddd</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1363695760420</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363696664757-24</Id><Topic><Title>drstone gets thrown off the GE board again? him and his vensh_1 alias?</Title><Username>carey50fairy</Username><Timestamp>1363177402658</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 08:23:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget Yoho...</Msg><Username>seanesq2001</Username><Timestamp>1363696664757</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:37:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363697110570-25</Id><Topic><Title>drstone will be here to profess his love for me once he finishes up on the GE board</Title><Username>sugar_brettches</Username><Timestamp>1363267578205</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:26:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ggggg</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1363697110570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363698472155-26</Id><Topic><Title>drstone will be here to profess his love for me once he finishes up on the GE board</Title><Username>sugar_brettches</Username><Timestamp>1363267578205</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:26:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>take your hopium</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363698472155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:07:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363698523074-27</Id><Topic><Title>Leave it to GOP to come up with a solution for the mess that America is now in economically.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363693923894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:52:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you GOD. Obama is the great satan.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363698523074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:08:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363698829439-28</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA DEFICIT SPENDING THE US BANKRUPT just like Greece is now.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363694221224</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:57:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Europe contagion is everywhere. It's a global economy. Europe had a housing bust worse than the USA. Eurozone fake AAA borrowing 10X worse than U.S. subprime fraud by illegal aliens and blacks getting free mortgages at church. Jesse Jackson Jr. wanted to go to jail for his own protection. Samsung is 20% of Korean GDP.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363698829439</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:13:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363699036323-29</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama American families cannot spend more than Mom &amp; Dad make in a year or they go bankrupt.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363693847488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama American families cannot spend more than Mom &amp; Dad make in a year or they go bankrupt. Look what happened to Greece mr.obama you spending fool. Stop using that Maxine Waters fuzzy ghetto math and balance the US budget. We the people demand it and do not want to be the next... *** Bend over Junior. Obama is gonna love you now.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363699036323</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:17:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363700397653-30</Id><Topic><Title>drstone will be here to profess his love for me once he finishes up on the GE board</Title><Username>sugar_brettches</Username><Timestamp>1363267578205</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:26:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's here right now. You don't recognize your lover's yohoho alias?</Msg><Username>wilmuth_farms</Username><Timestamp>1363700397653</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:39:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363702998559-31</Id><Title>It really is funny how stupid the tea billies are, how they will believe anything no matter how outrageous as long as it fits their demented</Title><Msg>philosophy, LOL “Here's the truth that the president won't tell you. Of every dollar that you hold in your hands, 70 cents of that dollar that's supposed to go to the poor doesn't. It actually goes to benefit the bureaucrats in Washington, D.C. — 70 cents on the dollar. That's how the president's caring works in practice. So $3 in food stamps for the needy, $7 in salaries and pensions for the bureaucrats who are supposed to be taking care of the poor. So with all due respect, I ask you, how does this show that our president cares about the poor?” — Rep. Michele Bachmann (R-Minn.), speaking at the Conservative Political Action Conference, March 16, 2013 but in the real world “I have seen this quoted back to me,” Tanner said in an interview Monday. “It is always quoted back to me wrong. I wrote about bureaucrats and others who serve the poor” — the whole panoply of people who receive federal dollars because of anti-poverty programs. Or, as Woodson originally put it, the “poverty industry.” Asked about Bachmann’s claim, Tanner said: “That’s not what I said.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363702998559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:23:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363703089504-32</Id><Topic><Title>It really is funny how stupid the tea billies are, how they will believe anything no matter how outrageous as long as it fits their demented</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363702998559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and of course then there is the truth- but that doesn't really matter in the tea billie world Indeed, the 2013 budget documents submitted to Congress by the Agriculture Department, which manages SNAP, shows that less than 6 percent of the program is spent on administrative costs. Only 166 people manage the $82 billion food-stamp program — many outside Washington — and the budget document says that staff salaries amount to one-third of 1 percent of USDA’s budget for food and nutrition programs.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363703089504</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:24:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363703224911-33</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this report yet? (CSCO)</Title><Username>mrowczynskibubblebutt</Username><Timestamp>1361804586311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:03:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like your free article.</Msg><Username>routxfelicia</Username><Timestamp>1363703224911</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:27:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363703321138-34</Id><Topic><Title>It really is funny how stupid the tea billies are, how they will believe anything no matter how outrageous as long as it fits their demented</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363702998559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so let's review bachmann says So $3 in food stamps for the needy, $7 in salaries and pensions for the bureaucrats who are supposed to be taking care of the poor. (so 70% is going to salaries and pensions she says) and the truth is and the budget document says that staff salaries amount to one-third of 1 percent of USDA’s budget for food and nutrition programs. So tea billies it isn't 70% it turns out to be 0.33% but tea billies are so stupid they believe anything</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363703321138</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:28:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363703443454-35</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO starting to move higher!</Title><Username>lucadobson</Username><Timestamp>1362659226270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 07:27:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report, subscribed</Msg><Username>browneantonio</Username><Timestamp>1363703443454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:30:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363703748890-36</Id><Topic><Title>It really is funny how stupid the tea billies are, how they will believe anything no matter how outrageous as long as it fits their demented</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363702998559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tea billies constantly looking to feed their outrage, facts don't matter, same old folks that used to like to lynch black men because of their own impotence</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363703748890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:35:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363703990024-37</Id><Topic><Title>It really is funny how stupid the tea billies are, how they will believe anything no matter how outrageous as long as it fits their demented</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363702998559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama, Biden and Lew overseas at the same time. Who is steering the ship? Captain of the Titanic left the bridge.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363703990024</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:39:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363704076665-38</Id><Topic><Title>It really is funny how stupid the tea billies are, how they will believe anything no matter how outrageous as long as it fits their demented</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363702998559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lulu Lemon has true transparency. Obama does not.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363704076665</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363704160644-39</Id><Topic><Title>Is there any question why everybody is shunning dumbivan now</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363649956170</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 19:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb---tell us again how you think Hitler and Mao were better people than George Bush---you lowlife piece of trash!</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363704160644</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:42:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363704289117-40</Id><Topic><Title>GREEN JOBS are another Obama utter failure. Most companies he funded are bankrupt now.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363694112816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was just a lesson about the free market and investing. The jobs are coming, but his investment had nothing to do with it. He threw money down a pit, and somebody else developed the new technology which will eventually create the jobs. Investing is whole different job than running the country. He needs to stick to finger pointing and blaming. He is a terrible investor.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1363704289117</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:44:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363704299500-41</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama American families cannot spend more than Mom &amp; Dad make in a year or they go bankrupt.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363693847488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well yohoho that might be what they tell you in teabagistan but in the real world things are a little more complicated, you see American Families, Corporations and Governments routinely spend more then they make in a year. What you perhaps meant was they can't consume more then they make in a year (even that is of course not true). You bought a house (or a trailer probably) at some point in your life. That would have been an investment and you would have spent a lot more that year then you made. Virtually every business that gets started spends more then it earns in it's early life, would you start no business in the country? Governments expense all capital investments, they don't capitalize them so by definition, unless you believe the Gov should make no investments ( no roads, bridges, aircraft carriers, medical studies) you are wrong again.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363704299500</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363704399918-42</Id><Topic><Title>It really is funny how stupid the tea billies are, how they will believe anything no matter how outrageous as long as it fits their demented</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363702998559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She probably said that because we lost 170 million jobs.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1363704399918</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363704550713-43</Id><Topic><Title>GREEN JOBS are another Obama utter failure. Most companies he funded are bankrupt now.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363694112816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well not really but all of the subsidies that Bush put into ethanol have been lost, solar energy costs have dropped by 80% thanks to Gov investments, it is the energy of the future,</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363704550713</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:49:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363705226267-44</Id><Topic><Title>GREEN JOBS are another Obama utter failure. Most companies he funded are bankrupt now.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363694112816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"solar energy costs have dropped by 80% thanks to Gov investments" German government? The Germans invented the modern technology which reduced the cost.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1363705226267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:00:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363705628328-45</Id><Topic><Title>GREEN JOBS are another Obama utter failure. Most companies he funded are bankrupt now.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363694112816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our government invested in the technical equivalent of the Commodore 64, while the Germans were building the Pentium.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1363705628328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:07:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363705785813-46</Id><Title>OBAMA IN VIOLATION OF U.S. LAW ON BUDGET</Title><Msg>his lame admin. still has no budget as required by law. He must be arrested and jailed, the SCOTUS should order this immediately, he is in contempt of the constitution and the rule of law of this nation.</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363705785813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:09:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363706080255-47</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IN VIOLATION OF U.S. LAW ON BUDGET</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363705785813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:09:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leave POTUS alone. He is taxing the rich, and giving to the poor. His band of merry men are going to rescue fair maidens and slay the dragons. He's black. Isn't that great?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1363706080255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363706503290-48</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IN VIOLATION OF U.S. LAW ON BUDGET</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363705785813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:09:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>funny userid!!! even if your posts don't make any sense.</Msg><Username>allnewmagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1363706503290</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:21:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363707198123-49</Id><Topic><Title>Secret CSCO Info Revealed</Title><Username>willson_ethan</Username><Timestamp>1363607782953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 07:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome news</Msg><Username>matthewthomas115</Username><Timestamp>1363707198123</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:33:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363707702507-50</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IN VIOLATION OF U.S. LAW ON BUDGET</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363705785813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:09:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as usual magloser, your post lack any intelligent content--why do you bother? Shoo, go away now.</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363707702507</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:41:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363707792118-51</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IN VIOLATION OF U.S. LAW ON BUDGET</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363705785813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:09:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't you just Impeach him? How'd that last Impeachy work out for you wingnutters?</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363707792118</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363707859079-52</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz, Marco Rubio- NEW GOP PLATFORM- appeal to CUBAN and WHITE AMERICANS ONLY</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1363693498183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:44:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A friggin Canadian and Fidel Rubio talkin to their bozo's?</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363707859079</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363708023333-53</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IN VIOLATION OF U.S. LAW ON BUDGET</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363705785813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:09:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The impeachment of Slick worked just fine other magloser's id. He lost credibility with all decent people LOL! He is seen now as a pathetic, woman-attacking rapist and loser world-wide!</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363708023333</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:47:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363708045788-54</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IN VIOLATION OF U.S. LAW ON BUDGET</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363705785813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:09:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The last one never even got to the floor? That was when you guys tried to impeach Bush.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1363708045788</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:47:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363708264374-55</Id><Title>Happy Anniversary wingnutters!</Title><Msg>March 19, 2013 Cheney Marks Tenth Anniversary of Pretending There Was Reason to Invade Iraq Posted by Andy Borowitz HOUSTON (The Borowitz Report)—In a sombre ceremony attended by former members of the Bush administration, the former Vice-President #$%$ Cheney marked the tenth anniversary of making up a reason to invade Iraq. The ceremony, held on the grounds of the Halliburton Company headquarters, brought together the former Defense Secretary Donald Rumsfeld, the former Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice, the former Deputy Secretary of Defense Paul Wolfowitz, and other key members of the lying effort. Calling the assembled officials “profiles in fabrication,” Mr. Cheney praised them for their decade of dedication to a totally fictitious rationale. “Making up a reason to invade a country is the easy part,” Mr. Cheney told them. “Sticking to a pretend story for ten years—that is the stuff of valor.” Mr. Cheney added that their “steadfast charade had raised the bar for all future administrations.” “When it is time to invade Iran or Venezuela, will the President have the will to make up an entirely fake reason to do it?” he asked. “That remains to be seen.” The ceremony ended on an emotional note, as Mr. Cheney placed a wreath on the Tomb of the Unknown W.M.D. Former President George W. Bush, who was said to be otherwise engaged, was represented at the event by a nude self-portrait.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363708264374</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:51:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363708320762-56</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IN VIOLATION OF U.S. LAW ON BUDGET</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363705785813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:09:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Clinton remains the most admired past president alive in the US, it's funny how disconnected from reality you pinheads are, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363708320762</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:52:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363708525847-57</Id><Topic><Title>GREEN JOBS are another Obama utter failure. Most companies he funded are bankrupt now.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363694112816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ethanol never made economic sense. Even saying," I have a good idea, let's burn food for energy", sounds dumb and it was and is. The solar improvements in efficiency weren't funded by the federal government at all, but by private industry. Solar isn't predicted to continue its efficiency curve and, therefore, will never be economic without subsidy. We are losing our competitive edge as a country at an increasing rate as we shut down coal ( and its 10,000 year supply) and watch energy costs go up by 40%.</Msg><Username>rsjjs2003</Username><Timestamp>1363708525847</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363708982896-58</Id><Topic><Title>GREEN JOBS are another Obama utter failure. Most companies he funded are bankrupt now.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363694112816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coal maybe the most expensive fuel in the world once you take into account externalities, solar prices are plummeting The unsubsidized cost of renewable power produced from solar and wind energy will be no more expensive than that from oil, natural gas, and coal by the end of the decade, Energy Secretary Steven Chu predicted during a speech at a Pew Charitable Trusts event late March before the Commerce Deptartment and ITC had made their final determinations on Chinese import duties. Chu pegged installed solar PV grid parity at around $1 per watt.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363708982896</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363709284174-59</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares?</Title><Username>fredric.sylvester</Username><Timestamp>1363621330780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 11:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good report :)</Msg><Username>bermudez.dexter</Username><Timestamp>1363709284174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:08:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363709327649-60</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IN VIOLATION OF U.S. LAW ON BUDGET</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363705785813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:09:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are right donkey! he should be arrested along with his entire administration of criminals!! He shows no sense whatsoever of accountabilty....Obama is worthless!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363709327649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:08:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363709341406-61</Id><Topic><Title>GREEN JOBS are another Obama utter failure. Most companies he funded are bankrupt now.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363694112816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are many who believe the books are cooked, and that the solar experience has yet to test it's lifecycle projections. Many investors could get burned on overzealous projections.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1363709341406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:09:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363709356928-62</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>vincent.middleton</Username><Timestamp>1362511286358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 14:21:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great job</Msg><Username>parish_charlotte</Username><Timestamp>1363709356928</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:09:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363709483908-63</Id><Title>THE NEW POPE CONDEMNS HILLARY'S NEW "POSITION". LMAO!</Title><Msg>her latest "pro#$%$ marriage" view as corrupt, evil and satanic! Well-put!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363709483908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:11:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363709626258-64</Id><Topic><Title>On an illegally wiretapped recording, President Lyndon B. Johnson caught Richard Nixon prolonging the Vietnam War to win the 1968 presidenti</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363709564068</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:12:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>of course, it's the only reason Bush invaded, remember his popularity ratings were at all time lows until he pulled the war card, tea billies are so stupid</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363709626258</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363709666170-65</Id><Title>the thing about the tea billies is they don't want to know the truth, it confuses them because it doesn't fit in their model of the world</Title><Msg>That trend has slowed in the second Obama administration, but the budget, planning capabilities and training programs of the State Department are still laughably small compared with those of the U.S. military. Money equals power, influence and a seat at the table in Washington. As one former national security reporter put it to me, weak civilian institutions leads to fewer potential civilian responses to crises. In his first major speech as secretary of state, John Kerry tried to put the size of the American civilian effort in perspective. He cited a recent poll that found most Americans believe the State Department and U.S. foreign aid programs consume 25 percent of federal spending. In fact, they receive 1.0 percent.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363709666170</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:14:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363709704365-66</Id><Topic><Title>THE NEW POPE CONDEMNS HILLARY'S NEW "POSITION". LMAO!</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363709483908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:11:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, only Willy would let that ugly fat broad take a mouthful of his willy!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363709704365</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:15:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363709726284-67</Id><Topic><Title>Is there any question why everybody is shunning dumbivan now</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363649956170</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 19:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363709726284</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:15:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363709727326-68</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>vincent.middleton</Username><Timestamp>1362511286358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 14:21:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good report :)</Msg><Username>bermudez.dexter</Username><Timestamp>1363709727326</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:15:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363709770861-69</Id><Topic><Title>THE NEW POPE CONDEMNS HILLARY'S NEW "POSITION". LMAO!</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363709483908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:11:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah I'm sure the Pope would approve of you and your comments</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363709770861</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:16:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363709847342-70</Id><Topic><Title>THE NEW POPE CONDEMNS HILLARY'S NEW "POSITION". LMAO!</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363709483908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:11:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL as if the Pope would approve of you gayhomo-abortion defenders!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363709847342</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:17:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363709867164-71</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares?</Title><Username>fredric.sylvester</Username><Timestamp>1363621330780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 11:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great job</Msg><Username>parish_charlotte</Username><Timestamp>1363709867164</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363710036113-72</Id><Topic><Title>Report: 1 in 3 seniors dies with, not of, dementia</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363709872356</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:17:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like thin film solar, that's at least ten years away.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1363710036113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:20:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363710191621-73</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO starting to move higher!</Title><Username>lucadobson</Username><Timestamp>1362659226270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 07:27:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very detailed and helpful report</Msg><Username>frankielloyd268</Username><Timestamp>1363710191621</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:23:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363710207149-74</Id><Title>Desperation setting in</Title><Msg>JuniorDumbivan beside himself with loneliness. After professing his love for Hitler and Mao he can't understand why other posters think he's a lowlife commie loving traitor.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363710207149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:23:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363710233546-75</Id><Topic><Title>THE NEW POPE CONDEMNS HILLARY'S NEW "POSITION". LMAO!</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363709483908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:11:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>she's a filthy criminal just like her bum husband, she has blood on her paws from benghazi for sure!</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363710233546</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:23:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363710453643-76</Id><Topic><Title>Report: 1 in 3 seniors dies with, not of, dementia</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363709872356</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:17:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the U.S. continues to find a welcoming market in Asia for its coal exports. Over 2012, the U.S. exported more than 120 million tons of coal, more than doubling figures from 2009, the Wall Street Journal reports."</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1363710453643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:27:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363710825342-77</Id><Topic><Title>Deal emerging in Albany could up New York's minimum wage up to $9 an hour by 2015 over three incremental bumps</Title><Username>philsimms</Username><Timestamp>1363710601534</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:30:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the unskilled and teenagers will see a rise in their unemployment as the raises take effect.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363710825342</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363711242628-78</Id><Topic><Title>THE NEW POPE CONDEMNS HILLARY'S NEW "POSITION". LMAO!</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363709483908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:11:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>she is your next president, assuming you live that long</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363711242628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:40:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363711727399-79</Id><Topic><Title>CNN: Congress tries to beat new shutdown deadline</Title><Username>philsimms</Username><Timestamp>1363710407090</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:26:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LULU showing a crack. LOL! NOW THAT'S FUNNY!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363711727399</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:48:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363712030183-80</Id><Topic><Title>CNN: Congress tries to beat new shutdown deadline</Title><Username>philsimms</Username><Timestamp>1363710407090</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:26:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>let's hope the tea billies commit political suicide and shut down the Gov</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363712030183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:53:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363712527272-81</Id><Title>Has Washington gone crazy?</Title><Msg>Govt.has approved reducing tuition program for service veterans due to sequester but just approved sending $37 million to Pakistan for their education programs since the sequester. What the hell is going on??</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363712527272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:02:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363712734241-82</Id><Topic><Title>Has Washington gone crazy?</Title><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363712527272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah that was the beauty of sequestration, they picked out only programs that made no sense to cut, to cut, it was so the GOP and DNC would both agree to compromise, but the GOP decided it would rather cut these programs then compromise</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363712734241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:05:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363713201448-83</Id><Title>No gun, no death, NRA murders another 16 year old</Title><Msg>Police say Caleb was fatally shot early Sunday after entering a neighbor's home through a back window. Gordley said his son snuck out of the house Saturday night and went drinking with friends. They walked home from the party and Caleb went in through a back window, mistaking the neighbor's house for his own. Caleb had lived in his home for less than a year and the houses look similar. Before the shooting, an alarm was activated inside the home, and the homeowner says he discovered 16-year-old Caleb A. Gordley on the stairwell. On Tuesday both parents said they do not blame the shooter for what happened.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363713201448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363713292280-84</Id><Topic><Title>Has Washington gone crazy?</Title><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363712527272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb, I will try to be polite.I read your comments comparing Bush to Hitler and Mao.I thought they were asinine and disgusting. And so I'm not interested in your opinion on anything I may post. In fact, I would prefer if you" shun" me. Now,you have a niceday.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363713292280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:14:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363713637231-85</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO starting to move higher!</Title><Username>lucadobson</Username><Timestamp>1362659226270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 07:27:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>interesting report, thanks!</Msg><Username>kennethalexander660</Username><Timestamp>1363713637231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:20:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363713648263-86</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA DEFICIT SPENDING THE US BANKRUPT just like Greece is now.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363694221224</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:57:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama the biggest deficit spending President of all times and he did it in 4 years. OUCH!</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363713648263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363713688180-87</Id><Title>DEMOCRATS HAVE NOT 'GONE' CRAZY....they have always been distorted, perverted, and dysfunctional</Title><Msg>its just that they mulitply and pass their insanity from generation to generation...their insanity and their unemployment benefits....it all gets passed on together.....to millions of slackers and droolers.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363713688180</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:21:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363713837414-88</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this report yet? (CSCO)</Title><Username>mrowczynskibubblebutt</Username><Timestamp>1361804586311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:03:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool picks. Please always share this to us.</Msg><Username>lecaniidbianca</Username><Timestamp>1363713837414</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:23:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363713848670-89</Id><Topic><Title>the thing about the tea billies is they don't want to know the truth, it confuses them because it doesn't fit in their model of the world</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363709666170</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:14:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Freshman GOPer claims wars in Iraq and Afghanistan ‘not responsible for’ debt Morgan Whitaker, @morganwinn 2:00 PM on 03/14/2013 Twitter75 Facebook2K+ 20 Freshman Congressman Tom Cotton of Arkansas downplayed the role that the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan have had on the nation’s debt Thursday morning, insisting that the overall impact is “relatively low.” Cotton spoke at a the “Too Many American Wars? Should We Fight Anywhere and Can We Afford It?” panel discussion at CPAC Thursday. “Can we afford this war? The answer is yes, we can afford it,”Cotton said. “We must afford it. We certainly have a staggering national debt. Our military is not responsible for that. As an historic average of a percent of our economy and federal spending, it’s still relatively low. It’s projected to trend downward.” BUT IN THE REAL WORLD A report released Thursday leading up to the 10th anniversary of the U.S.-led invasion of Iraq determined that that war alone has cost the U.S. $1.7 trillion dollars.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363713848670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:24:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363714016365-90</Id><Topic><Title>the thing about the tea billies is they don't want to know the truth, it confuses them because it doesn't fit in their model of the world</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363709666170</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:14:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>truth is it was only the GOP who committed voter fraud, you know, in the real world The Florida Department of Law Enforcement revealed Tuesday that two employees of a company hired by the Republican Party of Florida to register voters admitted they committed fraud during the 2012 election season. The two former employees of Strategic Allied Consulting are facing third degree felony charges after admitting that they submitted dozens of forged voter registration applications last fall ahead of the 2012 election. The employees, Rebekah Joy Paul and Christian Davis Price, told investigators they forged forms in order to meet the required number of applications and receive payment. Paul also said that her bosses at Strategic Allied instructed her to not register Democrats, although a lawyer for the company denies that allegation.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363714016365</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:26:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363714140886-91</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares?</Title><Username>fredric.sylvester</Username><Timestamp>1363621330780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 11:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks. Great report</Msg><Username>coopernancy789</Username><Timestamp>1363714140886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363714416315-92</Id><Title>everything is upside down in the rabbit hole, LOL</Title><Msg>Sarah Palin "I think it's appalling and a violation of our freedom of the press." —On negative media coverage of Republican congressional candidate Vaughn Ward, Boise, Idaho, May 21, 2010 cause the only way to preserve freedom of the press in the tea billie rabbit hole is to prohibit it, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363714416315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:33:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363714461359-93</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>vincent.middleton</Username><Timestamp>1362511286358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 14:21:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks. Great report</Msg><Username>coopernancy789</Username><Timestamp>1363714461359</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:34:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363714476872-94</Id><Topic><Title>Secret CSCO Info Revealed</Title><Username>willson_ethan</Username><Timestamp>1363607782953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 07:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome informations</Msg><Username>logangreen580</Username><Timestamp>1363714476872</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:34:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363714527640-95</Id><Title>And I'm pretty sure that wouldn't be a good thing!! LOL</Title><Msg>“Nuclear weaponry, of course, would be the be-all, end-all of just too many people in too many parts of our planet.” -- CBS interview with Katie Couric, September 25, 2008</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363714527640</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:35:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363714872103-96</Id><Title>Who am I ??</Title><Msg>HMMMM.....Well let's see.Junior says I'm Banjo, Flute,Capt Gail,Wonka, Doremi, Deadpainting, Ivanhoe,and probably some more I forgot LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL I have gained COMPLETE CONTROL of his one brain cell. .I am his every thought!!!! Everyone is me!!! HEEHEEHEEHEEHEEHEE DANCE ,MY PUPPET , DANCE!!!! I EFFING OWN YOU !!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363714872103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:41:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363715568230-97</Id><Topic><Title>Has Washington gone crazy?</Title><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363712527272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obama is running the country making sure he punishes americans because of the sequester he signed last year. he will use this to blame it on GOP. telling sob story of how gop hates service people.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363715568230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:52:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363715801023-98</Id><Title>liberals using debt ceiling to start fear blame game</Title><Msg>this is getting old-the panic and blame stuff needs to stop. grow up guys do your job.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363715801023</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:56:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363715907554-99</Id><Topic><Title>Who am I ??</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363714872103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:41:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just put the twit on ignore. it is just looking for attention. we know the only one on the board playing id game. hint as a typical liberal does -blaming others for doing what it is doing.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363715907554</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:58:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363715998337-100</Id><Title>Dividend Question</Title><Msg>Is the next dividend payment date on or about April 2?</Msg><Username>jog49</Username><Timestamp>1363715998337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363716024307-101</Id><Title>remember in 1996 clinton and libs voted down gays right to marry</Title><Msg>liberals are to young and nieve to understand how they are being played.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363716024307</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:00:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363716099372-102</Id><Title>vix calls</Title><Msg>making me so happy.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363716099372</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:01:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363716183048-103</Id><Topic><Title>Who am I ??</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363714872103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:41:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess you know I'm not you,Dead.LOL The idiot keeps accusing everybody and he's always wrong. I'M JUST ME!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363716183048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:03:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363716347476-104</Id><Title>IF ROMNEY-RYAN HAD BEEN ELECTED, WE WOULDN'T BE IN THIS MESS</Title><Msg>today of STILL NO RECOVERY, NO budget, Gay Marriage BS, Military scale-down, ETC ETC. But instead some total fools reelected the incompetent chimp Obama! You got what you asked for mowwwrons!</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1363716347476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:05:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363716395359-105</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares?</Title><Username>fredric.sylvester</Username><Timestamp>1363621330780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 11:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report !!</Msg><Username>ronda_skinner</Username><Timestamp>1363716395359</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:06:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363716448059-106</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Banjo, Flute,Capt Gail,Wonka, Doremi, Deadpainting,</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363715843814</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:57:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no, actually you are just a mentally-deficient DEM-PINKO suhkerofpeanusses!</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1363716448059</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:07:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363716466159-107</Id><Topic><Title>IF ROMNEY-RYAN HAD BEEN ELECTED, WE WOULDN'T BE IN THIS MESS</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1363716347476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But I hear repubs did an autopsy on themselves recently. Aren't autopsies done on dead things? LOL.</Msg><Username>ursofulofkrap</Username><Timestamp>1363716466159</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363716614190-108</Id><Topic><Title>IF ROMNEY-RYAN HAD BEEN ELECTED, WE WOULDN'T BE IN THIS MESS</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1363716347476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SAY HOW did that colonscopy of your go today? Did surf do you good? LMAOAY All of us are waiting for the autopsy of the Oloser Admin. for he is a LAMEDUCK who will only see gridlock from now on! LMAOAY</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1363716614190</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:10:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363716674580-109</Id><Title>looks like been will need to print more money</Title><Msg>come on benny print monkey print.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363716674580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:11:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363716781252-110</Id><Title>what happens when CA goes bankrupt?</Title><Msg>print benny print.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363716781252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363716785822-111</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>vincent.middleton</Username><Timestamp>1362511286358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 14:21:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report !!</Msg><Username>ronda_skinner</Username><Timestamp>1363716785822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:13:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363718266354-112</Id><Topic><Title>IF ROMNEY-RYAN HAD BEEN ELECTED, WE WOULDN'T BE IN THIS MESS</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1363716347476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we would be in a great depression and at war with iran</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363718266354</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363718271830-113</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Banjo, Flute,Capt Gail,Wonka, Doremi, Deadpainting,</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363715843814</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:57:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>,Pecker-wood, if I were you I'd want to be some else also!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1363718271830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363719079924-114</Id><Topic><Title>IF ROMNEY-RYAN HAD BEEN ELECTED, WE WOULDN'T BE IN THIS MESS</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1363716347476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clearly america wanted gay marriage and a military scale-down or Romney would have won. As for the rest of the budget concerns that has more to do with who is in charge of congress, and it is split so I doubt it would be much different.</Msg><Username>cubbies622</Username><Timestamp>1363719079924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:51:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363719101432-115</Id><Topic><Title>Who am I ??</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363714872103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:41:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but wait, I am Deadpainting !</Msg><Username>carey50fairy</Username><Timestamp>1363719101432</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:51:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363719723951-116</Id><Title>Can U imagine if Obama were POTUS when 9/11 happened?</Title><Msg>How would he have campaigned his way out of that one? Actually, the way it works is the BIG GUBMENT, party-before-country (D) POTUS screws everything up and the new GOP president has to clean up the mess...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1363719723951</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:02:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363720541725-117</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares?</Title><Username>fredric.sylvester</Username><Timestamp>1363621330780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 11:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks !</Msg><Username>wilkerson_carolyn</Username><Timestamp>1363720541725</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:15:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363720689569-118</Id><Topic><Title>what happens when CA goes bankrupt?</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363716781252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:13:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>China will have to bail them out, of course. Otherwise, America is broke.</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1363720689569</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363720834796-119</Id><Topic><Title>Who am I ??</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363714872103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:41:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stop pretending to be someone that you're not!</Msg><Username>dumbpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363720834796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363720924072-120</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>vincent.middleton</Username><Timestamp>1362511286358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 14:21:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks !</Msg><Username>wilkerson_carolyn</Username><Timestamp>1363720924072</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:22:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363721937929-121</Id><Title>LOL! at Democrats/Obama budget.</Title><Msg>The plan submitted by Senate Budget Chairman Patty Murray contrasts sharply. While we appreciate that the Senate actually produced a budget for the first time in four years, it is a huge disappointment. The budget submitted by Senate Democrats calls for $1.5 trillion in higher taxes, trillions more in new spending, and does absolutely nothing to address the broken entitlement system our country is facing. Senator Murray has no plan to ever balance the budget, and instead does the exact opposite - increasing spending and adding an additional $7 trillion to the national debt. Overall, Murray’s plan is very dangerous for Americans and our economy as a whole. Continuing out-of-control spending means raising taxes on you, at a time when many Americans can’t afford more tax increases. To not cut spending is irresponsible, but to not even mention it is pure insanity. We wish the Senate Democrats had put more serious effort into addressing the real problems we face.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363721937929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:38:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363721965473-122</Id><Title>Obama you owe the American people a responsible, balanced budget</Title><Msg>Obama you owe the American people a responsible, balanced budget. Our skyrocketing debt is damaging our economy and threatening our future. It's time to change course. Today, we're introducing a plan to do just that. House Republicans are offering a common-sense plan to balance the budget in ten years. The Senate Democrats' budget, on the other hand, never balances - ever. Balancing the budget isn't just about making numbers on a spreadsheet line up. It's about the well-being of the country. A balanced budget will revive our economy and expand opportunity. Now do your job Mr. Obama. Already Democrats are falsely attacking our budget. We need your support to help us push back and put in place real solutions to our fiscal challenges. Now go do your job Mr. President.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363721965473</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:39:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363721999604-123</Id><Title>It’s hard to think of a president that has been more of an Epic Failure than President Obama</Title><Msg>It’s hard to think of a president that has been more of an Epic Failure than President Obama. Even Carter is glad this guy came along, so at least he knows he is no longer the worst president ever. Here is just a short list of Obama’s Failures: 1. Hawaii is in Asia 2. Passing on the keystone pipeline. 3. Touts a Green Energy Company as exemplary that fails a year later. 4. Using the Gulf Oil Spill to promote Green Energy – instead of cleaning it up. 5. Thinking the Tea Party is a passing fad – or that they are racists. 6. Pulling out of Iraq with no clear victory over insurgent forces. 7. Trying to re-write history through speeches – with inaccurate information (i.e. Statue of Liberty) 8. Getting a Nobel Prize for being the most ineffective President in the history of the United States, though some say it was for his pigment. 9. Putting all legislation on the Internet for five days before it comes to a vote. 10. Returning the bust of Churchill to the Brits. 11. Giving a collection of DVDs to the British PM. 12. Denying the notion of American Exceptionalism. 13. Promising to close Gitmo — failing to do so. 14. Securing the Olympics for Chicago in 2016. 15. Naming numerous Communists/Socialists/Progressives to his various Czar positions and then watching them scurry for cover when Beck begins to call them out, forcing them to resign. 16. Government races for NJ, VA and the Senate Seat in Mass. 17. The midterm elections, which Obama himself called a shellacking. 18. Prediction that stimulus would ensure that unemployment doesn’t exceed 8%. 19. Bowing to just about everybody. 20. Proposing amnesty for illegal aliens to increase the population of voters for Democrat elections. 21. He said, I have visited 57 states. Now there is just 1 left to visit. 22. Obama to Medvedev…give me space I will have more flexibility after my election.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363721999604</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363722010542-124</Id><Topic><Title>LOL! at Democrats/Obama budget.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363721937929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:38:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U.S. Falls to 22nd in List of Top Countries for Foreign Investment: Milken Institute</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1363722010542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:40:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363722122345-125</Id><Title>mrkink42 - another GE board REJECT ! posting here!</Title><Msg>my oh my!</Msg><Username>pugsley_dimwitty</Username><Timestamp>1363722122345</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:42:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363722626367-126</Id><Topic><Title>LOL! at Democrats/Obama budget.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363721937929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:38:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is that "Obama taking from the rich, working out for you Pecker-woods? U.S. Companies Stashing More Cash Abroad As Stock Piles Hit Record $1.45T Corporate America has dramatically increased its cash piles over the past few years, stashing more and more Benjamins every year since 2007. In 2012, U.S. non-financial companies filled their coffers with an additional $130 billion, taking their total cash to a record $1.45 trillion as the economy has stagnated and the labor market has moved sideways. At the same time, a prohibitive corporate tax scheme coupled with emerging market growth have pushed U.S. firms to keep 58% of their cash, or $840 billion, overseas.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1363722626367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363723076352-127</Id><Title>Democrats in the Hall of Shame list of poster boys with zero family values.</Title><Msg>Democrats in the Hall of Shame list of poster boys with zero family values. Newest members Jesse Jackson Jr. scamming campaign money &amp; found guilty and Larry Brinkin, the gay activist arrested for child pornography today 3/14/13. 1. Bill Clinton the Cigar Sex expert with Monica. 2. Anthony Wiener the twitter pervert photo poster. 3. John Edwards who cheated on his dying wife. 4. Al Gore the massage in hotel sex pervert. 5. Barney Frank the #$%$ lover now married to another man. 6. Charley Rangel the tax cheat expert. 7. Gary Hart the boat cheating lover boy. 8. The 3- Kennedy Boys real hound dogs. 9. Former New Orleans mayor Ray Nagin 10. Jesse Jackson that is my baby after all. 11. Lance Armstrong another famous lying liberal. 12. Bob Menendez democrat Senate member that loves 16 year old girls. 13. Larry Brinkin, the gay activist arrested for child pornography today 3/14/13. 14. Obama &amp; Vera and neither are talking. Why do Liberals elect and love dirt bags like listed above.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363723076352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:57:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363723173140-128</Id><Topic><Title>socialist boy priorities-ffod stamps for illegals, education funds for pakistan</Title><Username>mr.kink42</Username><Timestamp>1363722075635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:41:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah those were the 98% that Bonehead wanted and got remember? Ya enjoying Boneheads sequestration, LOL Nearly half of Americans would blame Republicans if $1.2 trillion in spending cuts go into effect on March 1, according to a poll released Wednesday. Only 31 percent would blame President Barack Obama, according to the Pew Research Center/USA Today poll, while 49 percent would blame the congressional GOP. Eleven percent would blame both. you should be glad about sequestration, the gov should play no role in your life remember, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363723173140</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:59:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363723261304-129</Id><Title>Here is Obama &amp; Pope Joke for you CONSERVATIVES to enjoy!</Title><Msg>A Good Catholic Joke about the Pope &amp; Obama The Pope and Obama are on the same stage in Yankee Stadium in front of a huge crowd. The Pope leans towards Mr. Obama and said, "Do you know that with one little wave of my hand I can make every person in this crowd go wild with joy? This joy will not be a momentary display, but will go deep into their hearts and they'll forever speak of this day and rejoice!" Obama replied, "I seriously doubt that! With one little wave of your hand....Show me!" So the Pope backhanded him and knocked him off the stage! AND THE CROWD ROARED &amp; CHEERED WILDLY and there was happiness throughout the land Kind of brings a tear to your eye, doesn't it?</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363723261304</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:01:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363723670850-130</Id><Title>Bob was afraid of black people but would blow them for $20 LOL</Title><Msg>Robert “Bob” Allen, Florida state Rep. arrested in the afternoon at a Veteran’s Memorial Park for solicitation of prostitution from an undercover male officer inside a restroom. According to the papers, Bob “offer[ed] to perform oral sex for $20″. Bob later claimed that his offer had something to do with his being afraid of black people</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363723670850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:07:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363723723562-131</Id><Title>larry confessed and pled guilty, now he just has issues, LOL</Title><Msg>Larry Craig, Republican Senator for Idaho, was arrested on July 11, 2007, by plainclothes police officer investigating complaints of lewd behavior in a Minneapolis-St. Paul International Airport airport men’s room. On August 8 in Hennepin County Municipal Court in Bloomington, Minnesota, Craig entered a guilty plea and paid a $500 fine.. On September 1st, Craig subsequently announced his retirement from the Senate. Five days later, Craig changed his mind, renounced his retirement and began a battle to have his guilty plea overturned. Craig supported the Federal Marriage Amendment, which barred extension of rights to same-sex couples; he voted for cloture on the amendment in both 2004 and 2006, and was a cosponsor in 2008.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363723723562</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:08:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363723760499-132</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares?</Title><Username>fredric.sylvester</Username><Timestamp>1363621330780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 11:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great one.</Msg><Username>bernice_abbott</Username><Timestamp>1363723760499</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:09:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363723895220-133</Id><Title>The following are 55 facts about the debt and U.S. government finances</Title><Msg>that every American voter should know.... #1 While Barack Obama has been president, the U.S. government has spent about 11 dollars for every 7 dollars of revenue that it has actually brought in. #2 During the fiscal year that just ended, the U.S. government took in 2.449 trillion dollars but it spent 3.538 trillion dollars. #3 During fiscal year 2011, over a trillion dollars of government money was spent on 83 different welfare programs, and those numbers do not even include Social Security or Medicare. #4 Over the past four years, welfare spending has increased by 32 percent. In inflation-adjusted dollars, spending on those programs has risen by 378 percent over the past 30 years. At this point, more than 100 million Americans are enrolled in at least one welfare program run by the federal government. Once again, these figures do not even include Social Security or Medicare. #5 Over the past year, the number of Americans getting a free cell phone from the federal government has grown by 43 percent. Now more than 16 million Americans are enjoying what has come to be known as an "Obamaphone". #6 When Barack Obama first entered the White House, about 32 million Americans were on food stamps. Now, nearly 47 million Americans are on food stamps. And this has happened during what Obama refers to as "an economic recovery". #7 The U.S. government recently spent 27 million dollars on pottery classes in Morocco. #8 The U.S. Department of Agriculture recently spent $300,000 to encourage Americans to eat caviar at a time when more families than ever are having a really hard time just trying to put any food on the table at all. #9 During 2012, the National Science Foundation spent $516,000 to support the creation of a video game called "Prom Week", which apparently simulates "all the social interactions of the event." #10 The U.S. Department of Agriculture gave the largest snack food maker in the world (PepsiCo Inc.) a total of 1.3 million dollars in corporate welfare that was used to help build "a Greek yogurt factory in New York." #11 The National Science Foundation recently gave researchers at Purdue University $350,000. They used part of that money to help fund a study that discovered that if golfers imagine that a hole is bigger it will help them with their putting. #12 If you can believe it, $10,000 from the federal government was actually used to purchase talking urinal cakes up in Michigan. #13 The National Science Foundation recently gave a whopping $697,177 to a New York City-based theater company to produce a musical about climate change. #14 The National Institutes of Health recently gave $666,905 to a group of researchers that is studying the benefits of watching reruns on television. #15 The National Science Foundation has given 1.2 million dollars to a team of "scientists" that is spending part of that money on a study that is seeking to determine whether elderly Americans would benefit from playing World of Warcraft or not. #16 The National Institutes of Health recently gave $548,731 to a team of researchers that concluded that those that drink heavily in their thirties also tend to feel more immature. #17 The National Science Foundation recently spent $30,000 on a study to determine if "gaydar" actually exists. This is the conclusion that the researchers reached at the end of the study.... "Gaydar is indeed real and… its accuracy is driven by sensitivity to individual facial features" #18 Back in 2011, the National Institutes of Health spent $592,527 on a study that sought to figure out once and for all why chimpanzees throw poop. #19 The U.S. government spends more on the military than China, Russia, Japan, India, and the rest of NATO combined. In fact, the United States accounts for 41.0% of all military spending on the planet. China is next with only 8.2%. #20 In a previous article, I noted that close to 500,000 federal employees now make at least $100,000 a year. #21 In 2006, only 12 percent of all federal workers made $100,000 or more per year. Now, approximately 22 percent of all federal workers do. #22 If you can believe it, there are 77,000 federal workers that make more than the governors of their own states do. #23 During 2010, the average federal employee in the Washington D.C. area received total compensation worth more than $126,000. #24 The U.S. Department of Defense had just nine civilians earning $170,000 or more back in 2005. When Barack Obama became president, the U.S. Department of Defense had 214 civilians earning $170,000 or more. By June 2010, the U.S. Department of Defense had 994 civilians earning $170,000 or more. #25 During 2010, compensation for federal employees came to a grand total of approximately 447 billion dollars. #26 If you can believe it, close to 15,000 retired federal employees are currently collecting federal pensions for life worth at least $100,000 annually. That list includes such names as Newt Gingrich, Bob Dole, Trent Lott, #$%$ Gephardt and #$%$ Cheney. #27 During 2010, the federal government spent $33,387 on the hair care needs of U.S. Senators. #28 During 2010, U.S. Senators pulled $72,370 out of the "Senate Restaurant Fund". #29 During 2010, an average of $4,005,900 of U.S. taxpayer money was spent on "personal" and "office" expenses per Senator. #30 In 2013, 3.7 million dollars will be spent to support the lavish lifestyles of former presidents such as George W. Bush and Bill Clinton. #31 During 2011, the federal government spent a total of 1.4 BILLION dollars just on the Obamas. #32 When you combine all federal government spending, all state government spending and all local government spending, it comes to approximately 41 percent of U.S. GDP. But don't worry, all of our politicians insist that this is not socialism. #33 As I have written about previously, less than 30 percent of all Americans lived in a home where at least one person received financial assistance from the federal government back in 1983. Today, that number is sitting at an all-time high of 49 percent. #34 Back in 1990, the federal government accounted for just 32 percent of all health care spending in America. This year, it is being projected that the federal government will account for more than 50 percent of all health care spending in the United States. #35 The number of Americans on Medicaid soared from 34 million in 2000 to 54 million in 2011, and it is being projected that Obamacare will add 16 million more Americans to the Medicaid rolls. #36 In one of my previous articles, I discussed how it is being projected that the number of Americans on Medicare will grow from 50.7 million in 2012 to 73.2 million in 2025. #37 If you can believe it, Medicare is facing unfunded liabilities of more than 38 trillion dollars over the next 75 years. That comes to approximately $328,404 for each and every household in the United States. #38 In the United States today, more than 61 million Americans receive some form of Social Security benefits. By 2035, that number is projected to soar to a whopping 91 million. #39 Overall, the Social Security system is facing a 134 trillion dollar shortfall over the next 75 years. #40 When Barack Obama first took office, the U.S. national debt was about 10.6 trillion dollars. Now it is about 16.2 trillion dollars. That is an increase of 5.6 trillion dollars in less than 4 years. #41 The federal government has now run a budget deficit of more than a trillion dollars for four years in a row. #42 If right this moment you went out and started spending one dollar every single second, it would take you more than 31,000 years to spend one trillion dollars. #43 If you were alive when Jesus Christ was born and you spent one million dollars every single day since that point, you still would not have spent one trillion dollars by now. #44 Some suggest that "taxing the rich" is the answer. Well, if Bill Gates gave every single penny of his entire fortune to the U.S. government, it would only cover the U.S. budget deficit for 15 days. #45 If the federal government used GAAP accounting standards like publicly traded corporations do, the real federal budget deficit for 2011 would have been 5 trillion dollars instead of 1.3 trillion dollars. #46 The United States already has more government debt per capita than Greece, Portugal, Italy, Ireland or Spain does. #47 At this point, the United States government is responsible for more than a third of all the government debt in the entire world. #48 The amount of U.S. government debt held by foreigners is about 5 times larger than it was just a decade ago. #49 Between 2007 and 2010, U.S. GDP grew by only 4.26%, but the U.S. national debt soared by 61% during that same time period. #50 The U.S. national debt is now more than 37 times larger than it was when Richard Nixon took us off the gold standard. #51 The U.S. national debt is now more than 5000 times larger than it was when the Federal Reserve was first created. #52 The U.S. national debt jumped more on the very first day of fiscal year 2013 than it did from 1776 to 1941 combined. #53 Historically, the interest rate on 10 year U.S. Treasuries has averaged 6.68 percent. If the average interest rate on U.S. government debt rose to that level today, the U.S. government would find itself spending more than a trillion dollars per year just on interest on the national debt. #54 A recently revised IMF policy paper entitled “An Analysis of U.S. Fiscal and Generational Imbalances: Who Will Pay and How?” projects that U.S. government debt will rise to about 400 percent of GDP by the year 2050. #$%$ Boston University economist Laurence Kotlikoff is warning that the U.S. government is facing a gigantic tsunami of unfunded liabilities in the coming years that we are counting on our children and our grandchildren to pay. Kotlikoff speaks of a "fiscal gap" which he defines as "the present value difference between projected future spending and revenue". His calculations have led him to the conclusion that the federal government is facing a fiscal gap of 222 trillion dollars in the years ahead.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1363723895220</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363723908317-134</Id><Topic><Title>Is Obama really fit to be President or even run a Kool-Aide Stand? Now really.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1360329294457</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 08:14:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama was fit to run Acorn Thugs and he failed at that too. Acorn now bankrupt.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363723908317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:11:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363723918359-135</Id><Title>Child rape an important part of W's investigation techniques, what a moral party!!</Title><Msg>GOP Defense Secretary Donald Rumsfeld authorized the rape of children in Iraqi prisons in order to humiliate their parents into providing information GOP County Constable Larry Floyd was arrested for soliciting sex with an 8 year old girl. GOP Judge Mark Pazuhanich fondled a 10 year old girl &amp; was sentenced to 10 years GOP Party leader Bobby Stumbo was arrested for having sex with a 5 year old boy GOP Councilman John Collins pleaded guilty to sexually molesting 13 &amp; 14 year old girls GOP campaign worker Mark Seidensticker is a convicted child molester GOP Mayor Philip Giordano is serving a 37 year sentence in federal prison for sexually abusing 8 &amp; 10 year old girls</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363723918359</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363724053067-136</Id><Title>Only in the tea billie rabbit hole</Title><Msg>is the president that beat you twice the loser, LOL get ready for another DNC president till the tea billies die off</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363724053067</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:14:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363724110048-137</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>vincent.middleton</Username><Timestamp>1362511286358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 14:21:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great one.</Msg><Username>bernice_abbott</Username><Timestamp>1363724110048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363724421562-138</Id><Title>Dems blinked again.</Title><Msg>Dems dropped the proposed assault gun ban from their gun control bill. What happened,loons?? LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363724421562</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:20:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363724442743-139</Id><Title>Funny how those videos were destroyed when the investigation began</Title><Msg>Kids sodomized at Abu Ghraib, Pentagon has the videos - Hersh Complaining about "bureaucratic" hand-wringing in Washington, Rodriguez claims he had the authority to dispose of the tapes. “I wasn’t going to sit around another three years waiting for people to get up the courage,” to do what CIA lawyers said he had the authority to do himself, Rodriguez writes. ( in other words Cheney said do it with no paper trail) Child rape, a GOP delicacy</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363724442743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:20:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363724620351-140</Id><Topic><Title>Secret CSCO Info Revealed</Title><Username>willson_ethan</Username><Timestamp>1363607782953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 07:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good news</Msg><Username>tomallen906</Username><Timestamp>1363724620351</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363724739152-141</Id><Topic><Title>Desperation setting in</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363710207149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at all the topics JuniorIvan is trying in order to get someone..... anyone to talk to him!!LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL EFFING HILARIOUS!!!!! .HEHEEHEEHEEHEEHEEHEHEE</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363724739152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:25:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363724785417-142</Id><Topic><Title>Dems blinked again.</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363724421562</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:20:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what happened was the GOP would have defeated the whole bill, the DNC will have to settle for background checks and magazine restrictions and then use the GOP support for assault guns in the next election, gonna be some good commercials National polling makes quite clear that a majority of people support the assault weapons ban — 57 percent support it in a Washington .. funny how the GOP has managed to gerrymander themselves out of national politics</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363724785417</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:26:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363724843019-143</Id><Topic><Title>Dems blinked again.</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363724421562</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:20:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>funny how the GOP doesn't come out in support of one issue that the majority of Americans support</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363724843019</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:27:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363724886904-144</Id><Topic><Title>Dems blinked again.</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363724421562</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:20:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad I'm shunning JuniorIvan. I'd love to rub it in.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363724886904</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:28:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363725038984-145</Id><Topic><Title>Dems blinked again.</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363724421562</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:20:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's ok carie we understand why you are afraid to engage in constructive dialog, all tea baggers are, you morons live by the motto "Better to be thought of as a fool then to respond and remove all doubt." LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363725038984</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:30:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363725339633-146</Id><Title>Liberals What do Kim Jung Un of North Korea &amp; Barack Obama have in common?</Title><Msg>Liberals What do Kim Jung Un of North Korea &amp; Barack Obama have in common? Be honest. Kim Jung Un had NO military experience whatsoever before Daddy made him a four-star general in the military. This is a snot-nose twerp who has never accomplished anything in his life that would even come close to military leadership: he hasn't even so much as led a Cub Scout troop, coached a sports team or commanded a military platoon. So guess what is next? They make him the "beloved leader" of North Korea . Terrific! Oh, well; I'm sorry. I just remembered that we did the same thing here in the USA . We took an arrogant community organizer who has never worn a uniform and made him Commander-in-Chief; a guy who has never had a real job, worked on a budget or led anything more than an ACORN demonstration, and made him the leader of the USA .</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363725339633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:35:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363725482857-147</Id><Topic><Title>Here is Obama &amp; Pope Joke for you CONSERVATIVES to enjoy!</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363723261304</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:01:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libs have no sense of humor.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363725482857</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:38:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363725520094-148</Id><Topic><Title>It’s hard to think of a president that has been more of an Epic Failure than President Obama</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363721999604</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:39:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jimmy Carter is happy now he is #2.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363725520094</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363725654575-149</Id><Topic><Title>Only in the tea billie rabbit hole</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363724053067</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>doubtful there will ever be a GOP president again, the party won't last another 8 years, they have only won the popular vote once in the last 24 years and the demographics just get worse, after getting destroyed in the next Presidential election a new second party will emerge</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363725654575</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363725713979-150</Id><Topic><Title>Dems blinked again.</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363724421562</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:20:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>isn't it funny how Ivan posts dumb things and dumb.ivan posts smart things, just like in the rabbit hole, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363725713979</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363726638862-151</Id><Title>John Bonehead does a little self reflection, LOL</Title><Msg>“Gee whiz, there’s nobody here,” the Speaker murmured as entered the room, which was more than half empty.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363726638862</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363726858275-152</Id><Topic><Title>Is Obama really fit to be President or even run a Kool-Aide Stand? Now really.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1360329294457</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 08:14:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Ivanthehoe, It's good to see you back. You are a very funny poster</Msg><Username>jen.co44</Username><Timestamp>1363726858275</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363727353617-153</Id><Title>OK, SO WHY DOES OBAMA PLAY THE DEVIL ON THE BIBLE SHOW?</Title><Msg>isn't golf and basketball ghetto enough for him? You would think he would have more important stuff to do. When asked why by Jay Leno he said: " Yeah Jay but I always wanted to play my dad in a show!"</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363727353617</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:09:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363727581465-154</Id><Title>The reason Obama plays THE DEVIL is pretty simple.....</Title><Msg>HE IS!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363727581465</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363727935685-155</Id><Topic><Title>OK, SO WHY DOES OBAMA PLAY THE DEVIL ON THE BIBLE SHOW?</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363727353617</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:09:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he is probably playing himself then. But they say magoo/junior/dumbetc has a cameo in the next episode as Judas Iscariot and Magoo volunteered to bring his own kneepads for the role. Evidently he and some demon-possessed have a bathouse encounter with Pontius Pilate.</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363727935685</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:18:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363727995900-156</Id><Topic><Title>Dems blinked again.</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363724421562</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:20:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The spin here is laughable. Harry Reid dropped the assault gun proposal. The dems still run the senate.Harry couldn't get enough votes from his own people to pass it. A few dem senators were afraid voting for it might cost them their cushy jobs.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363727995900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:19:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363728068730-157</Id><Topic><Title>Dems blinked again.</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363724421562</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:20:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that beeyotch Feinstein didn't put out enough to the old dems to get it through</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363728068730</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:21:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363728478570-158</Id><Title>BOHENER GIVES DUMBIVAN A WOODY</Title><Msg>but then so does about every other dude huh. Dumb may have shyt for brains but you have to give him credit for being the one poster on this board who is usually most "in character" to his id, he is dumber than a bag of rocks.</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363728478570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:27:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363728807373-159</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares?</Title><Username>fredric.sylvester</Username><Timestamp>1363621330780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 11:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report, thanks!</Msg><Username>laneralph817</Username><Timestamp>1363728807373</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:33:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363728945990-160</Id><Topic><Title>BOHENER GIVES DUMBIVAN A WOODY</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363728478570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:27:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harry the wuss has 53 dem senators.But he dropped the assault gun ban. And Dumb blames it on the repubs.LOL Maybe old Harry cant count anymore...or maybe some of his dem buddies were afraid to vote for it.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363728945990</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:35:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363729466413-161</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Party admits Rush and Fox are hurting it From the Republican National Committee's post-mortem: As part of the Growth and Opportu</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363729247170</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:40:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so true, they let the tea billies in and now it is a cancer all sane voters are running from</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363729466413</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:44:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363729542822-162</Id><Title>funny how the tea billies claim victory in the face of defeat, still waiting for Mitt to get sworn in?</Title><Msg>anyone can beat Obama how's that gun control working out for you, the NRA is right you know, this is just the beginning The bargaining chip theory: Liberals have insisted for months — Greg Sargent, we are looking at you – that the ultimate goal of Obama’s push on guns was universal background checks on gun purchases, not the reinstatement of the assault weapons ban. The argument, made by Greg and others, was that Democrats were always going to be willing to bargain away the assault weapons ban since they knew it simply couldn’t pass. But, by pushing as hard for it for as long as they did, Democrats can now go to moderate legislators — not to mention the American people — and argue that broadening background checks is now the compromise position. Ask for the world, then bargain downwards.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363729542822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:45:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363729898172-163</Id><Topic><Title>Dying Iraq Veteran Eviscerates Bush, Cheney</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363729392983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:43:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw a lot of guys die in Vietnam.The ones who had a chance to talk spoke of their loved ones,especially mothers .</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1363729898172</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:51:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363730030379-164</Id><Topic><Title>Dying Iraq Veteran Eviscerates Bush, Cheney</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363729392983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:43:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it is perfectly clear Bush watched "Wag the Dog" and realized a war was his only chance at reelection, even then the ahole couldn't invade the right country, that's what a lifetime of getting beaten up as the skinny, weak stupid kid will do to you, to bad Dad had so much power to put an incompetent in the White House I write this letter, my last letter, to you, Mr. Bush and Mr. Cheney. I write not because I think you grasp the terrible human and moral consequences of your lies, manipulation and thirst for wealth and power. I write this letter because, before my own death, I want to make it clear that I, and hundreds of thousands of my fellow veterans, along with millions of my fellow citizens, along with hundreds of millions more in Iraq and the Middle East, know fully who you are and what you have done. You may evade justice but in our eyes you are each guilty of egregious war crimes, of plunder and, finally, of murder, including the murder of thousands of young Americans—my fellow veterans—whose future you stole. Young goes on to attack the "cowardice" of Bush and Cheney for avoiding military service themselves, and to encourage them to "stand before the American public and the world, and in particular the Iraqi people, and beg for forgiveness."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363730030379</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:53:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363730301407-165</Id><Topic><Title>Dying Iraq Veteran Eviscerates Bush, Cheney</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363729392983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:43:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he lied because he had an Oedipal complex and could never measure up to his father, he killed a million people and destroyed the world economy, just like Hitler, but of course even Hitler didn't torture</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363730301407</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:58:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363730302398-166</Id><Topic><Title>Dying Iraq Veteran Eviscerates Bush, Cheney</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363729392983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:43:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LBJ lied to. It was called the Gulf of Tonkin resolution. It cost 58000 American lives. You and Dumb should read that too.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1363730302398</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363730388659-167</Id><Topic><Title>Dying Iraq Veteran Eviscerates Bush, Cheney</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363729392983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:43:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>another useless war Crank, should have gotten 5 deferments like your hero Cheney, they sure make some good products there now for Walmart, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363730388659</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:59:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363730634903-168</Id><Topic><Title>Dying Iraq Veteran Eviscerates Bush, Cheney</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363729392983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:43:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cheney and Bush estimated the Iraq War would be over in months at a cost of $200 million or so, and that our troops would be greeted as liberators rather than invaders. How does #$%$ Cheney still get interviewed by any national news outfit. The guy has been wrong so many times, you think some outfits would learn from past mistakes.</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1363730634903</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:03:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363730673398-169</Id><Title>THE COWARD LIB DUMB/JUNIOR/SURF NEVER SERVED IN THE MILITARY</Title><Msg>but he sure has a badmouth for us vets who did. He constantly berates the Bushes and just about any real patriot, but hey, cowards are like him do that. Word is that he wears an army surplus uniform around airports hoping people will clap for him, but mostly he just gets beaen up because he doesn't know how to wear it properly.</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363730673398</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:04:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363730776841-170</Id><Topic><Title>Dying Iraq Veteran Eviscerates Bush, Cheney</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363729392983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:43:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kerry got three deferments, Biden's childhood asthma suddenly returned, Clinton went to England,many others avoided the war . Cheney is not my hero .My heroes are a bunch of guys no one ever heard of. Some of them died so you could make jokes about Wal-Mart.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1363730776841</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:06:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363730853916-171</Id><Topic><Title>REMEMBER IN 2008 WHEN OBAMA MADE ALL THE PROMISES BELOW? I DO AND HE LIED.</Title><Username>bachus_i00</Username><Timestamp>1363229697300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 22:54:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>REMEMBER IN 2008 WHEN OBAMA MADE ALL THE PROMISES BELOW? I DO AND HE LIED. Obama not fit to run anything.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363730853916</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:07:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363731057271-172</Id><Topic><Title>THE COWARD LIB DUMB/JUNIOR/SURF NEVER SERVED IN THE MILITARY</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363730673398</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AHHHHHHahahahahahaha! you have to understand, petty people like the jerk of whom you speak have low self-esteem, it makes them feel like "Big boys" if they attack REAL Men! But they will always be real man with balls wannabes! AHHHHHHHHAHAHAHAHAHA!</Msg><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1363731057271</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:10:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363731614807-173</Id><Topic><Title>Living father of Navy SEAL eviscerates the bloodthirsty Mus;lim monkey from Kenya</Title><Username>ivanhoeoflioxly</Username><Timestamp>1363731322188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:15:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AHHHHHHHHHHAHAHAHAHA! GOOD FOR HIM!</Msg><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1363731614807</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:20:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363731744891-174</Id><Topic><Title>Living father of Navy SEAL eviscerates the bloodthirsty Mus;lim monkey from Kenya</Title><Username>ivanhoeoflioxly</Username><Timestamp>1363731322188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:15:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And lets not forget the 6000 Americans murdered by the self serving policies draft dodgers Bush and Cheney and idiots like McCain and Grahm</Msg><Username>jen.co44</Username><Timestamp>1363731744891</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:22:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363732076474-175</Id><Topic><Title>Living father of Navy SEAL eviscerates the bloodthirsty Mus;lim monkey from Kenya</Title><Username>ivanhoeoflioxly</Username><Timestamp>1363731322188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:15:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both father and son Bush served in the military as Pilots "jen" you ignorant #$%$</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1363732076474</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:27:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363732395016-176</Id><Title>SLICK WILLY DODGED THE DRAFT IN ENGLAND AND PROTESTED</Title><Msg>our troops while they were fighting for liberty in SEA Asia. Johnny Kerry also protested with Commie Jane Fonda when he came home and through his medals back. But then at the dem convention he stands up and screams out: 'REPORTING FOR DUTY SIR!" WAY TO GO LURCH YOU HIPPOCRITE! LMAO!!!</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1363732395016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:33:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363732462922-177</Id><Title>Harry needs to retire</Title><Msg>Harry Reid blamed the death of the seven marines killed in Nevada today on the sequester.Now his handlers are trying to clean up after his stupid remark. All politics all the time with Harry.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363732462922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363732522929-178</Id><Topic><Title>Living father of Navy SEAL eviscerates the bloodthirsty Mus;lim monkey from Kenya</Title><Username>ivanhoeoflioxly</Username><Timestamp>1363731322188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:15:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah and where was Georgie stationed? Cheney had four deferments, These are your real warriors. But Cheney is laughing all the way to the bank with his loot.</Msg><Username>jen.co44</Username><Timestamp>1363732522929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:35:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363732799823-179</Id><Topic><Title>SLICK WILLY DODGED THE DRAFT IN ENGLAND AND PROTESTED</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1363732395016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:33:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kerry's medals were undeserved and so they had no value to him. Only medal I received in Nam was my Vietnam service medal and I am proud of it to this day.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1363732799823</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363733196549-180</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO starting to move higher!</Title><Username>lucadobson</Username><Timestamp>1362659226270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 07:27:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good informations</Msg><Username>jerrywhiting</Username><Timestamp>1363733196549</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363733481774-181</Id><Title>While Draftees Bayoneted VC</Title><Msg>Mitt was baynoting French toast and breakfast sausages with Trump, Limbaugh, Gingrich &amp; Cheney.</Msg><Username>cattfish_hunter</Username><Timestamp>1363733481774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:51:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363733577304-182</Id><Title>Seven Male Romney's &amp; Three Generations &amp; Not One Ever Served in The Military</Title><Msg>Amazing!</Msg><Username>cattfish_hunter</Username><Timestamp>1363733577304</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363733749542-183</Id><Title>While Young Soldiers Fixed Bayonets in Iraq &amp; Afghanistan</Title><Msg>Mitt Yells to his sons..."FIX BAYONETS, WE ARE HAVING PRIME RIB FOR BREAKSFAST BOYS!"</Msg><Username>cattfish_hunter</Username><Timestamp>1363733749542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:55:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363734416299-184</Id><Topic><Title>Harry needs to retire</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363732462922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:34:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a sick old man.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1363734416299</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:06:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363735486114-185</Id><Topic><Title>While Young Soldiers Fixed Bayonets in Iraq &amp; Afghanistan</Title><Username>cattfish_hunter</Username><Timestamp>1363733749542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:55:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to Obama the military doesn't have bayonets. Or have you forgotten the debates already?</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1363735486114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:24:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363736000143-186</Id><Topic><Title>While Young Soldiers Fixed Bayonets in Iraq &amp; Afghanistan</Title><Username>cattfish_hunter</Username><Timestamp>1363733749542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:55:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I should have added that bayonets were used more as a tool than a weapon. I never " fixed bayonet " one time in Nam. But I dug a lot of holes and opened cans with it. What branch were you in? Bet I already know.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1363736000143</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363736709221-187</Id><Title>Besides being delusional...</Title><Msg>In how many other ways is junior-dumb-alsmith-deep-magoo screwed up?</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1363736709221</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:45:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363737520935-188</Id><Title>Sarah bumbles again</Title><Msg>Of course, the Constitution can be interpreted in different ways. Could Palin's claim — that the Senate violated the Constitution by not passing a budget resolution — be valid? Not according to Laurence H. Tribe, the Carl M. Loeb university professor and professor of constitutional law at Harvard Law School. Tribe told us via email: "Her interpretation is completely invalid." Louis Fisher, a constitutional scholar who worked for the Library of Congress for four decades as a specialist in separation of powers and constitutional law, told us Palin's claim "seems like a big stretch to me." Fisher noted that "Congress complies with that clause in Article I by appropriating funds each year, even if the Senate does not produce a 'budget.' " He added, as we explained above, that the budget resolution "did not exist until the Budget Act of 1974." Douglas O. Linder, professor of law at the University of Missouri-Kansas City Law School, said, "I think it's kind of a stretch to be honest to say it's a violation of that section. … I think most constitutional scholars and most courts would disagree with her." Linder added that that's "not to say there's absolutely nothing to her argument." There are various interpretations to constitutional matters, after all. Palin also said that "[r]efusing to pass a budget is refusing to declare what [Congress] intends to do with the people's money." But as Fisher said, Congress passes annual appropriations bills. Budget resolutions aren't laws — they're outlines for spending, which is actually set in appropriations bills. As the Washington Postexplained this year, "A budget isn't necessary." The Democratic-controlled Senate Budget Committee argues that the Budget Control Act is indeed the budget for fiscal 2012 and 2013. It says the act "is even more extensive than a traditional budget resolution," because it's the law, can be enforced and requires discretionary caps for 10 years. We'll leave it to our readers to decide whether the Senate should have passed a budget resolution in recent years. But Palin's claim that the legislators violated the Constitution doesn't square with the relatively short history of budget resolutions — and scholars doubt a court would agree with her.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363737520935</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:58:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363737685845-189</Id><Title>FrankinFienstein is a joke</Title><Msg>No assault weapons ban because of 2014 elections. Time for that old bag to go home.</Msg><Username>celltones</Username><Timestamp>1363737685845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:01:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363737821392-190</Id><Topic><Title>DO WE HAVE A PRESIDENT OR DICTATOR?</Title><Username>vensh_1</Username><Timestamp>1363129918942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 19:11:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4 to 1 folks say we have a dictator as President.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363737821392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:03:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363737880224-191</Id><Topic><Title>DO WE HAVE A PRESIDENT OR DICTATOR?</Title><Username>vensh_1</Username><Timestamp>1363129918942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 19:11:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>70-24 folks say stoned a whacko.</Msg><Username>seanesq2001</Username><Timestamp>1363737880224</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363738057080-192</Id><Topic><Title>Dying Iraq Veteran Eviscerates Bush, Cheney</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363729392983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:43:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bet Ambassador Chris Stephens, Sean Smith, Tyrone Woods and Glen Doherty wish they could write Obama one last letter, might go something like this. "How come you put your election over sending us help?"</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1363738057080</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:07:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363738422586-193</Id><Title>Rand thanks for the 11 million votes, DNC</Title><Msg>As I noted this week in National Journal, Hispanics favor more expansive government, not Paul’s pinched libertarian vision of Washington’s responsibilities: But it’s on the question of big government that Hispanics stand most solidly with Democrats. The 2011 Pew Hispanic Center survey asked Latinos whether they would “pay higher taxes to support a larger government or pay lower taxes and have a smaller government”? Hispanics backed higher taxes and more government by 75 percent to 19 percent. For the population as a whole, 48 percent favored smaller government to 41 percent wanting big government. Even Obama’s top political adviser, David Plouffe, echoes the sentiment: “The bigger problem [Republicans have] got with Latinos isn’t immigration,” Plouffe told Time. “It’s their economic policies and health care. The group that supported the president’s health care bill the most—Latinos.” The coup de grace comes when Hispanics are asked to cite their top priority. Only 12 percent said immigration; half chose the economy and jobs—where they stand with Democrats. You can make a strong humanitarian and policy argument for immigration reform and a path to citizenship. But it’s harder to make the political argument. Republicans may not have much choice as noted by the RNC’s venimos en paz report that the party regulars are touting. But the idea that immigration reform is going to make Hispanics flock to the GOP seems dubious — it will take more than cosmetic touches, such as better Hispanic outreach, to really make a difference.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363738422586</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:13:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363738865992-194</Id><Topic><Title>DO WE HAVE A PRESIDENT OR DICTATOR?</Title><Username>vensh_1</Username><Timestamp>1363129918942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 19:11:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DO WE HAVE A PRESIDENT OR DICTATOR? Yes...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1363738865992</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:21:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363738950858-195</Id><Topic><Title>Desperation setting in</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363710207149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Piece of garbage Dumb should quit posting about Hitler and Mao being good guys. Instead go hang out with his OWS and take a poop on somebody's sidewalk.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363738950858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:22:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363738968790-196</Id><Topic><Title>Dying Iraq Veteran Eviscerates Bush, Cheney</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363729392983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:43:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you and 3 folks on FAUX news think this was an issue Cap, LOL the rest of us know it's just another case of tea billie unjustified outrage, you know you should go back and read "The little boy who cried wolf", then you would understand why no one listens to tin foil fruitcakes if everything is an outrage, then there is no outrage</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363738968790</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:22:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363739128952-197</Id><Title>We have an American diktator for president...</Title><Msg>A tin-pot, third-world, diktator who comes closer to Idi Amin than any POTUS before him. He has an agenda to be an historic president yet at the same time he does not govern but instead turns every moment into one long mellifluous campaign. He is a joke and his presidency is the punchline...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1363739128952</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:25:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363739294872-198</Id><Topic><Title>Harry needs to retire</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363732462922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:34:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obozo right hand henchman, what did you expect.</Msg><Username>joespada282</Username><Timestamp>1363739294872</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363739446235-199</Id><Topic><Title>We have an American diktator for president...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1363739128952</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:25:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The little Boy Who Cried Wolf TLBWCW</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363739446235</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:30:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363739478092-200</Id><Title>May be the reason for Junior and Dumb's fascination with Obama?</Title><Msg>David Freddoso noted in his book, "The Case Against Barack Obama", that many of Obama's adult associates were animal-dressers. "Unrepentant domestic terrorist William Ayers - ferrets in fezzes... Black liberation theologist Reverend Jeremiah Wright - white cats in Klan hats... Money-laundering political influence peddler Tony Rezko - badgers in burkas... with friends like these to help him feel 'normal', Obama's oft-disclaimed penchant for putting gerbils in lederhosen seemed a natural outlet for relieving the tension of the campaign trail."</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1363739478092</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:31:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363739628371-201</Id><Topic><Title>May be the reason for Junior and Dumb's fascination with Obama?</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1363739478092</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:31:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb and Junior would like to have a contest on which one gets his tongue farther up Barry's poopchute</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363739628371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363739652102-202</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid using dead marines to posture his agenda</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363739154685</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:25:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>funny 68% of Americans say your wrong, the tea billies are always wrong</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363739652102</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:34:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363740259967-203</Id><Topic><Title>Desperation setting in</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363710207149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we already established Bush killed a million people, started two wars (just like hitler) but hitler didn't torture people, your reading comprehension isn't very good, I think Hitler was horrible, but it's clear Bush is worser thanks for keeping this alive</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363740259967</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363740568032-204</Id><Topic><Title>Desperation setting in</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363710207149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All I see you established,dumb,is what a low life you are. You are really a" puke". And the million deaths is a flat out lie you got from some far left website.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363740568032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:49:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363741091918-205</Id><Title>What now, Mr.President ?</Title><Msg>Obama said the use of chemical weapons in Syria was his "red line". 26 died in a chemical attack today. Wonder what excuse Obama will use now.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363741091918</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:58:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363741490484-206</Id><Title>Saving the nation</Title><Msg>Obama left for Israel a little while ago. My question is can you revoke someones passport while they are out of the country?LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363741490484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363741765249-207</Id><Topic><Title>What now, Mr.President ?</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363741091918</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:58:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gotta love the GOP fire, aim, investigate everything in the rabbit hole is backwards, LOL While a U.S. official said there was no evidence that either Assad forces or the opposition had used chemical weapons in an attack in northern Syria, the chairman of the House Intelligence Committee, Rep. Mike Rogers, a Republican, said there was a "high probability" that the government had used the weapons. Funny how a House Member would have better and faster information then the NSC and the CIA!!!</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363741765249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363741848243-208</Id><Topic><Title>Saving the nation</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363741490484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:04:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>guess you wouldn't know having never left your trailer park wonka</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363741848243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:10:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363741944650-209</Id><Topic><Title>Saving the nation</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363741490484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:04:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Been on five continents and over 40 countries,Dumb.Oooopsie.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363741944650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:12:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363742186446-210</Id><Topic><Title>Seven Male Romney's &amp; Three Generations &amp; Not One Ever Served in The Military</Title><Username>cattfish_hunter</Username><Timestamp>1363733577304</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:52:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cheney is the badest</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363742186446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:16:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363742338063-211</Id><Topic><Title>What now, Mr.President ?</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363741091918</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:58:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny the administration says there is no evidence while Faux news reported it as a fact over 9 hours ago, we should dismantle our 300 billion dollar a year intelligence network and just get everyone a FOX newsfeed</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363742338063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363742338384-212</Id><Title>Definition of a racist:</Title><Msg>Someone who is winning an argument against a liberal.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363742338384</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363742895530-213</Id><Topic><Title>THE COWARD LIB DUMB/JUNIOR/SURF NEVER SERVED IN THE MILITARY</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363730673398</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>offacking course not lol! that demturd is a little chickenshet!</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363742895530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:28:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363743012915-214</Id><Topic><Title>OK, SO WHY DOES OBAMA PLAY THE DEVIL ON THE BIBLE SHOW?</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363727353617</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:09:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL!!!!!</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363743012915</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363743170086-215</Id><Title>WHEN DEMS LIKE JOHN KERRY RAZED VILLAGES, PILLAGED AND</Title><Msg>raped after the fashion of JEN-JUS-KONG! That's as close as it gets to a dem war hero! LMAO!!!!</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363743170086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:32:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363743280853-216</Id><Topic><Title>WHEN DEMS LIKE JOHN KERRY RAZED VILLAGES, PILLAGED AND</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363743170086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:32:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and "Jen-Jus-Kong" is Lurch's FAILED pronunciation of the name, not mine! LOL</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363743280853</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:34:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363743688061-217</Id><Topic><Title>IF ROMNEY-RYAN HAD BEEN ELECTED, WE WOULDN'T BE IN THIS MESS</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1363716347476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Virutally EVERY time gay marriage is put on a ballot it FAILS miserably! American DOES NOT want gay marriage, are you that stupid?</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363743688061</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:41:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363743692482-218</Id><Topic><Title>What now, Mr.President ?</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363741091918</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:58:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny, Oliver North was just on FOX and he said he doubted it was a chemical attack. More likely a trick to get us in the war. Time will tell.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363743692482</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363744049579-219</Id><Topic><Title>Not ALL Republicans are Racists....But...ALL RACISTS ARE REPUBLICANS!!!</Title><Username>floridadave2013</Username><Timestamp>1363743894552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:44:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Louis Farrakhan is a republican? The New Black Panthers are Republicans? Reverend Wright is a republican??</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363744049579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:47:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363744137932-220</Id><Topic><Title>Libdem's bogus Gun Ban shut down big time by American Patriots</Title><Username>ivanhoeoflioxly</Username><Timestamp>1363743925595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:45:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A few dem senators worried about their jobs helped too.lol</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363744137932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363744278516-221</Id><Title>ONLY THREE of the FIFTY STATES Ever Voted to Approve HomoMarriage</Title><Msg>Maine, Maryland, and Washington--that's it, and that was just this past November! All of the rest have voted it down when put on a ballot! But the lying lib pervert media tells us that "America is ready for gay marriage". BULLLLSHYTE! We need more heteromarriage and future taxpayers to support all of the old and aging people to come! Homomarriage and Abortions which are both pillars of the demented dem party only produce perversion and eventual economic collapse. Do the math lib simpletons!</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363744278516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:51:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363744471318-222</Id><Topic><Title>ONLY THREE of the FIFTY STATES Ever Voted to Approve HomoMarriage</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363744278516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:51:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary " evolving "yesterday leaves no doubt she's in for 2016 .The pandering starting early.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363744471318</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:54:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363744578136-223</Id><Topic><Title>ONLY THREE of the FIFTY STATES Ever Voted to Approve HomoMarriage</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363744278516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:51:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>true, she is hoping that people will forget about Benghazi and that she was against homomarriage before she was for it!</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363744578136</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:56:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363744809937-224</Id><Topic><Title>ONLY THREE of the FIFTY STATES Ever Voted to Approve HomoMarriage</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363744278516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:51:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It worked for Barry.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363744809937</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:00:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363744868655-225</Id><Topic><Title>ONLY THREE of the FIFTY STATES Ever Voted to Approve HomoMarriage</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363744278516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:51:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many Maine citizens are also actively trying to overturn it by putting it back on the ballot. As you point out, gay marriage = societal suicide.</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363744868655</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:01:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363745096235-226</Id><Topic><Title>Libdem's bogus Gun Ban shut down big time by American Patriots</Title><Username>ivanhoeoflioxly</Username><Timestamp>1363743925595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:45:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it also didn't hurt that an ugly beeyotch like Diane Frankenstein was behind the bill! LOL</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363745096235</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363745221627-227</Id><Topic><Title>Not ALL Republicans are Racists....But...ALL RACISTS ARE REPUBLICANS!!!</Title><Username>floridadave2013</Username><Timestamp>1363743894552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:44:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The real ones have money , the others are disillusioned and lost in hate !</Msg><Username>settegast_scholar</Username><Timestamp>1363745221627</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:07:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363745557763-228</Id><Topic><Title>DO WE HAVE A PRESIDENT OR DICTATOR?</Title><Username>vensh_1</Username><Timestamp>1363129918942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 19:11:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>W the decider was your #$%$, now 10 yrs. Later they cry iraq was a mistake , well it was so obvious ,but the majority was hoodwinked by rumsfeld and shotgun cheney , all which should be in the hague.</Msg><Username>settegast_scholar</Username><Timestamp>1363745557763</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363746493335-229</Id><Title>MY WISH IS THAT ALL DEMS WILL SOON BE GAY AND MARRIED!</Title><Msg>Because then it will only be a generation or so and theyh will self-destruct! YEAH BABY</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1363746493335</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:28:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363746654776-230</Id><Title>csco</Title><Msg>when does csco go x div.</Msg><Username>ace45644</Username><Timestamp>1363746654776</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:30:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363748195601-231</Id><Title>COWARDS OBAMA, BILL CLINTONGUE, CHUCK SHUMER = DRAFTDODGERS WHO NEVER SERVED IN THE MILITARY</Title><Msg>Cowards obama, bill clintongue, chuck shumer = draftdodgers who never served in the military</Msg><Username>panty_clad_hippo</Username><Timestamp>1363748195601</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363748767563-232</Id><Topic><Title>WHEN DEMS LIKE JOHN KERRY RAZED VILLAGES, PILLAGED AND</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363743170086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:32:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The American people were not deceived when John Kerry sailed into Boston Harbor in his wife's yacht fancying himself as a swiftboat admiral, giving the phony salute on tv and hollering "john kerry reporting for duty". Kerry was handilly defeated in the election.</Msg><Username>panty_clad_hippo</Username><Timestamp>1363748767563</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 23:06:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>