<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-11"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368245013543-1</Id><Title>Nice weekly close for CSCO.</Title><Msg>May 15th earnings report.</Msg><Username>pinkpanther_traders</Username><Timestamp>1368245013543</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 00:03:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368246272324-2</Id><Title>The BIGGEST CORRUPT COVER-UP IN AMERICAN HISTORY will</Title><Msg>… bring the monkey down. And then back up on a rope.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1368246272324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 00:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368251328518-3</Id><Title>if you wanna make 600k a year!!! heres how</Title><Msg>most common reason why people lose money trading is cuz they dont know how to trade properly. if you wanna make good an sold gain trades check out explosive alerts (google them) can go wrong with there picks!</Msg><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368251328518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 01:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>21</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368253310499-4</Id><Topic><Title>if you wanna make 600k a year!!! heres how</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368251328518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 01:48:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Become a congressman/woman or White house and trade on insider information?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1368253310499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 02:21:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368269516239-5</Id><Topic><Title>When Hillary finally tells the truth</Title><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1368242857304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>May 10, 2013 Vegas: Rove Attack Ads Seal Victory for Hillary Posted by Andy Borowitz LAS VEGAS (The Borowitz Report)—News that Karl Rove’s PAC, American Crossroads, has bought ads attacking Hillary Clinton has sent the Democrat’s stock soaring in Las Vegas, where oddsmakers now say she is virtually guaranteed to be the next President of the United States. “People were bullish on Hillary before this,” said Tracy Klugian, a leading Las Vegas oddsmaker for over forty years. “But the Rove thing makes it a lock.” After American Crossroads’s historic string of defeats in 2012, “Serious gamblers wait to see who Rove is supporting and then bet the house on the other side.” The oddsmaker’s only concern, he added, was that Rove’s involvement in the race will dry up all interest in betting on Republican candidates for 2016: “Right now I’m offering Marco Rubio at ninety thousand to one and I ain’t getting a bite.” While acknowledging that “there’s no sure thing” in the world of gambling, Mr. Klugian said that for professional gamblers, betting against Karl Rove is “as good as it gets.” “He’s the LeBron James of losing,” he said.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1368269516239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 06:51:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368270040376-6</Id><Topic><Title>When Hillary finally tells the truth</Title><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1368242857304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it will be a lie. LOSER!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368270040376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 07:00:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368270118899-7</Id><Topic><Title>The BIGGEST CORRUPT COVER-UP IN AMERICAN HISTORY will</Title><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1368246272324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 00:24:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bring the monkey down. HUGE LOSER!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368270118899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 07:01:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368270798801-8</Id><Title>Good news for teenage girls</Title><Msg>OBAMA ADMINISTRATION'S NEFARIOUS PLAN TO IMPREGNATE OUR COUNTRY'S TEENAGERS THWARTED BY JUDGE - Laura Bassett: "A federal judge on Friday denied the Obama administration's request to delay his order that the Plan B morning-after pill be made available over the counter without age limits. The judge sharply rebuked the administration for appealing his decision, calling the move politically motivated, 'frivolous,' and 'something out of an alternate reality.' The court battle over the morning-after pill began in December 2011, when Secretary of Health and Human Services Kathleen Sebelius overruled the Food and Drug Administration's recommendation that the pill be made available over-the-counter to all ages. Sebelius said that girls under the age of 17 should continue to only have access to the pill with a doctor's prescription. U.S. District Court Judge Edward Korman decided in April that Sebelius' decision was based on politics, rather than medical evidence. He ordered the Food and Drug Administration to lift all age limits on Plan B emergency contraception and sell it on pharmacy shelves next to the condoms." This judge is pretty awesome.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1368270798801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 07:13:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368274515706-9</Id><Topic><Title>The BIGGEST CORRUPT COVER-UP IN AMERICAN HISTORY will</Title><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1368246272324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 00:24:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Consider Benny Gazzi is the first time republicans pretend like they give a shyte about government employees, two veterans, and a gay democrat. consider that both SEAL vets would have had their benefits cut, the civillians would be furloughed, and ambassador Stevens would only be considered 3/5ths of a person under the GOP. Vegas giving good odds of Hillary to become #45, check it out!</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1368274515706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 08:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368277984074-10</Id><Title>This week in "Crazy": Tex Gov. gives History lesson....</Title><Msg>Rick Perry Texas governor Rick Perry dipped into his deep knowledge of American history on Sunday when he compared discriminating against gays to abolishing slavery. Perry made the tortured analogy during an appearance on the Family Research Council hate group’s “Stand With Scouts Sunday” webcast. “For pop culture to try to come in and tear [the Boy Scouts' history] up, and it just happens to be the flavor of the month, so to speak, and tear apart one of the great organizations that served millions of men, to help them become great men and great fathers, that isn’t appropriate” Perry said. Pointing to a portrait of Sam Houston, Perry continued, “[Houston] was against slavery, and he stood up, and very passionately said ‘Texas does not need to leave the Union.’” “That’s the type of principled leadership, that’s the type of courage,” that people need to show on the issue of segregating the Boy Scouts, Perry concluded. In reality, although Houston did oppose secession and the extension of slavery, he was also a slaveowner who opposed abolition. And Perry, of course, isn’t exactly a credible source on questions of secession. Ultimately, the lesson here is that — if this somehow wasn’t already clear — you probably shouldn’t take a history lesson from the “oops” guy.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1368277984074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 09:13:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368278057729-11</Id><Title>One can easily tell the Pukes have NOTHING to</Title><Msg>offer America for the foreseeable future by their actions regarding the Bengazi "scandal".They are SO scared of Hilliary kicking their azzes in 2016,and she WILL if she opts to run. GOP ready to push Benghazi case into 2014, beyond May 11, 3:33 AM (ET) By CHARLES BABINGTON WASHINGTON (AP) - Steady drips of information about a horrific night in Libya are fueling Republican arguments and ads designed to fire up the conservative base and undercut the Democrats' early favorite for president in 2016. Democratic and Republican strategists sharply disagree on the issue's power to influence elections next year and beyond. But after eight months of trying, Democrats are still struggling to move past last September's terrorist attack on the U.S. diplomatic compound in Benghazi, which killed ambassador Chris Stevens and three other Americans. Democrats insist that an independent inquiry, the dismissal of several State Department officials, and nine congressional hearings leave little new to say on the matter. But Friday turned up the sort of nuggets that feed conservative activists' belief that a major scandal may still be at hand. Newly revealed communications show that senior State Department officials pressed for changes in the talking points that U.N. Ambassador Susan Rice used a few days after the Benghazi attacks. These senior officials expressed concerns that Congress might criticize the Obama administration for ignoring warnings of a growing threat in Libya. The White House has insisted that it made only stylistic changes to the intelligence agency talking points, in which Rice suggested that spontaneous protests over an anti-Islamic video set off the deadly attack. The new details suggest a greater degree of political sensitivity and involvement by the White House and State Department.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368278057729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 09:14:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368278768710-12</Id><Topic><Title>The BIGGEST CORRUPT COVER-UP IN AMERICAN HISTORY will</Title><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1368246272324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 00:24:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your commie Kenyan was running guns to his Al Qaeda brothers in Syria and Stevens found out about it and your anti-American Mvslim had to silence him. The evil PieceOS faked the OBL charade and had to also murder 22 Navy SEALS in the Chinook helicopter to silence them forever because they knew the truth and it distracted the investigation into his fake 9 layer birth certificate. He is pure e v i l but there again, that's why you worship and glorify the Mvslim mutt you dumb CC.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1368278768710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 09:26:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368278952693-13</Id><Topic><Title>The BIGGEST CORRUPT COVER-UP IN AMERICAN HISTORY will</Title><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1368246272324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 00:24:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is pure e v i l but there again, that's why you worship and glorify the Mvslim mutt you dumb CC You are certainly a very silly child Zippy.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368278952693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 09:29:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368283321804-14</Id><Topic><Title>One can easily tell the Pukes have NOTHING to</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368278057729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 09:14:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Machiavellian president with his corrupt administration. Know one will survive.</Msg><Username>generic_erick</Username><Timestamp>1368283321804</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 10:42:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368288872651-15</Id><Topic><Title>4 PIT BULLS KILL WOMAN JOGGER. JOGGERS SHOULD BE ALLOWED TO JOG WITH GUNS</Title><Username>raymooondo</Username><Timestamp>1368238473206</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:14:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People bred those dogs. Do it to the owners, not the dogs.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368288872651</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 12:14:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368288950652-16</Id><Topic><Title>Dems politicized Benghazi WAY before the GOP decided to investigate...</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1368203557889</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:32:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumpity-Bump...</Msg><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1368288950652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 12:15:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368289019332-17</Id><Topic><Title>One can easily tell the Pukes have NOTHING to</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368278057729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 09:14:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound angry as usual. And frankly, somewhat desperate. In other words, you are a good representation of the Democrap party right now...</Msg><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1368289019332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 12:16:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368291412473-18</Id><Topic><Title>One can easily tell the Pukes have NOTHING to</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368278057729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 09:14:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, alqaedasmith, it has nothing to do with your evil Mvslim Messiah and Hillary murdering 4 AMERICANS. All you're concerned with is political power and all the free stuff you can get. You anti-American Mvslim garbage are blud thirsty skum.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1368291412473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 12:56:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368292184500-19</Id><Title>buy, hold or sell before the earning?</Title><Msg>opinions?</Msg><Username>thinkpadfan2001</Username><Timestamp>1368292184500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 13:09:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368296050395-20</Id><Topic><Title>buy, hold or sell before the earning?</Title><Username>thinkpadfan2001</Username><Timestamp>1368292184500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 13:09:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm very long and holding. Cisco is way undervalued and I think that it will continue to creep up. I do hope for the penny beat and good revenues and solid (but conservative) forecast. I think this is one of the best deals around.</Msg><Username>wcurr99</Username><Timestamp>1368296050395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 14:14:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368298250120-21</Id><Title>REPUKES SENDING MOTHER DAY POSTCARDS TO THEIR SISTERS...</Title><Msg>"happy mother's day mom"</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1368298250120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 14:50:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368302588940-22</Id><Topic><Title>buy, hold or sell before the earning?</Title><Username>thinkpadfan2001</Username><Timestamp>1368292184500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 13:09:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. Buy some, sell some, and then hold some. Otherwise, you might have to plan a wedding. Trade it, don't marry it.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1368302588940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:03:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368302819784-23</Id><Topic><Title>4 PIT BULLS KILL WOMAN JOGGER. JOGGERS SHOULD BE ALLOWED TO JOG WITH GUNS</Title><Username>raymooondo</Username><Timestamp>1368238473206</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:14:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I say do it to both the owners and the frankenstein killer monstrosity dogs that they created.</Msg><Username>george_wallace_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1368302819784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:06:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368302831252-24</Id><Topic><Title>REPUKES SENDING MOTHER DAY POSTCARDS TO THEIR SISTERS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1368298250120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 14:50:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yo momma should send me a get well soon card after what the doctor said the old hag gave me.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1368302831252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:07:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368303084166-25</Id><Title>IF EVERYONE WALKED AROUND WITH A LOADED AK47, USA WOULD BE ALOT SAFER</Title><Msg>IF EVERYONE WALKED AROUND WITH A LOADED AK47, USA WOULD BE ALOT SAFER because if some demoncrat occupier decided to shoot everyone would shoot back at him and he would be dead and save the taxpayers a trial costs.</Msg><Username>george_wallace_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1368303084166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:11:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368303267639-26</Id><Title>OBAMA HAS SECRET MEETING WITH ABC,CBS,NBC,MSNBC,CNN,AP to COLLABORATE ON COVERING UP BENGAZI NEGLIGENCE</Title><Msg>Obama has secret meeting with abc,cbs,nbc,msnbc,cnn,ap to collaborate on covering up bengazi negligence</Msg><Username>janet_reno_is_an_ugly_bitch</Username><Timestamp>1368303267639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368303501102-27</Id><Topic><Title>WHY DIDN'T OBAMA EVACUATE BENGAZI STAFF?? BRITAIN AND THE RED CROSS EVACUATED THEIR BENGAZI STAFF???</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_poverty</Username><Timestamp>1368237342663</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:55:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody from Obama owned news media (CBS,ABC,NBC,MSNBC,CNN,PBS ect) will ask Obama why he refused to evacuate USA Bengazi Embassy workers when Britain and the Red Cross evacuated their workers to safety.. If a Republican were president all of the Demoncrap party owned news media would be asking this question 24/7 everyday of the year nonstop.</Msg><Username>janet_reno_is_an_ugly_bitch</Username><Timestamp>1368303501102</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:18:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368303575868-28</Id><Topic><Title>RED CROSS EVACUATED BENGAZI WORKERS, OBAMA LEFT USA EMBASSY STAFF TO BE SLAUGHTERED.</Title><Username>the_galloping_goose</Username><Timestamp>1368237040033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:50:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I dont believe it had anything to do with his election chances. Romney was an inept weak and stupid candidate. I believe he enjoyed watching it.</Msg><Username>janet_reno_is_an_ugly_bitch</Username><Timestamp>1368303575868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:19:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368303748693-29</Id><Topic><Title>BRITAIN EVACUATED THEIR BENGAZI EMBASSY STAFF, OBAMA LET USA BENGAZI STAFF BE SLAUGHTERED</Title><Username>the_galloping_goose</Username><Timestamp>1368236980780</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:49:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I disagree. I believe Obama still would let the USA Embassy workers be killed because Obama ignorned his terorist watchlist and gave the boston marathon terorists welfare and citizenship despite the fact that they were on the terorist watchlist and despite the fact that Russia warned obama twice about these moslem radical killers.</Msg><Username>janet_reno_is_an_ugly_bitch</Username><Timestamp>1368303748693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:22:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368303783725-30</Id><Topic><Title>Good news for teenage girls</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1368270798801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 07:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, Judges are funny. When they say civil rights begin before birth in the third trimester, they pretty much mean that the President doesn't have the authority to preempt a 13 year old's civil rights.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1368303783725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:23:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368303841714-31</Id><Topic><Title>RED CROSS EVACUATED BENGAZI WORKERS, OBAMA LEFT USA EMBASSY STAFF TO BE SLAUGHTERED.</Title><Username>the_galloping_goose</Username><Timestamp>1368237040033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:50:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reelection had nothing to do with obama administrations chronic and habitual negligence.</Msg><Username>janet_reno_is_an_ugly_bitch</Username><Timestamp>1368303841714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:24:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368303933333-32</Id><Topic><Title>HILLARY AND SUSAN RICE GIVEN AWARDS FOR LETTING USA BENGAZI STAFF BE SLAUGHTERED LIKE PIGS</Title><Username>sean_penn_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1368237192585</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both Hitlery and Susan Rice are ugly old skkkkkanks.</Msg><Username>janet_reno_is_an_ugly_bitch</Username><Timestamp>1368303933333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:25:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368303974186-33</Id><Topic><Title>HILLARY AND SUSAN RICE GIVEN AWARDS FOR LETTING USA BENGAZI STAFF BE SLAUGHTERED LIKE PIGS</Title><Username>sean_penn_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1368237192585</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both Hitlery and Susan Rice are ugly sea hags.</Msg><Username>janet_reno_is_an_ugly_bitch</Username><Timestamp>1368303974186</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368304366440-34</Id><Title>70 YEAR OLD BEATS UP 24 YEAR OLD BLACK HOME INVADER, DEMONCRATS WANT HOME OWNER THROWN IN PRISON</Title><Msg>70 YEAR OLD BEATS UP 24 YEAR OLD BLACK HOME INVADER, DEMONCRATS WANT HOME OWNER THROWN IN PRISON for defending his family from an armed black 24 year old who wore a travon martin hoodie.</Msg><Username>soccer_and_dodgeball_mom</Username><Timestamp>1368304366440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:32:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368305007750-35</Id><Topic><Title>Good news for teenage girls</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1368270798801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 07:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OBAMA ADMINISTRATION'S NEFARIOUS PLAN TO IMPREGNATE OUR COUNTRY'S TEENAGERS THWARTED BY JUDGE - Laura Bassett: "A federal judge on Friday denied the Obama administration's request to delay his order that the Plan B morning-after pill be made available over the counter without age limits</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1368305007750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:43:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368305159348-36</Id><Title>CALIFORNIA RELEASING VIOLENT FELONS FROM PRISON DUE TO COSTS, WHY NOT HAVE GLADIATOR MATCHES TO PAY FOR COSTS???</Title><Msg>CALIFORNIA RELEASING VIOLENT FELONS FROM PRISON DUE TO COSTS, WHY NOT HAVE GLADIATOR MATCHES TO PAY FOR COSTS??? This way dangerous felons are not released to kill innocent people and the prison population shrinks everytime a felon gladiator is killed by another felon gladiator and if the gladiator matches are broadcast on HBO, SHOWTIME ect it will generate billions in new funding for prisons.</Msg><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1368305159348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:45:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368305256908-37</Id><Title>CALIFORNIA RELEASING VIOLENT FELONS FROM PRISON DUE TO COSTS, WHY NOT HAVE GLADIATOR MATCHES TO PAY FOR COSTS???</Title><Msg>CALIFORNIA RELEASING VIOLENT FELONS FROM PRISON DUE TO COSTS, WHY NOT HAVE GLADIATOR MATCHES TO PAY FOR COSTS??? If these dogfight matches are broadcast on pay per view it could generate billions of dollars for animal shelters.</Msg><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1368305256908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368305412047-38</Id><Title>ANIMAL SHELTERS COMPLAIN ABOUT FUNDING SHORTFALLS, WHAT NOT HAVE DOG FIGHT MATCHES</Title><Msg>ANIMAL SHELTERS COMPLAIN ABOUT FUNDING SHORTFALLS, WHAT NOT HAVE DOG FIGHT MATCHES that people pay to attend and that people can pay for on pay per view?? This would generate billions for animal shelters.and once a dog is defeated it is killed so the animal shelter population also decreases.</Msg><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1368305412047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:50:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368308065018-39</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner Goes Democrat, Admits 'We Can't Cut Our Way to Prosperity</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_7</Username><Timestamp>1368305336811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:48:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's just acknowledging that Obama has screwed us so bad with his TRILLions in spending that we are so far in debt, cuts won't do it anymore. In fact he's been saying all along that the problem is not just too many entitlements and pork but mainly it's the spendaholic Democrats who have no self control.</Msg><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1368308065018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:34:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368308847862-40</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner Goes Democrat, Admits 'We Can't Cut Our Way to Prosperity</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_7</Username><Timestamp>1368305336811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:48:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now THAT'S funny, LOLMAO @ U Jr ...</Msg><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1368308847862</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:47:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368315724504-41</Id><Topic><Title>buy, hold or sell before the earning?</Title><Username>thinkpadfan2001</Username><Timestamp>1368292184500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 13:09:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With a P/E just over 10, a dividend yield of 3.2%, there is little downside risk. With the overall market trading at a P/E of 15, it is only a matter of time before people start rotating out of the stocks with P/E's of 17-20, and into CSCO.</Msg><Username>garyg474</Username><Timestamp>1368315724504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 19:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368316971769-42</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner Goes Democrat, Admits 'We Can't Cut Our Way to Prosperity</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_7</Username><Timestamp>1368305336811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:48:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if I were you, I would do some reading, start at Columbus Discovered America and don't stop. You've missed a lot.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368316971769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 20:02:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368318597382-43</Id><Topic><Title>70 YEAR OLD BEATS UP 24 YEAR OLD BLACK HOME INVADER, DEMONCRATS WANT HOME OWNER THROWN IN PRISON</Title><Username>soccer_and_dodgeball_mom</Username><Timestamp>1368304366440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:32:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All Democrats should bend over, to be beaten by this old man! What fun, FOR EVERYONE! We know Democrats enjoy being beaten.....</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1368318597382</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 20:29:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368318724859-44</Id><Title>GAY MAFIA ATTACKS BOY SCOUTS.....why?</Title><Msg>because Gay is pathologic. They are miserable, and cannot be even slightly happy until they make you miserable!!! It's crystal clear. No one in the world demands to be a part of their Gay Pride Parades, eh?</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1368318724859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 20:32:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368319020135-45</Id><Topic><Title>CALIFORNIA RELEASING VIOLENT FELONS FROM PRISON DUE TO COSTS, WHY NOT HAVE GLADIATOR MATCHES TO PAY FOR COSTS???</Title><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1368305256908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wonderful idea! by having gladitorial contests in Calipornia, using violent felons and paying the living survivor of the knife, spear, machete battles , 100,000 dollars, and selling these violent contests on pay per view, the Calipornia prison system could better protect the non-criminals in Calipornia!! You sir, are a genius!!! Beautiful idea.....and brilliant too.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1368319020135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 20:37:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368320937766-46</Id><Topic><Title>buy, hold or sell before the earning?</Title><Username>thinkpadfan2001</Username><Timestamp>1368292184500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 13:09:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, investing in CSCO is much better than investing in some stocks like HD that has P/E ratio more than 17.</Msg><Username>dell_stk</Username><Timestamp>1368320937766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 21:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368322870330-47</Id><Topic><Title>GAY MAFIA ATTACKS BOY SCOUTS.....why?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1368318724859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 20:32:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Diversity is repressive tolerance: forced acceptance, social order, and social control. The far left progressives idea of Social Utopia.</Msg><Username>generic_erick</Username><Timestamp>1368322870330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 21:41:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368323502325-48</Id><Topic><Title>Good news for teenage girls</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1368270798801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 07:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's the problem! Just do what life long democrat and Obama supporter Ariel Castro did when he impregnated his three teenage victims- starve them for two weeks and hit them repeatedly in the stomach until they miscarried.</Msg><Username>generic_erick</Username><Timestamp>1368323502325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 21:51:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368323694564-49</Id><Topic><Title>HILLARY AND SUSAN RICE GIVEN AWARDS FOR LETTING USA BENGAZI STAFF BE SLAUGHTERED LIKE PIGS</Title><Username>sean_penn_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1368237192585</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OBAMA DENIED, PEOPLE DIED</Msg><Username>generic_erick</Username><Timestamp>1368323694564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 21:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368328648641-50</Id><Topic><Title>Good news for teenage girls</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1368270798801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 07:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If liberals didn't have double standards, they wouldn't have any. The "Plan B" is a pill which works prior to conception. The judge decided that it should be available to any person who wanted to avoid a pregnancy, including young girls. Obama tried to preempt the civil rights of girls under 17. It's pretty self-explanatory.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1368328648641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 23:17:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368328813068-51</Id><Topic><Title>GAY MAFIA ATTACKS BOY SCOUTS.....why?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1368318724859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 20:32:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tolerance doesn't extend to such things as Christmas displays or other religious observances. Those are unacceptable forms of free expression. You will conform.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1368328813068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 23:20:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368329952459-52</Id><Topic><Title>Dems politicized Benghazi WAY before the GOP decided to investigate...</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1368203557889</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:32:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumperrific!!</Msg><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1368329952459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 23:39:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368331033160-53</Id><Topic><Title>Dems politicized Benghazi WAY before the GOP decided to investigate...</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1368203557889</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:32:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumps in the road.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1368331033160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 23:57:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>