<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-10-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381647169113-1</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO UPGRADED YOU MUST SEE THIS - OMG!</Title><Username>piersonoagnecco</Username><Timestamp>1380891776558</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-04 09:02:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey dead I see you made up another id for me to put on ignore, pretty desperate to have me read your posts aren't you, LOL LOOOOOOOOOOOSER</Msg><Username>glennispwtodisco</Username><Timestamp>1381647169113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 02:52:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381653831536-2</Id><Topic><Title>Everyone loves CSCO</Title><Username>bigtraderjoe</Username><Timestamp>1381521267387</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-11 15:54:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wish i could trade like that</Msg><Username>wenteralex</Username><Timestamp>1381653831536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 04:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381663208706-3</Id><Topic><Title>Kwame Kilpatrick That Campaigned For Obama Sentenced To 28 Years</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381558123205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-12 02:08:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya, I realize that, but "Drill Here, Drill Now" is obsessed with picking winners and losers, ask President Romney!</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381663208706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 07:20:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381664116127-4</Id><Title>What are these jerks thinking?</Title><Msg>JOHN KASICH DEFIES PARTY, EMBRACES MEDICAID EXPANSION - Well his next primary just got a lot more interesting. Jeff Young: "Ohio Gov. John Kasich (R) will circumvent the majority-Republican legislature in his state to advance an expansion of Medicaid benefits to 275,000 people under President Barack Obama's health care reform law, according to a report published Friday in the Columbus Dispatch. Kasich, who has been campaigning across Ohio and lobbying lawmakers since February to accept federal money to provide Medicaid to more poor residents, will present a proposal to the state funding board that could fast-track the expansion,the Columbus Dispatch reported. The GOP-led legislature has blocked Kasich's proposal to date...Kasich is one of 10 Republican governors who have broken with their party to support the Medicaid expansion, although they all maintain they continue to oppose the underlying Obamacare law. Most recently, Pennsylvania Gov. Tom Corbett (R) unveiled a plan that would partially privatize and expand Medicaid, following similar laws enacted by Iowa Gov. Terry Branstad (R) and Arkansas Gov. Mike Beebe (D) and the GOP-led legislatures in their states. Florida Gov. Rick Scott (R) also endorsed the Medicaid expansion, only to see it blocked by his state legislature."</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381664116127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 07:35:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381664954944-5</Id><Title>"Internal polls show Romney beating Obama".....</Title><Msg>Delusion is a funny thing. With less than a week left in the New Jersey senate race, Republican Steve Lonegan is 12 points behind Cory Booker but that didn’t stop Lonegan from saying the following. “When I win, Obama will fold. [...] My victory in this election on Wednesday will send a message to Barack Obama, Harry Reid and Nancy Pelosi that the American people want an end to Obamacare and the rest of the President’s radical agenda,” said Lonegan. “Republicans need to hold firm because seven days from today when Bob Menendez escorts me down the Senate aisle for my swearing in, the message about what our party should do will be clear for all.” The relevant thing to note here is that Lonegan got ‘Barack Obama’, ‘Harry Reid’, ‘Nancy Pelosi’, ‘Obamacare’ and ‘radical agenda’ all into the same sentence. This is important because when addressing right-wing loons, there is no need to bring up real ideas on how to solve the big problems. A little trash talk on how you’ll take down Obamacare by your mere presence in the Senate and a mention of Obama, Reid and Pelosi as dangerous individuals out to destroy your beloved country and you’ve made your little Fox-bots content and secure. Poll numbers indicating that Lonegan will be crushed next Wednesday by Booker can be conveniently ignored…as can every other fact that messes with a winger’s narrative. Very much like Republicans who believed that their internal polls showed Romney defeating Obama last November, Lonegan has his own internal poll numbers that have him edging out Booker. And once that happens, well hey, the dynamics on the shutdown and Obamacare will shift dramatically. President Obama and Reid will no doubt relent, get down on their knees and repeal the Affordable Care Act rather than have to deal with the mighty and invincible Steve Lonegan in the Senate. And that’s how it’s going down next Wednesday…if not in everyone’s mind, at least in Steve Lonegan’s.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381664954944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 07:49:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381672265015-6</Id><Title>We need to stop the ACA woopsie I mean medicare.</Title><Msg>(CNN) -- If we allow this awful measure to stand, predicted the conservative spokesman, "behind it will come other federal programs that will invade every area of freedom as we have known it in this country until one day...we will wake to find that we have socialism [and] we are going to spend our sunset years telling our children and our children's children what it once was like in America when men were free." This could be a tea party representative warning about the perils of Obamacare and willing to keep the government closed until it is delayed or repealed. But it was Ronald Reagan speaking back in 1961. And the program he viewed as the driving wedge of socialism was Medicare.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381672265015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 09:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381676451184-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Carney</Title><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381619663424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-12 19:14:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sittin in a tree, K, I, S, S, I, N, G, first comes luv, then comes gay marriage, then comes Michelle with a wookie carriage.</Msg><Username>byrdwasaproudkkkmember</Username><Timestamp>1381676451184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 11:00:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381678415410-8</Id><Title>from around the web, party before country</Title><Msg>My wife and I are currently lifelong registered republicans in FL, and have contributed generously to it and its candidates over the years. We own a small business employing 5.5 plus ourselves.. We currently pay their health insurance @ 100%, . The FL GOP has done everything they can to stop Obamacare and would not set up an exchange, in addition when it appeared it was the law, they decided to go with the Fed option. However, in a brazen move, the FL legislature passed a bill a few months back to disallow the State Insurance commissioner from negotiating or regulating any health rates. He is required to do this for every other insurance product sold in the state, the GOP went out of their way to try and make the citizens of FL pay more for Obamacare, so it will look like an expensive mistake, they could care less about us, the voters, and probably costing us $billions. In addition to that, the GOP Guv Scott now has forbid any health navigators from using State office building and property and tried to ban them from using any public buildings. He apparently did not realize that health navigators have been around for years and have been used by the public to guide seniors with Medicare. Now you have this mess in DC, led by the Tea Party. Last night, we found the county website to fill out a change in our voters registration, you fill it our on line, print, sign and mail. We changed to "no party" affiliation. Our changes to being an "I" are now in the mail. I wonder if it would help solve the many messes, the worst about to happen, if 50% of American voters were Independent?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381678415410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 11:33:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381683041099-9</Id><Title>Just amazes me, that we allow</Title><Msg>Obama and Hillary to get away without answering for the deaths of Christopher Stevens, Sean Smith Glen Doherty and Tyrone S. Woods! If they had been our family members, we might look a little closer for the truth!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381683041099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 12:50:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381683228503-10</Id><Title>What the hell is IRS</Title><Msg>doing sending personal information to the white house? What's up with that, plan to send us Christmas cards?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381683228503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 12:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381688953331-11</Id><Topic><Title>Just amazes me, that we allow</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381683041099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 12:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It also amazes me how the main stream media ignores this? Makes you wonder!</Msg><Username>douglasrobidoux</Username><Timestamp>1381688953331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 14:29:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381689796473-12</Id><Topic><Title>What the hell is IRS</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381683228503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 12:53:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>O'Lucifer is no American even if he was born in this country, which he was not, he is a Kenyan spy spying on America and Americans and that's why the commie liberal anti-American losers on the left love and worship him because it doesn't affect them since they're not "Americans." . Beware the Kenyan spy, for it is e fill, liberal, and it lives to lie.</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381689796473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 14:43:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381689992752-13</Id><Topic><Title>Just amazes me, that we allow</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381683041099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 12:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The main stream leftist Soros controlled media doesn't' care who or how many Americans the nnuslim murders, that's why they're helping him with all of his cover-ups, because like him, they're e fill anti-American blud thirsty Marxists too.</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381689992752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 14:46:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381690779797-14</Id><Topic><Title>UNION WORKERS (FORMER D AND F STUDENTS IN HIGH SCHOOL) PRODUCE INFERIOR PRODUCTS</Title><Username>lvl2gay</Username><Timestamp>1381547265733</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-11 23:07:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I use to be a supervisor at a steel mill and had the misfortune of having to supervise union 'workers' and your comments are a perfect description of union 'workers'. They are the laziest, dumbest and greediest slackers on earth. These lazy bums did as little work as possible and did the most incompetent poor quality work.and what gets me is I caught them smoking pot and couldn't fire them. I promptly found another job (in computer programming) and it wasn't long after that the steel mill shutdown and all those worthless union workers were unemployed. I make alot more money than those union bums will ever make and will always be employed because I'm among the best in my field</Msg><Username>b0ss_hawg</Username><Timestamp>1381690779797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 14:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381690874795-15</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRATS BLOCK BUS FROM DEPORTING ILLEGALS CONVICTED OF CRIMES</Title><Username>soul_train_dancers</Username><Timestamp>1381620179080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-12 19:22:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats like Hillary wanted to give felons in prison the right to vote because democrats want crime to pay.</Msg><Username>b0ss_hawg</Username><Timestamp>1381690874795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:01:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381690930433-16</Id><Topic><Title>STUDY SHOWS THAT TOKEN AFFIRMATIVE ACTION BLACK GUYS HAVE INFERIOR JOB PERFORMANCE</Title><Username>harry_reid_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1381544841984</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-11 22:27:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree the comments made is true.</Msg><Username>b0ss_hawg</Username><Timestamp>1381690930433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:02:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381690976177-17</Id><Topic><Title>TOO MANY INFERIOR UNQUALIFIED INNER CITY CRIMINALS BEING HIRED BECAUSE OF AFFIRMATIVE ACTION</Title><Username>the_galloping_goose</Username><Timestamp>1381532002587</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-11 18:53:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sad but true</Msg><Username>b0ss_hawg</Username><Timestamp>1381690976177</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381691111978-18</Id><Topic><Title>UGLY OBESE OGRES LIKE MANCHELLE OBAMBA SHOULDN'T BE SELF PROCLAIMED EXPERT ON SLIMNESS AND BEAUTY.</Title><Username>son_of_sam_was_a_democrat</Username><Timestamp>1381546683444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-11 22:58:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Couldn't agree more. Manchelle is one ugly beast.</Msg><Username>b0ss_hawg</Username><Timestamp>1381691111978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:05:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381691226107-19</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ADMINISTRATION TRIES TO SHUTDOWN THE OCEAN DUE TO GOVT SHUTDOWN</Title><Username>susan_rice_is_an_ugly_ol_hag</Username><Timestamp>1381001306815</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-05 15:28:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It just shows that Obama is a mean petty and malicious bully who likes to destroy peoples lives.</Msg><Username>b0ss_hawg</Username><Timestamp>1381691226107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:07:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381691389144-20</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat polls poll democrats, why would any clear-thinking American believe them?</Title><Username>husseinsdeathpanel</Username><Timestamp>1381678813409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 11:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The polls were sponsored by the Wall Street Journal, which leans to the right &amp; is high-information GOP. That's why the polls are to be believed. Anarchy is a ' bridge-too-far' for the business community.</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1381691389144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:09:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381691538554-21</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ARMING LOW IQ PARK RANGERS WITH MACHINE GUNS TO HARASS/BULLY 80 YEAR OLDS AND TOURISTS</Title><Username>janet_reno_is_an_ugly_bitch</Username><Timestamp>1381465049809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-11 00:17:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously Obama is a cowardly bully who likes to send his armed brownshirt park rangers to harass and bully 80-90 year old WW2 Veterans in wheel chairs and walkers who are paying their respects to their fallen comrades from WW2. What kind of lowlife turd would bully a 90 year old man in a wheel chair???</Msg><Username>b0ss_hawg</Username><Timestamp>1381691538554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381692108517-22</Id><Title>REPUBLICANS WANT TO CUT SPENDING...HOW ABOUT ALL THE FOREIGN AID WE GIVE TO OTHER</Title><Msg>Countries...to the tune of like 50+ BILLION last year.</Msg><Username>futureperson</Username><Timestamp>1381692108517</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381692112886-23</Id><Title>CROWD AND WORLD WAR 2 VETERANS STORM WW2 MEMORIAL DEFEATING OBAMAS PARK RANGER BROWNSHIRTS</Title><Msg>Crowd and world war 2 veterans storm ww2 memorial defeating obamas park ranger brownshirts. read full story at wtop news (103.5 fm).</Msg><Username>twirling_dancer_giggles</Username><Timestamp>1381692112886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:21:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381692408788-24</Id><Topic><Title>REPUBLICANS WANT TO CUT SPENDING...HOW ABOUT ALL THE FOREIGN AID WE GIVE TO OTHER</Title><Username>futureperson</Username><Timestamp>1381692108517</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:21:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree. Why is USA borrowing money to give to Egypt , Greece, haiti and other loser countries when USA cant even pay its own bills???</Msg><Username>raymooondo</Username><Timestamp>1381692408788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:26:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381692923775-25</Id><Topic><Title>CROWD AND WORLD WAR 2 VETERANS STORM WW2 MEMORIAL DEFEATING OBAMAS PARK RANGER BROWNSHIRTS</Title><Username>twirling_dancer_giggles</Username><Timestamp>1381692112886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:21:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good! Fuhk the commie obama and his storm troopers</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1381692923775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:35:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381693209084-26</Id><Title>More on nnuslim monkey returns alleged 2,700 year old ancient artifact to his Iranian brothers</Title><Msg>Turns out the more on brain dead nnuslim monkey skrewed his nnuslim brothers over big time because the "ancient artifact" was a FAKE like the Kenyan and it was made IN,… wait for it,…………………. 1999!!! . What a stupid piece of siht the monkey is. . Just when you thought the boooger eating coke nosed commie Kenyan nnuslim monkey couldn't' get any stupider, he does it in his typical brain dead blud thirsty fashion.</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381693209084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:40:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381693339897-27</Id><Title>COWARDLY HUSSEIN OBAMMY TO ROB SOC. SEC. RECIPIENTS!</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (AP) — For the second straight year, millions of Social Security recipients, disabled veterans and federal retirees can expect historically small increases in their benefits come January. Preliminary figures suggest a benefit increase of roughly 1.5 percent, which would be among the smallest since automatic increases were adopted in 1975, according to an analysis by The Associated Press. Next year's raise will be small because consumer prices, as measured by the government, haven't gone up much in the past year. The exact size of the cost-of-living adjustment, or COLA, won't be known until the Labor Department releases the inflation report for September. That was supposed to happen Wednesday, but the report was delayed indefinitely because of the partial government shutdown. SO if you voted for him you screwed yourselves old dems!</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1381693339897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:42:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381693715452-28</Id><Title>U.S. Veteran Patriots storm the white house and mall area tearing down his barricades!!!</Title><Msg>The Military HATES the e fill nnuslim from Kenya and they're calling for his IMPEACHMENT in D.C. at this very moment. . America strikes back against Dark Invader's anti-American E-Fill Empire!! . God bless America and to hel with Hussein!!!!</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381693715452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:48:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381693838283-29</Id><Topic><Title>COWARDLY HUSSEIN OBAMMY TO ROB SOC. SEC. RECIPIENTS!</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1381693339897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:42:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if only I could take back my vote from Obama, I would gladly cut off my own arm from voting for him if his election could be Undone!</Msg><Username>alsmith58l</Username><Timestamp>1381693838283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:50:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381693903326-30</Id><Topic><Title>COWARDLY HUSSEIN OBAMMY TO ROB SOC. SEC. RECIPIENTS!</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1381693339897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:42:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah Obama controls the tea party, LOL there really is no reality left in teabillistan Republicans seem intent on alienating the last group of voters that is hanging with them: old white people. First consider Rep. Paul Ryan's (R-WI) adding Medicare to their shutdown and debt ceiling ransom note. Then add to that the demand of 50 House Republicans in a letter written by Rep. Reid Ribble (R-WI) that House Speaker John Boehner include slashing Social Security in the hostage taking. They seem to think that making Social Security cuts will allay the fears that they are creating by flirting with default. "Fixing [their word] Social Security," Ribble writes on behalf of the 50, "would send a strong message to financial markets that we are willing to responsibly address our nation's long-term fiscal issues." Yes, that will distract the financial markets from impending doom. Here are some of their demands for Social Security benefit cuts: Cutting Social Security benefits with a chained CPI cost-of-living formula; Raising the Social Security retirement age; and Means-testing Social Security benefits. [...] Ribble spells out exactly how the upcoming “fiscal deadlines” can be used to get these Social Security proposals through Congress. First, you increase the debt ceiling for six weeks, then in the intervening six weeks you attach Social Security legislation to a longer-term increase in the debt ceiling.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381693903326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381694855465-31</Id><Title>In the 1960 and 70's race riots</Title><Msg>at least the blacks burned their own business's and homes, Obama burning the country because he cannot get his way!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381694855465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 16:07:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381694895825-32</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ARMING LOW IQ PARK RANGERS WITH MACHINE GUNS TO HARASS/BULLY 80 YEAR OLDS AND TOURISTS</Title><Username>janet_reno_is_an_ugly_bitch</Username><Timestamp>1381465049809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-11 00:17:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would O'Bama do that? Especially since he's busy ARMING the Mexican Drug Cartel with HIS ILLEGAL FAST AND FURIOUS GUNS.</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381694895825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 16:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381694954381-33</Id><Topic><Title>In the 1960 and 70's race riots</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381694855465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 16:07:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If he gets HIS way,… America will cease to exist.</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381694954381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 16:09:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381695783255-34</Id><Topic><Title>TOO MANY INFERIOR UNQUALIFIED INNER CITY CRIMINALS BEING HIRED BECAUSE OF AFFIRMATIVE ACTION</Title><Username>the_galloping_goose</Username><Timestamp>1381532002587</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-11 18:53:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The nnuslim monkey couldn't have gotten past the 3rd grade without affirmative action. . It helped him every e fill step of his brain dead way into the white house. . Affirmative action produces negative results. Just look at the death and destruction the commie Kenyan has wrought upon America and the world.</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381695783255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 16:23:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381696056311-35</Id><Title>country getting tired of crazy, looks like the DNC will take back the house</Title><Msg>Just 28 percent of Americans have a favorable impression of the Republican Party, down 10 percentage points from last month, according to a Gallup poll. The polling firm called it a "record low," noting that "this is the lowest favorable rating measured for either party since Gallup began asking this question in 1992."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381696056311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 16:27:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381696407078-36</Id><Topic><Title>COWARDLY HUSSEIN OBAMMY TO ROB SOC. SEC. RECIPIENTS!</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1381693339897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:42:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"yeah Obama controls the tea party" Uhhh only in your qwear wetdreams dumbo! LMAO!!!!</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1381696407078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 16:33:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381698431661-37</Id><Title>I support the GOP position to eliminate social security, LOL</Title><Msg>But the Republicans won't let the 70-plus percent opposition to cuts in Medicare and Social Security dissuade them. They've come up with a new plan that sugarcoats their attempts to eviscerate Social Security and Medicare. It's called a "mandatory global spending cap" and it's nothing more than the House Republican budget in disguise. The Republicans like this plan because, when you ask everyday voters if they support a "mandatory global spending cap" they think it sounds pretty good. What better way to force the government to "live within its means"? But support turns into solid opposition the moment people understand that the "mandatory global spending cap" would require mandatory cuts in Medicare and Social Security. In fact, this proposal isn't a way to make the government "live within its means" -- it's really a way to cut Medicare and Social Security in order to give more tax breaks to millionaires. It's a way to reduce the "means" that normal people live on, and hand them over to the Donald Trumps and Paris Hiltons of the world.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381698431661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 17:07:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381698808629-38</Id><Topic><Title>COWARDLY HUSSEIN OBAMMY TO ROB SOC. SEC. RECIPIENTS!</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1381693339897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:42:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did you finally decide to become an American Patriot and not a Democrat?</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381698808629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 17:13:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381699387037-39</Id><Topic><Title>In the 1960 and 70's race riots</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381694855465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 16:07:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(you hicks need to understand the constitution) We Do, Obama does not -- he has shredded and using the strips to kindle the fire that is burning America, you raciest Pecker-wood!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381699387037</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 17:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381701130151-40</Id><Title>southern tea billies, world class stupid</Title><Msg>A large number of Louisiana Republicans think President Barack Obama is to blame for the federal government's poor response to Hurricane Katrina, according to a new Public Policy Polling survey released Wednesday -- despite the fact that the storm occurred three years before he took office. The Democratic-leaning polling firm, which provided its results to Talking Points Memo, found that 29 percent of Louisiana Republicans said Obama was responsible for the Katrina response.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381701130151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 17:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381701642472-41</Id><Topic><Title>A surprisingly high percentage of Americans</Title><Username>juniorsclassmateoriginal</Username><Timestamp>1381700630837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 17:43:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As long as none of them are so diabolically dim wittedlly brain dead stupid they say, corpse man,… then they're okay. . O'Kenyan thinks that the sun revolves around 57 States.</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381701642472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 18:00:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381702520990-42</Id><Title>bat #$%$ crazy</Title><Msg>1. Michele Bachmann: 'Obama is part of Al Qaeda and end times are near.' To the extent that she is capable of rational decision-making, Minn. Rep. Michele Bachmann decided this week might be a fitting time to remind the public that she is batshit crazy. During a radio interview, she spun out her theory that, A) President Obama is arming terrorists, generally, and Al Qaeda, specifically. And B) This is cause for rejoicing because it is a sign that the end times are near.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381702520990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 18:15:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381702906420-43</Id><Topic><Title>southern tea billies, world class stupid</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381701130151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 17:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is the kind of #$%$ one finds in the newspapers on April's fool. Unreal.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381702906420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 18:21:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381703178796-44</Id><Topic><Title>bat #$%$ crazy</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381702520990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 18:15:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That chick is not even aware she is married to a gay guy. So little chance she is aware of anything else.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381703178796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 18:26:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381703315194-45</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Veteran Patriots storm the white house and mall area tearing down his barricades!!!</Title><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381693715452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:48:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My, myyyy so that is what a teabilly sounds like without his daily meth.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381703315194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 18:28:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381703812537-46</Id><Topic><Title>bat #$%$ crazy</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381702520990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 18:15:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wait I think he prayed away his gay and got paid by the Guberment to do it</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381703812537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 18:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381705474481-47</Id><Topic><Title>In the 1960 and 70's race riots</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381694855465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 16:07:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>capt .best part of him ended up on the ground after the neighbors dog was done....with his mom</Msg><Username>gelinasalan</Username><Timestamp>1381705474481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 19:04:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381705958597-48</Id><Title>VIOLENT BLACK DEMOCRAT AND OBAMA VOTER AARON ALEXIS, 34, GOES ON SHOOTING RAMPAGE IN DC NAVY YARD LEAVES 13 DEAD</Title><Msg>VIOLENT BLACK DEMOCRAT AND OBAMA VOTER AARON ALEXIS, 34, GOES ON SHOOTING RAMPAGE IN DC NAVY YARD LEAVES 13 DEAD. Democrats silent on the gun violence by one of their own and call it a case of industrial unrest.</Msg><Username>white_power_democrats</Username><Timestamp>1381705958597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 19:12:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381707058988-49</Id><Title>BLACKS COMMIT 99.5% OF ALL VIOLENT GUN CRIMES EVEN BLACK COPS LIKE CHRIS DORNER WENT ON GUN KILLING SPREE</Title><Msg>Black democrats commit 99.5% of all violent gun crimes even black cops like chris dorner went on gun killing spree</Msg><Username>manchelle_is_sasquatch</Username><Timestamp>1381707058988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 19:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381707783081-50</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA DC COPS GUN DOWN UNARMED FEMALE BLACK OBAMA VOTER WITH TODDLER IN HER CAR</Title><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1380892626439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-04 09:17:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama administration and black obama voters are responsible for 99.5% of all the gun violence in the USA. Time for Congress to ban the Obama administration from having any guns. These trigger happy Obama DC cops opened fire in the middle of a busy street full of people without any concern for the infant in the car, the unarmed mother or any bystanders</Msg><Username>kwanza_beauty_queen</Username><Timestamp>1381707783081</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 19:43:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381709451576-51</Id><Title>O'Commie Care, law of the land?</Title><Msg>If it was, the nnuslim would not have been able to unconstitutionally and unilaterally change at will over a dozen or so times just because HE thinks he's Emperor. . And here you thought it was the law of the land. . But only if you're a kool-aid drinking dyed in the wool brain dead commie Kenyan worshiping anti-American mow Ron.</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381709451576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 20:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381709811914-52</Id><Title>TOM BRADY THE GREATEST PRESSURE QB OF ALL TIME !!!</Title><Msg>What a beast !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381709811914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 20:16:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381709812674-53</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA DC COPS GUN DOWN UNARMED FEMALE BLACK OBAMA VOTER WITH TODDLER IN HER CAR</Title><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1380892626439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-04 09:17:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it would have been the Kenyan's ugly spawn in the car or Miriam Carey that could have had their life's saved,… in the e fill words of heartless Harry Reid,… "Why would we want to do that?"</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381709812674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 20:16:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381710213142-54</Id><Topic><Title>bat #$%$ crazy</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381702520990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 18:15:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And she's on the House Intelligence Committee. Lord help us all...</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1381710213142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 20:23:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381710518268-55</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Veteran Patriots storm the white house and mall area tearing down his barricades!!!</Title><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381693715452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:48:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are just eatin' out of their hand Hoe, you poor old fool. There would be no barricade to wrap in a flag if it weren't for puke Cruz and his insurgent gang. They may not be destroying America, but they ARE destroying what's left of the GOP. So sad....</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1381710518268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 20:28:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381711617982-56</Id><Topic><Title>bat #$%$ crazy</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381702520990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 18:15:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You voted fpr Obama, and she is the crazy person. Oh, yeah Cisco is still a boatload of doodoo.</Msg><Username>dphorstick</Username><Timestamp>1381711617982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 20:46:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381711721832-57</Id><Topic><Title>bat #$%$ crazy</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381702520990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 18:15:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Three facts but no insight. Thanks I guess.</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1381711721832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 20:48:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381714138428-58</Id><Title>What is Dumb doing</Title><Msg>My lover makes fun of people posting on the weekend but he's been here all day!!I I'm going to bite my sweeties testicles next time we have sex.On second thought,he likes that. Maybe I wont go off in his mouth.That'll hurt him!!!!!</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmateoriquinal</Username><Timestamp>1381714138428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 21:28:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381714853191-59</Id><Topic><Title>What is Dumb doing</Title><Username>juniorsclassmateoriquinal</Username><Timestamp>1381714138428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 21:28:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol dead so desperate to have me read his post he has to make up a new id every time I put him on ignore, LOL LOOOOSER member since 10 minutes ago LOL ignore</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381714853191</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 21:40:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381715630981-60</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ACCUSED SEXUAL HARRASSMENT WHEN AT HARVARD</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1375371759696</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-01 11:42:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumpity-Boop...</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381715630981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 21:53:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381715762865-61</Id><Title>WOW, look at those Obama Futures...</Title><Msg>Deep, deep lobster red...</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381715762865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 21:56:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381716361266-62</Id><Topic><Title>What is Dumb doing</Title><Username>juniorsclassmateoriquinal</Username><Timestamp>1381714138428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 21:28:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Darling, why are you being so grumpy tonight ?? It was just hours ago we gazed into each others eyes and vowed our undying love while vigorously stroking each others weener.</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmateoriqinal</Username><Timestamp>1381716361266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 22:06:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381716744965-63</Id><Topic><Title>What is Dumb doing</Title><Username>juniorsclassmateoriquinal</Username><Timestamp>1381714138428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 21:28:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL gonna make up a new id every time I put your new one on ignore LOOOOOOOSER?, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381716744965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 22:12:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381718000212-64</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ACCUSED SEXUAL HARRASSMENT WHEN AT HARVARD</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1375371759696</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-01 11:42:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ok, but Obama's mom was assraped by a tribe of angry lesbians, that's how he was conceived</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1381718000212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 22:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381718172272-65</Id><Title>Affirmative Action is racist and promotes racism where there isn't any</Title><Msg>Sharpton, JJ and O'Lucifer are all anti-American racists and use their hatred of whites to promote their upcoming race wars.</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381718172272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 22:36:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381718344967-66</Id><Title>1000S OF VETERANS PUSH OBAMA'S EFFEMINATE, GAYBARRIERS</Title><Msg>AWAY FROM WW2 MEMORIAL AND penetrate his perimeter DEEPLY Sunday afternoon, making him look like the little sissy he is. Soon after this weaksissyBarry was seen flying away in Marine1, crying and scared like a wittle baby! LMAO!!! You go gurl!!!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1381718344967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 22:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381718655953-67</Id><Title>DA REVOLUTION COME!</Title><Msg>we chased the mutt out of town today when we penetrated and discarded his stupid barriers around the WW2 memorial. To quote Clint Eastwood in El Camino: "Have you ever met someone that you wished you hadn't fuhked with? Well we are that guy Omuslim!!" LMAO!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1381718655953</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 22:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381718807728-68</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Veteran Patriots storm the white house and mall area tearing down his barricades!!!</Title><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381693715452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:48:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah and Oby flew away in Marine1 to keep from getting tar and feathered!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1381718807728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 22:46:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381719109312-69</Id><Title>Wow Palin and Cruz manage to round up</Title><Msg>a hundred protesters, LOL (which is a million in teabilliestan) The federal government shutdown has lasted nearly two weeks, but the Washington blame game is still open for business. Hundreds of demonstrators pushed past barricades at the sealed-off World War II Memorial Sunday as part of a "Million Vet March" to protest the closing of war memorials, a demonstration that extended to the White House. (funny Palin and Cruz together could only get 100 people to join them, wonder what they paid them.) On top of the million trucker protest that got 6 truckers, WOW I'm sure the 3 million unpaid federal workers votes will be dwarfed by those 106 votes, that's the way math works in the upside down tea billie land</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381719109312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 22:51:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381719323243-70</Id><Topic><Title>1000S OF VETERANS PUSH OBAMA'S EFFEMINATE, GAYBARRIERS</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1381718344967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 22:39:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weird how Jaysa only speaks in latently homoerotic runons...</Msg><Username>asdfv99</Username><Timestamp>1381719323243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 22:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381719444703-71</Id><Title>TED CRUZ: "OBAMA NEEDS TO STOP HOLDING AMERICAN VETERANS HOSTAGE"</Title><Msg>by barricading their memorlals that they have EARNED A RIGHT to visit! We will visit them whenever we damnwell please you stupid little pig!</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1381719444703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 22:57:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381719451267-72</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Veteran Patriots storm the white house and mall area tearing down his barricades!!!</Title><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381693715452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 15:48:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's too good for the e fill anti-American Marxist piece of nnuslim siht. . The military hates the nnuslim monkey for his crimes against them and America. . Just like all American Patriots do.</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381719451267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 22:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381719464286-73</Id><Topic><Title>WOW, look at those Obama Futures...</Title><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381715762865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 21:56:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You better sell off and invest in Glenn Beck seeds and Goldline LOL</Msg><Username>asdfv99</Username><Timestamp>1381719464286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 22:57:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381719867070-74</Id><Topic><Title>TED CRUZ: "OBAMA NEEDS TO STOP HOLDING AMERICAN VETERANS HOSTAGE"</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1381719444703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 22:57:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're gat tam right we will. . The illegal little pig alien Kenyan thinks he can stop Americans. . Being a nnuslim from Africa the stupid little pig Kenyan has no idea what Americans are capable of when he attacks them.</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381719867070</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 23:04:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381720000878-75</Id><Topic><Title>WOW, look at those Obama Futures...</Title><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381715762865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 21:56:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tea billies don't have investments, and wall street money and the Chamber of Commerce money is fleeing the GOP, we are witnessing the complete utter destruction of a political party, gonna be funny watching the tea billies try and get elected with all the rich people donating money to throw them out. LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381720000878</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 23:06:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381721288812-76</Id><Title>BIG PAPI ROCKS THE HOUSE !!!</Title><Msg>GRAND SLAM BOTTOM OF THE 8th</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381721288812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-13 23:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>