<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-12"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368333108058-1</Id><Title>THANK GOD</Title><Msg>…. the whistle blower American Patriots DID NOT STAND DOWN!!!!!!! They weren't going to obey the evil Mvslim monkey's order because they're COURAGEOUS AMERICANS and they know he's an anti-American Kenyan spy WHO MURDERED THEIR AMERICAN FRIENDS. God bless those Patriots for speaking the truth,… the TRUTH,... something the anti-American commie liberals HATE.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1368333108058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 00:31:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368352424768-2</Id><Topic><Title>IF EVERYONE WALKED AROUND WITH A LOADED AK47, USA WOULD BE ALOT SAFER</Title><Username>george_wallace_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1368303084166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:11:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But how does that help with the low information BLACK and HISPANIC voter problem ???</Msg><Username>black911operator</Username><Timestamp>1368352424768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 05:53:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368352587425-3</Id><Title>BLACKS AND HISPANICS</Title><Msg>Have a lot to be proud don't they ??? And then there's HerThighNess, I've come to far to tired... Don't help the BLACK person at work, and don't do any business with HISPANICS</Msg><Username>black911operator</Username><Timestamp>1368352587425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 05:56:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368352730454-4</Id><Topic><Title>WHY DIDN'T OBAMA EVACUATE BENGAZI STAFF?? BRITAIN AND THE RED CROSS EVACUATED THEIR BENGAZI STAFF???</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_poverty</Username><Timestamp>1368237342663</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:55:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why haven't they used the low level embassy personal ???</Msg><Username>black911operator</Username><Timestamp>1368352730454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 05:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368352843478-5</Id><Topic><Title>HILLARY AND SUSAN RICE GIVEN AWARDS FOR LETTING USA BENGAZI STAFF BE SLAUGHTERED LIKE PIGS</Title><Username>sean_penn_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1368237192585</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hands down for the next two Nobel Peace prizes</Msg><Username>black911operator</Username><Timestamp>1368352843478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 06:00:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368359640014-6</Id><Title>Earnings will be the key for short term</Title><Msg>The stock has done well with nearly 27% growth on a 52 week basis. It is up nearly 40% from the 52 week low of ~$15 made in July. Despite this, the P/E is reasonable at around 12 and the forward P/E is 10 indicating moderate expectations on the growth front by the market. Even the price to sales and price to book is around 2.35 and 2 respectively which is reasonable if the profit margin of 20% is factored. In the last quarter the revenue growth was 5% and the the net income increased marginally (excluding 926 million tax settlement). With $46 billion cash and $16 billion debt, the company looks reasonably placed on the liquidity front. The future growth is dependent on the turnaround in economies of the world as sales are dependent on the increase in spending by the government and the private sector. Though there have been some signs of recovery, the confidence is not strong enough to indicate a reversal of the gloom. It recently got a favorable ruling in the patent infringement lawsuit against VirnetX Holdings and that is also a small positive. These lawsuits have been on the rise and patent monetizing has become a business model now. Companies have even changed their businesses to take advantage of the growth in the IP business. Spherix IP (SPEX), known for drug research in diabetes and atherosclerosis, recently became a full service IP company and purchased several telecom patents. For Cisco, the growth in revenues &amp; net margins is better than IBM &amp; Intel when compared with 2011. Overall, it still looks good for the long term, provided the economy performs. Of course, this is true for almost all the stocks. The earnings and the guidance on May 15 will be the key trigger for the stock performance in the near term.</Msg><Username>investora2z</Username><Timestamp>1368359640014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 07:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368360982680-7</Id><Topic><Title>BLACKS AND HISPANICS</Title><Username>black911operator</Username><Timestamp>1368352587425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 05:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>' "Don't help the BLACK person at work, and don't do any business with HISPANICS" USA self suicide! LoL!.</Msg><Username>bvioml123</Username><Timestamp>1368360982680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 08:16:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368362931651-8</Id><Topic><Title>inbred: 'Don't help the BLACK person at work, and don't do any business with HISPANICS '</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_7</Username><Timestamp>1368361918828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 08:31:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Black911operator' s post was disgusting, but you refer to white people as crackers. You are just as dumb and racist as he is. Should we call all liberals racists because you are ??</Msg><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1368362931651</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 08:48:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368364163896-9</Id><Topic><Title>inbred: 'Don't help the BLACK person at work, and don't do any business with HISPANICS '</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_7</Username><Timestamp>1368361918828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 08:31:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do have my facts straight. You are a black racist, don't like white people and refer to them as crackers.</Msg><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1368364163896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 09:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368365241253-10</Id><Title>EVER NOTICE: Sundays are the Republicans Favorite Days to Post Hate..</Title><Msg>.........right behind Christmas and Easter....... It brings out the Christian in them.</Msg><Username>exordium_terminus</Username><Timestamp>1368365241253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 09:27:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368366229034-11</Id><Topic><Title>EVER NOTICE: Sundays are the Republicans Favorite Days to Post Hate..</Title><Username>exordium_terminus</Username><Timestamp>1368365241253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 09:27:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>May 11, 2013 Fox: New Evidence Hillary Killed Lincoln Posted by Andy Borowitz WASHINGTON (The Borowitz Report)—In what may be the most serious allegation ever made against the former Secretary of State, Fox News Channel reported today that Hillary Clinton was involved in the conspiracy to murder President Abraham Lincoln. The latest charge against Mrs. Clinton was reported by Fox host Sean Hannity, who said that the evidence of her role in the Lincoln assassination came mainly in the form of e-mails. According to Mr. Hannity, “If it’s true that Hillary Clinton killed Lincoln, this could have a major impact on her chances in 2016.” The accusation against Mrs. Clinton drew a strong response from Sen. Lindsey Graham (R.—S. Carolina): “There’s been a concerted effort by Hillary Clinton to cover up her role in President Lincoln’s murder. She has said nothing about it. This is bigger than Watergate, the Cuban missile crisis, and the Second World War put together.” Responding to the allegation, Mrs. Clinton issued a terse statement indicating that she could not have participated in Lincoln’s assassination because she was born in 1947. “That’s what she wants us to believe,” Sen. Graham said.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1368366229034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 09:43:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368369260492-12</Id><Topic><Title>inbred: 'Don't help the BLACK person at work, and don't do any business with HISPANICS '</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_7</Username><Timestamp>1368361918828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 08:31:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blacks are the majority of racists in America now. Whitey is the new minority to suppress. Byproduct of Affirmative Action - a program started by, you guessed it - Democrats. Lib racists like junior are a symptom of what America has become...</Msg><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1368369260492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:34:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368369428774-13</Id><Topic><Title>EVER NOTICE: Sundays are the Republicans Favorite Days to Post Hate..</Title><Username>exordium_terminus</Username><Timestamp>1368365241253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 09:27:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do you reprobates dig up this #$%$ anyway? Or do you just pull it out of your rectums...</Msg><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1368369428774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:37:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368373719144-14</Id><Topic><Title>WHY DIDN'T OBAMA EVACUATE BENGAZI STAFF?? BRITAIN AND THE RED CROSS EVACUATED THEIR BENGAZI STAFF???</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_poverty</Username><Timestamp>1368237342663</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:55:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By David Edwards As The Daily Dolt noted on Thursday, terrorists attacked U.S. embassies 12 times while President George W. Bush was in office. At least eight of those attacks occurred while Rumsfeld was serving as secretary of Defense. Including the attacks on Tuesday, U.S. embassies have come under attack twice since Obama took office. Number of dead: 60 Number of outraged epublicans: 0</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1368373719144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 11:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368374135695-15</Id><Topic><Title>EVER NOTICE: Sundays are the Republicans Favorite Days to Post Hate..</Title><Username>exordium_terminus</Username><Timestamp>1368365241253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 09:27:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They live on this site 365 day a year so in the hell would they even know which day of the week it even is? Bunch of really old pathetic lonely wheezers living on social security with only enough money to purchase a quart of cheap wine and month to month internet service.</Msg><Username>hitof1y60</Username><Timestamp>1368374135695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 11:55:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368374790270-16</Id><Title>Ain't it Funny How...</Title><Msg>If there's a scandal involving a Republican, he's fair game but when it's Democrats the Lib-Dems cry foul and say Republicans are just 'playing politics'? Benghazi won't go away because now it is SO obvious that Hillary and Obama were obfuscating to protect Bammy's reelection. The truth, like freezing water underground must eventually come to the surface...</Msg><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1368374790270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 12:06:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368376261528-17</Id><Topic><Title>Ain't it Funny How...</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1368374790270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 12:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>13 attacks occurred while Busch Lite vacationed on his dude ranch for 720 days: January 22, 2002. Calcutta, India. Gunmen associated with Harkat-ul-Jihad al-Islami attack the U.S. Consulate. Five people are killed. June 14, 2002. Karachi, Pakistan. Suicide bomber connected with al Qaeda attacks the U.S. Consulate, killing 12 and injuring 51. October 12, 2002. Denpasar, Indonesia. U.S. diplomatic offices bombed as part of a string of "Bali Bombings." No fatalities. February 28, 2003. Islamabad, Pakistan. Several gunmen fire upon the U.S. Embassy. Two people are killed. May 12, 2003. Riyadh, Saudi Arabia. Armed al Qaeda terrorists storm the diplomatic compound, killing 36 people including nine Americans. The assailants committed suicide by detonating a truck bomb. July 30, 2004. Tashkent, Uzbekistan. A suicide bomber from the Islamic Movement of Uzbekistan attacks the U.S. Embassy, killing two people. December 6, 2004. Jeddah, Saudi Arabia. Al Qaeda terrorists storm the U.S. Consulate and occupy the perimeter wall. Nine people are killed. March 2, 2006. Karachi, Pakistan again. Suicide bomber attacks the U.S. Consulate killing four people, including U.S. diplomat David Foy who was directly targeted by the attackers. (I wonder if Lindsey Graham or Fox News would even recognize the name "David Foy." This is the third Karachi terrorist attack in four years on what's considered American soil.) September 12, 2006. Damascus, Syria. Four armed gunmen shouting "Allahu akbar" storm the U.S. Embassy using grenades, automatic weapons, a car bomb and a truck bomb. Four people are killed, 13 are wounded. January 12, 2007. Athens, Greece. Members of a Greek terrorist group called the Revolutionary Struggle fire a rocket-propelled grenade at the U.S. Embassy. No fatalities. March 18, 2008. Sana'a, Yemen. Members of the al-Qaeda-linked Islamic Jihad of Yemen fire a mortar at the U.S. Embassy. The shot misses the embassy, but hits nearby school killing two. July 9,</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1368376261528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 12:31:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368377994406-18</Id><Topic><Title>WHY DIDN'T OBAMA EVACUATE BENGAZI STAFF?? BRITAIN AND THE RED CROSS EVACUATED THEIR BENGAZI STAFF???</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_poverty</Username><Timestamp>1368237342663</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:55:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He missed the 3 AM phone call. Michelle was snoring.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1368377994406</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 12:59:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368378111020-19</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings will be the key for short term</Title><Username>investora2z</Username><Timestamp>1368359640014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 07:54:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yah sure. WSJ published end of QE notice just after the market closed on Friday, May 10th. Typical for this type of highly important information.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1368378111020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 13:01:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368379256831-20</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA AND HILLARY GUILTY OF BENGHAZI DERELICTION OF DUTIES</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1368047888562</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:18:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Greg, I have great respect for your relationship with Clay. It is the CSCO boards equivalent of Butch and Sundance, Tom and Huck Finn, or dare I say...Maverick and Iceman.....Greg and Clayveus, clear as day. http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x82qpw_top-gun-maverick-iceman_gaylesbian#.UY_PRZ0o73g</Msg><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1368379256831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 13:20:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368379498060-21</Id><Title>WHEN CAN ALL DEMOCRATS GO HOME? ...to Cuba</Title><Msg>Don't all Democrats feel at home in a repressive, entitled, poorly functioning, derelict, declining and decadent community, like Cuba? Sure they do, lots of poverty, miserable health care, horrid transportation, the main employment is in the SEX TRADE for Europeans and Canadians who use Cuba as a giant brothel. And Castro is the pimp. Is that like Obimbo? He's sending money to failing green businesses, the way a desparate old man gives money to young women, to 'love' him? Does that make the DNC the pimp?</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1368379498060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 13:24:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368382642462-22</Id><Title>meanwhile in the real world</Title><Msg>Robert Michael Gates (born September 25, 1943) is a retired civil servant and university president who served as the 22nd United States Secretary of Defense from 2006 to 2011. Prior to this, Gates served for 26 years in the Central Intelligence Agency and the National Security Council, and under President George H. W. Bush as Director of Central Intelligence. Gates was also an officer in the United States Air Force and during the early part of his military career, he was recruited by the CIA Gates: "Difficult if not impossible" to get military assets to Benghazi in time Former Defense Secretary Robert Gates said he would not have approved a rushed proposal to send military assets to Benghazi to halt the September 2012 attack on a U.S. diplomatic facility there, saying, "The one thing that our forces are noted for is planning and preparation before we send people in harm's way, and there just wasn't time to do that."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1368382642462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 14:17:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368388684079-23</Id><Topic><Title>Ain't it Funny How...</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1368374790270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 12:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe, but the HUGE difference is there was not ensuing cover-up to cover his #$%$ like with Obammy and Hillary. You see, gfo dunderhead, it's not just what happened in Benghazi - it's how it was handled thereafter. Dems = Party before country, ALWAYS...</Msg><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1368388684079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 15:58:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368389487008-24</Id><Topic><Title>meanwhile in the real world</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1368382642462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 14:17:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The one CRITICAL detail you're missing is that even before the attack, repeated requests for support were ignored by the State Dept. They KNEW an attack was imminent. And what about the Navy SEAL that painted the target and there was NO air support. He was a sitting duck and was killed. But you just keep on making excuses for these corrupt politicians who will ALWAYS put party ahead of country...</Msg><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1368389487008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:11:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368390358378-25</Id><Topic><Title>IF EVERYONE WALKED AROUND WITH A LOADED AK47, USA WOULD BE ALOT SAFER</Title><Username>george_wallace_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1368303084166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:11:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Low Info blacks and hispanics are mostly gang member criminals who shoot at rival gang memberss everyday in their neighborhoods and their favorite weapon is an AK47 machine gun. They love the illegal machine guns that they buy on the black market with no paperwork to help Obama track them.. They dont give a rats #$%^% about Obama gun laws because they have never obeyed these gun laws and never will.</Msg><Username>who_eats_collard_greens</Username><Timestamp>1368390358378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:25:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368390484991-26</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA HAS SECRET MEETING WITH ABC,CBS,NBC,MSNBC,CNN,AP to COLLABORATE ON COVERING UP BENGAZI NEGLIGENCE</Title><Username>janet_reno_is_an_ugly_bitch</Username><Timestamp>1368303267639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:14:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In reality the democrat party writes the news for AP, ABC,CBS,NBC,MSNBC,CNN ect. The purpose of the secret meeting is to brainstorm and come up with ideas on how to coverup Obama scandal and make it go away so that those responsible get away with murder.</Msg><Username>who_eats_collard_greens</Username><Timestamp>1368390484991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:28:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368390647531-27</Id><Topic><Title>BRITAIN EVACUATED THEIR BENGAZI EMBASSY STAFF, OBAMA LET USA BENGAZI STAFF BE SLAUGHTERED</Title><Username>the_galloping_goose</Username><Timestamp>1368236980780</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:49:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Britain did not have one life lost in Bengazi because they actually care about the safety of their Embassy staff and promptly evacuated their Bengazi Embassy staff when the staff was worried about their own safety. and asked for help. Hillary decided to buy a bunch of SUV's for the Vienna European Embassy Staff instead of evacuating USA Bengazi Embassy Personell to safety.</Msg><Username>who_eats_collard_greens</Username><Timestamp>1368390647531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:30:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368390764172-28</Id><Topic><Title>RED CROSS EVACUATED BENGAZI WORKERS, OBAMA LEFT USA EMBASSY STAFF TO BE SLAUGHTERED.</Title><Username>the_galloping_goose</Username><Timestamp>1368237040033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:50:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would not be suprized if it is later discovered that the WH occupier enjoyed watching Ambassodor Stevens and his office mates be slaughtered in Bengazi.</Msg><Username>who_eats_collard_greens</Username><Timestamp>1368390764172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:32:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368390966907-29</Id><Topic><Title>BRITAIN EVACUATED THEIR BENGAZI EMBASSY STAFF, OBAMA LET USA BENGAZI STAFF BE SLAUGHTERED</Title><Username>the_galloping_goose</Username><Timestamp>1368236980780</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:49:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barack Hussein Obloodguilty didn't want to let it get out that Al Qaeda is alive and thriving after he made such a big political point of killing OsamaBL. He and Hillary obfuscated for two reasons: A. His reelection, and B. Hillary's chances for 2016 Conniving, culpable forgers of falsehood is what they are - Party Before Country - ALWAYS.</Msg><Username>doji_rubicon</Username><Timestamp>1368390966907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:36:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368390995443-30</Id><Title>market correction is on the way</Title><Msg>protect buy vxx</Msg><Username>sherry757583</Username><Timestamp>1368390995443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:36:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368391101135-31</Id><Topic><Title>meanwhile in the real world</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1368382642462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 14:17:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The British and the Red Cross evacuated their personnel when the personnel were concerned about their safety and asked for help. Obama and Hillary ignored Ambassodor Stevens and his staffs plea for help.</Msg><Username>pic_n_save_democrat</Username><Timestamp>1368391101135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:38:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368391879645-32</Id><Title>Leave Hillary Alone! William Kristol Says Republicans Should Stop Running ‘Ridiculous’ Ads On Benghazi</Title><Msg>Ultra conservative Willliam Kristol understands the GOP is making themselves look ridiculous and likely picking up votes for Hillary.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1368391879645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:51:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368391988088-33</Id><Title>PUBLIC SCHOOL UNION TEACHER ARRESTED FOR HAVING SEX WITH A DOG WHILE STUDENTS WATCH</Title><Msg>PUBLIC SCHOOL UNION TEACHER ARRESTED FOR HAVING SEX WITH A DOG WHILE STUDENTS WATCH. This is the kind of demoncrat union skkkkum 'teaching' in public schools.</Msg><Username>keating_5_john_mccain_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1368391988088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:53:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368392575792-34</Id><Title>MOST PUBLIC SCHOOL UNION TEACHERS ARE CHILD MOLESTORS AND SEX OFFENDER DEGENERATES</Title><Msg>Most public school union teachers are child molestors and sex offender degenerates</Msg><Username>janet_napalitano_is_ugly</Username><Timestamp>1368392575792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:02:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368393121411-35</Id><Title>UNION TEACHER FIRED FOR FORCING STUDENTS TO STOMP ON USA FLAG BUT WAS PAID $131,000</Title><Msg>UNION TEACHER FIRED FOR FORCING STUDENTS TO STOMP ON USA FLAG BUT WAS PAID $131,000 as a condition of the firing. WHAT THE ????</Msg><Username>sean_penn_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1368393121411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:12:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368393462376-36</Id><Title>PUBLIC SCHOOL UNION TEACHER FORCED KIDS TO CALL TERORISTS FREEDOM FIGHTERS AND FORCED KIDS TO WEAR BURKAS</Title><Msg>Public school union teacher forced kids to call terorists freedom fighters and forced kids to wear burkas. time ban all public school unions.</Msg><Username>unions_r_criminal_gangs</Username><Timestamp>1368393462376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:17:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368393882647-37</Id><Title>MOST PUBLIC SCHOOL UNION TEACHERS ARE ANTI-AMERICA LOWLIFE SKKKKUM</Title><Msg>Most public school union teachers are anti-america lowlife skkkkum</Msg><Username>fukk_france_dot_com</Username><Timestamp>1368393882647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:24:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368402473174-38</Id><Topic><Title>PUBLIC SCHOOL UNION TEACHER FORCED KIDS TO CALL TERORISTS FREEDOM FIGHTERS AND FORCED KIDS TO WEAR BURKAS</Title><Username>unions_r_criminal_gangs</Username><Timestamp>1368393462376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:17:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberalism at it's evil diabolical anti-American finest, teach kids that the Founding Fathers were terrorists and teach them that Mvslim terrorists are freedom fighters. This is the way of the evil blood thirsty murderous Kenyan and his corrupt commie cronies. Hussein is the enemy of America. A true terrorist, Mvslim raised and Mvslim bred. Inbred.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1368402473174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 19:47:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368403934589-39</Id><Topic><Title>IF EVERYONE WALKED AROUND WITH A LOADED AK47, USA WOULD BE ALOT SAFER</Title><Username>george_wallace_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1368303084166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 16:11:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama TRACK THEM? Obama gave them to them! Ever hear of Fast and Furious.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1368403934589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 20:12:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368404213516-40</Id><Topic><Title>UNION TEACHER FIRED FOR FORCING STUDENTS TO STOMP ON USA FLAG BUT WAS PAID $131,000</Title><Username>sean_penn_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1368393121411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:12:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hard to believe they paid Obama that much. It's usually much more. Even though he doesn't do it for the money.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1368404213516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 20:16:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368409629225-41</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings will be the key for short term</Title><Username>investora2z</Username><Timestamp>1368359640014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 07:54:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CSCO needs to start growing again. It's nice getting the dividend again but would like to see the stock head to its early 2000 highs again. If they can start making over $.50 a quarter then I can us heading to $30 a share over the next year. Nice to actually see a 1 in a 1000 post about Cisco and not the political dribble that has infested this board.</Msg><Username>michsteve09</Username><Timestamp>1368409629225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 21:47:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368412124607-42</Id><Title>Tea Party's rational solutions dominate conversation..Democrats drool</Title><Msg>Yes, the Tea Party's brilliant, insightful, common sense solutions to the serious problems created in America by Democrats is both stunning and dominant....the end of 'Democrat' as we know it, is imminent and fondly hoped for by all Americans..long live the Tea Party!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1368412124607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:28:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368413861223-43</Id><Topic><Title>Leave Hillary Alone! William Kristol Says Republicans Should Stop Running ‘Ridiculous’ Ads On Benghazi</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1368391879645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:51:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sir,are correct. The only factions trying to desperately discredit the x-secretary, are the GOP, and their media lackey's. The GOP is so fearful of Hillary's candidacy in 2016', that they will beat the Benghazi incident for all they think it's worth. Problem is it's not worth The exaggerated misconceptions that are easily proven baseless by officials of the Obama administration. The end result, Hillary emerges stronger then ever,as a vindicated victim,falsely accused by the typical GOP prim objective policy of discrediting any and all members of the Obama administration. Ergo the GOP, losses more credibility with the public, and defeats it selves again. Wise up GOP, if all you got are your erroneous scenarios and misconceptions, of the Benghazi incident , to prepare for the 2016' campaign, like your previous presidential candidates; you ain't got nothing.</Msg><Username>fss13</Username><Timestamp>1368413861223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:57:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368414739047-44</Id><Title>Is this message board for real?</Title><Msg>Hard to believe so many racist, low-life people still exist in this country. Or, maybe it's really just 1 or 2 a-holes who have nothing better to do all day and night than clutter the board with their venom. Get a life and join the 21st century. Your way of thinking is dying a quick death..</Msg><Username>who_is_at_fault</Username><Timestamp>1368414739047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368416334061-45</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee and his dangerous talk is conspiring</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1368145794234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sort of looks like you will be cleaning that BS off your feet for a few days. Need to be careful what you walk into without knowing the facts. But then you are a Liberal Socialist Tree Hugging Pecker-wood with and Obama chip implanted in your brain, and the only thing the chip does, is repeat. Obama lies. PS if you are still supporting him, then you are one sick sucker that everyone should stay away from.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1368416334061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:38:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368416423302-46</Id><Title>SHHHHH, YOU NEED TO BE VERY QUIET NOW....</Title><Msg>my little liberal democraty friends....too much #$%$ has been exiting your lips....so shhhhhh, be very quiet now</Msg><Username>adolphlhitler</Username><Timestamp>1368416423302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:40:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368416959474-47</Id><Topic><Title>SHHHHH, YOU NEED TO BE VERY QUIET NOW....</Title><Username>adolphlhitler</Username><Timestamp>1368416423302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:40:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you see how a gang of negars fired on a parade in New Orleans today...what worthless Obamavoters they are!</Msg><Username>heinrichfhimmler</Username><Timestamp>1368416959474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:49:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368417015463-48</Id><Topic><Title>Is this message board for real?</Title><Username>who_is_at_fault</Username><Timestamp>1368414739047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:12:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, you obviously haven't experienced the HAL board. CSCO board is rookie hour compared to the dead end Rushbots over at HAL.</Msg><Username>oil_for_bullets_initiative</Username><Timestamp>1368417015463</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:50:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>