<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367159228132-1</Id><Topic><Title>Democratic Senator Max Baucus Calls Obamacare a TRAINWRECK</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1367062028381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 07:27:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>King was a seditious, womanizing, anarchist, and is today venerated as honorable, and approaching near sainthood status, among a generation who never lived during his era of civil insurrection. *** Martin Luther King was a Republican. Abraham Lincoln was a Republican.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1367159228132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 10:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367159280899-2</Id><Topic><Title>AND THE ALMIGHTY SAID</Title><Username>demcrapsodomites</Username><Timestamp>1367090749519</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 15:25:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all sodomites are dems -- FILTHY HOMOS!!! *** smelly peckers</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1367159280899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 10:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367160594467-3</Id><Topic><Title>RUSSIA ARRESTS 140 MOSLEM TERORISTS, OBAMA GIVES MOSLEM TERORISTS WELFARE AND CITIZENSHIP #$%$?</Title><Username>communism_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1367099335971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 17:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Russia tortured and killed hundreds of thousands of people in Chechnya. Russian repressive policies in Chechnya is what created the radical Muslim fighters in that country in the first place. Even now, Russian Chechnya policy still stinks and is creating lots more terrorists. Teabagger nut jobs want the US to emulate Russia because they love Russia so much.</Msg><Username>lemonteeth79</Username><Timestamp>1367160594467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 10:49:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367161545759-4</Id><Title>Hyper inflation next big economic event</Title><Msg>Hyper inflation starts fast and moves fast. Look at every chart from economic history.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1367161545759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 11:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367161613456-5</Id><Topic><Title>RUSSIA ARRESTS 140 MOSLEM TERORISTS, OBAMA GIVES MOSLEM TERORISTS WELFARE AND CITIZENSHIP #$%$?</Title><Username>communism_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1367099335971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 17:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Russia knows how to deal with the problem, unlike Obama's FBI.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1367161613456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 11:06:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367161980975-6</Id><Title>REPUKES TURNING PUTIN LOVING COMMUNISTS NOW...</Title><Msg>You have to live the ironic lives the pukes live in. And they take Putin at his word. LMAO ! Show me a repuke and you'll show me an idiot.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1367161980975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 11:13:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367162128744-7</Id><Topic><Title>Finished any rands atlas shrugged</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1367076910406</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:35:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bob Jones or Pat Robertson's 'academia'. LMAO !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1367162128744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 11:15:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367162383641-8</Id><Topic><Title>Even his Mom thinks the Bush's have done enough damage</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1366989842968</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spoken like a kept woman who hasn't lifted a finger her whole life. By the way 'this mommy dearest' created 4 creepy sons. The cow cannot be respected.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1367162383641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 11:19:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367165334580-9</Id><Topic><Title>RUSSIA ARRESTS 140 MOSLEM TERORISTS, OBAMA GIVES MOSLEM TERORISTS WELFARE AND CITIZENSHIP #$%$?</Title><Username>communism_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1367099335971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 17:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama= The enemy of my enemy is my friend. He support Jihad against Christians and Jews. It's in plain view- Obama supports Islamic Jihadist that oppose Judeo-Christian people with traditional family values, mostly right wing conservatives "clinging to their guns and religion". His administration has and will continue soft-pedal violent Muslin Extremism... Ft. Hood, Benghazi, Boston Bombing etc., and blame game conservatives.</Msg><Username>generic_erick</Username><Timestamp>1367165334580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 12:08:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367165424630-10</Id><Title>This should help Keystone pipeline approval</Title><Msg>Explosion Reported At Detroit Tar Sands Refinery Posted: 27 Apr 2013 04:36 PM PDT Another explosion, this time near Detroit: DETROIT (WWJ) – BREAKING – There has been an explosion at the Marathon Detroit Refinery and a mandatory evacuation order is in effect for the area just off of Schafer from Ropp down to Dix and all the way down to Outer Drive per Melvindale police. Reports of the explosion came in from several listeners to WWJ Newsradio 950 just before 6 p.m. and it appears that one of the tankers on the site may have exploded. Marathon Detroit Refinery told WWJ that they were trying to get the situation under control but could not comment further. The controversial site is a major destination for tar sands oil, and is in Michigan's single most polluted zip code: More recently, residents have been concerned about huge black piles appearing along the Detroit River. They're made up of a material known as petroleum coke, or petcoke, that originates from the Marathon facility and is being sold to a company called Koch Minerals LLC. Marathon said that since they do not own either the petcoke or the property where the mounds of the petcoke were dumped, they are not responsible for moving it. The Michigan Department of Environmental Quality (DEQ) conducted tests on the petcoke, following concerns expressed by U.S. Reps. Gary Peters (D-Bloomfield Township) and John Conyers (D-Detroit), but found them not to be hazardous. Not satisfied with these results, State Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Detroit) collected samples for independent testing last month and is now waiting on the results. She's also concerned about the potential for polluted stormwater to flow into the Detroit River, although DEQ Water Resources Division spokesman Andrew Hartz told the Detroit News last week that the piles are being managed to prevent that sort of runoff. Petcoke may form combustible dust concentrations in air. Is this another case of unregulated industry go</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1367165424630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 12:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367165956134-11</Id><Topic><Title>Finished any rands atlas shrugged</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1367076910406</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:35:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rand was a third-rate thinker and fifth-rate writer, and her many acolytes in the Republican Party crank out an inexhausti­ble supply of derivative gruel based her reed-thin philosophy­. The real irony is that such people long ago turned off the thinking part of their brains in exchange for her cartoonish­, paint-by-n­umbers world view. And each of these sad patsies regards himself as a "Great Man". Pathetic. "[The Native Americans] didn't have any rights to the land and there was no reason for anyone to grant them rights which they had not conceived and were not using.... What was it they were fighting for, if they opposed white men on this continent? For their wish to continue a primitive existence, their "right" to keep part of the earth untouched, unused and not even as property, just keep everybody out so that you will live practicall­y like an animal, or maybe a few caves above it. Any white person who brought the element of civilizati­on had the right to take over this continent.­" -- "Q and A session following her Address To The Graduating Class Of The United States Military Academy at West Point, New York, March 6, 1974" An interesting thing is happening right now around the GOP budget proposal. A broad coalition of religious voices is criticizing the morality of the choices reflected in budget cuts and tax policy. And they’ve specifically targeted Ryan and his praise for Rand, the philosopher who once said she “promote[d] the ethic of selfishness.”</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1367165956134</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 12:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367169015447-12</Id><Topic><Title>Hyper inflation next big economic event</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1367161545759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 11:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no inflation wink wink</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1367169015447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 13:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367173814206-13</Id><Topic><Title>This should help Keystone pipeline approval</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1367165424630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 12:10:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thousands of illegal immigrants already released And that has what to do with the oil pipeline explosion Zippy?</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1367173814206</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 14:30:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367179032345-14</Id><Topic><Title>Poetic justice in Boston bombing, the libs got what the asked for by supporting terrorists</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1367174894363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 14:48:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, people should be worried about terrorists. My condolences to all the people hurt or killed in Boston. However, outside of the 9/11 terrorist attack when Bush was president, the chances of being harmed by terrorists is extremely small. Being killed by terrorists should actually be the least of any person’s worries. People should be much more worried about NRA supported whackos who kill people doing normal activities such as walking on the streets, attending class, working in an office, or just watching a movie. The chances of being killed in such situations is thousands of times higher than being killed by terrorists. There is a lot of blood on the NRA who sees all these killings happen and yet they cannot even let a bill to tighten background checks to be passed.</Msg><Username>lemonteeth79</Username><Timestamp>1367179032345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367179622835-15</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ADMIN ANNOUNCES THAT THEY DONT CHECK CITIZENSHIP FOR FOOD STAMPS URGES ILLEGALS T APPLY 4 FOOD STAMPS</Title><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1367109590769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 20:39:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The boston moslem terorists Tsarnaev brothers were on Obama's terorist watchlist yet he still gave them welfare and citizenship so why would Obama care if criminal illegals get welfare benefits???</Msg><Username>panty_clad_hippo</Username><Timestamp>1367179622835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 16:07:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367179808917-16</Id><Topic><Title>WHILE OBAMA GOLFING AND SUBVERTING 2ND AMENDMENT, RUSSIANS RECORDING BOSTON TERORIST CONVERSATIONS</Title><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1367107790996</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 20:09:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would not suprize me if Obama let this evil terorist mother of Tsarnaev enter the USA even though she is on Obama's terorist watch list, even though she praised her son for killing people at the boston marathon and even though the russians shared the recording with Obama implicating her as a participant of the bombing.</Msg><Username>panty_clad_hippo</Username><Timestamp>1367179808917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 16:10:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367180140308-17</Id><Topic><Title>USSR TOLD OBAMA BOSTON TERORIST NAME TWICE AND OBAMA LET TERORIST BOMB BOSTON</Title><Username>theory_of_evolution_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1366859868817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 23:17:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The mother of these Tsarnaev terorist brothers is also on Obama's terorist watchlist and wants to come here to visit her son. She is claiming financial hardship. Anyone want to bet that Obama gives here a free airplane tickets and free 5 star hotel stay at taxpayer expense?? Obama gave the Tsarnaev brothers welfare and citizenship when they were on his terorist watchlist.</Msg><Username>panty_clad_hippo</Username><Timestamp>1367180140308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 16:15:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367180263423-18</Id><Topic><Title>Hyper inflation starting</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1366917515163</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:18:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The new clean coal from Ohio State doesn't even burn. There is no fly ash, and no clinkers. The reduction of these pollutants is all they need to expand use under current guidelines. Development will likely be impeded by chicken little and his band of "sky is falling" eco-nuts. They react it chemically. The current model is to use the heat from the reaction to fire a boiler. The CO2 can be fully captured, bringing it into compliance with future regulations. Did you know that the manufacture of ethanol creates additional carbon dioxide in the fermentation process? Even Algae emits carbon dioxide at night, as do all other bio-fuel plant sources. Plants absorb CO2 in the light cycle, and give some back in the dark cycle. Coal is being treated unfairly by the eco-nuts. This new technology cleans it up beyond any reasonable expectations.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1367180263423</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 16:17:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367180918514-19</Id><Topic><Title>RUSSIA ARRESTS 140 MOSLEM TERORISTS, OBAMA GIVES MOSLEM TERORISTS WELFARE AND CITIZENSHIP #$%$?</Title><Username>communism_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1367099335971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 17:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(Russia tortured and killed hundreds of thousands of people in Chechnya0 And our forefathers had the American Indian Holocaust, know as the "500 year war" "World's Longest Holocaust In The History Of Mankind And Loss Of Human Lives." Does that make us better than the Russians, Pecker-wood?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1367180918514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 16:28:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367181846676-20</Id><Topic><Title>This should help Keystone pipeline approval</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1367165424630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 12:10:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe it will speed up drilling in the gulf. Even sawdust at a lumber mill can explode. Maybe they should make housing illegal and we can all go back to living in tents and teepees?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1367181846676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 16:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367182714915-21</Id><Title>MICHELLE OBAMA: BEARDED LADY, AMAZON,</Title><Msg>side-show attraction and aunt jemima wannabe. And dey it is</Msg><Username>demcrapsodomites</Username><Timestamp>1367182714915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 16:58:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367184570870-22</Id><Topic><Title>KRUGMAN: "Bush lied us into war. Let’s repeat that: he lied us into war."</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1367183451647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 17:10:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul Krugman's a liberal tree hugging pecker-wood and a nutcase! The Krugman Argument He doesn’t say so outright, but Krugman seems to be saying the European sovereign debt crisis is essentially a myth. Apparent, for him, there are no conditions where social welfare spending can cause unmanageable debt growth. Apparently, for him, you are charged high interest rates because of the currency you use instead of being a bad credit risk and owe lots of money. In support of this view Krugman says: •Other country’s have expensive social programs without debt problems •High interest borrowing rates are caused by borrowing in foreign currencies That is his entire argument in a ‘nutshell’… so as to speak.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1367184570870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 17:29:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367185239350-23</Id><Topic><Title>RUSSIA ARRESTS 140 MOSLEM TERORISTS, OBAMA GIVES MOSLEM TERORISTS WELFARE AND CITIZENSHIP #$%$?</Title><Username>communism_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1367099335971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 17:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>American’s past cannot be compared against the Russian present. The US now is not the same as the US that it was over 100 years ago when much of the Native Americans were wiped out. The US is also not the same as the slave holding nation we once were. A country can only grow and improve if it recognizes the errors of its past and rectify its mistakes for the present and the future. Our past mistakes cannot be an excuse for us to turn a blind eye to the genocide Russians are inflicting on Chechnya right now. If we only compare ourselves to our dark past, we would have allowed Germany to continue with its #$%$ ideology after WWII. Is the #$%$ slave labor system any worst or better than the slave labor system we have in the past? There is no difference if you are playing the role of the slave in either system. It is stupid that some people are actually praising and encouraging the use of torture and humiliation of al-Qaeda suspects we capture. This course of action will not make the US safer, it will make the world more dangerous for us. For every prisoner we capture and torture, there will be many more to take his/her place. We will just end up having more terrorists to fight.</Msg><Username>lemonteeth79</Username><Timestamp>1367185239350</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 17:40:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367187078568-24</Id><Topic><Title>RUSSIA ARRESTS 140 MOSLEM TERORISTS, OBAMA GIVES MOSLEM TERORISTS WELFARE AND CITIZENSHIP #$%$?</Title><Username>communism_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1367099335971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 17:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(It is stupid that some people are actually praising and encouraging the use of torture and humiliation of al-Qaeda suspects we capture. This course of action will not make the US safer, it will make the world more dangerous for us.) If this is true, then: Well, lets see -- no torture has been used for a number of years by American's so why not take your family over to Syria for a vacation - put a sign out front of your room saying -- "I am and American" I am sure they will give you a warm welcome - pecker-wood</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1367187078568</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 18:11:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367188114770-25</Id><Title>For a Marxist This Market is Soaring To Historic Highs Under Obama</Title><Msg>You OLD Baggers didn't listen to Limbaugh and Beck and sit on the sidelines did you? Wow! What a bunch of dumbfks!</Msg><Username>usa_censored_citzen</Username><Timestamp>1367188114770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 18:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367191081017-26</Id><Topic><Title>More results from the communist party</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1367073483141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 10:38:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.....DING!</Msg><Username>quincymagoo</Username><Timestamp>1367191081017</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 19:18:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367191820209-27</Id><Title>10 Mariachis of La Reyna de Monterrey Killed in Car Accident in Mexico. USA to blame</Title><Msg>10 Mariachis of La Reyna de Monterrey Killed in Car Accident in Mexico. USA to blame because USA did not send 10 Helicopter to take the Mariachis from Mexico to a USA hospital for free Obama healthcare.</Msg><Username>pancho_villa_gomez</Username><Timestamp>1367191820209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 19:30:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367202670891-28</Id><Topic><Title>MICHELLE OBAMA: BEARDED LADY, AMAZON,</Title><Username>demcrapsodomites</Username><Timestamp>1367182714915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 16:58:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! I was having a mediocre to shity day before I read this and then almost split my side laughing at this and thinking of what a HUGE oinking pig she appears to be at times!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1367202670891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 22:31:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>