<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-21"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363841317502-1</Id><Topic><Title>I beat the hell out of liberal moveon bloggers today on GE Board.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363825864329</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:31:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>welcome to the club, I enjoy doing the same here as often as I please, But then again, the libs here are sissies and easy to beat the hell out of</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363841317502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 00:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363841956341-2</Id><Topic><Title>I beat the hell out of liberal moveon bloggers today on GE Board.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363825864329</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:31:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jen: shhhhhh shhhhhhh, you need to be very quiet now friend, shhhhhhh quiet now...</Msg><Username>adolphlhitler</Username><Timestamp>1363841956341</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 00:59:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363865114277-3</Id><Title>Freshman REP. Thomas Massie- R-KY - the RYAN BUDGET is a PRETEND VOTE!</Title><Msg>Freshman Republican: Ryan Budget ‘A Pretend Vote’ It's also a waste of time and tax payer money that could be used for something NOT 'pretend'...like real jobs... Freshman Rep. Thomas Massie (R-KY) told a roomful of reporters Wednesday that the upcoming House vote on the Paul Ryan budget is all for show, with no real consequences, because the proposal is "dead on arrival" in the Senate. "You know, I'm new here but what I'm learning is that the budget is just kind of a guideline," Massie said on a panel with nine other House conservatives. "And it's sort of a pretend guideline because we know it's dead on arrival in the Senate. So it's all about optics and messaging." The Kentuckian said he intends to vote No on the Ryan plan because it doesn't cut spending enough, although other conservatives appear ready to vote Yes. "We know it's dead on arrival," Massie said. "We know it's a pretend vote HOW DESPICABLE!</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363865114277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 07:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363866095162-4</Id><Topic><Title>Tried to make Junior rich</Title><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363830422154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:47:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Although Uni-Pixel's story sounds grand, it also hasn't made its UniBoss platform on a large scale before, meaning it's going to be trial and error galore as its rapidly tries to expand its production line. Let's also keep in mind that it isn't as if Uni-Pixel is the only player in this space as well. Its unwillingness to reveal its PC-making partner coupled with its recent history of losses as it developed its new technologies leaves me highly skeptical of its current rally.</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363866095162</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 07:41:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363868937363-5</Id><Topic><Title>juniorsclassmate_5 • PLEASE KEEP YOU PROMISE OR DO YOU LIE DAILY LIKE OBAMA DOES.</Title><Username>vensh_1</Username><Timestamp>1363129405988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 19:03:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>juniorsclassmate_5- still a jobless troll living with his Mom at 32. Something is wrong with this #$%$.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363868937363</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:28:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363869147280-6</Id><Title>Obama now has a Legacy. Read it below and weep.</Title><Msg>List of Obama’s Failures It’s hard to think of a president that has been more of an Epic Failure than President Obama. Even Carter is glad this guy came along, so at least he knows he is no longer the worst president ever. Here is just a short list of Obama’s Failures: 1. Hawaii is in Asia 2. Passing on the keystone pipeline. 3. Touts a Green Energy Company as exemplary that fails a year later. 4. Using the Gulf Oil Spill to promote Green Energy – instead of cleaning it up. 5. Thinking the Tea Party is a passing fad – or that they are racists. 6. Pulling out of Iraq with no clear victory over insurgent forces. 7. Trying to re-write history through speeches – with inaccurate information (i.e. Statue of Liberty) 8. Getting a Nobel Prize for being the most ineffective President in the history of the United States, though some say it was for his pigment. 9. Putting all legislation on the Internet for five days before it comes to a vote. 10. Returning the bust of Churchill to the Brits. 11. Giving a collection of DVDs to the British PM. 12. Denying the notion of American Exceptionalism. 13. Promising to close Gitmo — failing to do so. 14. Securing the Olympics for Chicago in 2016. 15. Naming numerous Communists/Socialists/Progressives to his various Czar positions and then watching them scurry for cover when Beck begins to call them out, forcing them to resign. 16. Government races for NJ, VA and the Senate Seat in Mass. 17. The midterm elections, which Obama himself called a shellacking. 18. Prediction that stimulus would ensure that unemployment doesn’t exceed 8%. 19. Bowing to just about everybody. 20. Proposing amnesty for illegal aliens to increase the population of voters for Democrat elections. 21. He said, I have visited 57 states. Now there is just 1 left to visit. 22. Obama to Medvedev…give me space I will have more flexibility after my election.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363869147280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:32:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363869188376-7</Id><Title>GREEN JOBS are another Obama utter failure. Most companies he funded are bankrupt now.</Title><Msg>GREEN JOBS are another Obama utter failure. Most companies he funded are bankrupt now. "The Obama Administration Has Managed The Nearly Impossible Feat Of Turning Energy Policy Into A Money Loser, Pouring Taxpayer Dollars Into Green-Energy Busts Like Solyndra."(Editorial, "The Non-Green Job Boom," The Wall Street Journal, 11/28/11) Obama Predicted His Investments In Green Energy Would Create 5 Million Jobs PROMISE: In 2008, Then-Senator Obama Claimed His Investments In Green Energy Would Create 5 Million New Jobs. OBAMA: "And I'll invest $150 billion over the next decade in affordable, renewable sources of energy -- wind power, and solar power, and the next generation of biofuels -- an investment that will lead to new industries and 5 million new jobs that pay well and can't be outsourced."(Sen. Barack Obama, Acceptance Speech Remarks At The Democratic National Convention, Denver, CO, 8/28/08) FAILURE: The Failure Of Obama's Green Jobs Programs “Gets More Embarrassing By The Day.”“The green jobs subsidy story gets more embarrassing by the day. Three years ago President Obama promised that by the end of the decade America would have five million green jobs, but so far some $90 billion in government spending has delivered very few.”</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363869188376</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:33:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363869286640-8</Id><Title>OBAMA 2013 NEW SLOGAN YOU CAN NOT ARGUE with FAILURE.</Title><Msg>Obama 2013 new slogan you can not argue with failure.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363869286640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363869307045-9</Id><Title>Only thing wrong with America is spelled O-B-A-M-A</Title><Msg>Only thing wrong with America is spelled O-B-A-M-A</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363869307045</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:35:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363869373311-10</Id><Title>GE board infested with little girl cartoon charactrers - like vensh_1 and drstone3</Title><Msg>funny!</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363869373311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363869373874-11</Id><Title>Leave it to GOP to come up with a solution for the mess that America is now in economically.</Title><Msg>I bought a bird feeder. I hung it on my back porch and filled it with seed. What a beauty of a bird feeder it was, as I filled it lovingly with seed. Within a week we had hundreds of bird taking advantage of the continuous flow of free and easily accessible food. But then the birds started building nests in the boards of the patio, above the table, and next to the barbecue. Then came the poop. It was everywhere: on the patio tile, the chairs, and the table everywhere! Then some of the birds turned mean. They would dive bomb me and try to peck me even though I had fed them out of my own pocket. And others birds were boisterous and loud. They sat on the feeder and squawked and screamed at all hours of the day and night and demanded that I fill it when it got low on food. After a while, I couldn't even sit on my own back porch anymore. So I took down the bird feeder and in three days the birds were gone. I cleaned up their mess and took down the many nests they had built all over the patio. Soon, the back yard was like it used to be quiet, serene and no one demanding their rights to a free meal. Now let's see. Our government gives out free food, subsidized housing, free medical care and free education, and allows anyone born here to be an automatic citizen. Then the illegal’s came by the tens of thousands. Suddenly our taxes went up to pay for free services; small apartments are housing 5 families; you have to wait 6 hours to be seen by an emergency room doctor; your child's second grade class is behind other schools because over half the class doesn't speak English. Corn Flakes now come in a bilingual box; I have to ‘press one ' to hear my bank talk to me in English, and people waving flags other than 'Old Glory' are squawking and screaming in the streets, demanding more rights and free liberties. Just my opinion, but maybe it's time for the government to take down.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363869373874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363869425766-12</Id><Title>Lazy Obama spends more time on March Madness picks of final four than doing a Budget.</Title><Msg>Obama you owe the American people a responsible, balanced budget. Our skyrocketing debt is damaging our economy and threatening our future. It's time to change course. Today, the GOP is introducing a plan to do just that. House Republicans are offering a common-sense plan to balance the budget in ten years. The Senate Democrats' budget, on the other hand, never balances - ever. Balancing the budget isn't just about making numbers on a spreadsheet line up. It's about the well-being of the country. A balanced budget will revive our economy and expand opportunity. Now do your job Mr. Obama. Already Democrats are falsely attacking our budget. We need your support to help us push back and put in place real solutions to our fiscal challenges. Now go do your job Mr. President. President Obama American families cannot spend more than Mom &amp; Dad make in a year or they go bankrupt. Stop using that Maxine Waters fuzzy ghetto math and balance the US budget. We the people demand it and do not want to be the next Greece. Did you fail math at Harvard and High School?</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363869425766</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:37:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363869472954-13</Id><Title>Obama wasted $16,643,000,000,000,000.00 in deficit spending T/D just Google National Debt Clock</Title><Msg>Obama wasted $16,643,000,000,000,000.00 in deficit spending T/D just Google National Debt Clock. We all know liberals post lies here 24/7 so fact check yourself.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363869472954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:37:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363869601112-14</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA 2013 NEW SLOGAN YOU CAN NOT ARGUE with FAILURE.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363869286640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dr. Stone is ON FIRE this morning... true to his word.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363869601112</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:40:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363869647257-15</Id><Title>Notice how DRSTONE posts here 24/7 LOL</Title><Msg>and he is so stupid he thinks 16 trillion is 16 Quadrillion, LOL tea billies are stupid, enough said</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363869647257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363869656361-16</Id><Topic><Title>Obama wasted $16,643,000,000,000,000.00 in deficit spending T/D just Google National Debt Clock</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363869472954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:37:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People like you should be taken out and shot. Don't you have anything better to do than fill up stock discussion boards with your lies?</Msg><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363869656361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:40:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363869687945-17</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA 2013 NEW SLOGAN YOU CAN NOT ARGUE with FAILURE.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363869286640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what a pinhead, he has what about 300 posts in the last 12 hours, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363869687945</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:41:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363869712771-18</Id><Topic><Title>Notice how DRSTONE posts here 24/7 LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363869647257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:40:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he goes back and forth between GE and CSCO</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363869712771</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:41:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363869724226-19</Id><Title>Note to jerks</Title><Msg>This is a Csco message board, not a political web site. Please take your trash somewhere else.</Msg><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363869724226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363869810327-20</Id><Topic><Title>Note to jerks</Title><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363869724226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:42:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Macros are all that matter to the algos.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363869810327</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:43:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363869818049-21</Id><Topic><Title>Notice how DRSTONE posts here 24/7 LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363869647257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:40:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What on earth is wrong with this person? Notice that its' mainly Obama haters that do this sort of thing.</Msg><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363869818049</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:43:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363869859358-22</Id><Topic><Title>Notice how DRSTONE posts here 24/7 LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363869647257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:40:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A very mentally unstable demographic watches FOX NEWS religiously</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363869859358</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363870133194-23</Id><Title>So back to CISCO .. what is wrong?</Title><Msg>Why is Cisco down 2.5% pre-market??? Is this related to poor Oracle earnings? I can't find any other news.</Msg><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363870133194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:48:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363870174831-24</Id><Title>REPUBLICANS ONLY PLATFORM POSITION: ATTACK OBAMA</Title><Msg>REPUBLICANS ONLY PLATFORM POSITION: ATTACK OBAMA Is to attack Obama. What a brilliant strategy! Pukes have nothing and everybody can see that except for the blind and brainwashed. That was the pukes strategy during the election (OUR ONLY GOAL IS TO MAKE SURE THAT OBAMA IS A ONE TERM PRESIDENT) .... What's up with that? How did that work out for you pukes? And after the CPAC circus we can see once again, once you go full STUPID/CRAZY why not STAY THE COURSE. The world has changed, and let's hope that pukes never figure that out, for our entertainment, and love of our country. REPUBS=MASSIVE_STUPIDITY</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363870174831</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:49:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363870211680-25</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats are the party of LIARS, ADULTERERS, CROOKS, PERVERTS, and CORPORATE WELFARE SUPPORTERS</Title><Username>vensh_1</Username><Timestamp>1363787578735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree-Democrats are the party of LIARS, ADULTERERS, CROOKS, PERVERTS, and CORPORATE WELFARE SUPPORTERS</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363870211680</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:50:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363870336787-26</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats are the party of LIARS, ADULTERERS, CROOKS, PERVERTS, and CORPORATE WELFARE SUPPORTERS</Title><Username>vensh_1</Username><Timestamp>1363787578735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why do you kill ponies?</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363870336787</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:52:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363870498080-27</Id><Topic><Title>REPUBLICANS ONLY PLATFORM POSITION: ATTACK OBAMA</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363870174831</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:49:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No we are attacking his policies and everything he stands for, which the typical Demasses' pavlonian response is racism charges!</Msg><Username>coco_b_98</Username><Timestamp>1363870498080</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:54:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363870522453-28</Id><Title>downgrades by analysts</Title><Msg>I just saw that some analyst group downgraded Cisco. If the stock drop as much as the pre-market drop it is a great buying opportunity. I listened to an interview with a market analyst the other day who said his group believed the overall market is in a secular bull market. So who do you believe? My take is that the internet is not going away, Cisco is a market leader, has a great balance sheet and that dips will occur especially when talking heads talk down about firms.</Msg><Username>albacornus</Username><Timestamp>1363870522453</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:55:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363870525723-29</Id><Title>CSCO &amp; JNPR downgraded at FBR Capital</Title><Msg>FBR Capital downgraded Cisco to Underperform on concerns the company will be challenged to offset declining routing and switching demand. The firm lowered its price target for shares to $17 from $22. FBR Capital downgraded Juniper (JNPR) to Underperform on concerns the company will be challenged to offset declining routing and switching demand. The firm lowered its price target for shares to $15 from $18.</Msg><Username>dmyoungmba</Username><Timestamp>1363870525723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363870808198-30</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO &amp; JNPR downgraded at FBR Capital</Title><Username>dmyoungmba</Username><Timestamp>1363870525723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:55:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for posting that. Wow,screwed by analysts again. And investors are buying into that, selling Cisco.</Msg><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363870808198</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:00:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363870926059-31</Id><Topic><Title>downgrades by analysts</Title><Username>albacornus</Username><Timestamp>1363870522453</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:55:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure -- analysts are just analysts, but, it looks to me like a lot of investors are believing this because they are selling -- too bad I laready own the darn stock!</Msg><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363870926059</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:02:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363870935249-32</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO &amp; JNPR downgraded at FBR Capital</Title><Username>dmyoungmba</Username><Timestamp>1363870525723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:55:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fedex, Orcl, Germany slowing down, Cyprus hour glass running out of sand, rockets hit Israel, North Korea rattles sabres -- we're going to ALL TIME HIGHS TODAY!!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363870935249</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:02:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363871266871-33</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO &amp; JNPR downgraded at FBR Capital</Title><Username>dmyoungmba</Username><Timestamp>1363870525723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:55:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That runs contrary to Dan Niles' (MOBILCOM) assessment of CSCO -- that the big Tier 1 telecoms, after a three year drop in capital expenses, have announced plans for significant spending increases to accomodate all-IP Unified Communications investment in the trend towards retiring legacy circuits. His one mentioned stock was Cisco as a significant beneficiary. Who to believe? I'll go with the announced spending plans. All the best.</Msg><Username>dachmeister4u</Username><Timestamp>1363871266871</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363871654600-34</Id><Topic><Title>Is Obama really fit to be President or even run a Kool-Aide Stand? Now really.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1360329294457</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 08:14:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please the guy ran Acorn Thugs and libs made him Prez. How dumb are they?</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363871654600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:14:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363871763775-35</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO &amp; JNPR downgraded at FBR Capital</Title><Username>dmyoungmba</Username><Timestamp>1363870525723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:55:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw Dan on CNBC and agree with his assessment. It's interesting that FBR's opinion is given any credence whatsoever, as they can't even get their own house in order, having recently conducted a reverse 1-4 share split.</Msg><Username>dmyoungmba</Username><Timestamp>1363871763775</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:16:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363871828709-36</Id><Topic><Title>So back to CISCO .. what is wrong?</Title><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363870133194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:48:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes It is because of Oracle.</Msg><Username>homerunmandan</Username><Timestamp>1363871828709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363871877835-37</Id><Topic><Title>DO WE HAVE A PRESIDENT OR DICTATOR?</Title><Username>vensh_1</Username><Timestamp>1363129918942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 19:11:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Folks voted and say Obama is a Dictator. Soory Libs you voted for him.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363871877835</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:17:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363872103915-38</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this report yet? (CSCO)</Title><Username>mrowczynskibubblebutt</Username><Timestamp>1361804586311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:03:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this the General Consensus?</Msg><Username>ricomincjoanne</Username><Timestamp>1363872103915</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:21:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363872528941-39</Id><Title>csco when dividend ex-date?</Title><Msg>csco when dividend ex-date?</Msg><Username>edallast</Username><Timestamp>1363872528941</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363872626345-40</Id><Topic><Title>Tried to make Junior rich</Title><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363830422154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:47:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have posted consistently about UNXL,Junior. And you know it. You preferred acting like a child instead of heeding good advice.Your choice.As for winkipuss post,I have no illusions about UNXL.I only daytrade it and will be gone at the first hint of significant bad news.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363872626345</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363872944645-41</Id><Title>New Pope &amp; Obama Joke! LOL!</Title><Msg>Here is Obama &amp; Pope Joke for you CONSERVATIVES to enjoy! A Good Catholic Joke about the Pope &amp; Obama The Pope and Obama are on the same stage in Yankee Stadium in front of a huge crowd. The Pope leans towards Mr. Obama and said, "Do you know that with one little wave of my hand I can make every person in this crowd go wild with joy? This joy will not be a momentary display, but will go deep into their hearts and they'll forever speak of this day and rejoice!" Obama replied, "I seriously doubt that! With one little wave of your hand....Show me!" So the Pope backhanded him and knocked him off the stage! AND THE CROWD ROARED &amp; CHEERED WILDLY and there was happiness throughout the land Kind of brings a tear to your eye, doesn't it?</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363872944645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:35:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363872998465-42</Id><Topic><Title>So back to CISCO .. what is wrong?</Title><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363870133194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:48:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>has nothing to do with oracle . Some lousy jerk at FBR capital downgraded it and of course a lot of fools listen to these idiots ..</Msg><Username>composerx1</Username><Timestamp>1363872998465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363873100948-43</Id><Topic><Title>juniorsclassmate_5 • PLEASE KEEP YOU PROMISE OR DO YOU LIE DAILY LIKE OBAMA DOES.</Title><Username>vensh_1</Username><Timestamp>1363129405988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 19:03:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>juniorsclassmate_5 - now posting on GE board under another one of his wack'o names he uses at moveon blogging office. Exposed again and embarssing his mom again.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363873100948</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:38:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363873293014-44</Id><Topic><Title>So back to CISCO .. what is wrong?</Title><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363870133194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:48:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is FBR Capital. Who the h-ll are they and why does everyone suddenly believe them? 3% in one hour?? Nonsense.</Msg><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363873293014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363873436836-45</Id><Topic><Title>So back to CISCO .. what is wrong?</Title><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363870133194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:48:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We should at least see a bounce here. Csco in one hour has made a monthly low. Incredible. So much for charts! Funny how analysts are the last ones to assign a realistic price target, yet they love coming in a shooting down a good stock. that's fun for them.</Msg><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363873436836</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:43:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363873657435-46</Id><Title>drstone you promised to never return to the GE board---GOOD RIDDANCE!</Title><Msg>But you did promised to do that under your demedici alias too didn't you, whacko?</Msg><Username>walleyefry</Username><Timestamp>1363873657435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:47:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363873790646-47</Id><Title>Michele Bachmann Congresswoman Runs From Questions</Title><Msg>The CPAC conference is often dismissed as a conglomerate of only the most extreme fringes of conservatism, but many young Republicans still congregate at this King-making conference in hopes that their voice will get equal representation at the table. At day 3, Representative Michele Bachmann (R-Minn.) invigorated the crowds with a hateful speech decrying President Obama's supposed mishandling of the September 11 attack to the American consulate in Benghazi — where four Americans, including Ambassador Chris Stevens, were killed. She painted the president out to be apathetic and incompetent – ignoring the "crying screams of Americans." She then described a lavish staff of chefs, movie projectionists and dog walkers that were costing the taxpayers millions. When confronted by Dana Bash of CNN to account for her made-up numbers, Bachmann ran away and deflected the questions – the political equivalent of "nah nah nah, I can't hear you." The only thing more tragic than the existence of politicians like Bachmann is how much we've normalized their presence in the political arena. Whether you blame super PACs, gerrymandering or bad media – there are a growing number of candidates who utilize fanatical voting blocks to secure their place in office. In turn, they imprison themselves in a beholden state of extreme ideology, desperate to avoid any impression that they've betrayed their insulated constituents. When Bachmann famously summarized President Obama's trip to India as a $200 million "boondoggle" – she was again called out on her contrived statistics. Her response spoke to the core of the problem: "these are the numbers that have been coming out in the press." There does exist a feedback loop in today's media, where anyone who publishing something online can be utilized as a source of "news" long enough for talking heads to disseminate the story. The original posters can be self-published nut jobs, anonymous blogg</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363873790646</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:49:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363873818296-48</Id><Title>Junior mourning today.</Title><Msg>Harry Reems, the well-hung star of " Deep Throat " dies at 65. Junior is beside himself with grief and has removed Harry's picture from his bedroom ceiling.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363873818296</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:50:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363874273911-49</Id><Topic><Title>So back to CISCO .. what is wrong?</Title><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363870133194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:48:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this price dump has caused a sell signal in the stocastics stat and the price has fallen below the 30 day moving aver. this needs to get back over that 30 day ma over we will go lower .. these #$%$ who open their idiot mouths have their own agendas for doing cr.p like this .they probably bought puts ahead of this scam . if they were so good at it , they would not be working behind a desk .. they would be sailing yachts .</Msg><Username>composerx1</Username><Timestamp>1363874273911</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:57:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363874291455-50</Id><Topic><Title>So back to CISCO .. what is wrong?</Title><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363870133194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:48:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>on about 2/11 FBR upgrades CSCO, and not one thing has changed. Oh, and they had the lowest PT at 22, There are 33 buy ratings with a pt near 24. Likely FBR wants to reload cheaper. Their call is softness in hardware, DAH, CSCO knows that and is transitioning to software. There is nothing to this call but a market knee jerk. We are 6 weeks from earnings and at a time pre earnings when most stocks do weaken. After earnings FBR will upgrade again, like last month.</Msg><Username>burnaka</Username><Timestamp>1363874291455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:58:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363874430576-51</Id><Title>BIG NEWS OUT ON--BCCI-- READ YAHOO NEWS HEADLINES$$$</Title><Msg>MASSIVE UPSIDE COMING</Msg><Username>strong.data</Username><Timestamp>1363874430576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:00:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363874834291-52</Id><Title>help us john asap need stock buy back</Title><Msg>ok</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363874834291</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:07:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363875071014-53</Id><Title>OBAMA HUFFED AND PUFFED AND DID NOTHING TO SYRIA</Title><Msg>for using chemical weapons against its own people. No sanctions, nothing. This is a tacit approval of their inhumane, animal-like abuses of fellow human beings. SHAME, SHAME, SHAME on you Obama!</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363875071014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:11:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363875263350-54</Id><Title>OBAMA you can redeem yourself By targeting a Drone Strike On Magoo's House</Title><Msg>sure, his house would almost implode on itself anyways with just a moderate wind--make it look like an accident then, Vince foster/Slick WIllie style!</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363875263350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:14:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363875371027-55</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this report yet? (CSCO)</Title><Username>mrowczynskibubblebutt</Username><Timestamp>1361804586311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:03:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>waiting for the update.</Msg><Username>produktionsregelsmarion</Username><Timestamp>1363875371027</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:16:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363875430469-56</Id><Title>Yes It is because of Oracle. pos stock suckstoday</Title><Msg>sad</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363875430469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:17:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363875572949-57</Id><Title>never go green today sucks</Title><Msg>ok</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363875572949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363875767937-58</Id><Title>fpos stock sucks today help us god</Title><Msg>21.50 close</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363875767937</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:22:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363875787771-59</Id><Topic><Title>WHY IS THE TEA PARTY SO POPULAR ALL OVER AMERICA?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363803802085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:23:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surfy, you sad drooler! And I say that with great compassion and genuine concern for your mental capacity. As a kind and caring fellow, I wish you all the best and am sending you a carton of Depens for your bowel incontinence. It's hard to be a Democrat, and trying to balance the insanity of that position is part of your decline. Embrace reality, and live healthy longer! Abandon the nonsense of the Democratic party and re-enter life as a joyful adventure!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363875787771</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363875808508-60</Id><Topic><Title>WHY IS THE TEA PARTY SO POPULAR ALL OVER AMERICA?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363803802085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:23:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I read it, interesting!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363875808508</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363875823087-61</Id><Topic><Title>So back to CISCO .. what is wrong?</Title><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363870133194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:48:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is more likely that csco meets or beats on earnings, FBR who changes their buy sell at a whim will go back to buy, not that it matters. By year end CSCO likely 26-28</Msg><Username>burnaka</Username><Timestamp>1363875823087</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:23:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363875854333-62</Id><Topic><Title>So back to CISCO .. what is wrong?</Title><Username>zugtoo</Username><Timestamp>1363870133194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:48:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Months to break higher, one day to lose gains, classic csco</Msg><Username>smathan75</Username><Timestamp>1363875854333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:24:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363876000799-63</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA you can redeem yourself By targeting a Drone Strike On Magoo's House</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363875263350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:14:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah but then he would be accused by PETA of doing harm to an animal, sooo ok, it works for me.</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363876000799</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:26:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363876015846-64</Id><Topic><Title>juniorsclassmate_5 • PLEASE KEEP YOU PROMISE OR DO YOU LIE DAILY LIKE OBAMA DOES.</Title><Username>vensh_1</Username><Timestamp>1363129405988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 19:03:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>juniorsclassmate_5 - does everyone LOL! at this moron troll daily on Csco Board. Poor guy does not even own the stock and his so broke he still lives with his mother in her basement. Pray he gets some help.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363876015846</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:26:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363876082666-65</Id><Title>It’s hard to think of a president that has been more of an Epic Failure than President Obama.</Title><Msg>It’s hard to think of a president that has been more of an Epic Failure than President Obama. Even Carter is glad this guy came along, so at least he knows he is no longer the worst president ever. Here is just a short list of Obama’s Failures: 1. Hawaii is in Asia 2. Passing on the keystone pipeline. 3. Touts a Green Energy Company as exemplary that fails a year later. 4. Using the Gulf Oil Spill to promote Green Energy – instead of cleaning it up. 5. Thinking the Tea Party is a passing fad – or that they are racists. 6. Pulling out of Iraq with no clear victory over insurgent forces. 7. Trying to re-write history through speeches – with inaccurate information (i.e. Statue of Liberty) 8. Getting a Nobel Prize for being the most ineffective President in the history of the United States, though some say it was for his pigment. 9. Putting all legislation on the Internet for five days before it comes to a vote. 10. Returning the bust of Churchill to the Brits. 11. Giving a collection of DVDs to the British PM. 12. Denying the notion of American Exceptionalism. 13. Promising to close Gitmo — failing to do so. 14. Securing the Olympics for Chicago in 2016. 15. Naming numerous Communists/Socialists/Progressives to his various Czar positions and then watching them scurry for cover when Beck begins to call them out, forcing them to resign. 16. Government races for NJ, VA and the Senate Seat in Mass. 17. The midterm elections, which Obama himself called a shellacking. 18. Prediction that stimulus would ensure that unemployment doesn’t exceed 8%. 19. Bowing to just about everybody. 20. Proposing amnesty for illegal aliens to increase the population of voters for Democrat elections. 21. He said, I have visited 57 states. Now there is just 1 left to visit. 22. Obama to Medvedev…give me space I will have more flexibility after my election.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363876082666</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:28:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363876230735-66</Id><Title>SO BAMA INHERITED A MESS? REALLY? WELL</Title><Msg>all presidents do to one degree or another. Firemen "inherit" messes all the time...but have you ever seen one of them pour gas on it?</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363876230735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:30:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363876388015-67</Id><Topic><Title>drstone you promised to never return to the GE board---GOOD RIDDANCE!</Title><Username>walleyefry</Username><Timestamp>1363873657435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:47:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ggg</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363876388015</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:33:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363876458698-68</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this report yet? (CSCO)</Title><Username>mrowczynskibubblebutt</Username><Timestamp>1361804586311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:03:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice work.</Msg><Username>plnnranna</Username><Timestamp>1363876458698</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:34:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363876886899-69</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA HUFFED AND PUFFED AND DID NOTHING TO SYRIA</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363875071014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:11:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the inaction of Obigtalk just proves that like all libs, they talk a lot about human rights, etc. etc. but in reality they will just be spectators to atrocities against their fellow man. That is why when Bush Sr. went into Iraq against Sadam it made them so crazy: a man with balls acting heroically-that always infuriates the little balless wonders! LMAO</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363876886899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363877104561-70</Id><Topic><Title>SO BAMA INHERITED A MESS? REALLY? WELL</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363876230735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:30:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bush left the worst economy since the great depression but i guess all presidents get that....wait....ROTF!!!! teabillies aren't that stupid,are they?</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1363877104561</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:45:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363877123926-71</Id><Topic><Title>Junior mourning today.</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363873818296</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior ignoring me today LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL ARE YOU REFUSING TO DANCE, PUPPET, DANCE!!!!!! HEEHEEHEEHEEHEHEE HILARIOUS!!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363877123926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:45:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363877304043-72</Id><Title>sold at loss good luck</Title><Msg>KBH 21.82 +0.25 +1.16%</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363877304043</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:48:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363877362225-73</Id><Topic><Title>The US Invasion of Iraq Was a Crime and Its Perpetrators Are Murderers</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363874123234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The mother whose dead body was found in the bombed ruins of Baghdad, holding her baby so tight they could not be pried apart and had to be buried together, can no longer be dismissed as "collateral damage." That mother and child, and the more than 3,000 Iraqi civilians killed directly by U.S. bombs and artillery fire in the first month alone, as well as the Iraqi troops killed while defending their country against an arguably unlawful and unreasonable attack, may have been victims of criminal homicide That's just an example of Georgette W Bush "LIBERATING" his good friends in Iraq,AFTER he couldn't find those TONS of WMDs that he said Saddam possessed.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1363877362225</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363877498316-74</Id><Topic><Title>SO BAMA INHERITED A MESS? REALLY? WELL</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363876230735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:30:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when W left office we weren't the trillions in debt that Obams has given us, spending and impoverishing our children's future with his worthless obamacare failed BS</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363877498316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:51:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363877575924-75</Id><Topic><Title>The US Invasion of Iraq Was a Crime and Its Perpetrators Are Murderers</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363874123234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No problem with prying people apart after Obama's drone strikes. They are in little pieces.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363877575924</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:52:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363877765052-76</Id><Topic><Title>Tried to make Junior rich</Title><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363830422154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:47:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UNXL at 31.75 today. Junior and his other ids talking about Iraq instead. Funny.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363877765052</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:56:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363877795796-77</Id><Title>WHY ISN'T THE MEDIA PUBLISHING DAILY DEATH COUNTS ON AFGHANISTAN?</Title><Msg>of U.S. troops and Civilians? Whatsamatter you commies pieces of shet, doesn't it suit your traiterous pinko moveon agenda now?</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363877795796</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363877875741-78</Id><Topic><Title>The US Invasion of Iraq Was a Crime and Its Perpetrators Are Murderers</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363874123234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes,and a very successful program. Thanks for crediting Bush,fool.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363877875741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363878007519-79</Id><Topic><Title>SO BAMA INHERITED A MESS? REALLY? WELL</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363876230735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:30:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a crude and school boy like comment to make. What are you like 10 years old (Mentally). We got “Bushwhacked” is what we got. No other President since Roosevelt has inherited an economy this bad.</Msg><Username>hughes1953</Username><Timestamp>1363878007519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:00:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363878132627-80</Id><Title>OBAMA BOOED IN ISRAEL AS HE CRITICIZES THEM FOR</Title><Msg>building settlements in and near the West Bank. Obama is an Anti-God fool who once again stepped all over it.</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363878132627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:02:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363878251073-81</Id><Title>will go back to buy, not that it matters. By year end CSCO likely 26-28</Title><Msg>will go back to buy, not that it matters. By year end CSCO likely 26-28</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363878251073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:04:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363878362666-82</Id><Title>In 2009 Obama promised to keep unemployment from rising above 8 percent</Title><Msg>He lied.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363878362666</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:06:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363878389489-83</Id><Title>ratings with a pt near 24. Likely FBR wants to reload cheaper</Title><Msg>ratings with a pt near 24. Likely FBR wants to reload cheaper</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363878389489</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:06:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363878420488-84</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA BOOED IN ISRAEL AS HE CRITICIZES THEM FOR</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363878132627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:02:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spouting off again about things he doesn't understand -- throw Obama out!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363878420488</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363878422445-85</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this report yet? (CSCO)</Title><Username>mrowczynskibubblebutt</Username><Timestamp>1361804586311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:03:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just subscribed. I am hoping for the best.</Msg><Username>maticienhelene</Username><Timestamp>1363878422445</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:07:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363878431403-86</Id><Title>Obama promised to put all bills on the White House web site for five days before signing them.</Title><Msg>Obama promised to put all bills on the White House web site for five days before signing them. We are still waiting liar Obama.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363878431403</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:07:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363878455979-87</Id><Title>Obama promised to have the congressional health care negotiations broadcast live on C-SPAN.</Title><Msg>Another Obama lie.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363878455979</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:07:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363878548778-88</Id><Title>Obama promised to end earmarks.</Title><Msg>Obama promised to end earmarks. He has more now than ever. Harry Reid and Pelosi are king &amp; queen of earmarks.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363878548778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:09:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363878581389-89</Id><Title>Obama promised to make peace with direct, no precondition talks with Americas most hate-filled enemies</Title><Msg>Obama promised to make peace with direct, no precondition talks with Americas most hate-filled enemies during his first year in office, ushering in a new era of global cooperation.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363878581389</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:09:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363878607134-90</Id><Topic><Title>It’s hard to think of a president that has been more of an Epic Failure than President Obama.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363876082666</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must have a pea for a brain. First Isn't this message board supposed to be about Cisco Systems Stock?? Second, Hawaii is in the middle of the Pacific Ocean, not real close to Asia as you indicate. Regardless, Hawaii is STILL a state in the United States of America? I bet you would say that Alaska was in Asia too, Alaska being a lot closer to Asia that Hawaii is?? Take your right wing political #$%$ to somewhere else. This message board is intended for information about Cisco, not your intense dislike for President Obama. Get a brain and GROW UP!</Msg><Username>hughes1953</Username><Timestamp>1363878607134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:10:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363878646367-91</Id><Topic><Title>SO BAMA INHERITED A MESS? REALLY? WELL</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363876230735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:30:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Illegal aliens and Obama voters defaulting on the mortgages crashed the economy. Obama has no solution just empty promises. Obama has prolonged what should have been a short and naturally occurring business cycle recession into a continuing global depression that is progressively getting worse.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363878646367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363878652282-92</Id><Title>Obama promised to end no-compete contracts with the government.</Title><Msg>Just another whopper lie by Obama.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363878652282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:10:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363878758832-93</Id><Title>Obama promised for a new era of bipartisan cooperation in all matters.</Title><Msg>Obama has totally divided the country we all love. Shame on him.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363878758832</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:12:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363878788983-94</Id><Topic><Title>SO BAMA INHERITED A MESS? REALLY? WELL</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363876230735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:30:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL so "huge1953" (no typo), are you an ignorant Obama koolaid guzzler or what!?! His point is Obama took a thriving economy that was a little weak at the time and MADE IT TEN TIMES WORSE by adding MORE TAXES and ASTRONOMICAL UNemployment! Nice try DOOFUS!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363878788983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:13:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363878828223-95</Id><Title>Obama promised to have chosen a home church to attend Sunday services with his family by Easter of last year.</Title><Msg>What re-join Rev. Wrights church of hate he was a member at for 20 years.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363878828223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363878834078-96</Id><Topic><Title>It’s hard to think of a president that has been more of an Epic Failure than President Obama.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363876082666</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buddy, you have been brainwashed by #$%$ and you swallowed all of it. BBWHHAHHAHHAHHHAHHAAAAA!!! Obama was born in Jakarta like his sister Maya who also has a Hawaiian birth certificate too. Barry has Lolo's big ears.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363878834078</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:13:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363878907841-97</Id><Title>ge up csco down fpos stock sucks today never go green that a no brainer sad but #$%$ you</Title><Msg>s</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363878907841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363878985701-98</Id><Topic><Title>In 2008 Obama promised to close the detention center at Guantanamo in the first year.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363878396007</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:06:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am hoping for the best. *** BWHHWHHWHHAHAHHAHHAHHA!!!! YOU GO $GIRL. MUP$PET POWER. Put the pants on and bend over!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363878985701</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:16:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363879107812-99</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA BOOED IN ISRAEL AS HE CRITICIZES THEM FOR</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363878132627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:02:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama getting booed everywhere he goes. His appoval just hit 3 month low.</Msg><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363879107812</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:18:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363879111325-100</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA BOOED IN ISRAEL AS HE CRITICIZES THEM FOR</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363878132627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:02:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes yohoho, but then we can't expect a mooslum to understand or appreciate the Israelies. Could Armageddon happen under Oloser? YES</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363879111325</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:18:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363879203869-101</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA MADE A MESS OF OUR COUTRY.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363878936912</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:15:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did he have to #$%$ all over the beautiful usa? *** He spewed #$%$ that people wanted to here so he could win. He said anything to get elected. Dr. Stone, you correctly diagnosed Obama as being afflicted with narcissistic personality disorder. Time for Barry to check into the Mayo Clinic. He needs an intervention. Let Biden take over. He's known Bibi for years!!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363879203869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:20:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363879572955-102</Id><Title>Investor Relations Department</Title><Msg>Investor Relations Department Cisco Systems, Inc. 170 West Tasman Drive San Jose, CA 95134-1706 USA Phone: (408) 227-CSCO Fax: (408) 853-3683</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363879572955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:26:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363879609041-103</Id><Topic><Title>Investor Relations Department</Title><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363879572955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:26:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phone: (408) 227-CSCO</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363879609041</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363879949934-104</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA MADE A MESS OF OUR COUTRY.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363878936912</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:15:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to find a purpose in life. constantly spreading your senseless gibberish over these boards is a waste of everyone's time!</Msg><Username>jen.co44</Username><Timestamp>1363879949934</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:32:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363880289733-105</Id><Title>Oracl miss was DUE to a new product launch and customers waiting to buy... This has nothing to do</Title><Msg>with csco. ORCL earnings were negatively impacted more by currency exchange rates than soft business. They actually had record earnings and FCF, these down grades are bogus. The new oracl cloud platform goes from 8 processors to 32, which would you buy? That and the fact oracle only gets 8% of sales from hardware to begin with.</Msg><Username>burnaka</Username><Timestamp>1363880289733</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:38:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363880393865-106</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA MADE A MESS OF OUR COUTRY.</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363878936912</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:15:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jen....shhhhhhhh, you need to be quiet now....like a little mouse, soo soooo quiet now..shhhhhh</Msg><Username>adolphlhitler</Username><Timestamp>1363880393865</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:39:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363880500294-107</Id><Title>drstone posts- adolphlhitler answers- seems appropriate !</Title><Msg>LMAO!!</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363880500294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363880739703-108</Id><Topic><Title>drstone posts- adolphlhitler answers- seems appropriate !</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363880500294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you "winkipuss" get offended for "Jen"....HMMMMMMM! LOL!</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363880739703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:45:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363880808280-109</Id><Topic><Title>drstone posts- adolphlhitler answers- seems appropriate !</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363880500294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you douchebag !</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363880808280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363880959008-110</Id><Topic><Title>drstone posts- adolphlhitler answers- seems appropriate !</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363880500294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol and btw, how is that #$%$ Jen? I haven't seen it for a couple days! MEOOOOWWW</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363880959008</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:49:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363880978036-111</Id><Topic><Title>drstone posts- adolphlhitler answers- seems appropriate !</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363880500294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumbivan was here posting that both Hitler and Mao weren't as bad as Bush .Winkipus should move to another subject.LOL Embarrassing the libs.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363880978036</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:49:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363881208098-112</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA BOOED IN ISRAEL AS HE CRITICIZES THEM FOR</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363878132627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:02:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets face it, Obama dealing with foreign policy is what you get when you elect an incompetent community organsizing, voting "present" senator based on racism.</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363881208098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:53:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363881209849-113</Id><Topic><Title>drstone posts- adolphlhitler answers- seems appropriate !</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363880500294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Must have made my point. Libs start calling you names when they lose.LOL</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363881209849</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:53:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363881233586-114</Id><Topic><Title>drstone posts- adolphlhitler answers- seems appropriate !</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363880500294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who's Jen ? Jennifer McCarthy ?Jennifer Lopez?</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363881233586</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:53:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363881256560-115</Id><Title>this is rotten news from pin heads at fbr</Title><Msg>Cisco Systems (NASDAQ:CSCO) and Juniper Networks (NYSE:JNPR) shares faced some issues when FBR Capital Markets Analyst Scott Thompson cut his ratings to Underperform, or the equivalent of sell, from market perform, on both companies, as he believes that both companies will likely face challenges in offsetting weaker-than-expected demand for routing and switching products as they transition to more software and services business models. Also, Thompson decided to reduce his price target to $17 a share from $22 on Cisco, and he cut Juniper’s outlook to $15 a share from $18, MarketWatch reported.</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363881256560</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:54:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363881598248-116</Id><Title>Today's "serial adulterer", example</Title><Msg>Newt Gingrich Underscores NOM’s Hypocrisy and Desperation By: Alvin McEwen Wednesday March 20, 2013 7:20 am As the National Organization gets ready for its march, the group can’t stop tripping over itself with embarrassment. Today’s example – Newt Gingrich. NOM posted a video clip of Newt Gingrich speaking about Sen. Rob Portman. Portman, a conservative Republican senator, recently revealed that he now supports marriage equality because of his relationship with his gay son. In a blog post, NOM celebrates the fact that Gingrich said marriage should be between a man and a woman. However in Gingrich’s case, that should be a man and three women. Remember, Gingrich divorced his first wife of 18 years after an affair with another woman. He subsequently married this woman but divorced her after 12 years and had an affair with another woman whom he is now currently married to. NOM is using this guy to defend marriage? This guy? Seriously? A commentator to NOM’s blog put it better than I ever could: It’s difficult to underestimate the sheer bare-faced chutzpah of this man and the fawning reverence paid to him by NOM and others, the outright cognitive dissonance it takes to believe that marriage is between one and one woman FOR LIFE and then to say he is an exemplar and supporter of marriage. He isn’t. He is a destroyer of families, the very core of NOM’s arguments. I would have more respect if there was at least one word addressing this hypocrisy.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363881598248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363881811233-117</Id><Topic><Title>Today's "serial adulterer", example</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363881598248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:59:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two words for gfo99 ----------Bill Clinton</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363881811233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:03:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363881987815-118</Id><Title>OBAMA'S GIRLFIREND GENEVIEVE COOK</Title><Msg>he wrote about her because she has made such a lingering impact on his mind...She writes about him in her diary which has recently been published.. So evidently he is BI. We can only hope Larry Sinlair doesn't read it.</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363881987815</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363882092674-119</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA'S GIRLFIREND GENEVIEVE COOK</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363881987815</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:06:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>by the way....did I mention she is WHITE?</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1363882092674</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:08:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363882223538-120</Id><Title>never see 21.05 again that was my cost sold at 20.90 stop out #$%$ you</Title><Msg>suck</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363882223538</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:10:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363882315469-121</Id><Title>CA will be next to fall the way of europe.</Title><Msg>San Bernadino is bankrupt but they approve pay raises for gov union thugs</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363882315469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:11:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363882367543-122</Id><Title>I BLAME OBAMA FOR THE FACT I AM STUCK ON THIS MESSAGE BOARD!!</Title><Msg>I BLAME OBAMA FOR THE FACT I AM STUCK ON THIS MESSAGE BOARD!! I also blame him for the fact that I .. Flunked out of special ed in high school That I am impotent That my belly makes me look pregnant That my IQ is low That I was too stupid to get in on GE at its low That I am full of resentment that Romney lost because smarter Democrats That I have to continue to create multiple ID's because each of my post are always more stupid than the last. That my mom left my dad for a black man That this board consumes my life</Msg><Username>dumbpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363882367543</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363882384413-123</Id><Title>never see 21.05 again done this fpos day</Title><Msg>ok</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363882384413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:13:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363882541744-124</Id><Title>The Life of deadpainting.....</Title><Msg>The Life of deadpainting..... The last thing that he does each night is to make sure that the orderly understands that he must be up before the first lib. Once up in the morning he removes his rubber pants and his urine soaked diaper and without showering he slaps on a clean extra absorbent adult diaper for a full day of trolling for lib attention. He checks his spiral notebook to decide which alias would draw the most attention and makes his choice. To start the morning he chooses carey or ivan because that was yesterdays poster that gave him a half chubby before he slipped into his alcoholic coma and went to sleep the night before. He has a couple of orderlies use the hydraulic lift to host his fat body out of bed and into the wheelchair so his day can begin as if has for the last 6 years. Life for this loser never changes. He knows that he's a loser, but at his age he's just marking time now. It won't be long now and he'll have a stroke or a coronary. He gets no exercise other than the tips of his fingers. He hasn't seen his feet in years. He lost his teeth years ago and today it's just a diet of pudding, oatmeal and a string of 2 liter sodas. What people are witnessing is a broke-down backwater hayseed trolling for any kind of attention people will give him. Just the type of person your primary teachers warned you about if you dropped out of school. What a pathetic loser!!</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363882541744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:15:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363882920032-125</Id><Topic><Title>never see 21.05 again done this fpos day</Title><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363882384413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:13:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>john refused to help today</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363882920032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:22:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363883026231-126</Id><Title>The Life of Junior</Title><Msg>Flitting from board to board using hundreds of ids seeking attention. Makes feeble attempts at humor which always fall flat. Guy is just an obnoxious loser who deserves every ones pity.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363883026231</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363883210480-127</Id><Title>hpq higher now csco pos never go green today orcl went up 50 cent since i bought sold csco thank god</Title><Msg>ok</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363883210480</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:26:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363883233652-128</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA BOOED IN ISRAEL AS HE CRITICIZES THEM FOR</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1363878132627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:02:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah and look how many jewish americans voted for him. Israel knows he isn't their friend</Msg><Username>albacornus</Username><Timestamp>1363883233652</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:27:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363883264745-129</Id><Topic><Title>The Life of Junior</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363883026231</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:23:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have been prepared for this for some time now. I dug a 12' deep bunker with corrugated steel roof and 4 feet of concrete poured walls and top. I also took the precaution to load up on kyptonite in case the aliens decide to side with the liberals. I strung garlic around the bunker door and nailed a huge cross on the door. I purchased the extra strength aluminum foil and put 23 layers on my army surplus steel helmet.. I can't even count how much ammunition I got and am putting some silver tip bullets up just in case Obama is a Shape-shifter</Msg><Username>carey50fairy</Username><Timestamp>1363883264745</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:27:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363883286847-130</Id><Topic><Title>The Life of deadpainting.....</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363882541744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:15:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't pick on my friend!</Msg><Username>carey50fairy</Username><Timestamp>1363883286847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:28:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363883386779-131</Id><Topic><Title>The Life of deadpainting.....</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363882541744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:15:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just back from the gym, you nailed it, LOL thanks for the laughs</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363883386779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:29:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363883426014-132</Id><Topic><Title>The Life of Junior</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363883026231</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:23:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for confirming what I said about your " humor " LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL OH, BOY. OH,JEEZ!!!!OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOPSIE!! HEEHEEHEEHEEHEEHEE</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363883426014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363883444614-133</Id><Title>never ever see 21.00 again today that it good luck</Title><Msg>or</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363883444614</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363883516088-134</Id><Topic><Title>The Life of deadpainting.....</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363882541744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:15:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Gym" is lib codeword for bathhouse. LOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363883516088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363884173724-135</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO starting to move higher!</Title><Username>lucadobson</Username><Timestamp>1362659226270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 07:27:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>important info</Msg><Username>stark_b</Username><Timestamp>1363884173724</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:42:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363884674602-136</Id><Title>CHAMBERS JOHN T 2,623,660 Sep 10, 2012</Title><Msg>CHAMBERS JOHN T 2,623,660 Sep 10, 2012</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363884674602</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363884866233-137</Id><Title>Junior steps in it again</Title><Msg>Best thing Obama has done as prez is kill a lot of Al-Qaeda with drones. So today Junior pipes up with " Bush started the drone program". LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL Thanks for giving Bush an attaboy, Junior. HEEHEHEEHEEHEEHEE WHAT AN EFFING MORON !!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363884866233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:54:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363884917488-138</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR CSCO BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT</Title><Username>brunogreen109</Username><Timestamp>1362328379111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:32:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good</Msg><Username>wworren</Username><Timestamp>1363884917488</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:55:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363884993744-139</Id><Title>intc is higher than csco both at 21.05 in morning intc better stock that a no brainer csco will never see 21.05 today again</Title><Msg>ok</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363884993744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:56:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363885540560-140</Id><Title>watch going down all day now sell move on from it never buy it again rotten wall street and fbr rot in hell</Title><Msg>#$%$</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363885540560</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:05:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363885845161-141</Id><Topic><Title>Junior steps in it again</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363884866233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:54:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hard for Junior to concentrate while fantasizing about his tongue being six inches up Obama's fanny.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363885845161</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:10:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363885943192-142</Id><Title>do not buy this stock you be sorry</Title><Msg>ok</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363885943192</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:12:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363885993538-143</Id><Topic><Title>New Pope &amp; Obama Joke! LOL!</Title><Username>drstone3</Username><Timestamp>1363872944645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:35:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sddd</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363885993538</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:13:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363886047743-144</Id><Topic><Title>GOP BASHING POINT: ANYONE CAN BEAT OBAMA - MAJOR FAIL!!!!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1362068812081</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 11:26:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hhh</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363886047743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:14:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363886197104-145</Id><Title>this stock sucks never see 21.05 again my cost fpos stock thank god sold it never buy again</Title><Msg>sucks</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363886197104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:16:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363886249870-146</Id><Title>ron.wallach is lost and is on the wrong messageboard</Title><Msg>we forgive you ron.wallach</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363886249870</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:17:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363886265799-147</Id><Topic><Title>do not buy this stock you be sorry</Title><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363885943192</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:12:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your right</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363886265799</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:17:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363886406975-148</Id><Title>wall street #$%$ rot in hell cause loss today f sucks</Title><Msg>ok</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363886406975</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:20:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363886409069-149</Id><Topic><Title>ron.wallach is lost and is on the wrong messageboard</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363886249870</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:17:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are lost and in the wrong world.Lalaland is some place else, not here,Loser.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363886409069</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:20:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363887271662-150</Id><Title>Whatever happened to gun control ?</Title><Msg>Board loons pretty quiet about the assault gun ban.Did Harry Reid stab you guys in the back ??</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363887271662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363887283654-151</Id><Title>Please provide evidence that a bigger government would have the negative effects you state</Title><Msg>Please provide evidence that a bigger government would have the negative effects you state. Our history shows the opposite to be the case. When capitalism was left to do as it pleased, we have slavery, indentured servitude, debtors prisons, child labor, sweat shops and a whole host of Social Darwinist horrors. Also Enron! The more its been regulated, the better the lives for most Americans have become. There is no evidence to support your belief that more government means bad things will happen. Of course, we need to be vigilant about what government does and doesn't do. Like ending our wars, reversing the privatization of everything including the prison system. But good government will improve quality of life. Its absence will just make plutocrats fat and happy</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363887283654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363887410017-152</Id><Title>sad day</Title><Msg>sad</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363887410017</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:36:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363887612130-153</Id><Topic><Title>sad day</Title><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363887410017</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Roy, go home now. Time for you to go home !</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363887612130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:40:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363887718836-154</Id><Title>only get stock up is 20 billion buy back to22</Title><Msg>ok</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363887718836</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:41:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363888407354-155</Id><Title>Now we will see what happens when the dog catches the bus, LOL</Title><Msg>Senate Democrats will force a vote on the House-passed budget crafted by Rep. Paul Ryan to make a political point. Democrats noted that Senate Republicans, after praising the Ryan budget, didn’t try to introduce a version of it in the Senate. So they’re going to introduce it themselves. The House passed the Ryan plan, which tries to balance the budget in the long term by cutting spending, repealing Obamacare, and overhauling Medicare while avoiding any tax increases, Thursday morning on a mostly party-line vote.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363888407354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:53:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363888424503-156</Id><Topic><Title>only get stock up is 20 billion buy back to22</Title><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363887718836</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:41:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they aren't going to use al that cash for new products or acquisitions they should use it to buy back stock whihc is currently way under valued. O/s shares are too many.</Msg><Username>hairytoadus01</Username><Timestamp>1363888424503</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:53:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363888458869-157</Id><Topic><Title>Whatever happened to gun control ?</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363887271662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:34:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tea billies love fetuses, children not so much</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363888458869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363888503004-158</Id><Title>GOP supports ownership of ASSAULT WEAPONS in every home!!!!!</Title><Msg>A magazine CLIP on every table!</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363888503004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:55:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363889178012-159</Id><Title>21.50 CSCO130322P00021500 0.73 Up 0.67 0.71 0.73 2,216 4,625 this why it down</Title><Msg>21.50 CSCO130322P00021500 0.73 Up 0.67 0.71 0.73 2,216 4,625</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363889178012</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:06:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363889274110-160</Id><Title>Ben Carson for President, LOL</Title><Msg>This would be great, the racist tea baggers won't vote for him cause he is black and the blacks won't vote for him cause he is GOP, this would be the end of the GOP, Maybe a Carson, Palin ticket, the dream ticket, LOL Overnight, he was embraced by conservatives including those at The Wall Street Journal editorial page, which proclaimed, “Ben Carson for President” — a suggestion Dr. Carson helped feed at a high-profile gathering last weekend, the Conservative Political Action Conference. He was interrupted by sustained cheers when he coyly said, “Let’s just say if you magically put me in the White House...” In an interview in his office at Johns Hopkins University, he said he had been told for years that he could have a political career. It would be built on his compelling personal story that began in poverty in Detroit, leading to fame through pioneering work separating conjoined twins and his own self-help and inspirational books, including “America the Beautiful: Rediscovering What Made This Nation Great.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363889274110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:07:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363889513828-161</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO starting to move higher!</Title><Username>lucadobson</Username><Timestamp>1362659226270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 07:27:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very nice article!</Msg><Username>bakos_david</Username><Timestamp>1363889513828</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:11:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363889828176-162</Id><Topic><Title>IF YOU THINK the Obama Market is Down today, JUST WAIT</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1356633902055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 13:45:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior loves the Obama market. BUY THE DIP BUY THE DIP BUY THE DIP "Business sentiment and confidence is way down. People are more cautious right now in business than they are in the stock market. That's how we get very high valuation multiples on stocks, but businesses are pulling back</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363889828176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363890010065-163</Id><Topic><Title>Whatever happened to gun control ?</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363887271662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:34:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gubmint bankruptcy and shutdown is a higher priority. Chicago has toughest gun control laws in the country and it solves nothing. The Obama voter drug dealers will keep on being animals.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363890010065</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:20:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363890321773-164</Id><Title>SMASHING COCKROACHES IS.......</Title><Msg>sort of like solving the Democrat problem...but not quite. Democrats have many similarities however, and are equally hard to convert to sane, rational folk. It can be done, but requires a great deal of electro-shock therapy and frontal readjustment. Brain training is useful when the Democrat is off his drugs long enough to be almost sober. Job therapy is the most effective but the hardest procedure to use in Democrat re-programming. Any sort of labor, including thoughtful analysis is hard for a Democrat and cattle prods are useful in on the job training when the Democrat sits down again, for the 15th time in the past hour, or when, at the keyboard, their eyes glaze over and they begin to drool!!! They need a lot of management...</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363890321773</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:25:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363890353558-165</Id><Title>GOP says don't raise taxes on the multirich,cut programs for the poor.Who cares about the poor.</Title><Msg>House passes GOP budget plan promising deep cuts Mar 21, 12:22 PM (ET) By ANDREW TAYLOR WASHINGTON (AP) - The Republican-controlled House passed a tea party-flavored budget plan Thursday that promises sharp cuts in safety-net programs for the poor and a clampdown on domestic agencies, in sharp contrast to less austere plans favored by President Barack Obama and his Democratic allies. The measure, similar to previous plans offered by Budget Committee Chairman Paul Ryan, R-Wis., demonstrates that it's possible, at least mathematically, to balance the budget within a decade without raising taxes. But its deep cuts to programs for the poor like Medicaid and food stamps and its promise to abolish so-called "Obamacare" are nonstarters with the president, who won re-election while campaigning against Ryan's prior budgets. It passed on a mostly party-line 221-207 vote. The House measure advanced as the Democratic Senate debated its first budget since the 2009 plan that helped Obama pass his health care law. The dueling House and Senate budget plans are anchored on opposite ends of the ideological spectrum in Washington, appealing to core partisans in the warring parties that are gridlocked over persistent budget deficits. Obama is exploring the chances of forging a middle path that blends new taxes and modest curbs to government benefit programs. "The president has an opportunity during this critical debate to come forward and to help make this part of his legacy, like it has become part of the Clinton legacy: working together on behalf of the American people to solve what we know is a crisis in our country," said House Speaker John Boehner, R-Ohio. He was referring to President Bill Clinton's success in working with a GOP Congress to generate budget surpluses over 1998-2001. "We can't continue to spend money that we don't h</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1363890353558</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363890579519-166</Id><Topic><Title>GOP supports ownership of ASSAULT WEAPONS in every home!!!!!</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363888503004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fff</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363890579519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:29:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363890706854-167</Id><Title>YES...TEA PARTY DOES not SUPPORT HIGHER TAXES, ON RICH OR 'POOR'...AND YES, TEA PARTY DOES</Title><Msg>support gun ownership...and yes the Tea Party does favor cutting all the entitlement programs...so that way, 'poor' people begin to take care of themselves and become rich people!! Instead of remaining in entitlement prison, whining that others buy their booze, beer, cigs, food, pay their rent and buy their condoms.....really?</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363890706854</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:31:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363890809690-168</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush started the drone assassination program</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363888475542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:54:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so do you support the drone program? Since Bush started, I mean. So was Bush smarter than Obama? I guess you think so, or at least that seems to be your analysis...on the other hand, everyone is smarter than Obimbo, the Doofus Goober.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363890809690</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:33:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363891124174-169</Id><Topic><Title>if jesus were alive today, walter would refuse to sit next to him on a plane</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363891062090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:37:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he'd profile him for being an arab terrorist !</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363891124174</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:38:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363891183926-170</Id><Topic><Title>YES...TEA PARTY DOES not SUPPORT HIGHER TAXES, ON RICH OR 'POOR'...AND YES, TEA PARTY DOES</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363890706854</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:31:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course it exempts the pentagon. We have lived in a military state since Nov 1963. Anybody who thinks this joke of a government is a democracy needs to take their pacifier out of their mouth and grow up fast.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1363891183926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:39:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363892213311-171</Id><Title>A fire ball of a stock in the last hour of today's stagnant market (OCLR)</Title><Msg>About to</Msg><Username>chase4money</Username><Timestamp>1363892213311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363892463225-172</Id><Topic><Title>A fire ball of a stock in the last hour of today's stagnant market (OCLR)</Title><Username>chase4money</Username><Timestamp>1363892213311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:56:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo! Inc. (YHOO) -NasdaqGS 22.85 Up 0.75(3.40%) 2:57PM EDT - Nasdaq Real Time Price</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363892463225</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363892896747-173</Id><Title>Benny stealing money</Title><Msg>“At this stage of a recovery normalized interest rates should be around 2-3%,” says Rickards. “Apply that 2-3%…to the entire multi-trillion-dollar deposit base of the United States of America and that’s a $400-billion per year wealth transfer from savers to bankers so they can pay themselves bigger bonuses or make crazy bets.” Over time, Rickards says, that wealth transfer could reach $1 trillion. Rickards says zero interest rates are just one way the Fed is fleecing depositors. Others include increasing inflation, which Bernanke is trying to do, and taxing deposits like Cyprus is pushing for. “Bernanke is stealing more money from depositors than Cyprus is... looting everyday Americans—teachers, firemen and retirees,” says Rickards.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363892896747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:08:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363893007164-174</Id><Topic><Title>A fire ball of a stock in the last hour of today's stagnant market (OCLR)</Title><Username>chase4money</Username><Timestamp>1363892213311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:56:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ron, you suk !!!</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363893007164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:10:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363893133787-175</Id><Topic><Title>YES...TEA PARTY DOES not SUPPORT HIGHER TAXES, ON RICH OR 'POOR'...AND YES, TEA PARTY DOES</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363890706854</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:31:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok, Surfy, I'm with you...the Defense budget should be cut like all of the Federal budget...I'd cut everything 2-3% every year for 10 years...furthermore, I'd have Federal hiring freeze and not replace ANY Federal employee who retires...once you've got the Federal work force down by 25% via natural retirement...then you can consider new hires..... Federal government is out of control.....your future is threatened by those bozo's...</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363893133787</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:12:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363893307783-176</Id><Topic><Title>GOP supports ownership of ASSAULT WEAPONS in every home!!!!!</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363888503004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>uuu</Msg><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363893307783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363893334743-177</Id><Title>WHAT THEY'RE SAYING ABOUT DRSTONE'S 5 YEARS OF TOTAL INSANITY ON GE</Title><Msg>-- drstone last post was at 2 a.m after more than 18 hours of posting and his first was at 6 a.m. "It's a scientific fact that people that suffer from mental illness rarely sleep more than four hours in a single span. It's one of the main reason mental hospital hospitals sedate their patients and keep them from roaming. Take the mentally ill person that calls himself drstone (no doubt after his therapist) for a prime example. Here's a person that anyone who as ever visited this board for more than two minutes knows with certainty that this person is clinically insane. And like the vast majority of mentally ill people that are obsessed with a certain object or individual drstone is obsessed with posting politics all day and night that consumes his entire life." "You will find people that aren't suffering from a mental disorder may discuss their politics with a passion and move on with their lives five minuts after the political discussion has ended, but not drstone. Drstone is not passionate with his politics like a normal person would be, he is menatlly disturbed. Anyone that would spend their entire awake moments so obsessed with posting is not normal. This is a person that is in desperate need of some serious psychotherapy." "There should be no doubt in your mind that he is suffering from schizophrenia. And for those that wish to engage him to express a point or a proven fact relating to reality might just as well be talking to a piece of chalk. You just are never going to get through to a mentally deranged person (THINK ABOUT IT) Sometimes even professionals have to throw in the towel knowing full well that some people are just beyond help and can do nothing but medicate them to prevent them from hurting themselves or those around them." "The best thing people can do is realize that he is insane and place him on ignore. He'll move on to other boards where after a short period of time they too will realize that they are arguing with the insane.</Msg><Username>russelltrader12</Username><Timestamp>1363893334743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:15:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363893358097-178</Id><Topic><Title>SMASHING COCKROACHES IS.......</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363890321773</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:25:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this needs to be read over and over and over, in front of every high school economics class!!! Using a cattle prod sounds like the perfect solution to our constipated Senate!!!!</Msg><Username>schnitlerbeim</Username><Timestamp>1363893358097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:15:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363893758851-179</Id><Topic><Title>SMASHING COCKROACHES IS.......</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363890321773</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:25:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup, we do need to move more Democrats to Cuba. They need more hard labor for sugar cane. It is good for Democrats to fall into a coma in the sugar cane plantation after six hours of hard work!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363893758851</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:22:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363893824531-180</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush started the drone assassination program</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363888475542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:54:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has followed Bush's direction on Iraq and Afghanistan as well as the war on terror.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363893824531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:23:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363894131607-181</Id><Topic><Title>A fire ball of a stock in the last hour of today's stagnant market (OCLR)</Title><Username>chase4money</Username><Timestamp>1363892213311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:56:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most popular are the April 20 and 21 puts, which have seen around 28,400 and 17,800 contracts cross the tape, respectively. Volume has exceeded open interest at both strikes, and the majority of the soon-to-be front-month puts traded on the ask side, pointing to buy-to-open activity. More specifically, the volume-weighted average price (VWAP) of the 20-strike puts is $0.11, meaning the buyers will profit if CSCO breaches the $19.89 level (strike price minus VWAP) within the next month or so. Meanwhile, the VWAP of the 21-strike puts is $0.31, indicating a breakeven of $20.69 for the buyers. As alluded to earlier, though, these option "bears" could be CSCO shareholders in disguise. By purchasing puts against their long stock positions, the buyers lock in an acceptable sale price (the strikes) for their CSCO shares, should the equity take a turn for the worse in the near term. Regardless of motive, today's preference for puts marks a change of pace among CSCO's options crowd. On the International Securities Exchange (ISE), Chicago Board Options Exchange (CBOE), and NASDAQ OMX PHLX (PHLX), traders have bought to open more than three calls for every put during the past two weeks. In fact, the stock's 10-day call/put volume ratio of 3.53 ranks in the 80th percentile of its annual range, suggesting option buyers have initiated bullish bets over bearish at a faster-than-usual pace. At last check, CSCO has given up 0.2% to linger in the $21.62 ballpark. So far this week, the security has surrendered about 0.8%, after touching a two-year acme of $21.98 on Monday.</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363894131607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:28:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363894223656-182</Id><Topic><Title>IF YOU THINK the Obama Market is Down today, JUST WAIT</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1356633902055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 13:45:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for buying the dip Junior.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363894223656</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:30:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363894402255-183</Id><Topic><Title>GOP says don't raise taxes on the multirich,cut programs for the poor.Who cares about the poor.</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1363890353558</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are 50% on the hand out now how much more can we stand?</Msg><Username>doely_1</Username><Timestamp>1363894402255</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:33:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363894564789-184</Id><Topic><Title>Benny stealing money</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363892896747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:08:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Richards is correct once Benny counterfits enough $ for his banker brothers he'll start unwinding, it has nothing to do with the economy just transfer of wealth to his type</Msg><Username>jen.co44</Username><Timestamp>1363894564789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363894654746-185</Id><Topic><Title>Now we will see what happens when the dog catches the bus, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363888407354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:53:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Ryan can get just one vote on his budget he'll do better than Obama EVER did on his.Ooooopsie.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363894654746</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:37:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363894987689-186</Id><Title>bankers lined their pockets with savers money</Title><Msg>thanks benny. biggest scam and tax in history fed printing. good luck 60 somthing. hope you have enough dog food to last 40 more years.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363894987689</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:43:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363895115442-187</Id><Topic><Title>Benny stealing money</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363892896747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:08:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it will kill savers and retierees. this is the greatest scam in history trillions given to bankers to fix the mess they caused.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363895115442</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363895193053-188</Id><Topic><Title>Now we will see what happens when the dog catches the bus, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363888407354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:53:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So true!! Obimbo has yet to post a budget...he is quite infatuated with being President still and has yet to learn how to actually govern...he likes Executive Orders, since they are much like Imperial Decrees....the man is an absolute clown...really....a clown. He ought to be in Circ de Soleil....the land of loony...</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363895193053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:46:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363895304575-189</Id><Topic><Title>Benny stealing money</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363892896747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:08:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its the Mother of all PONZIS</Msg><Username>jen.co44</Username><Timestamp>1363895304575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:48:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363895384647-190</Id><Title>Crammer</Title><Msg>hahahaha remember when the markets were at lows and ben announce QE. he was dancing around with his sound bites like an idiot court jesture saying he knows nothing. hahahahah now he say ben is genius. look out this is about to back fire. crammer knows nothing. ask yourself if he is so smart why is he not rich trading stocks? instead he is on tv dancing around like an idiot.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363895384647</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363895391054-191</Id><Title>DOES IT MATTER IF OBIMBO'S GALLUP RATING NOW AT 46%????</Title><Msg>MAYBE... It only matters if the Senate collapses into Democratic doo too</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363895391054</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:49:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363895522322-192</Id><Title>ARE DEMOCRATS MORE POPULAR THAN DYSENTERY?</Title><Msg>in some places.....San Francisco is one, where diarrhea is a very important business....</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363895522322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363895579356-193</Id><Topic><Title>GOP supports ownership of ASSAULT WEAPONS in every home!!!!!</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363888503004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good keep you mooches from taking our stuff.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363895579356</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363895684618-194</Id><Title>Tough Day For White CSCO Owners!,..</Title><Msg>I Told Y'all In July 2010 To Trade Your CSCO For Halliburton When They Were Both $22.22! Oh Well?,..</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363895684618</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:54:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363895732770-195</Id><Topic><Title>Junior steps in it again</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363884866233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:54:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Junior, tell us again about how all them bad Al-Qaeda guys killed in the last five years was because of the great George Bush.LOLOLOOLOLOLOLOL OH BOY, OH JEEZ!!!.!!! DID YOU REALLY STICK YOUR FOOT IN YOUR MOUTH THIS TIME!! !HEEHEEHEEHEEHEE</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363895732770</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:55:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363895856186-196</Id><Title>what consequence came from the end of BUBBLE$?</Title><Msg>TELL ME NOW</Msg><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1363895856186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:57:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363895876129-197</Id><Title>Ivan, a three-way at my house tonight; you me and dead !</Title><Msg>will be a lot of fun !</Msg><Username>carey50fairy</Username><Timestamp>1363895876129</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:57:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363895889783-198</Id><Title>Bernanke Said, "We'll Adjust Rates When Unemployment Stays @ 6.5% For 3 Months'!,...</Title><Msg>Now Let's See If Pukes Block Another Jobs Bill!,..</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363895889783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363895991615-199</Id><Topic><Title>GOP supports ownership of ASSAULT WEAPONS in every home!!!!!</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363888503004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't be late to the 3 way !</Msg><Username>carey50fairy</Username><Timestamp>1363895991615</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:59:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363896306545-200</Id><Topic><Title>Ivan, a three-way at my house tonight; you me and dead !</Title><Username>carey50fairy</Username><Timestamp>1363895876129</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't be late!</Msg><Username>carey50fairy</Username><Timestamp>1363896306545</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:05:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363896323730-201</Id><Topic><Title>ARE DEMOCRATS MORE POPULAR THAN DYSENTERY?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363895522322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:52:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior has a constant anal drip due to his absolutely disgusting sexual practices.LOLOLOLOL His sphincter muscle has been jammed into the bottom of his stomach.LOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363896323730</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363896382698-202</Id><Topic><Title>ARE DEMOCRATS MORE POPULAR THAN DYSENTERY?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363895522322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:52:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>remember to make full use of your sphincter muscles tonght!</Msg><Username>carey50fairy</Username><Timestamp>1363896382698</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:06:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363896605300-203</Id><Title>GOOGLE: "L-curve", Watch: "Zeitgeist", "Capitalism Hits The Fan", "Money as Debt"</Title><Msg>Then Maybe Some Of You FOX NEWS Zombies Will Begin To Understand Who Screwed Who!,. Follow The Money!,...</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363896605300</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:10:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363896716332-204</Id><Topic><Title>Benny stealing money</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363892896747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:08:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Options players from both sides of the trading aisle are flocking to Cisco Systems, Inc. (NASDAQ:CSCO - 20.94) today, despite the stock falling 3.4% after some negative analyst attention. Specifically, FBR Capital downgraded CSCO to "underperform" from "market perform," and lowered its price target to $17 from $22. Nevertheless, roughly 24,000 calls have crossed the tape so far, more than doubling the equity's expected intraday call volume. Meanwhile, approximately 28,000 puts have changed hands, which is quadruple the norm. On the bullish end of the spectrum, speculators have zeroed in on the April 21 call, where nearly 3,300 contracts have traded at a volume-weighted average price (VWAP) of $0.39. The majority of them were exchanged at the ask price, and implied volatility was last seen 3.4 percentage points higher -- hinting at buy-to-open activity. If these calls were, in fact, bought to open, traders are hoping CSCO will rise north of breakeven at $21.39 (strike price plus the VWAP) by front-month expiration.</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363896716332</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:11:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363896717988-205</Id><Title>Is That What You White Trash Are Calling Romney Now., "Dysentery"?</Title><Msg>Wow You Ignorant Filth Are Sore Losers!,..</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363896717988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:11:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363896865466-206</Id><Topic><Title>GOOGLE: "L-curve", Watch: "Zeitgeist", "Capitalism Hits The Fan", "Money as Debt"</Title><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363896605300</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:10:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "L-curve" MORON!</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363896865466</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:14:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363897083212-207</Id><Title>Hey Santelli! If You Want To End QE Then Tell Your Puke Buddies To Pass The Jobs Bill!,..</Title><Msg>Senate Republicans Block Another Jobs Bill, Face Backlash From American Public,.... The method Republicans have used to block all jobs legislation in the past two years is the same. A jobs bill comes up, it is filled with positive things for the economy, Republicans filibuster debate, this shields them from having to make floor speeches on why they don't want tax breaks for small businesses... etc. Why? Well, if the economy recovers too strongly before an election, Republicans will lose power. If jobs numbers look too good, people will want to keep the same party. By Republicans blocking all jobs legislation and keeping jobs numbers from improving they believe this is their ticket to power. In other words, if you and other Americans suffer just long enough it will pay off for Republicans. They sacrifice the citizens' jobs with the hopes that they will create more Republican jobs in Congress.</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363897083212</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:18:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363897337061-208</Id><Topic><Title>GOP supports ownership of ASSAULT WEAPONS in every home!!!!!</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363888503004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>winkipoosey: shhhhhhhhhhh be very quiet now.....shhhhhhhhhh be quiet now and spread it! shhhhhhhh</Msg><Username>adolphlhitler</Username><Timestamp>1363897337061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:22:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363897579875-209</Id><Title>Racist White Trash Never Learn! After Nixon, You Tried Another Puke Raygun The Baby-Robber,...</Title><Msg>"poppy" The War Starter, Then His Idiot Son "w", What Is It With You Filth?,. Learn Filth!</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363897579875</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:26:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363897604160-210</Id><Topic><Title>Racist White Trash Never Learn! After Nixon, You Tried Another Puke Raygun The Baby-Robber,...</Title><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363897579875</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:26:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hhhhhh</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363897604160</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:26:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363898998626-211</Id><Topic><Title>Racist White Trash Never Learn! After Nixon, You Tried Another Puke Raygun The Baby-Robber,...</Title><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363897579875</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:26:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Compared to Obama, Bush was a murderer... Obama didn't prosecute a war that killed over a million souls based on a complete lie. Bush, Cheney and Rumsfeld conspired to murder over 100,000 souls on the FIRST day of their illegal war ALONE. Subsequent numbers suggest a million souls is probably even conservative. Additionally, the US economy has been savaged by military spending since then. Obama is spending on LIFE, not death, a fact that murderous Republicans cannot tolerate. IMHO most Republicans will burn in Hell</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363898998626</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:49:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363899602575-212</Id><Title>So yeah, why the rush to buy at 21.9 last Friday?</Title><Msg>Didn't have anything to do with gaming options now did it? Well see here you go have all you want over $1 lower. What's that? You don't want it now? No momentum you say? Well, it has some momentum now can't you see......in the other direction. 10 million bullish articles on seeking alpha and motley fool can't be wrong can they?</Msg><Username>carpet.bomber</Username><Timestamp>1363899602575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:00:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363899764173-213</Id><Title>Coming for you rbb guns now</Title><Msg>A10 year old died after being accidentally shot in the head by his brothers bb gun. Libs are outraged and will introduce a bill to ban all assault bb guns.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1363899764173</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:02:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363902302602-214</Id><Title>Barney Frank, Maxine Waters &amp; Mike Oxley(R) AGREED On Fannie &amp; Freddie in 2003!</Title><Msg>Mike Oxley(R) Chair Of The Banking &amp; Financial Services,... Gave "w" Lip Service From 2003 Until 2006 Six Bills &amp; Nothing Passed!,. BUT They Did Pass The American Dream Down-Payment Act In Dec. 2003!</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363902302602</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:45:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363903023111-215</Id><Topic><Title>GOP supports ownership of ASSAULT WEAPONS in every home!!!!!</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363888503004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HEY! I agree with Hitler you need to #$%$ you crazycvnt!</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363903023111</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363903024023-216</Id><Topic><Title>Barney Frank, Maxine Waters &amp; Mike Oxley(R) AGREED On Fannie &amp; Freddie in 2003!</Title><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363902302602</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:45:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh in the rabbit hole Barney and Maxine passed the American Dream Down-Payment act? LOL Let's see here were the sponsors of the bill 9 cosponsors (9R) (show) Sessions, Jefferson “Jeff” [R-AL] Crapo, Michael [R-ID] (joined Apr 09, 2003) Brownback, Samuel “Sam” [R-KS] (joined Apr 28, 2003) Burns, Conrad [R-MT] (joined May 13, 2003) Hagel, Charles “Chuck” [R-NE] (joined May 14, 2003) Santorum, Richard “Rick” [R-PA] (joined Jun 05, 2003) Campbell, Ben [R-CO] (joined Jun 25, 2003) Enzi, Michael [R-WY] (joined Oct 14, 2003) Murkowski, Lisa [R-AK] (joined Nov 20, 2003)</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363903024023</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:57:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363903090734-217</Id><Topic><Title>GOP supports ownership of ASSAULT WEAPONS in every home!!!!!</Title><Username>winkipuss</Username><Timestamp>1363888503004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no problem most GOPers don't have the brains to fire a weapon ie ":shotgun Cheney"</Msg><Username>jen.co44</Username><Timestamp>1363903090734</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:58:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363903120185-218</Id><Topic><Title>Barney Frank, Maxine Waters &amp; Mike Oxley(R) AGREED On Fannie &amp; Freddie in 2003!</Title><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363902302602</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:45:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh sorry those were the cosponsors here is who introduced it, notice not one DNC every one of them (all 10 GOP) S. 811 (108th): American Dream Downpayment Act Introduced: Apr 08, 2003 (108th Congress, 2003–2004) Sponsor: Sen. Wayne Allard [R-CO] Status: Signed by the President</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363903120185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:58:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363903334044-219</Id><Title>American Dream act tea billies blame on the DNC</Title><Msg>LOL Introduced by a GOPER Cosponsored by 9 GOPERS and this is what W had to say at the signing Last year I set a goal to add 5.5 million new minority homeowners in America by the end of the decade. That is an attainable goal; that is an essential goal. And we're making progress toward that goal. In the past 18 months, more than 1 million minority families have become homeowners. (Applause.) And there's more that we can do to achieve the goal. The law I sign today will help us build on this progress in a very practical way. Many people are able to afford a monthly mortgage payment, but are unable to make the down payment. So this legislation will authorize $200 million per year in down payment assistance to at least 40,000 low-income families. These funds will help American families achieve their goals, and at the same time, strengthen our communities. And there's more to do, as well. We'll continue to pursue a broad agenda to help people own a home. There are three steps I want to describe to you right quickly about what we intend to do. First, those who apply for mortgages should be made aware of all the costs and warned about predatory lenders who take advantage of inexperienced buyers. So we've doubled the funds for housing counseling services, including those run by faith-based and community groups.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363903334044</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363903387331-220</Id><Title>Ever notice how liberals on this board</Title><Msg>Do nothing but call people dumb and make personal attacks on beliefs they themselves don't have. Sound like Obama the last 5 years.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1363903387331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:03:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363903460306-221</Id><Topic><Title>Barney Frank, Maxine Waters &amp; Mike Oxley(R) AGREED On Fannie &amp; Freddie in 2003!</Title><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363902302602</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:45:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I Know That Moron!,. The Point Is "w" Said The GSEs Were Passing Bad Paper, But Encouraged More Lending Anyway Idiot !,..</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363903460306</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:04:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363903508947-222</Id><Title>LIBS HAVE KILLED AN AVE OF ONE MILLION BABIES PER YEAR</Title><Msg>since 1973 through their sacred god of abortion....and then they tell us they want to do away with assault rifles (whatever that is!). How many people have assault rifles killled compared to your abortionist's scapels you crazy facking loons!?! If we had those 40 million people contributing to our economy and tax base we wouldn't be in the economic mess we are in now and YOU socialists wouldn't have blood on your hands before God!</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363903508947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:05:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363904067832-223</Id><Title>Ivan has made a new low in stupidity</Title><Msg>blames Barney Frank and Maxine Water for the American Dream DownPayment Act in Dec 2003 You know the one introduced by a Republican, cosponsored by 9 other republicans, voted for BY EVERY SINGLE GOP SENATOR, and bragged about by Bush when he signed it in front of a large gathering at HUD? LOL Teabillies are beyond stupid</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363904067832</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363904098316-224</Id><Title>Why Republicans should stop talking about Roe v. Wade</Title><Msg>Potter Stewart, an Eisenhower appointee who was one of five Republican-appointed justices in the 7-to-2 majority in Roe, Majority (Roe) Chief Justice Warren Burger Justice William O. Douglas Justice William J. Brennan Justice Potter Stewart Justice Thurgood Marshall Justice Harry Blackmun* Justice Lewis Powell Dissenting (Wade) Justice Byron White Justice William Rehnquist * Justice Blackmun wrote the majority opinion. Gallup poll showed 60 percent opposed overturning Roe.</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363904098316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:14:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363904231430-225</Id><Title>ivanhoeoflioxly</Title><Msg>Hey Ivan, If all those comments you make about our President and Country Savior, were true; don.t you find the fact that he won the election in a LANDSLIDE a little hard to swallow ?</Msg><Username>jen.co44</Username><Timestamp>1363904231430</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:17:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363904261894-226</Id><Topic><Title>LIBS HAVE KILLED AN AVE OF ONE MILLION BABIES PER YEAR</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363903508947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:05:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh but the goofy tards have a new plan to increase the tax base now, it's called Gay Marriage! There will be scores of taxpayers that will pop out of their hairy butts from those perverted "unions" dontcha know! lol</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363904261894</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:17:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363904833016-227</Id><Title>Junior loves Bush now</Title><Msg>Today Junior posted that the drone program was all Bush's idea. You know the program thats been killing all them meanie Al-Qaeda guys. Only really good things thats happened under Obama and now Junior gives all the credit to Bush.Amazing!! Thanks for being honest though ,Junior."W" really appreciates it.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363904833016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:27:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363904954342-228</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Santelli! If You Want To End QE Then Tell Your Puke Buddies To Pass The Jobs Bill!,..</Title><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363897083212</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:18:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rrrr</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363904954342</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363905012348-229</Id><Topic><Title>Is That What You White Trash Are Calling Romney Now., "Dysentery"?</Title><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363896717988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:11:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glenn Beck!</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363905012348</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363905124273-230</Id><Topic><Title>Why Republicans should stop talking about Roe v. Wade</Title><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363904098316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Morons!,..</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363905124273</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:32:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363905371678-231</Id><Title>Standing Ovation for Obama</Title><Msg>In Israel, teabillies cry</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363905371678</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:36:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363905855148-232</Id><Topic><Title>LIBS HAVE KILLED AN AVE OF ONE MILLION BABIES PER YEAR</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363903508947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:05:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberalism ("progressives" yeah right!) is a mental disease you see. For only in their way of thinking can you by murdering millions of innocent people some how improve the life of an individual or nation, just as only in their way of thinking can RAISING taxes bring about an economic recovery!</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363905855148</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363906047226-233</Id><Title>Oh no, looks like we have a small error over this GlobaL Warming!</Title><Msg>PARIS — A new examination of what is essentially the universe's birth certificate allows astronomers to tweak the age, girth and speed of the cosmos, more secure in their knowledge of how it evolved, what it's made of and its ultimate fate. Sure, the universe suddenly seems to be showing its age, now calculated at 13.8 billion years – 80 million years older than scientists had thought. It's got about 3 percent more girth – technically it's more matter than mysterious dark energy – and it is expanding about 3 percent more slowly. So, if we are 80 million years older and or expanding about 3 percent more slowly, then we have 2.4 million more years before this Global Warming deal kicks in. I can live with that! OPEN OUR OIL AND COAL OPERATIONS EVERYWHERE AND LETS GET BACK TO WORK, I LIKE BIG CARS, FAST BOATS AND AIRPLANES! BRING THE JOBS ON! If Solar and Will mills are so good, you Tree Hugging Pecker-woods can stick the Green energies when the sun don't shine. Because the say good things will not hurt you!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1363906047226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:47:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363906545254-234</Id><Topic><Title>LIBS HAVE KILLED AN AVE OF ONE MILLION BABIES PER YEAR</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363903508947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:05:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are one of the many people that have a problem with definitions. A fetus is not a baby. Look it up. Then your twisted thinking continues with..."If we had those 40 million people contributing to our economy and tax base we wouldn't be in the economic mess we are in now." I wonder how many aborted births that could have gone to full term would be from under-educated teens that would become part of the already bloated welfare burden. You judge people as if you were God. Freedom of choice, for a woman, should and currently does include that she decides if her pregnancy results in birth. Besides...if the law were to change, abortions would continue regardless. You can argue the morality all you want. Learn to accept reality.</Msg><Username>karnut2000</Username><Timestamp>1363906545254</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:55:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363906713491-235</Id><Topic><Title>Standing Ovation for Obama</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363905371678</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb, you are dumber than we figured, that was not a standing ovation, they got up because they thought they were picking a firing squad, pecker-wood!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1363906713491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:58:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363906835725-236</Id><Title>Cramer &amp; Cisco</Title><Msg>A history lesson...quite a few years ago Money magazine did an article with the one stock pick from roughly half a dozen analysts. Cramer was one of them. His top pick for the year was Cisco. It was $70 then. Has anyone ever determined the buy and hold strategy of Cramer's charitable trust? Cramer is bullish today against the current downgrade...oh well. Cramer may be a Cisco bull when he turns 80.</Msg><Username>karnut2000</Username><Timestamp>1363906835725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:00:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363907040423-237</Id><Topic><Title>LIBS HAVE KILLED AN AVE OF ONE MILLION BABIES PER YEAR</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363903508947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:05:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey karnuts, since when should someone's "freedom of choice" involve murdering another defense human being you wacko, self-centered LIB. A fetus is TOTALLY a human being and many can live outside the womb at the age they are murdered! God has said "thou shall not murder" in His word. Are you a racist? You "JUDGE" these unborn babies assuming they are mostly blacks or other minorities who will end up on the welfare rolls!! On what basis you bigot! Their WORTH has nothing to do with how YOU value them. Many great people were born/adopted from "under-educated teen" women who had babies! I hope Donkey lets you have it too.</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363907040423</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:04:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363907138858-238</Id><Topic><Title>Why Republicans should stop talking about Roe v. Wade</Title><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363904098316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yyyy</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363907138858</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363907464786-239</Id><Title>More ice loss through snowfall on Antarctica,....</Title><Msg>Stronger snowfall increases future ice discharge from Antarctica. Global warming leads to more precipitation as warmer air holds more moisture – hence earlier research suggested the Antarctic ice sheet might grow under climate change. Now a study published in Nature shows that a lot of the ice gain due to increased snowfall is countered by an acceleration of ice-flow to the ocean. Thus Antarctica’s contribution to global sea-level rise is probably greater than hitherto estimated, the team of authors from the Potsdam Institute for Climate Impact Research (PIK) concludes. “Between 30 and 65 percent of the ice gain due to enhanced snowfall in Antarctica is countervailed by enhanced ice loss along the coastline,” says lead-author Ricarda Winkelmann. For the first time, an ensemble of ice-physics simulations shows that future ice discharge is increased up to three times because of additional precipitation in Antarctica under global warming. “The effect exceeds that of surface warming as well as that of basal ice-shelf melting,” Winkelmann says. Snow piling up exerts pressure on the ice, thus it flows faster to the coast During the last decade, the Antarctic ice-sheet has lost volume at a rate comparable to that of Greenland. “The one certainty we have about Antarctica under global warming is that snowfall will increase,” Winkelmann explains. “Since surface melt might remain comparably small even under strong global warming, because Antarctica will still be a pretty chilly place, the big question is: How much more mass within the ice sheet will slowly but inexorably flow off Antarctica and contribute to sea-level rise, which is one of the major impacts of climate change.” Since snowfall on the ice masses of Antarctica takes water out of the global water cycle, the continent’s net contribution to sea-level rise could be negative during the next 100 years – this is what a number of global and regional models suggest. The new f</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363907464786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:11:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363907838345-240</Id><Title>GLOBAL WARMING CAUSING MUCH COLDER WEATHER....they said.....???</Title><Msg>Hmmmmmm, wow, is the sky falling too? Yes, warmer atmosphere holds more water vapor causing more snowfall that pushes ice out the top of your head...........and then sea levels rise and Godzilla jumps out of the Marianna trench and bites San Francisco in two...all of America rejoices!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363907838345</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:17:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363908254837-241</Id><Topic><Title>WITHIN MINUTES AFTER THE MARINE ACCIDENT DEATHS WERE REPORTED</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363800051115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:20:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>see it's stoopidphks like you that are ruining the country. You vote on the abortion issue only so the slaughter of Iraqi's and Americans troops and the 2 trillion dollars bus spent on the war don't bother you-- But here's a little secret dummphk the GOP loves abortion and most GOPERS (except the christ-stains) support right to choose as well.</Msg><Username>rationalthought11</Username><Timestamp>1363908254837</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:24:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363908384307-242</Id><Topic><Title>Obama wanted 98%and got it</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363455784938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 13:43:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's a useless waste of skin-- But I like him because, like a good donkey, he comes when I call and he shows everyone what the teapig mentality is all about.</Msg><Username>rationalthought11</Username><Timestamp>1363908384307</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:26:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363908497805-243</Id><Title>donkeydouchebags or ivanhoeoflioxly</Title><Msg>ivanhoeoflioxly whether it is your twisted thinking or whomever donkeydouchebags is aguing the same point as yours, a fetus isn't a baby. I am not agreeing with the medical professionals (if they even should be called that) who do to full term or near-full term life as you've described. Do you understand? Maybe not. I am able to uphold a woman's right to abort a fetus. No one else has to agree but many do...AND MORE IMPORTANTLY, the law allows for my point of view being legal. Do all you can to get the law changed but that appears utterly misplaced to be a conversation appropriate at this stock message board...then again, you and donkeydouchebags don't fall in the appropriate category.</Msg><Username>karnut2000</Username><Timestamp>1363908497805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:28:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363909005494-244</Id><Title>never see 21.50 again that a no brainer fpos stock for pin heads brain dead ,never buy again sold at loss today fpos stock</Title><Msg>ok</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363909005494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:36:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363909138365-245</Id><Title>Bitumen!, XL Pipeline Would Transport Bitumen!</Title><Msg>Bitumen is a black, oily, viscous material that is a naturally-occurring organic byproduct of decomposed organic materials. Also known as asphalt or tar, bitumen was mixed with other materials throughout prehistory and throughout the world for use as a sealant, adhesive, building mortar, incense, and decorative application on pots, buildings, or human skin. The material was also useful in waterproofing canoes and other water transport, and in the mummification process toward the end of the New Kingdom of ancient Egypt. It is also flammable.</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363909138365</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:38:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363909547876-246</Id><Title>Once again fathers gun used to</Title><Msg>kill his son, nice good thing he had that gun, otherwise his kid would be alive, Southgate — The eighth-grade student who shot himself to death himself Thursday in a bathroom at Davidson Middle School took the gun from a family member's home, police said. The firearm, a .40 caliber Glock handgun, was legally registered, said Thomas Coombs, Southgate's public safety director. Coombs would not identify the family member who owned the gun. Police and school officials said it did not appear the student, who they would not identify, was bullied.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363909547876</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363910348530-247</Id><Topic><Title>Once again fathers gun used to</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363909547876</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah,aint it too bad Harry Reid couldn't get enough dems to back Feinsteins assault gun ban.lol</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1363910348530</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:59:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363910601667-248</Id><Topic><Title>Standing Ovation for Obama</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363905371678</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bibi cant stand Obama.Surely you don' t believe political rhetoric,dummy.</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1363910601667</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 20:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363911166859-249</Id><Topic><Title>Standing Ovation for Obama</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363905371678</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Israelis do not love Obama.He has a10 percent approval rating there .There have been several demonstrations against his visit.He got an ovation for the way he responded to a heckler during his speech. If Obama is so wonderful why do you find it necessary to lie for him?</Msg><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1363911166859</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 20:12:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363913696079-250</Id><Topic><Title>ARE DEMOCRATS MORE POPULAR THAN DYSENTERY?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1363895522322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:52:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonder how dumbivan handles giving Junior a rimjob with that constant anal drip going on???</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363913696079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 20:54:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363914844023-251</Id><Title>What a surprise Corruption in Chicago politics.</Title><Msg>William Beavers Verdict Theatrical Cook County Commissioner Found Guilty Of Tax Evasion DNC: "its ok, we have a thousand lined up to take his place" **Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO) Act, Title 18, United States Code, Sections 1961-1968. When it was passed in 1970, Congress’ goal was to eliminate the ill-effects of organized crime on the nation’s economy. Today, although seldom used against the Mafia, RICO is a common claim in federal courts, usually asserted by the purported victims of white collar crimes.</Msg><Username>captgailwife</Username><Timestamp>1363914844023</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 21:14:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363915127283-252</Id><Topic><Title>LIBS HAVE KILLED AN AVE OF ONE MILLION BABIES PER YEAR</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363903508947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:05:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>see the thing is--the libs have long ago abandoned any kind of conscious about anything other than what buys them political capital. Like an atheistic communist therefore, they are gambling that there IS NO God! That's one heck of a big gamble! Because if they believed in answering to a God, any God, for their treatment of the innocent and defenseless, within moments after their death, they would go nowhere near their current practice of INFANTICIDE. So lib atheists you just need to ask yourself on the day you die: Am I feeing lucky as I breathe this final breath? Well, are you PUNKS?! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!</Msg><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1363915127283</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 21:18:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363915282963-253</Id><Topic><Title>LIBS HAVE KILLED AN AVE OF ONE MILLION BABIES PER YEAR</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363903508947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:05:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>any kind of "conscience" that is, answer: they have NONE!</Msg><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1363915282963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 21:21:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363916184038-254</Id><Topic><Title>donkeydouchebags or ivanhoeoflioxly</Title><Username>karnut2000</Username><Timestamp>1363908497805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:28:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>karnuts, apart from what the Bible says (and many other religious books), even the "free dictionary" defines a fetus like this: "the embryo of a mammal in the later stages of development, when it shows all the main recognizable features of the mature animal, esp a human embryo from the end of the second month of pregnancy until birth Compare". Notice the words "Human" and the phrase "it shows all the main recognizable features of the mature animal,". IT'S A HUMAN! HUMAN! HUMAN! Got it!??? Another part of your elementary, flawed logic implies: "If it is legal it must good, moral, or acceptable"! So since you are probably an anti-death penalty LIB, does that mean it's good, moral, acceptable for the gubment to put others to death then BECAUSE IT's LEGAL! LOL! How about smoking! It's LEGAL! ETC. ETC.! Just because "it's legal" doesn't make it right! What Hitler did to the Jews was "Legal" in #$%$ Germany too! Abortiion IS animalistic, depraved, EVIL behavior! How many young girls never got the chance to become WOMEN and have a CHOICE because of it! Grow a brain!!! You sound like someone who feels guilty because you helped fund an abortion or encouraged some poor girl to get one. SHAME ON YOU!!!!!</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1363916184038</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 21:36:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363917843495-255</Id><Title>But then you could say that about anyone in Texas now couldn't you?</Title><Msg>Headline: "Texas gunman brain dead;"</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363917843495</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 22:04:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363923117494-256</Id><Topic><Title>As A Matter Of Fact Obama Was A Harvard Legacy His Father Earned A Master's in Economics</Title><Username>the.word999</Username><Timestamp>1363919934087</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 22:38:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IMO U R The Son Of An Evil Racist W H O R E !</Msg><Username>dei.verbum</Username><Timestamp>1363923117494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:31:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363923545988-257</Id><Title>GLOBAL COOLING BRINGS SNOWSTORMS IN SPRING</Title><Msg>GLOBAL COOLING BRINGS SNOWSTORMS IN SPRING. I dont see Al Gore or any of the global warming fraudsters wearing speedo bikinis in the snowstorm to demonstrate how hot it is.</Msg><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1363923545988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:39:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363923686362-258</Id><Title>ISRAELIS MARCH WITH HUGE SIGNS OF OBAMA WITH PINOCCHIO NOSE</Title><Msg>ISRAELIS MARCH WITH HUGE SIGNS OF OBAMA WITH PINOCCHIO NOSE. Obviously everyone knows that this guy is a lying conniving bad man.</Msg><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1363923686362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363923783476-259</Id><Title>OBAMA PITBULL JANET NAPOLITANO WONT EXPLAIN HER BUYING BILLIONS OF ROUNDS OF AMMO AND MILLIONS OF MACHINE GUNS</Title><Msg>Obama pitbull janet napolitano wont explain her buying billions of rounds of ammo and millions of machine guns that the demonrats want to ban.</Msg><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1363923783476</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:43:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363924100752-260</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA PITBULL JANET NAPOLITANO WONT EXPLAIN HER BUYING BILLIONS OF ROUNDS OF AMMO AND MILLIONS OF MACHINE GUNS</Title><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1363923783476</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:43:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While demonrat Obama's pitbull (demonrat Janet Napolitano) of homeland security is buying up all the machine guns that the demonrats want to ban and billions or rounds of ammo for those machine guns, Democrat anti-gun zealot Diane Feinstein is standing on the Senate Floor showing off every kind of machine gun that all the democrat street gang members have and demanding that only the goverment and criminal street gangs who vote democrat be allowed to have these machine guns.</Msg><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1363924100752</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363924489101-261</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA PITBULL JANET NAPOLITANO WONT EXPLAIN HER BUYING BILLIONS OF ROUNDS OF AMMO AND MILLIONS OF MACHINE GUNS</Title><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1363923783476</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:43:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't it obvious that the Obama administration plans to disarm law abiding Americans and have ugly ogre Janet Napalitano use those machine guns against disarmed Americans in our homeland.</Msg><Username>democrat_occupier_wall_of_doodoo</Username><Timestamp>1363924489101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:54:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363924774405-262</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA PITBULL JANET NAPOLITANO WONT EXPLAIN HER BUYING BILLIONS OF ROUNDS OF AMMO AND MILLIONS OF MACHINE GUNS</Title><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1363923783476</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:43:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama and Holder claim it is lawful to use drones to kill Americans on our soil because these two bad men want to use drones to kill Americans but dont want to limit themselves to only drones that is why Obama's henchwoman Janet Napalitano is buying up all the machine guns and billions of rounds of ammo for use against Americans on our own soil.after the Obama administration confiscates all our guns.</Msg><Username>unions_r_criminal_gangs</Username><Timestamp>1363924774405</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>