<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-21"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350794065077-1</Id><Title>A cheap Genuine Apple iPad Mini : "The Competition's Worst Nightmare"</Title><Msg>Apple's smaller iPad forecast to become 'Competition's Worst Nightmare' 10/19/12 at 6:59am AppleInsider | Kasper's Automated Slave Tablet makers have Failed to Compete with Apple in the $400-and-up market segment, and a new, smaller iPad priced below $300 is only expected to make matters Worse for the Competition. Analyst Shaw Wu with Sterne Agee said he believes Apple's so-called "iPad mini" will prove to be "The Competition's Worst Nightmare." He noted that competitors are already Struggling to Compete against the $399 iPad 2 and $499 iPad, and Apple hitting an even lower price point will only Expand its share of the tablet market. The main question, Wu said, is whether Apple will "Go for The Kill" against competitors and accept lower margins to reach the $199 price point of its competitors, such as the Google Nexus 7 and Amazon Kindle Fire HD. Wu doesn't believe Apple needs to hit the $199 price point and match Google and Amazon. In fact, he thinks Apple could sell its smaller iPad for around $350 and it would still be a Success. He noted that Apple already has a product at the $199 price point with its entry-level iPod touch, while the iPad 2 is available for $399. He thinks an iPad mini for either $299 or $349 makes the most sense for the company. This week, Apple sent out invitations for an event next Tuesday in San Jose, Calif., where it has promised it will show "a little more." The company is widely expected to unveil a new 7.85-inch iPad it will sell for the holiday shopping season, as well as new Mac hardware headlined by a 13-inch MacBook Pro with Retina display. The iPad mini is expected to feature a smaller bezel than the full-size iPad, and could run a screen resolution of 1,024-by-768 pixels that would allow it to run native iPad 2 applications without any modifications. It is also expected to have forward and rear facing cameras, as well as the new smaller Lightning connector found on the iPhone 5 and latest iPods." Of those Twenty Four (24) cute little Genuine iPad Mini models which are coming next week, let's assume that the entry model is priced at, say, a Mini-scule $249.99 Could be Quite a Nightmare, right boys? It sure Will be.</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1350794065077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 00:34:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>54</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350794398733-2</Id><Topic><Title>A cheap Genuine Apple iPad Mini : "The Competition's Worst Nightmare"</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1350794065077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 00:34:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Of those Twenty Four (24) cute little Genuine iPad Mini models which are coming next week, let's assume that the entry model is priced at, say, a Mini-scule $249.99 Could be Quite a Nightmare, right boys? It sure Will be." Why, it's just like Jen said before: "Apple does what Apple does and Nobody else is going to compete with them." -- Jen Hsun Huang, MobileBeat, March 4, 2011.</Msg><Username>ibest.here</Username><Timestamp>1350794398733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 00:39:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>51</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350795475607-3</Id><Topic><Title>A cheap Genuine Apple iPad Mini : "The Competition's Worst Nightmare"</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1350794065077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 00:34:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe Apple is relocating? Their Thermonuclear War against android that is. From the Courtroom. To the Store shelves.</Msg><Username>perceptive.best</Username><Timestamp>1350795475607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 00:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>43</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350824165974-4</Id><Topic><Title>How are the 7 inch tablets doing?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1350763882777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 16:11:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd buy AAPL at $1! LOL :).</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1350824165974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 08:56:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350825760593-5</Id><Topic><Title>AMD down 16.8%</Title><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1350686653256</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 18:44:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD could be toast, they must have cut down on R&amp;D spending, something I think is the end of the line for any tech company as they won't get cheap money again, maybe the Abu Dhabi government takes control after bankruptcy.. @whosunw: Jen-Hsun said that CPU's are fast enough long time ago, what's needed is GPUs to speed things up, and soon ARM chips are fast enough as well, that will kill AMD. Microsoft and Apple both have their main operating systems ported to ARM, just wait for it to mature and you'll will most likely see AMD and INTEL suffering.</Msg><Username>razorgarf</Username><Timestamp>1350825760593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 09:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350831405969-6</Id><Topic><Title>A cheap Genuine Apple iPad Mini : "The Competition's Worst Nightmare"</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1350794065077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 00:34:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I will spend every penny of Apple's $40bn in the bank, to right this wrong. I'm going to destroy Android, because it's a stolen product. I'm willing to go thermonuclear war on this." -- Apple founder Steve Jobs Like to read more about it? Of course you would. Google this : Steve Jobs Said He'd 'Go Thermonuclear War' On Google Over iPhone 'Theft'</Msg><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1350831405969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 10:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350832247963-7</Id><Topic><Title>A cheap Genuine Apple iPad Mini : "The Competition's Worst Nightmare"</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1350794065077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 00:34:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When is the update Nexus 7 due out? Should blow away any iPad mini - sounds like a womans device. Price should keep the Nexus competitive wouldn't you think. Even with the lower cost of a Nexus it'll still beat a mini iPad, no?</Msg><Username>goodnyet</Username><Timestamp>1350832247963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 11:10:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350834200184-8</Id><Topic><Title>A cheap Genuine Apple iPad Mini : "The Competition's Worst Nightmare"</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1350794065077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 00:34:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With the Nexus 7 tablet having likely only sold between 800,000 to 1m units in the third quarter of this year, -- according to the official Android Community website -- it probably IS time for Google to "refresh" that newly launched device. Like the Xoom tried to do, remember?</Msg><Username>ct.bestula</Username><Timestamp>1350834200184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 11:43:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350834618121-9</Id><Topic><Title>A cheap Genuine Apple iPad Mini : "The Competition's Worst Nightmare"</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1350794065077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 00:34:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oops. I forgot the link to that official Android Community site. That says the Nexus 7 "likely sold 800,000 to 1 million units in the third quarter of this year." Here it is. Google likely to have sold close to 1m Nexus 7 tablets Android Community</Msg><Username>best.again</Username><Timestamp>1350834618121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 11:50:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350839654359-10</Id><Topic><Title>A cheap Genuine Apple iPad Mini : "The Competition's Worst Nightmare"</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1350794065077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 00:34:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Best ! I appreciated the article that you shared with us, Steve Jobs Said He'd 'Go Thermonuclear War' On Google Over iPhone 'Theft' I particularily like this part; "Though the book focuses on Jobs, it also offers insight into the man to whom Jobs entrusted the future of Apple: Tim Cook, Apple's former chief operating officer who took over for Jobs as CEO following Jobs' resignation in August. Jobs did not ask Cook if he would take on the role of COO. He informed him, telling Cook on a flight to Japan, "I've decided to make you COO." "I'm a good negotiator," Jobs said of Cook. "But he's probably better than me because he's a cool customer." EVERY good company needs a Good Negotiator at the Helm, right boys? They sure do. Separately, did Jen ever get a license from Intel to use those x86 patents? You know, which he needed to get that seven (7) year Project Denver "let's use software to copycat an x86" scheme to work. Thanks again, Best.</Msg><Username>thanks.best</Username><Timestamp>1350839654359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 13:14:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350845159420-11</Id><Title>Wu : Microsoft Is Charging Way Too Much for the Surface. Doomed to come In 4th Place at Best</Title><Msg>Microsoft Is Charging Way Too Much For The Surface And It's Doomed To Come In Fourth Place At Best Business Insider | Jay Yarow | October 18, 2012 "Microsoft is charging way too much for its Surface tablet, and it's doomed to come in last place, says Sterne Agee analyst Shaw Wu in a new note this morning. With Microsoft charging $499 for an intro level Surface without cover, and $599 for the Surface with its keyboard cover, Microsoft is going to be fighting Apple at the high end, while leaving room for Google and Amazon to clean up on the low end. He writes, "Surface's high pricing could prove to be a fatal mistake and relegate it to be a niche No. 4 or No. 5 player. We believe Nexus 7 and Kindle Fire HD will likely see considerably higher volume given their low $199 price points and stronger ecosystems with iPad retaining its commanding No. 1 position." (He thinks Microsoft should have charged $300 for the Surface plus the cover.) He also says that supply chain checks suggest Microsoft is only making 2-3 million Surfaces, which will automatically limit sales versus Apple, Google, and Amazon. Despite the small sales, Microsoft will still take sales from its traditional partners like Dell, HP, Acer, and HTC. In other words, Microsoft is going to fail to sell a lot of Surface tablets, while at the same time limiting the sales of its partners. Sounds like a mess, if Wu is right." My my my. "High pricing could prove to be a fatal mistake" for those usurious Microsoft tablets.</Msg><Username>bested.again</Username><Timestamp>1350845159420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 14:45:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350850093654-12</Id><Topic><Title>A cheap Genuine Apple iPad Mini : "The Competition's Worst Nightmare"</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1350794065077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 00:34:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? Even though Google is struggling trying to find customers for their Nexus 7, -- and struggling Badly -- they can still buy their own trophy at the Computex 2013 show, right? "Best New Tablet with between 800,000 and 1 million units" And then Jen can order another trophy too. "Best New Tegra 3 Powered Tablet with between 800,000 and 1 million units" Really nice trophies for only $1,750 each, boys. Well, plus VAT tax, of course.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1350850093654</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 16:08:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350851275983-13</Id><Topic><Title>A cheap Genuine Apple iPad Mini : "The Competition's Worst Nightmare"</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1350794065077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 00:34:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Master? While those purchased Computex trophies look really blingy and all in the nvidia Visitor's Reception area, -- and they DO distract the visitors from perusing the nvidia Annual Report/10-K -- wouldn't it be cheaper to just tear-out page 28 from the 10-K's in the aforementioned nvidia Visitor's Reception area?</Msg><Username>best.clone185</Username><Timestamp>1350851275983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 16:27:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350852461316-14</Id><Topic><Title>Wu : Microsoft Is Charging Way Too Much for the Surface. Doomed to come In 4th Place at Best</Title><Username>bested.again</Username><Timestamp>1350845159420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 14:45:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>msft has made the decision NOT to compete in the appliance market. Their reasoning probably goes somthing like this: we don't have the infrastructure to compete with free, so we will abandon that market until we can set up that infrastructure by going into to high end market for now, while getting our usual $100 for windoz. Of course that ain't going to work, Android will continue to encroach upwards and grow and grow and grow and upend windwoz from the bottom up. Ballmer decidedly does not have the ability of a Bill Gates to turn the whole company around on a dime and head in a completely different direction, ala when Gates recognized the threat of the net.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1350852461316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 16:47:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350856902617-15</Id><Title>NVDA Earnings - Nov 8 (Get out!)</Title><Msg>Based on Dow's earnings trend - expect bloodbath.</Msg><Username>geegaboo</Username><Timestamp>1350856902617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350857902139-16</Id><Topic><Title>Google's big event on October 29: a FULL plate.....</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1350857116011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:05:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, that will be my x'mas present to myself, a 10" Android tablet with quad A-15s! And all for 350! Quad A9s are so 'yesteday' really obsolete. And Ballmer say, " but but but..... only $100 for Windoz...."</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1350857902139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:18:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350858093202-17</Id><Topic><Title>Google's big event on October 29: a FULL plate.....</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1350857116011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:05:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nexus is about pushing the envelope of hardware/software. Goog has rotated hardware/oem for evtery 3 release. You can bet it will be anything but T3 and Asus. But really, 3 is so obsolete. On with A15s... for Samsung, qcom... but I guess not for nvda. Where's Wayne???</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1350858093202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:21:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350858182696-18</Id><Topic><Title>Google's big event on October 29: a FULL plate.....</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1350857116011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:05:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whatever release inventory msft/Lenovo/Asus have buillt for winRT, they will have to end up dumping it at firesaale prices.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1350858182696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:23:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350858245569-19</Id><Title>Google big event Oct 29th - Samsung Manta 10' tablet</Title><Msg>Google and Samsung will announce a new 10-inch tablet codenamed "Manta" at its October 29th event, according to The Next Web. LG Nexus 4, featuring a quad-core 1.5 GHz Qualcomm APQ8064 Snapdragon</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1350858245569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350859157980-20</Id><Topic><Title>Google's big event on October 29: a FULL plate.....</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1350857116011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:05:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our sympathies go out to nvidia baggies. On losing-out on Everything. Again. The new $99 Nexus 7 tablet -- China-based WonderMedia Technologies PRIZM WM8950 single-core 800 MHz Cortex-A9 CPU with Mali-400 Graphics Processing Unit. The new co-branded Samsung Nexus 10 tablet -- Samsung Exynos 5 processor inside. The new LG Nexus 4 smartphone -- Qualcomm Snapdragon quad-core 1.5 GHz processor. Better luck on the next Google "refresh", boys.</Msg><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1350859157980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:39:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350861218048-21</Id><Topic><Title>Google's big event on October 29: a FULL plate.....</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1350857116011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:05:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe Apple could buy 'em by the ton. And have the Foxcomm workers fish-out the Qualcomm multi-mode radio parts. They're scarce and on allocation, don't u know.</Msg><Username>bests.idea</Username><Timestamp>1350861218048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 19:13:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350865241199-22</Id><Title>A New Nexus 7 will Destroy the iPod Touch</Title><Msg>First off, the Nexus 7 is a very nice device and it does what you’d want by functioning as a daily tablet; it’s fast enough to play mobile games, watch videos, surf the web, launch apps and does so in a capable ecosystem. I still think the Apple ecosystem is better, and Android may get to the level eventually, but its just not there yet. I feel Jellybean is a good enough OS over previous versions that I would feel comfortable handing that to any technology-challenged relative to use with ease. When combined with the specs its “good enough,” but when you consider the pricing, the Nexus 7 is a solid buy. So if the rumors of a 32GB version of the Nexus 7 at a price comparable or cheaper than the existing 16 GB model are true, this complicates Apple’s product line drastically. Lets say the 32 GB Nexus 7 sells for $249, compare that to a $299 32 GB iPod touch. Sure the iPod touch comes with headphones, a rear facing camera, a revolutionary loop and a 4-inch display vs. a 7-inch Nexus 7 display (you may prefer a smaller screen or a larger screen) but how will they compare to most consumers? So how does Apple compete against a $249 7-inch, 32 GB tablet and a iPad Mini without pricing out its own iPod touch? The company will try and come close to a $350 price point and try to point out the value of the iPod touch (convenient form factor, camera use, Nike+ support), but it will be a hard sell, one I believe that in the long run may result in the end of the iPod Touch. Source: technobuffaloDOTcom/companies/apple/a-new-nexus-7-will-destroy-the-ipod-touch/</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1350865241199</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 20:20:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350871918767-23</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Earnings - Nov 8 (Get out!)</Title><Username>geegaboo</Username><Timestamp>1350856902617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:01:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>earnings have to be pretty bad to justify the current price. More likely to go up. Especially if price is still around $12 or lower at that time. If its 15 then ya a drop could happen from weakness but at 12 the earnings and outlook would have to be bad for that to happen. Nvidia is only going to be stronger with AMD being so weak. Project Denver is practically around the corner. Nvidia is close to having a top to bottom solution to mobile with Tegra/Icera combo processors coming out soon. The only thing dragging this company down is the broader market. Don't go lumping Nvidia in with the rest of the market. You will likely be eating your shorts.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1350871918767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 22:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350872445529-24</Id><Topic><Title>Google's big event on October 29: a FULL plate.....</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1350857116011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:05:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jeepers Best, Take a lookie. At what snatched the new $99 Google Nexus 7 tablet away from nvidia. Google this to see it's little mugshot and rap sheet: PRIZM WM8950 - WonderMedia Technologies, Inc. And the best part is, the little WonderMedia Technologies PRIZM WM8950 hoodlum, -- which Google has selected for their new $99 Google Nexus 7 tablet -- probably grew-up in the EXACT SAME BUILDING in Taiwan as the nvidia Tegra. So they're like clone relatives, really. Except the WonderMedia Technologies PRIZM WM8950 made off with the goods, and kicked it's nvidia Tegra cousin, well, to the curb.</Msg><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1350872445529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 22:20:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350873820363-25</Id><Topic><Title>Google's big event on October 29: a FULL plate.....</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1350857116011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:05:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? What do you think the cost is? Of the WonderMedia Technologies PRIZM WM8950 ARM CPU plus Mali GPU? It can't be much, right? If the Entire new Nexus 7 will sell for just $99 bucks. So maybe $3 to $4 bucks per chip? My my my. However shall the loss-ridden Tegra compete with that? Hummm? Maybe not test 'em, and let the customer pick out the good ones themselves. Keeps the cost down, don't u know.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1350873820363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 22:43:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350874218649-26</Id><Title>is everyone now short? it's the american way!!</Title><Msg>profiting on the country's downfall...tell me it ain't so...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1350874218649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 22:50:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350874463074-27</Id><Topic><Title>Google big event Oct 29th - Samsung Manta 10' tablet</Title><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1350858245569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:24:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The title of you post says 10 foot tablet. Will it be the GeForce 68000 or the Tegra 4000? Who makes the screen Samsung or LG? Will it be portable or will it be solar powered? Maybe they should market it at Home Depot as a wall tablet for graffiti in Inglewood so people don't write trash on the Space Shuttle. Who builds the protective cover? Maybe we'll get the answers on the 29th.</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1350874463074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 22:54:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350877803686-28</Id><Topic><Title>Latest IPad Mini rumor: $329 for 16GB, WiFi only variant, $429 and $529 for 32GB and 64GB vaiants</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1350874466379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 22:54:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ibbey, Your rumor is gonna look silly on Tuesday. When Apple announces the Real pricing for the iPad Mini.</Msg><Username>ibest.here</Username><Timestamp>1350877803686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 23:50:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>