<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344657691000-1</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC hit record revenues in July</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1344649371000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 21:42:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- "TSMC posted strong revenue results and soaring profits for its 2Q12. The company expects to expand sales revenue by about 7 percent sequentially in 3Q12, which is roughly in line with TSMC's historical average for the third calendar quarter." "We are now seeing a dip in our revenue in the fourth quarter from the third quarter," the Taipei Times quoted Chang as saying. Chang also sees a strong rebound in the second quarter of 2013 after the inventory adjustment." Interesting right? It sure is. TSMC's Chairman Chang just put a great quarter in the books. But unlike current nvidia CEO Jen-Hsun Huang, he is forthright and honest about telling his shareholders that it's Grim Times ahead. -</Msg><Username>best.again</Username><Timestamp>1344657691000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 00:01:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344658353000-2</Id><Title>Trefis post earnings analysis: 49+% upside for NVDA</Title><Msg>http://www.trefis.com/stock/nvda/articles/138157/nvidia-posts-solid-earnings-backed-by-tegra-3-kepler-architecture/2012-08-10</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1344658353000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 00:12:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344658605000-3</Id><Title>repost: TSMC hit record revenues in July</Title><Msg>Great news for NVIDIA; 28nm capacity constraint easing fast... http://www.taipeitimes.com/News/biz/archives/2012/08/11/2003539958</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1344658605000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 00:16:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344659096000-4</Id><Topic><Title>repost: TSMC hit record revenues in July</Title><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1344658605000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 00:16:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Jeepers Best, While TSMC had a good 2Q, did you see Chairman Chang's grim outlook for the 4Q and first quarter of 2012? http://eetimes.com/electronics-news/4390786/Morris-Chang-cuts-forecast Ugly ugly ugly. "A slowdown is coming", says the guy that watches the Order Book, and makes all of nvidia's chips for them. -</Msg><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1344659096000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 00:24:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344659708000-5</Id><Topic><Title>wtf Happpened Today...</Title><Username>poellpe</Username><Timestamp>1344640523000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 19:15:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, I suppose because you're a long-term investor in NVDA, you're absolutely THRILLED with today's performance. LOL! If so, please tell me what other stocks you own, so I can avoid them like the plague.</Msg><Username>istudyfish</Username><Timestamp>1344659708000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 00:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344659713000-6</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC hit record revenues in July</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1344649371000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 21:42:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- "Morris Chang, Chairman and CEO of leading foundry chipmaker Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. Ltd., has Warned that a Slowdown is Coming to the chip market and has cut his forecast for the total semiconductor market's annual growth, according to reports." http://eetimes.com/electronics-news/4390786/Morris-Chang-cuts-forecast Could be why none of those 29 analysts that follow nvidia gave an upgrade to Buy today, right?. The whole sector is about to be whacked. And whacked badly. Says the Chairman of TSMC. -</Msg><Username>seeking.best</Username><Timestamp>1344659713000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 00:35:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344664605000-7</Id><Title>TSMC July sales hugely up: 12% m/m; 37% y/y</Title><Msg>http://www.digitimes.com/news/a20120810VL201.html Morris Chang got paid by big customer Jen Hsun Huang.</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1344664605000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 01:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344665565000-8</Id><Title>New! Wikipad gaming tablet powered by Tegra 3</Title><Msg>http://techblab.net/wikipad-gaming-tablet-10-inch-tegra-3-quad-core-tablets/</Msg><Username>lordgaga81</Username><Timestamp>1344665565000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 02:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>46</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344669910000-9</Id><Topic><Title>wtf Happpened Today...</Title><Username>poellpe</Username><Timestamp>1344640523000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 19:15:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was naive to expect to blast past 15 and 16, especially in one go and at the first attempt. Yesterday was the first time this stock had tried to go past its long term resistance, the 600 MA, and backing up this TA resistance are 4 interleaved resistance points all the way from 14.48 to 16.45. You will need a lot more buying to get from here to past 16.5 but it could happen over time if the news keeps being good. Consider it a very steep wall that has to be climbed but once climbed could unlock much easier progress. http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_N/threadview?m=tm&amp;bn=13029&amp;tid=691216&amp;mid=691224&amp;tof=6&amp;frt=2</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1344669910000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 03:25:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344670215000-10</Id><Topic><Title>wtf Happpened Today...</Title><Username>poellpe</Username><Timestamp>1344640523000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 19:15:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at the action from February. When the 200 MA death crossed the 600 MA it dragged the stock from 16.9 to 14.24. TA is important in understanding stock movements. http://stockcharts.com/c-sc/sc?s=nvda&amp;p=D&amp;yr=1&amp;mn=0&amp;dy=0&amp;i=t48569423554&amp;r=1344512759294</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1344670215000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 03:30:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344680401000-11</Id><Topic><Title>wtf Happpened Today...</Title><Username>poellpe</Username><Timestamp>1344640523000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 19:15:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are full of garbage .There is no 600 day moving average.You seems you don't know what the hell you are talking about.99% of professionals follow the 50 day moving average as a sign of first buying signal but could be false signal unless cont to go up until crosses 200dma and closes above it for a few days.This is the most confirmed buying signal when the stock crosses up 200 dma for a few trading days and the stock will have even huge upside potential by at least 50% to 200% when the stock forms a golden cross line where 50dma crosses up 200 dma.Now i put it to rest for you to learn from the pros.</Msg><Username>nusaiba</Username><Timestamp>1344680401000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 06:20:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344686449000-12</Id><Title>Despite Nexus 7, Asustek's revenues plunge 16%</Title><Msg>- Oh my! My my my. Maybe that Tegra-powered Nexus 7 tablet is doing too well after all? Asustek's revenue plunged 16.14% in July. http://www.digitimes.com/news/a20120810PD206.html Asustek, Pegatron see sequential drops in July revenues Monica Chen, Taipei; Steve Shen, DIGITIMES [Friday 10 August 2012] Asustek Computer has announced revenues of NT$30.207 billion (US$1.01 billion) for July 2012, declining 16.14% on month and 5.18% on year. Asustek CFO David Chang attributed the decline in July revenues to the pending launch of Windows 8 as consumers are wait for new notebooks as well as new motherboards to hit the market. Sales are expected to remain sluggish in August, Chang noted, adding that the overall sales picture will not become clear until mid-October. However, booming sales of the Nexus 7 tablet PC in the US have helped boost Asustek's brand image as well as its sales in that market, Chang claimed. Meanwhile, EMS provider Pegatron Technology has posted consolidated revenues of NT$63.718 billion for July, slipping 3.2% on month but rising 23% on year. For the first seven months of 2012, revenues amounted to NT$394.764 billion, up 66% on year. Pegatron is conservative about its performance for the third quarter and expects its notebook shipments to drop within 10% sequentially due to weak PC demand in the global market." Sales are expected to remain sluggish in August, boys. According to Chief Chang, the out-of-stock Revenue tracker. -</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1344686449000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:00:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>77</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344686949000-13</Id><Topic><Title>wtf Happpened Today...</Title><Username>poellpe</Username><Timestamp>1344640523000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 19:15:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh dear a little knowledge is a dangerous thing in your very clueless hands. Would you consider 'Jordan Roy-Byrne, CMT (Trendsman) is a Chartered Market Technician, a member of the Market Technicians Association and from 2010-2011 an official contributor to the CME Group, the largest futures exchange in the world. He is the publisher and editor of TheDailyGold Premium. Jordan has 14 years of investing experience.' to be a professional ? http://thedailygold.com/author/admin/ Well listen to him talking about the 300 and 600 day averages affecting Gold and Silver prices ... http://www.kitco.com/ind/Trendsman/jan182012A.html The point you are throughly missing is that any amount of days moving average can be important if you can point to a chart and show it has had a direct influence on price movement, i.e. provided support and/or resistance. Currently Nvidia's chart suck, the 600 (14.69) is above the 200 (14.02) and the 200 is above the 50 (13.02) when you really want that all reversed if you want the stock to fly on minimal volume so that you have golden cross and not death cross conditions. The stock will have to stay above the 600 for enough time to allow the 50 to cross the 200 and the 200 to cross the 600 if you want to see $20+ days again. http://stockcharts.com/c-sc/sc?s=nvda&amp;p=D&amp;yr=1&amp;mn=0&amp;dy=0&amp;i=t48569423554&amp;r=1344512759294</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1344686949000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344689444000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Despite Nexus 7, Asustek's revenues plunge 16%</Title><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1344686449000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:00:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Who needs Asus, right boys? Just because Asustek represents 4/9ths of nvidia's tablet part customers, we'll find new ones, don't u know. Eventually. http://www.nvidia.com/object/tegra-supertablets.html &lt; sniff sniff &gt; What's that? Burning Toast? -</Msg><Username>good_point_best</Username><Timestamp>1344689444000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:50:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>72</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344689665000-15</Id><Title>testing</Title><Msg>a test</Msg><Username>lesmwk</Username><Timestamp>1344689665000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344689979000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Despite Nexus 7, Asustek's revenues plunge 16%</Title><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1344686449000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:00:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- "Asustek CFO David Chang attributed the decline in July revenues to the pending launch of Windows 8 as consumers are wait for new notebooks as well as new motherboards to hit the market. Sales are expected to remain sluggish in August, Chang noted, adding that the overall sales picture will not become clear until mid-October." -</Msg><Username>best.again</Username><Timestamp>1344689979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>68</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344691378000-17</Id><Title>testing</Title><Msg>a test</Msg><Username>sgeneris1</Username><Timestamp>1344691378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 09:22:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344692307000-18</Id><Topic><Title>testing</Title><Username>sgeneris1</Username><Timestamp>1344691378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 09:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a test?</Msg><Username>doggonedogeatdog2</Username><Timestamp>1344692307000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 09:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344694837000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Despite Nexus 7, Asustek's revenues plunge 16%</Title><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1344686449000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:00:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somebody can't read, right boys? "Asustek CFO David Chang attributed the decline in July revenues to the pending launch of Windows 8 as consumers are wait for new notebooks as well as new motherboards to hit the market." FAIL</Msg><Username>snakeplizkn</Username><Timestamp>1344694837000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:20:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>40</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344696659000-20</Id><Topic><Title>RSI looking very good on NVIDIA Corporation</Title><Username>vickiprisoc</Username><Timestamp>1344696224000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:43:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RSI of NVDA looking too good, and that was one of the reasons NVDA is temperarily held back RSI is at around 70 now - when it is at this level, a short-term top has been reached until other factors triggers a breakout. With the options expiry approaching, massive efforts are being excerted to push NVDA down for a week - please, do yourself a favor, don't touch those cheap on month calls, the big option players will make sure your August 15 calls are rendered worthless. Some idiots on this board urged innocent folks to buy the options just a few days before earnings - the guy was either evil or insane. Totally clueless.</Msg><Username>lordgaga81</Username><Timestamp>1344696659000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:50:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344697735000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Despite Nexus 7, Asustek's revenues plunge 16%</Title><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1344686449000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:00:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>best the pest is a know Village Idiot on the NVIDIA board. He is the one who gives his own posts all five starts (sometimes &gt; 100 of them) while the most informative posts on NVIDIA products got 100 one-star ratings. A totally mental case....likely an escaped patient from some asylum.</Msg><Username>lordgaga81</Username><Timestamp>1344697735000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:08:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>39</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344698985000-22</Id><Title>Imperative Momentum Stepping In</Title><Msg>I am thrilled! It clearly shows they understand the technical aspects of the stock market and are accurate in predicting its future direction. http://SUCCESSFULTRADERS.INFO</Msg><Username>maximilienehk782</Username><Timestamp>1344698985000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:29:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344699405000-23</Id><Title>Romney picks a Palin</Title><Msg>Ryan is bombastic, polarizing, capable of mixing it up and controversial, all similar characteristics of the last GOP VEEP candidate. Instead of a moderate choice like Pawlenty, someone the public could see as a President should God forbid the need arise, Romney caves to pressure from the GOP power structure. Good job Mitt, you just pulled the same move as McCain and handed the election to Obama.</Msg><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1344699405000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:36:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344700639000-24</Id><Title>Another tegra 3 phone in china</Title><Msg>http://www.digitimes.com/news/a20120809PD223.html China market: K-Touch rolling out low-priced quad-code smartphone Daniel Shen, Taipei; Steve Shen, DIGITIMES [Friday 10 August 2012] China-based smartphone vendor K-Touch has rolled out a quad-core smartphone, the Hornet II, priced at CNY1,999 (US$314) compared to CNY2,999 of a comparable model, the MX4, launched by fellow vendor Meizu in June. K-Touch's pricing for quad-core models will make it difficult for other vendors to set their prices high when they are trying to step into the quad-core segment in China, said industry sources. The Hornet II comes with a 4.5-inch touchscreen, a 1.5GHz Tegra 3 processor, and an 8-megapixel camera, running on Android 4.0. HTC, Samsung Electronics and LG Electronics have already rolled out quad-core models targeting the high-end segment with prices set higher than US$660, the sources noted. China-based ZTE is scheduled to launch its first quad-core model, the Era, in the third quarter with the price likely to be set below CNY3,000 in order to remain competitive, said the sources. Meanwhile, Huawei will delay the launch of its quad-core model, the Ascend D1 Quad to the fourth quarter. Qualcomm's forthcoming quad-core platform, the S4 Pro APQ8064, will attract more China-based smartphone vendors to venture into the segment, pushing the prices of quad-core models down further, said the sources.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1344700639000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:57:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>53</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344703247000-25</Id><Title>Lots of spamers on here now</Title><Msg>I wish Yahoo could wipe these guys out</Msg><Username>a36ftsloop</Username><Timestamp>1344703247000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344703442000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Lots of spamers on here now</Title><Username>a36ftsloop</Username><Timestamp>1344703247000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:40:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Use the 'Report Abuse' button on the right and select Spam from the drop down menu and send and a day later their posts will be removed.</Msg><Username>mas7777728</Username><Timestamp>1344703442000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:44:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344703940000-27</Id><Topic><Title>What a great week for me!</Title><Username>mira_jacklyn21</Username><Timestamp>1344698006000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very good chart analysis.</Msg><Username>sherron_aisha31</Username><Timestamp>1344703940000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:52:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344705388000-28</Id><Title>Positive Writeup in Barrons on NVIDIA</Title><Msg>see page 20 This should get this stock to $20.00 I hope before Thanksgiving.</Msg><Username>deputyhatchet</Username><Timestamp>1344705388000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 13:16:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>47</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344706928000-29</Id><Topic><Title>testing</Title><Username>sgeneris1</Username><Timestamp>1344691378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 09:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a test</Msg><Username>doggone2912</Username><Timestamp>1344706928000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 13:42:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344707710000-30</Id><Title>Longs have nothing to lose sleep on (part 2, a repost)</Title><Msg>eir951 wrote: This is a superior company that is being held back from running. I'd love to hear just a thoughtful justification for the action day to day. We should be in the $20s, but my years of observation of this stock have me feeling we'll see $13s again before we see $20. I would defer to your longtime observations on the daily trading quirks of the stock. (To borrow a Briticism, bollocks to those bloody MM stitch-ups, LOL.) Suffice to say the following: 1) The peculiar (some may call it disproportionate) ‘punishment’ of a particular stock is all but unique. For example, fans of tech stocks like MSFT and MRVL would be the first to agree that these stocks are under-appreciated, and lest one forget, they are both dividend-yielding investments no less, at 2.7 and 2.2% respectively. 2) The previous material supply issue (coupled with the earlier Thai floods) that severely crimped the Q2 y/o/y performance comparison, did take the shine off its once stellar price (justifiably so the shorts would say). But with that overcome (hopefully for a good long while) and the timely adjustment/transition to mobile apps almost fully in gear, NVDA is poised to return to its winning ways in sales numbers and in investors' sentiment--the latter of which is really not that hard to be re-cultivated as numbers become increasingly self-evident. I am especially encouraged by the sanguine outlook issuing forth from the CC on Thursday. The corollary: more analyst updates are a matter of course. 3) Expect no precipitous near-term price shoot-up of NVDA; (we missed out on the mo due to some inopportune market events). As usual, any upward trajectory of the price movement would be marked by gyrations of peaks and valleys, and would surely be moderated by the market mood at large. Yesterday’s rather bizarre trading dynamic is but a reminder of the stock’s extreme vulnerability to external factors. I would agree with ibexx’s remark that the odds of a sub-14 price regression are low and be only fleeting at worst. Now, at the risk of sounding presumptuous (and even Pollyannaish), I would call the high at 16.5 before this quarter is out, with the bulk of trading activities snugly straddling the range between 15 and 16 in this time period. Humor me if there are out there those with lenses of the same ilk as mine. Of course, my prognosis is predicated on a shock-free domestic and global economy during this 3rd Q. (Chances of further serious deterioration of the jobless rate at home are less than 50-50 for the next 3 months; then again further woes from Europe and this time from China cannot be discounted.) 4) ibexx88 posted: PLEASE REFRAIN FROM USING STOP LOSS - the MMs would take one look at the order book and drop the bid precipitously and take your stops, before you know it the bid is raised again and your shares are gone. A salient point made. If one has subscription to level 2 quotes, it is of interest to note that NVDA’s stop losses that are set 20 to 30 cents to the prevailing trading price on any day are by and large triggered more than 50% of the time. One would be better off taking profit outright off the table than using ‘protective’ stops with the assumption that it would turn out to be more ‘profitable’ over the long haul. One final observation: Friday was actually a low volume trading day on the Big Board and NASDAQ. Yet for NVDA it was unusually heavy with almost 3X the usual volume and over twice of the day before. But despite the very heavy volume it did little to shave the price at the end of the day. This I read to be a positive development, in effect a consolidating action of the previous day’s 3% gain. GLTA doggone (had to repost under different handle due to an admin glitch</Msg><Username>lesmwk</Username><Timestamp>1344707710000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 13:55:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>31</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344710306000-31</Id><Title>Which fund got out of their position?</Title><Msg>There can be no other explanation for the volume yesterday. If you think about it, it would be the perfect time for them if they wanted to move their money into another stock with much higher return long term. Just thought.</Msg><Username>ghadji</Username><Timestamp>1344710306000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:38:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344711262000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Romney picks a Palin</Title><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1344699405000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:36:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney is a puppet he doesn't make any decisions, same as his running mate. This is how the good ol boys (GOB) require it.</Msg><Username>ghadji</Username><Timestamp>1344711262000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:54:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344711765000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Romney picks a Palin</Title><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1344699405000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:36:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you just compare Sarah Palin to a Congressman that will shred Biden in a debate, and actually talk dollars and cents solutions to the American people? LOL</Msg><Username>snakeplizkn</Username><Timestamp>1344711765000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:02:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344713111000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Romney picks a Palin</Title><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1344699405000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:36:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryan ran circles around Obama uncovering all the gimmicks, and facts during the presidential summit before they forced through the healthcare bill on Christmas eve. He's extremely capable and knows the budget inside and out unlike Obama.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber22</Username><Timestamp>1344713111000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:25:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344713492000-35</Id><Title>Samsung outs a dual-core ARM Cortex A15 chip with 2560x1600 display support</Title><Msg>http://www.theinquirer.net/inquirer/news/2198158/samsung-outs-a-dualcore-arm-cortex-a15-chip-with-2560x1600-display-support</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344713492000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:31:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>39</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344714032000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's Tegra CPU will be...</Title><Username>crtechni</Username><Timestamp>1344543651000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 16:20:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not discounting the massive influx of sales to Nvidia from the Windows 8 launch in October, I'd like to highlight the massive increase of Android market share with just the Nexus 7 launch alone. Unbelievable uptake on the new era of quad-core devices coming to market faster than you can say Tegra 3. hehehehe MUST READ: http://www.readwriteweb.com/mobile/2012/08/googles-new-nexus-7-tablet-gives-android-an-instant-boost.php Looks like Nvidia has ALL their bases covered. Android, CHECK Windows8, CHECK iOS, ? ;) ;) $37 in 2013 is coming imho.... http://finance.yahoo.com/echarts?s=NVDA+Interactive#symbol=nvda;range=5y;compare=;indicator=volume;charttype=area;crosshair=on;ohlcvalues=0;logscale=off;source=undefined; The CEO said this next quarter will show the massive sales of the Tegra 3 from all the partnerships and product wins. Don't buy at $37, BUY NOW which is totally revealed by the massive volume of the last 4 trading days. http://finance.yahoo.com/q/hp?s=NVDA&amp;a=07&amp;b=7&amp;c=2012&amp;d=07&amp;e=10&amp;f=2012&amp;g=d The SMART MONEY IS IN. =) It's time to let NVDA fly.</Msg><Username>halcyon5224</Username><Timestamp>1344714032000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>31</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344714229000-37</Id><Topic><Title>Uptrending RSI and MACD on NVIDIA Corporation</Title><Username>celestineniedermayer</Username><Timestamp>1344713670000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:34:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WARNING SPAM!</Msg><Username>a36ftsloop</Username><Timestamp>1344714229000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:43:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>21</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344714639000-38</Id><Topic><Title>Another tegra 3 phone in china</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1344700639000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:57:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's good news for consumers. What's even better is that Nvidia's expertise in CPU/GPU integration will be dominating even the great rivals such as Samsung. Tegra/Kepler is a quad-core CPU/12 core GPU (Google Nexus 7) which will surpass the performance and offer the competitive prices that the market craves. ($199, July 2012) Nvidia already IS THE PERFORMANCE LEADER (fastest, most power efficient PAGE2) with Kepler at 32x now. MAY 2012 http://www.nvidia.com/content/PDF/kepler/NV_DS_Tesla_KCompute_Arch_May_2012_LR.pdf</Msg><Username>Mengsai</Username><Timestamp>1344714639000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:50:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>52</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344714909000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung outs a dual-core ARM Cortex A15 chip with 2560x1600 display support</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344713492000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:31:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>meant to reply to this thread, my mistake http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_N/threadview?m=te&amp;bn=13029&amp;tid=691383&amp;mid=691383&amp;tof=1&amp;frt=2#691383</Msg><Username>Mengsai</Username><Timestamp>1344714909000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>32</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344715065000-40</Id><Title>Anyone see this?</Title><Msg>Ostensibly, this is a smart move by Microsoft as it pairs with Intel (Nasdaq: INTC  ) and NVIDIA (Nasdaq: NVDA  ) to maximize power and graphics. These two processing giants are renowned for quality products and should continue that trend with the Surface in connectivity and resolution.</Msg><Username>a36ftsloop</Username><Timestamp>1344715065000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:57:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>20</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344715660000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Which fund got out of their position?</Title><Username>ghadji</Username><Timestamp>1344710306000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:38:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody got out of their positions. They are just stuffing the channel and front running the bid. Crooked as an italian mountain road.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1344715660000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:07:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344715997000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Despite Nexus 7, Asustek's revenues plunge 16%</Title><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1344686449000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:00:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Geez Best, Everybody and their brother is chopping their future outlook here. Except Jen, of course. He owns entirely too much nvidia stock to be honest. Intel. "But the company also cut its revenue guidance somewhat for the third fiscal quarter, citing a challenging macroeconomic environment." Qualcomm Inc. "But the chip-maker “moderated” its full-year view, lowering the top-end of its forecast for both revenue and adjusted earnings per share." Texas Instruments. "The global economic environment is causing both [customers and distributors] to become increasingly cautious in placing new orders. Our backlog grew last quarter but orders slowed in the month of June and our backlog coverage for September is lower than normal." Advancing Micro Devices. "AMD and other chipmakers are grappling with slowing demand, as consumers shift to mobile devices and economic growth weakens in Europe and emerging markets... reflecting disappointing sales in Europe and China." HTC. "HTC’s struggles did not relent in the second quarter as the company’s profit tumbled 58% compared to the same quarter last year. To make matters worse, the company’s third-quarter guidance sees sales dropping by 23% as margins continue to thin. HTC’s revenue declined at an even swifter rate during the first month of the quarter, and investors reacted on Monday and Tuesday by shaving more than $1 billion from the company’s market capitalization in just two days. “HTC’s weak third- quarter outlook means it will continue to lose market share and any market-share gains in China won’t likely offset its substantial loss in its key Europe and U.S. markets." Asustek Computer Inc. "Asustek CFO David Chang attributed the decline in July revenues to the pending launch of Windows 8 as consumers are wait for new notebooks as well as new motherboards to hit the market. Sales are expected to remain sluggish in August, Chang noted, adding that the overall sales picture will not become clear until mid-October." It's a novel excuse, right? "Consumers are waiting for Windows 8 devices to launch." The best excuse yet came from whoever the company was that said that nobody is buying anything until they see the Genuine Apple iPad 3 and iPhone 5 next month. It could be that Nobody actually knows why their order books are shrinking at an alarming rate, so they just guess at the reason. The Chairman would look silly to tell analysts, "I dunno", right? And then other companies start chopping their orders simply because they see the smarter companies like Intel and Qualcomm, saying that their order books have imploded. And the whole thing snowballs because it's become UNFASHIONABLE to be building electronic devices. Or ordering any parts. Like from nvidia. In the interim, why own any semiconductor stock, right? Probably just dead money for six (6) months or so. Maybe longer. -</Msg><Username>geez.best</Username><Timestamp>1344715997000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:13:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>68</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344716707000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Which fund got out of their position?</Title><Username>ghadji</Username><Timestamp>1344710306000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:38:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How would one go about sending a complaint to the SEC? The more complaints the greater the chance of them doing something about this stuff. The news coming out on this company is amazing. I have no doubt it could be a double if they let it play out.</Msg><Username>a36ftsloop</Username><Timestamp>1344716707000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:25:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344716959000-44</Id><Title>Tangled web of buyout amd rumors</Title><Msg>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/external/xwscheats/SIG=13lu2h5og/*http://wallstcheatsheet.com/stocks/qualcomm-considers-amd-purchase-and-4-chip-and-big-data-stocks-on-the-move.html/?ref=YF The question is what are you really getting? 2nd rate graphics? Chips that don't sell? Declining market and market share? Now if they bought Nvidia it would cost a little more but they would get top of the line. Growing market share in growth areas. Honedtly I think we're a better fit with Intel. How about us buying amd? For those who know much more than me,what would they have we could use? Eliminate a graphics competitor. Keeping us beat down in price accomplishes two things. It makes any acquisition we make very expensive while any suitor can save billions in a buyout offer.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1344716959000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:29:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344717458000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Despite Nexus 7, Asustek's revenues plunge 16%</Title><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1344686449000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:00:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jeepers best, aren't you smart enough to know that everytime you use your 30 different yahoo Ids to rate other posters with one star it removes your whole moronic thread off the Board. Somebody is not smart at all, right boys!? FAIL FAIL FAIL</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1344717458000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:37:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>40</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344717682000-46</Id><Topic><Title>Despite Nexus 7, Asustek's revenues plunge 16%</Title><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1344686449000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:00:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somebody can't read, right boys? "Asustek CFO David Chang attributed the decline in July revenues to the pending launch of Windows 8 as consumers are wait for new notebooks as well as new motherboards to hit the market." FAIL</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1344717682000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:41:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>39</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344718308000-47</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's Tegra CPU will be...</Title><Username>crtechni</Username><Timestamp>1344543651000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 16:20:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could be the mini and the Kindle.</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1344718308000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:51:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>31</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344718522000-48</Id><Topic><Title>Longs have nothing to lose sleep on (part 2, a repost)</Title><Username>lesmwk</Username><Timestamp>1344707710000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 13:55:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>also, the run up to earnings was unusual. A lot of swing trade profit taking on Friday.</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1344718522000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:55:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>30</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344718616000-49</Id><Topic><Title>EETimes comments on appointment of AMD's new sales chief (NEGATIVELY)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1344716854000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:27:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD is no longer a threat to NVDA, they missed the mobile market entirely.</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1344718616000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:56:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344718749000-50</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone see this?</Title><Username>a36ftsloop</Username><Timestamp>1344715065000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:57:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MSFT surface is largely ignored here as MSFT has not had any success in the hardware market, save Xbox. If they can achieve even modest sales, NVDA will fly even higher.</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1344718749000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:59:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344719485000-51</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone see this?</Title><Username>a36ftsloop</Username><Timestamp>1344715065000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:57:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MSFT surface is largely ignored here&gt;&gt; You don't know what you are talking about. If you just keep quiet, no one will know you are ignorant.</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1344719485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>21</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344720158000-52</Id><Topic><Title>Tangled web of buyout amd rumors</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1344716959000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD is dirt cheap ~ $3B - NVDA is ~ $10B and they would have to pay at least $12B - $15B because of the growing and healthy profits. Buy AMD for cheap jointly and have joint patent protection - AMD has tonnes of patents in GPUs and CPUs. NVDA buying AMD would be a huge defocus on a X86 market that's barely growing each year vs ARM mobile growing &gt; +30% a year. X86 performance is Process Technology driven - and there is no way to beat Intel at that - you can have a small advantage but it's blown away as soon as Intel comes out with a new process technology node and they are far ahead in that aspect. The X86 architecture is pretty much mature and relatively rigid - that's why it's impossible for it to compete with ARM on a price performance - process node basis.</Msg><Username>qmtai2</Username><Timestamp>1344720158000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:22:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344720278000-53</Id><Topic><Title>Tangled web of buyout amd rumors</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1344716959000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BVDA is not for sale It won't happen have another dream - a more realistic one</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1344720278000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:24:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344720286000-54</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung outs a dual-core ARM Cortex A15 chip with 2560x1600 display support</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344713492000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:31:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- WOW! nvidia gets leap-frogged again! This time by Samsung. Samsung outs a dual-core ARM Cortex A15 chip with 2560x1600 display support Retina display resolution for tablets By Lawrence Latif | Samsung outs a dual-core ARM Cortex A15 chip with 2560x1600 display support Retina display resolution for tablets By Lawrence Latif | Fri Aug 10 2012 16:05 CHIPMAKER Samsung has released the Exynos 5 Dual system-on-chip (SoC) for tablets. Samsung's Exynos SoC processors power a number of high-end smartphones and tablets, however the firm has announced the Exynos 5 Dual will support resolutions higher than Apple's Retina display. The firm said the dual-core chip will support 2560x1600 WQXGA display resolution. Samsung's Exynos 5 Dual is a dual-core 1.7GHz chip that is based on the ARM Cortex A15 architecture. The firm also cited 12.8GB/s bandwidth to two-port 800MHz LPDDR3 RAM but it is the graphics capability of the SoC powered by ARM's Mali T604 architecture that shines, sporting full profile support for OpenCL and OpenGL ES 2.0 as well as 60FPS HD 1080p playback for 3D video. Samsung also touted the Exynos 5 Dual SoC's ability to process 8MP at 30FPS and attach a camera that has zero shutter lag. The firm also said the module's embedded Displayport controller and PHY are integrated into the chip to cut down on power, space and cost. As a graphic illustration of how the desktop monitor market has stagnated, Apple launched the first widely available WQXGA Cinema Display back in 2004 and it has still not been surpassed. Samsung's announcement strongly suggests that next year could see the same 2560x1600 resolution on 7in or 10in displays. For Samsung the Exynos 5 Dual is the first ARM Cortex A15 chip that uses its 32nm High-K metal gate process node. Like most ARM Cortex A15 processors, the Exynos 5 Dual chip is expected to end up in tablets rather than smartphones. µ" Looks like the only left to do with that aging obsolete Tegra line is pull the plug on it, boys. -</Msg><Username>best_design.wins</Username><Timestamp>1344720286000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:24:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>40</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344720409000-55</Id><Topic><Title>Tangled web of buyout amd rumors</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1344716959000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A hostile takeover could only happen to a trouble company where the board and CEO are willing - none of that applies to NVIDIA. I've seen your posts advocating a buyout of NVDA - not fair to your otherwise intelligent contributions to this board.</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1344720409000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344720461000-56</Id><Topic><Title>EETimes comments on appointment of AMD's new sales chief (NEGATIVELY)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1344716854000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:27:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is this fascination in American board rooms with folks who either speaks like they are snorting something or speaks like they are ejaculating something from their rear ends. Can't think of anything else :)</Msg><Username>qmtai2</Username><Timestamp>1344720461000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344720651000-57</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung outs a dual-core ARM Cortex A15 chip with 2560x1600 display support</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344713492000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:31:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Exynos5's CPU performance may not exceed that of Tegra 3" It will probably smoke Tegra 3...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344720651000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:30:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>38</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344720671000-58</Id><Topic><Title>Tangled web of buyout amd rumors</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1344716959000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should read "troubled company"</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1344720671000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:31:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344721193000-59</Id><Topic><Title>Tangled web of buyout amd rumors</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1344716959000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only viable candidates are 1) Intel - antitrust issues potentially and NIH 2) BRCM - At $19B cap they can possibly buy it at $12B ($20 a share)and derive HUGE synergies and provide TOTAL solutions including the nuts and bolts to hold the product together. Jensun would have to run the combined company :) 3. Usoft - NOT. Apple - NOT Anytime soon - NOT! Anytime at all - Almost NEVER So let's talk about next week's price movement - Friday above $15 if unless WW3 starts in EU.</Msg><Username>qmtai2</Username><Timestamp>1344721193000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:39:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344721304000-60</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone see this?</Title><Username>a36ftsloop</Username><Timestamp>1344715065000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:57:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok thanks for the advice. Someone who owns 65k shares from 11.20 Really should know what he's talking about. I agree.</Msg><Username>a36ftsloop</Username><Timestamp>1344721304000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>20</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344721450000-61</Id><Topic><Title>Romney picks a Palin</Title><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1344699405000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:36:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Love it! The only person that would have been a "better" pick would have been Cheney. I hope Cheney is not disappointed. Now we know why Ron Paul was holding out his delegates - can't ask for a better Father Chaperon! :)</Msg><Username>qmtai2</Username><Timestamp>1344721450000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:44:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344721596000-62</Id><Topic><Title>Romney picks a Palin</Title><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1344699405000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:36:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obummer is a one term pres. That was a great move.</Msg><Username>a36ftsloop</Username><Timestamp>1344721596000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344721600000-63</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung outs a dual-core ARM Cortex A15 chip with 2560x1600 display support</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344713492000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:31:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>clock tick for clock tick, A15s are 50% more performance than A9s. And I believe A15s are built to run up to 2G. At 2G it will be equal to Tegra 3 running at 1.5G. That's multi-thread benchmark. For everyday use where things are not that multi-threaded, dual core A15 will offer a better user experience. The two hottest names of mobile are more than keeping up their processor dev of nvda. All that extra money piled on by Jen has not really produced any real processor advantage nor enough sales to break even.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1344721600000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:46:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>42</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344721744000-64</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone see this?</Title><Username>a36ftsloop</Username><Timestamp>1344715065000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:57:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a p.r.I.c.k. But we all know that by now</Msg><Username>a36ftsloop</Username><Timestamp>1344721744000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:49:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>20</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344723670000-65</Id><Topic><Title>Barron's big article on NVIDIA - why it looks attractive""""</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1344707680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 13:54:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great read. Thank you</Msg><Username>a36ftsloop</Username><Timestamp>1344723670000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 18:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>44</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344723731000-66</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung outs a dual-core ARM Cortex A15 chip with 2560x1600 display support</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344713492000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:31:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.anandtech.com/show/6148/samsung-announces-a15malit604-based-exynos-5-dual</Msg><Username>mas798</Username><Timestamp>1344723731000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 18:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>35</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344724144000-67</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung outs a dual-core ARM Cortex A15 chip with 2560x1600 display support</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344713492000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:31:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- "Samsung, having manufactured the A5X for Apple, learned from the best." Hey! Everybody is slavishly rippin' me off! -</Msg><Username>ibest.here</Username><Timestamp>1344724144000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 18:29:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>41</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344724184000-68</Id><Title>If there was ever a buyout candidate nvda</Title><Msg>Is it. Now with Lenovo on board. And a chip shortage That won't end. Someone's gonna gobble them up Also they gave rev guidance of 1.25 bil That may rise is supply constraints ease No brainier stocks going higher</Msg><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1344724184000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 18:29:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344724619000-69</Id><Topic><Title>If there was ever a buyout candidate nvda</Title><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1344724184000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 18:29:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Did you forget? Microsoft has First and Last Rights of Refusal. On the whole place. Jen gave 'em a free Call option. They really should make nvidia "legend stock". Where they print in red down the left margin, "These shares are subject to a Call held by Microsoft. 'Cause folks are Always forgetting that. -</Msg><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1344724619000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 18:36:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344725102000-70</Id><Topic><Title>Tangled web of buyout amd rumors</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1344716959000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOu were way off your rocker, sir! BRCM? There is nothing in Broadcom's product mix that Jen Hsun would want. Broadcom is basically a "Dollar General" store - a little bit of everything but nothing really outstanding. Now I can accurately gauge your intelligence/knowledge levels - not very becoming, so don't even ask!</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1344725102000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 18:45:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344726624000-71</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone see this?</Title><Username>a36ftsloop</Username><Timestamp>1344715065000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 15:57:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for a mature response</Msg><Username>a36ftsloop</Username><Timestamp>1344726624000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 19:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344730010000-72</Id><Topic><Title>Despite Nexus 7, Asustek's revenues plunge 16%</Title><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1344686449000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:00:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somebody can't read, right boys? "Asustek CFO David Chang attributed the decline in July revenues to the pending launch of Windows 8 as consumers are wait for new notebooks as well as new motherboards to hit the market." FAIL</Msg><Username>snakeplizkn</Username><Timestamp>1344730010000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 20:06:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>41</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344730402000-73</Id><Topic><Title>Summary of NVIDIA news this week (1)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1344708833000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:13:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the post</Msg><Username>snakeplizkn</Username><Timestamp>1344730402000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 20:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>47</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344730510000-74</Id><Topic><Title>Positive Writeup in Barrons on NVIDIA</Title><Username>deputyhatchet</Username><Timestamp>1344705388000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 13:16:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Positive news is all over the place, should trend up next week to mid 15s, at least.</Msg><Username>snakeplizkn</Username><Timestamp>1344730510000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 20:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>46</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344730652000-75</Id><Topic><Title>Barron's big article on NVIDIA - why it looks attractive""""</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1344707680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 13:54:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great, thanks</Msg><Username>snakeplizkn</Username><Timestamp>1344730652000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 20:17:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>45</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344730764000-76</Id><Topic><Title>New! Wikipad gaming tablet powered by Tegra 3</Title><Username>lordgaga81</Username><Timestamp>1344665565000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 02:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gaming has been a big driver of graphics in tablets.</Msg><Username>snakeplizkn</Username><Timestamp>1344730764000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 20:19:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>48</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344732488000-77</Id><Topic><Title>Positive Writeup in Barrons on NVIDIA</Title><Username>deputyhatchet</Username><Timestamp>1344705388000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 13:16:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not optionx expiry week...</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1344732488000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 20:48:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>33</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344737106000-78</Id><Topic><Title>Tangled web of buyout amd rumors</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1344716959000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Last I checked - you need more than a CPU/GPU to make a cell phone or a tablet for starters - Power Management, GPS, NFC, and Wifi. Broadcom when they are ready with their Arm Mobile offerings would be a very serious threat because they have everything under one roof and their RF solutions are probably the most advance and most integrated in the market - perfect for Mobile. The only missing piece is a great Arm CPU/GPU. Nvidia is very weak outside of the CPU/GPU - that's why these two would be a killer combo. QCOM bought Atheros so they can own more of what goes into the CP/Tablets and eventually hope to be a one stop shop.</Msg><Username>qmtai2</Username><Timestamp>1344737106000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 22:05:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>