<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348980394600-1</Id><Topic><Title>Tim has Cooked Apple - Put A Fork In It: It Is Done</Title><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1348972564903</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a Are you pumper boys STILL whining? Whining whining whining. About losing out on the sale of Two Hundred Million (200,000,000) cellphone parts. For the Genuine Apple iPhone 5. Well actually, it's Four Hundred Million (400,000,000) cellphone parts that nvidia cuda won.. If you count the processor and baseband radio chips separately. The Largest Cellphone Parts Order in the History of the Industry. And nvidia lost out on both parts. ( sigh ) Give it up, boys. Bashing Apple after losing that Elephantine order isn't gonna move nvda by one penny ($000.01). Nope. It'll just make folks think that Jen hired a bunch of incessant whiners.</Msg><Username>dr.bester</Username><Timestamp>1348980394600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:46:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348980752726-2</Id><Topic><Title>Head and Shoulders Playing Out for NVDA</Title><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1348950381602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 16:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The unfortunate thing is there r some truth to what u r saying. In April 2012, when it broke the slanted neckline, it fell $3 hard. This time, unless it rallies fast, else it may be heading down again.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348980752726</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:52:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348981590247-3</Id><Topic><Title>INtel's claim of Clover Trail TDP being 1.7 mW is completely misleading....this number applies only to an idle state</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348980031648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow! Just 1.7 milliwatts of juice when the Intel x86 Clover Trail device is in idle. That's really really low power. Sounds like the Intel x86 Clover Trail beats the pants off the Tegra 3's little Ninja core in power management. Read all about it: Tegra 3 missed performance goals by wide margins</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1348981590247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:06:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348981634127-4</Id><Title>One thing that frustrates me about nvidia, kai phone promises</Title><Msg>They r early in their foray into quad core. They promised cheap quad core phones. Yet they delay launching til competition from qualcom and mediatek caught up with them. Now others are getting many design wins. #$%$!</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348981634127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:07:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348982693302-5</Id><Title>Where's the iDiot who's so proud of his iphone5? !</Title><Msg>He boasts changing from his BB and that iPhone 5 sold 5 mil units fast. IPhone one to four did not have such long laundry lists of problems. IPhone one to four did not have its CEO coming out to apologize. IPhone 5 sold well not bcos of its greatness but bcos of one to fours success. This iDiot really should just shove his iPhone into HisAss.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348982693302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:24:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348982766195-6</Id><Topic><Title>One thing that frustrates me about nvidia, kai phone promises</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348981634127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:07:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Making mulit-generational wealth on nvda is an art. 1. Sell on the promises and marketing hype. 2. Buy-to-Close on the delays and missed specs and lost orders. 3. Whistle on the way to the Bank. 4. Repeat with every chip generation. Remember all the Project Denver hype to took nvda to $26? Multi-generational wealth was made on THAT one for sure. The original Project Denver scheme to copycat a Genuine Intel x86 processor failed so badly that they Abandoned the project. Pity the frustrated folks that bought the hype at $26.</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1348982766195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:26:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348984005969-7</Id><Topic><Title>One thing that frustrates me about nvidia, kai phone promises</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348981634127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:07:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U r right. I never buy their hype. They are marketing guys. I was only surprised that til now, they did not push up stocks higher so that they could announce some crap for a euphoria to unload shares. It usually happens every 2 year's. Every 2 year's it will have a double share price from its low. At least a double. This low is $11.5, yet doesn't seem to be happening. Head and shoulder top seems to be in place.If so, u r right. This is gonna go quite lower.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348984005969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348984472294-8</Id><Topic><Title>One thing that frustrates me about nvidia, kai phone promises</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348981634127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:07:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why I agree and disagree when u bashers say this is a pos. Agree bcos Nvidia is not for buy and hold strategy. It's for trading. Buy low sell high. Only disagree that this a pos below $15, cos thought its low enough . But who knows how low is low. Sigh.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348984472294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:54:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348986630315-9</Id><Title>Intel's Rosepoint is here. The Intel Atom plus digital radio</Title><Msg>Man 'o Man! Those guys at Intel work fast. Much faster than the dawdlers at icera/nvidia, that's for sure. BEHOLD, BOYS! The first-ever Genuine Intel Atom processor -- with integrated digital radio. That's right -- all right there on the same little piece of Intel silicon. Like Qualcomm does. Google this, boys: How large is Intel's digital radio? Impressive, right? It sure is. But the question from nvidia shareholders is -- where the heck is nvidia's "Grey"? The acquisition of icera was announced May 9, 2011 for $367,000,000.00 of shareholder's cash -- for the sole purpose of putting a cheap little radio in the Tegra chips, right? And what has happened since, you ask? Delay after delay after delay after delay after delay. "End of 2013" is the latest word. As in, more than two-and-a-half YEARS after buying icera. As in, Still More Than a Year From Now. At best.....</Msg><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1348986630315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 02:30:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348995189391-10</Id><Topic><Title>INtel's claim of Clover Trail TDP being 1.7 mW is completely misleading....this number applies only to an idle state</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348980031648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only 1.7W for a quad-threaded 1.8 GHz dual-core when going flat out which is half what the previous 3W single-core 1.5 GHz Z670 did so Intel have improved their tablet performance/watt by a factor of 4 going from 45nm to 32nm. arkDOTintelDOTcom/products/70105/Intel-Atom-Processor-Z2760-1MB-Cache-1_80-GHz arkDOTintelDOTcom/products/55663/ Both the cpu and gpu performance of Cloverview will exceed the 2W Tegra 3 by 50% at lower power and only 15% greater die size and unlike Nvidia they don't have to pay a foundry to make them making true net margins greater. It will also have full PC business legacy compatibility. eetimesDOTcom/electronics-news/4397303/Slideshow--Intel-carves-new-path-to-x86-tablets pcworldDOTcom/article/2010798/clover-trail-tablets-pitched-as-workplacefriendly.html The gpu will be a bit faster per clock than Apple's one ... POWERVR SGX545 delivers real-world performance of 40 million polygons/sec and 1 Gpixels/sec fillrate at 200MHz imgtecDOTcom/news/Release/index.asp?NewsID=516 POWERVR SGX543 delivers real-world performance of 35 million polygons/sec and 1 Gpixels/sec fillrate at 200MHz imgtecDOTcom/News/Release/index.asp?NewsID=428</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348995189391</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 04:53:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349006236693-11</Id><Topic><Title>One thing that frustrates me about nvidia, kai phone promises</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348981634127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:07:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't expect much phone penetration till integrated LTE...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349006236693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 07:57:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349008488869-12</Id><Topic><Title>Tim has Cooked Apple - Put A Fork In It: It Is Done</Title><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1348972564903</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jobs had his share of mistakes over the years like the antenna issue that never should have happened. His I pad mini proclamation has turned out to be wrong. The fact that the competition is forcing Apple into a shorter development time on bringing features to market is starting to show. Perhaps they can count on the complete dedication of their user base to buy irregardless of any quality deficiencies such as maps which is the worst in the mobile world.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber22</Username><Timestamp>1349008488869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 08:34:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349009375138-13</Id><Topic><Title>INtel's claim of Clover Trail TDP being 1.7 mW is completely misleading....this number applies only to an idle state</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348980031648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra 3 is 100mW idle in comparison vr-zoneDOTcom/articles/mwc-2012-nvidia-samples-tegra-3--tegra-4-to-oem-partners/15014.html 'Bear in mind that first generation of Tegra 3 cores only worked at 1.3-1.4GHz, as the company was constrained by strict thermal guidelines (100 mW idle, 2W TDP).'</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349009375138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 08:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349012813537-14</Id><Title>Baller and the pumper boyz here can say they want</Title><Msg>about how much 'Office is worth this or that', how much 'genuine windoz expeirence is worth this or that'..... but at end of the day, if winRT is not sub $350, Ballmer is conceding the whole sub $500 space to non-windows appliances. That has already happened for netbooks. And of course, once that happens, will be like Detroit conceding small cars in the 70s.... once it got going, it encroaches UP. Ballmer can taking apart the whole PC ecosystem (bye bye HP, Dell, Acer, Lenovo.....) and learn a new way of making a living.... or he can be labeled as the guy who destroyed the franchise. Same for intel. Take apart the sweet margins and start selling $20 SoCs, or watch their processor market share fall apart. No more wintel tax. Go el goog go!</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1349012813537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:46:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349013853822-15</Id><Topic><Title>Baller and the pumper boyz here can say they want</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1349012813537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe what u say is true. Only this way can msft have a strong app store. And strong app store will attract more users. An expensive device will reduce adoption rate and users may not have patience to wait for app store development. Unless of course windows phone sell like hot cakes. Which I am not too sure. Also ever since balmer spoke, msft share price been labouring. It was strong when. rumor has it that win rt is selling at 299 or 199 . But once he classified it ain't gonna be, uh oh!</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349013853822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:04:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349016272765-16</Id><Topic><Title>INtel's claim of Clover Trail TDP being 1.7 mW is completely misleading....this number applies only to an idle state</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348980031648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The new Intel x86 Clover Trail uses just 1.7 milliwatts of juice when it's in idle mode. Yet the Tegra 3 uses a whopping 100 milliwatts when that fifth little ninja core claims to be idling around -- but probably isn't. So Best? It's nvidia mismanagement again, right? Of the little nvidia ninja core. It's supposed to be in its little ninja bed -- asleep. But noooooo. It's up listening to tunes on its little ninja iPod, using its little ninja hairdryer, talking to its little ninja friends on its little ninja cellpone -- all sorts of stuff. Resulting in the little ninja core using a whole bunch of juice when it's in "idle". Clearly a total lack of ninja management. Again.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1349016272765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349020137601-17</Id><Topic><Title>One thing that frustrates me about nvidia, kai phone promises</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348981634127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:07:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Don't expect much phone penetration till integrated LTE....", writes getanid61 in denial. Dude -- Give it up. The SoC + integrated radio ship has sailed. Without nvidia. By the time dawdling nvidia get around to releasing its "Grey" chip in late 2013, they will be over Two Years behind Qualcomm, and One Year behind Intel. Who will do doubt be into their second generation LTE radios by then. And have all the best OEM's on long-term purchase orders already. The ship has sailed without nvidia. Again.</Msg><Username>bestodon</Username><Timestamp>1349020137601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349021573975-18</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Rosepoint is here. The Intel Atom plus digital radio</Title><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1348986630315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 02:30:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That LTE integrated radio ship has sailed, Best. Without nvidia. By the time the dawdlers at icera/nvidia get their integrated LTE working, all the best OEM's will have signed long-term purchase orders. Elsewhere.</Msg><Username>bestodon</Username><Timestamp>1349021573975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:12:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349022570664-19</Id><Topic><Title>Baller and the pumper boyz here can say they want</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1349012813537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>intel has exactly the same problem as msft. The question is not about the technical merits of Atom, I have zero doubt intc will get it there one day. Is intel ready to $20 soc biz? no more wintel tax, how sweet. tks el goog!</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1349022570664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:29:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349025193971-20</Id><Topic><Title>INtel's claim of Clover Trail TDP being 1.7 mW is completely misleading....this number applies only to an idle state</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348980031648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Best, you are one funny witty guy and right most of the time lol. Actually I am not totally convinced that the Ninja core doesn't have a lower sleep state but damned if I can find a number for it anywhere. Perhaps if Nvidia started giving out proper datasheet like documentation instead of glossy misleading slides they might help their cause more !</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349025193971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:13:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349027501321-21</Id><Topic><Title>INtel's claim of Clover Trail TDP being 1.7 mW is completely misleading....this number applies only to an idle state</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348980031648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mars, Do those glossy, misleading slides which substitute for Tegra 3 "spec sheets" mention anything about an "integrated ninja mini bar?"</Msg><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1349027501321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:51:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349028799844-22</Id><Title>shadow CEO tells of acquiring another company</Title><Msg>great to have cash in these times..</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349028799844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:13:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349034825968-23</Id><Topic><Title>shadow CEO tells of acquiring another company</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349028799844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:13:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Market will punish this stock, -- and punish it Badly -- if Jen makes another lame acquisition like icera. The quickest way to $10 bucks, boys. "Nvidia today announces the acquisition of....."</Msg><Username>i_know_best</Username><Timestamp>1349034825968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:53:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349036828469-24</Id><Topic><Title>Head and Shoulders Playing Out for NVDA</Title><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1348950381602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 16:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would rather sell than buy, based on mixed signals. NVDA Technical Analysis Summary: NEUTRAL Moving Averages: STRONG SELL Indicators: MILD BUY</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1349036828469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349037194377-25</Id><Topic><Title>Head and Shoulders Playing Out for NVDA</Title><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1348950381602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 16:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You belong on Fox News or the Wall Street Journal blogs. TA is based on probabilities, and works 90 percent of the time. That's all I'm posting. You don't have to believe everything you read on these boards, but don't accuse anyone of fund raising for the loser Romney. It's the worst insult you can hurl at anybody. Obama has him by the jugular and will crush him come election day.</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1349037194377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:33:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349037548431-26</Id><Title>September 28 short interest</Title><Msg>Will know this week how much the short interest on NVDA has changed. A higher short interest may be a good thing, because this has such a high Beta.</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1349037548431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:39:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349039912571-27</Id><Topic><Title>September 28 short interest</Title><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1349037548431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:39:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A higher short interest IS a good thing for the shorts. Given the history of insider trading in this stock (*), it probably means that the hedgies have received Bad News from their nvidia insider connections, -- like a copy of the First Trial Balance or something -- and they are merrily shorting accordingly. (*) Looking for a good education in the history of insider trading in nvidia stock? Copy this: Feds crack down on insider trading -- nvidia mentioned Then scroll up to the upper left of this page. And paste it into the box that says Search, right below where it says NVIDIA Corporation Message Board. Happy reading, boys. Oh, and be sure to look for the word "tippees". Ya gotta Love that word, right? Tippees</Msg><Username>i_know_best</Username><Timestamp>1349039912571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349040502574-28</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel's Clover Trail SoC a "bloated nightmare" (fast forward to answer: Y)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348898962339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 02:09:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ha! Oh dear, one particular intel fanboi looks stupid today. Not for the first time though.</Msg><Username>daysofshred30000000000</Username><Timestamp>1349040502574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:28:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349040600369-29</Id><Topic><Title>September 28 short interest</Title><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1349037548431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:39:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? I some parts of the country -- primarily around Madison Wisconsin -- that another name for cows, right? Tippees</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1349040600369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:30:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349040698108-30</Id><Topic><Title>INtel's claim of Clover Trail TDP being 1.7 mW is completely misleading....this number applies only to an idle state</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348980031648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Makes sense . It will be in sleep modus most of the day anyways due to lack of decent AUTONOMY...lol</Msg><Username>daysofshred30000000000</Username><Timestamp>1349040698108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:31:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349040699520-31</Id><Topic><Title>INtel's claim of Clover Trail TDP being 1.7 mW is completely misleading....this number applies only to an idle state</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348980031648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Makes sense . It will be in sleep modus most of the day anyways due to lack of decent AUTONOMY...lol</Msg><Username>daysofshred30000000000</Username><Timestamp>1349040699520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349041010343-32</Id><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Msg>Thinking about buying 500shares For my daughter</Msg><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349041614413-33</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why, that's impossible to answer without know the circumstances. 1. How much do you like your daughter? 2. Can she afford to lose Everything? 3. Do she already own Apple?</Msg><Username>good_one_best</Username><Timestamp>1349041614413</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:46:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349041795165-34</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She's only 3years old</Msg><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041795165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:49:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349043117924-35</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a leading edge technology stock, they are all risky calculated gambles over that length of period as the technology and competition can change so much over that period. You might want to take annual reviews if you do. This stock looks stable enough for the next year and might even rise a bit if the results are good. Stock is currently being bottled by all its moving averages which are overhead.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349043117924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:11:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349043426509-36</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel's Clover Trail SoC a "bloated nightmare" (fast forward to answer: Y)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348898962339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 02:09:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No-one is as stupid as you, the Nvidia pumper who was buying all the way from $26 to $13 during 2011 while claiming it was on the way to $40 by Dec 2011 ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349043426509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:17:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349046116648-37</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Long term.... yes NVidia will be in forefront of ARM64 CPUs... which will take over the planet over the next decade...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349046116648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:01:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349046866098-38</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Give a daugher some stock, and you'll feed her for a week. Teach your daughter how to count cards in Vegas, and she'll take care of her old man for a lifetime."</Msg><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1349046866098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:14:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349047750756-39</Id><Topic><Title>September 28 short interest</Title><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1349037548431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:39:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm referring to a potential short squeeze that could take it higher.</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1349047750756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349048178083-40</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy something that pays a dividend and has been around some time. Like Pfizer, Alcoa, or some other Dow stock. If you must own technology, MSFT or INTC may be better. Good dividend and growth potential.</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1349048178083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349049402163-41</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never buy stock in a company who's life expectancy is significantly less than the buyer's. -- Bestfucius</Msg><Username>bestfucius</Username><Timestamp>1349049402163</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:56:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349051300751-42</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Buy something that pays a dividend" NVDA is my only stock that doesn't... I keep it for this company is gonna grow this decade... Too many new markets they're going into &amp; expanding...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349051300751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 20:28:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349051434906-43</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You hope ;-). Apple's 64-bit chip is guaranteed sales, is Nvidia's ? Anyway I don't think you have quite understood how this competition thing works, the customers decides the winners not the big OEMs otherwise 64-bit Intel IA-64 Itaniums would be all the rage rather than the AMD designed x86-64 products which Intel was forced to copy due to customer demand.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349051434906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 20:30:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349052270615-44</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't mean they will be successful in any if them. This mobile SoC business was supposed to be running at $1bn annual revenue and breakeven by now, how is that turning out ? Intel and AMD are bringing out more and more powerful integrated cpu/gpu designs every generation which actually impacts on the core business here. This company's success or even its long term existence is not guaranteed.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349052270615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 20:44:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349054042942-45</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I don't think you have quite understood how this competition thing works" Sure... NOT !!! " the customers decides the winners not the big OEMs" Hmmm...guess if Apple chooses a Broadcom modem instead of a Qualcomm modem... the customer may not buy it... Apple's decision has NO impact then.... IF Apple would choose another SOC, would customers care... Must be true for OEMs too :)</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349054042942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:14:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349054619268-46</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This mobile SoC business was supposed to be running at $1bn annual revenue and breakeven by now" Agree... "how is that turning out ? " slower than advertised... "Intel and AMD are bringing out more and more powerful integrated cpu/gpu designs every generation which actually impacts on the core business" True again... but NVidia will come out with more powerful integrated cpu/gpu and is going into new markets with the introduction of their ARM64... you completely under-estimate the impact of this one !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!'</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349054619268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349055129272-47</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia is not an OEM and is reliant on a popular big OEM first choosing it and then secondly having a commercially successful product. Neither is guaranteed over many years. So far Tegra 1, 2 and 3 have all been commercially unsuccessful in that they have collectively cost more to develop than the profit they have brought in. Meanwhile in 2013 Haswell and Xeon Phi will have Nvidia's core profitable businesses, GPU and PSB, clearly in its target sights ....</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349055129272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:32:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349055475879-48</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't Wayne supposed to be here by now, Stark next year ? How about the Tegra 3+ ? I am not underestimating anything as nothing new is appearing fast as I told you it wouldn't at the time. Nvidia are always way too optimistic in their forecasts. Project Denver, Maxwell ? Where are all these products ? If you go back far enough on Nvidia's glossy forecasts slides they should all be appearing now or soon.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349055475879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:37:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349055846586-49</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you waste your time on the nvda board? No self respect?</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1349055846586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349056354833-50</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nvidia is not an OEM" ya think... "and is reliant on a popular big OEM first choosing it and then secondly having a commercially successful product." yeah...same for their competitors... "So far Tegra 1, 2 and 3 have all been commercially unsuccessful in that they have collectively cost more to develop than the profit they have brought in. " yeah... but Tegra revenue is growing... every product develops the infrastructure more... and Microsoft is porting to ARM !!!! "Meanwhile in 2013 Haswell and Xeon Phi" Yes, Xeon Phi, How many more $Billions$ has INtel lost on Xeon Phi than NVidia has lost on Tegra ?? It was $3B at Larrabee... :) "will have Nvidia's core profitable businesses" not nearly as much as ARM64 will have on INtel's core profitable businesses... "GPU and PSB, clearly in its target sights ...." Agree... but INtel has been trying to commoditize the GPU for 15 yrs now... as you say, "How did that work out"...?? :)</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349056354833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349056554765-51</Id><Topic><Title>Tim has Cooked Apple - Put A Fork In It: It Is Done</Title><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1348972564903</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To wit, check out this video youtubeDOTcom/watch?v=d9jQYYX0LI0</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1349056554765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349056895834-52</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Wasn't Wayne supposed to be here by now, Stark next year ?" Yes, everything seems to have got pushed back a year... "I am not underestimating anything as nothing new is appearing fast as I told you it wouldn't at the time. " I don't think anyone is expecting Tegra 4 before Q1 2013 "Nvidia are always way too optimistic in their forecasts. Project Denver, Maxwell ?" Last statements said Project Denver next year, and Maxwell 2014... Though they've hinted we might see a first Project Denver look in Q4 this year... "Where are all these products ? " Where is 2013 ?? Speaking of forecasts... How much was INtel off for Larrabee... I mean Xeon Phi ?? btw, good to have you back...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349056895834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 22:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349057060728-53</Id><Title>Must See: great iPhone video</Title><Msg>Check out youtubeDOTcom/watch?v=d9jQYYX0LI0</Msg><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1349057060728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 22:04:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349060221757-54</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good stock to hold For next.20years?</Title><Username>robvano79</Username><Timestamp>1349041010343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just judging from your reply...have you ever attended an actual school? You sound like you are dumber than a rock.</Msg><Username>t84b49</Username><Timestamp>1349060221757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 22:57:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349060571141-55</Id><Title>U.S. appeals court to Google: Your injunction in Germany is nonsense. Now go FRAND your patents.</Title><Msg>HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA ! Google/Motorola had won an injunction banning Microsoft's stuff in Germany, right? Microsoft appealed it. And the U.S. Appeals Court told Google/Motorola that their "injunction" in Germany was crapola -- and to license the disputed patents to Microsoft -- under FRAND (Fair, Reasonable, and Non-Discriminatory) terms. So Google/Motorola thought they had a Ban on Microsoft's stuff for the planet, -- starting with Germany -- and instead came out of the U.S. Appeals Court with nothing but a new garden-variety tear-it-off-the-pad FRAND licensee -- namely Microsoft. HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA ! You can "search" for news of Google's latest court Defeat by cutting-and-pasting this: Google loses appeal, continues to be barred from enforcing German injunction against Microsoft "The noose keeps tightening [on Google] and it appears to be only a question of when, not if, Motorola will have to extend a standard-essential patent license to Microsoft on truly FRAND terms."</Msg><Username>bestfucius</Username><Timestamp>1349060571141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:02:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>18</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349061762662-56</Id><Topic><Title>Tim has Cooked Apple - Put A Fork In It: It Is Done</Title><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1348972564903</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Source: Washington Post Ever find yourself frustrated with how smoothly Siri seems to work for the folks in Apple’s commercials but not for you? A New York man has filed a class-action suit against Apple, saying that the company has been “misleading and deceptive” about what the iPhone 4S virtual assistant can do. “For example,” the suit reads, “in many of Apple’s television advertisements, individuals are shown using Siri to make appointments, find restaurants and even learn the guitar chords to classic rock songs or how to tie a tie.” According to the plaintiff, Frank M. Fazio, the commercials have misled him to buy the iPhone 4S to get Siri but that he has had a lot of trouble using the software. The lawsuit claims that Apple’s advertisements are “fiction.” wwwDOTwashingtonpostDOTcom/business/technology/apple-hit-with-siri-suit-over-what-the-program-can-really-do/2012/03/13/gIQAYdmS9R_story.html</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1349061762662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349061771779-57</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. appeals court to Google: Your injunction in Germany is nonsense. Now go FRAND your patents.</Title><Username>bestfucius</Username><Timestamp>1349060571141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:02:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? Maybe Google could { wait for it now } SEARCH for a Higher Court? HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA !</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1349061771779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:22:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349062656414-58</Id><Topic><Title>Tim has Cooked Apple - Put A Fork In It: It Is Done</Title><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1348972564903</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While Apple have spent recent times mainly focused on accusing other companies of copying trivial things from their products (said to even include the shape of a rounded rectangle), they are now on the receiving end of such claims themselves, with a railway authority in Switzerland accusing the American technology giant of blatantly copying a famous clock design that they created in the 1940′s. The iOS6 system update for Apple products featured a facelift for a number of areas of basic service on their products, including their ‘clock’ app, which the state-owned Swiss Federal Railways company (Schweizerische Bundesbahnen, SBB) recognise as their own trademark, with claims that Apple have unlawfully copied the design (with their digital version appearing identical to the SBB’s) and that they are now drafting a lawsuit for compensation or removal of Apple’s clock. The design, which notably features a circular tip to the red ’second’ hand, was a creation of SBB employee Hans Hilfiker in 1944, and is commonly used in railway stations worldwide (particularly Switzerland) due to its global recognition for reliability, and also seen on watches from Mondaine, who hold a licence to use the patented design. An SBB spokesperson stated to local newspaper Tages-Anzeiger that while the company were pleased Apple paid tribute to the design by using it, they had no right to put it on their product. It is claimed that Apple have been in similar arguments over clocks before, only in 2009, they were the ones threatening app makers Tapbots due to their clock being ‘too similar’ to the one on iOS. The resemblance between the latest one on the operating system and the long-standing Swiss railway design, though, is one that is obvious, so surely this would class as part of the ‘stealing’ that Apple preach other companies not to do? They must have done something wrong here, as it probably takes a bit of added effort to annoy people in the world’s most politically-neutral country… Source: wwwDOTworldtvpcDOTcom/blog/apple-accused-of-stealing-design-like-swiss-clockwork/#ixzz280zEryw5</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1349062656414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:37:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>