<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346559027228-1</Id><Topic><Title>The new Wahoo should also investigate jeepers.best's attempted bribery (also known bestnhighest.wins and 100 other Wahoo IDs)</Title><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1346556033571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 23:20:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Besty, you are not reporting me to the new Yahoo for the attempted bribery reference? Oh I wonder why? I know, I know - I could just hear you praying in your soiled seat, and hoping the new Y admin wouldn't find out and everyone would just forget. Well, I won't let that happen. LOL</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1346559027228</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:10:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346559027243-2</Id><Topic><Title>The new Wahoo should also investigate jeepers.best's attempted bribery (also known bestnhighest.wins and 100 other Wahoo IDs)</Title><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1346556033571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 23:20:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Besty, you are not reporting me to the new Yahoo for the attempted bribery reference? Oh I wonder why? I know, I know - I could just hear you praying in your soiled seat, and hoping the new Y admin wouldn't find out and everyone would just forget. Well, I won't let that happen. LOL</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1346559027243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:10:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346559027332-3</Id><Topic><Title>The new Wahoo should also investigate jeepers.best's attempted bribery (also known bestnhighest.wins and 100 other Wahoo IDs)</Title><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1346556033571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 23:20:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Besty, you are not reporting me to the new Yahoo for the attempted bribery reference? Oh I wonder why? I know, I know - I could just hear you praying in your soiled seat, and hoping the new Y admin wouldn't find out and everyone would just forget. Well, I won't let that happen. LOL</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1346559027332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:10:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346560620740-4</Id><Topic><Title>EXTRA! EXTRA! -- Apple Sues Samsung Over 4 More iPatents</Title><Username>bestville_daily_gazette</Username><Timestamp>1346554228339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:50:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . Kinda begs the question, right boys? It sure does. Just how much revenue nvidia loses if Apple's iAttorneys are meritorious in getting the Samsung Captivate Glide -- powered by the nvidia Tegra 2, don't u know -- banned from sale in these United States? Guess we'll just have to wait for the Court documents to find out the volume of Samsung Captivate Glides made. . .</Msg><Username>best.again</Username><Timestamp>1346560620740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:37:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346565323108-5</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: Production of iPhone screens delayed at Sharp</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346564330410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 01:38:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . "Sharp is one of the THREE suppliers of liquid-crystal-display panels for the next iPhone. The other two suppliers are Japan Display Inc. -- a new company that combined three Japanese electronics makers' display units -- and South Korea's LG Display Co. (034220.SE). LG Display and Japan Display HAVE started shipping the screens to Apple, according to people familiar with the situation. It is unclear whether the delay at Sharp could lead to supply problems for the new iPhone. Carolyn Wu, a Beijing-based spokeswoman for Apple, declined to comment. In July, people familiar with the situation said that the next iPhone will use in-cell LCD panels, a new technology that makes the smartphone's screen thinner by integrating touch sensors into the LCD, eliminating the need for a separate touch-screen layer. But the people said that in-cell panels are technologically more difficult to mass produce compared with conventional LCD panels. LG Display Chief Executive Han Sang-beom said last week the company began mass producing in-cell LCD panels." Three (3) suppliers, boys. And two appear to be cranking out Apple's thinner, more technologically advanced LCD panels just fine. Also notice, there is no mention whatsoever in the article about ibexx's made-up nonsense that, "there may not be a launch in Q3." Read it for yourself. Google on, "iPhone screen production delayed at Sharp" . . .</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1346565323108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 01:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346577943626-6</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: Production of iPhone screens delayed at Sharp</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346564330410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 01:38:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is the old board?</Msg><Username>ugs</Username><Timestamp>1346577943626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 05:25:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346587882871-7</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: Production of iPhone screens delayed at Sharp</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346564330410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 01:38:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>However long the delay, the locked-in mind-numbed Apple robots will just wait to be summoned to make their annual purchase whenever they become available. Fortunately increased competition will entice new customers with better performance, advanced gaming, enterprise adaptability, and value.</Msg><Username>bestisapest</Username><Timestamp>1346587882871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:11:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346591807755-8</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: Production of iPhone screens delayed at Sharp</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346564330410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 01:38:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>xbit.lab says "postponement" or "shortage" re. the new iphone launch. That's the major tone of the tech journalists.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1346591807755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 09:16:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346591808113-9</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: Production of iPhone screens delayed at Sharp</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346564330410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 01:38:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>xbit.lab says "postponement" or "shortage" re. the new iphone launch. That's the major tone of the tech journalists.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1346591808113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 09:16:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346599702981-10</Id><Topic><Title>EXTRA! EXTRA! -- Apple Sues Samsung Over 4 More iPatents</Title><Username>bestville_daily_gazette</Username><Timestamp>1346554228339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:50:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As I have told you on countless ocassions, this is entirely irrelevant to NVDA. First, there are months of post-trial motions, the hearing on injunctive relief isn't even set until December. Second, even if an injunction is entered in December it will be immediately stayed pending appeal, Third, even if the injunction is held up 18 months later at the Federal Circuit, you would be looking at a ban on a Tegra 2 product in 2014.....we will be talking about Tegra 5 by then and all of the Tegra 2 inventory will be long gone, and already paid for by Samsung. Whether or not Samsung has to pay royalties on sales of it's devices is of no concern to NVDA. Finally, this case will settle long before that, money will be exchanged and life will go on. Your posts are laugh out loud stupid, why you keep lobbing me softballs is mind boggling. You can now go back to talking to your 150 dffierent Yahoo IDs.</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1346599702981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:28:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346601309856-11</Id><Title>Yahoo, you will lose advertisement revenues with this new board</Title><Msg>Very slow and difficult to read and navigate. I predict a lot of viewers will just stay away and reduce your web traffic. GET RID OF IT BEFORE IT"S TOO LATE.</Msg><Username>lordgaga81</Username><Timestamp>1346601309856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346604105059-12</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo, you will lose advertisement revenues with this new board</Title><Username>lordgaga81</Username><Timestamp>1346601309856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:55:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Whining lordgaga81. Always whining. About this or that. Look. If you don't like the new wahoo board -- then leave. Vote with your feet -- and hasta la bye-bye. Happy trails and sayonara to you, lordgaga81 The best Members that remain won't miss you. Or your aforementioned whining messages. . Meanwhile, the fine remaining Members, -- the best and most loyal Members, don't u know -- will click frequently and vigerously on the banner ads here, generating Unprecedented Obscene Profits for the generous sponsor of Our global venue. Fewer whining Members, but much improved click-thru revenue. It's wahoo's way of weeding out the weak, unprofitable ones. . . .</Msg><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1346604105059</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:41:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346607750000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Can this be true?</Title><Username>miss_iona15</Username><Timestamp>1346605052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:57:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will This Move Continue?</Msg><Username>susy_rebeca45</Username><Timestamp>1346607750000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 13:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346608409512-14</Id><Title>Stock gonna pop. NVDA</Title><Msg>Starting Tuesday media frenzy over AMZN New tablet. NVDA will be mentioned in most Articles. Mo mo guys will grab it. Probably go to Mid 15's then sell off</Msg><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1346608409512</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 13:53:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346608917653-15</Id><Topic><Title>EXTRA! EXTRA! -- Apple Sues Samsung Over 4 More iPatents</Title><Username>bestville_daily_gazette</Username><Timestamp>1346554228339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:50:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . "When the Injunction [against Samsung selling their patent-finfringing devices in the U.S.] is entered in December it will be immediately stayed pending appeal", writes patent_killr, clearly a novice when it comes to the Law. . The staying of an Injunctive Relief is not immediate, automatic nor certain. . The burden is on Samsung to meet four (4) requirements. So says the Federal Rules of Civil Procedure. Each of which Samsung will struggle with, any will likely Fail. "Under the Federal Rules of Civil Procedure, a losing party [Samsung] has a right to delay (stay) payment of monetary damages pending appeal of the decision. That right, however, does NOT [repeat, does NOT] extend to Staying an Order for Iinjunctive Relief. Thus, in those cases the losing party must file emergency motions for a stay pending appeal. Appellate courts apply a four factor test to determine whether to issue a stay of injunctive relief pending appeal. The party requesting the stay [Samsung] must show; (1) a likelihood of success on the merits of the appeal; (2) that the requesting party will suffer irreparable injury absent a stay; (3) that the stay will not unduly harm other parties interested in the proceeding; and (4) that a stay serves the public interest. The Federal Circuit has held that either of the first two factors can be (and often are) dispositive Namely, the court has held that the party can be awarded a stay based upon either (1) a strong likelihood of success on the merits of the appeal or (2) a substantial case on the merits coupled with harm factors that "militate in its favor." So let's look at the factors, shall we? (1) Samsung lost, and lost Badly. It was crystal clear that Samsung did willfully and deliberately conscript Apple's iPatents, without paying anything. Samsung's own email evidence put them away. Their likelihood of success on appeal? Forgetta 'bout it. (2) and (3) These factors offset. Samsung could whine to the Judge about "irreparable injury" and this and that if their stuff is Banned from sale in the U.S. -- but what about the Irreparable Injury to "other interested party" Apple? Hummm? Apple is iDamaged irreparably if Samsung is permitted to keep selling their cheap, tawdry knock-off stuff during the period of their lame appeal. So these two arguments zero-out -- and it's Tough Bananas for Samsung. (4) A stay of the Injunction banning Samsung from selling their slavishly copied stuff is NOT in the public interest. If fact, to do so makes a mockery of the entire Patent System of property rights. Apple invented it. They patented it. Apple gave fair warning to Samsung that they were infringing on their iPatents. Samsung continued to deliberately and willfully steal Apple's property rights. Apple's world-class iAttorneys dragged Samsung to court, where they were cattle prodded with a billion volts, de-horned, castrated and branded into submission. A jury of their peers weighed and balanced the evidence, and found Samsung guilty. With damages due to Apple of over One Billion Dollars. Okay. So Samsung gets the right to delay (stay) payment of the monetary damages pending their lame appeal of the decision. But NOT a stay of the Judge's Injunction. Oh no no no. Samsung likely can't meet the four factors for a stay of the Injunction banning the sale of their patent-infringing stuff. Sorry about your Samsung Captivate Glide being injunctively banned, boys. . . .</Msg><Username>plaintiff.best</Username><Timestamp>1346608917653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346610872872-16</Id><Title>What do you think will happen to NVDA stock price if</Title><Msg>on 9/6 Amazon announces new Kindles with no Tegra inside? I don't think it will trigger much of a sell off if any.</Msg><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1346610872872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:34:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346611974761-17</Id><Title>I just bought another Nexus 7</Title><Msg>Great product! One for me and one for the kids. $199.00? GO NVIDIA!!!!!!</Msg><Username>buddha541995</Username><Timestamp>1346611974761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:52:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346613982080-18</Id><Topic><Title>I just bought another Nexus 7</Title><Username>buddha541995</Username><Timestamp>1346611974761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:52:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . It appears you don't like your kids much. Poor kids. All the other cool kids in school will have Genuine Apple iPads, -- or the even cooler Genuine Apple iPad Mini -- and buddha's kids will have that cheap knock-off Google device. Without many apps for homework. And they'll no doubt fall further and further behind in school. Just because Dad was too cheap to buy the best for his kids. Shameful. Just shameful. . .</Msg><Username>dr.bester</Username><Timestamp>1346613982080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 15:26:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346614786739-19</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen to NVDA stock price if</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1346610872872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . With a P/E of 18.48 -- nvda is already priced to perfection. Any failure to win what Jen has baked-into his questionable guidance will cause nvda to plunge off the cliff. There is zero tolerance for disappointment here. With a P/E of 18.48. . .</Msg><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1346614786739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 15:39:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346615296219-20</Id><Topic><Title>EXTRA! EXTRA! -- Apple Sues Samsung Over 4 More iPatents</Title><Username>bestville_daily_gazette</Username><Timestamp>1346554228339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:50:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, novice....right. I don't need to scour the Internet for generic legal publications to cut and paste. By way of background, you started this silly series of postings about Apple last week..arguing that Android was going out of business as a result of this verdict. Now that you realize what everyone else already knew, namely, that you are clueless, you are now making noise about a Samsung product that includes a Tegra 2 being banned, maybe, in 2013...ROTFL. Seriously? First, in your foolish attempt at rebutting me, somebody that deals with this issue everyday, you point out that Apple has the patent and a jury verdict in it's favor. You therefore reason that there wont be a stay of an injuntion on appeal to the CAFC. Ummm...that is always the case at the appeal stage...so let's move past that sillyness. You argue that Samsung is unlilkely to win the appeal, yet you don't even know what they are appealing! Appeals aren't "I should have won the case"....they are very specific procedural and evidentiary disputes, claim construction, jury instructions, inappropriate standards, etc. Samsung may be asking for a remand on these issues, a new trial, etc. You have no idea what you are talking about, so you cannot possibly #$%$ a likelihood of succeeding. Second, there isn't even an injunction to stay yet, and there may never be. That wont even be decided until late December (oral hearing is December 6th, decision may take longer). AGAIN all of this is academic, and not the least bit related to NVDA, but since you clearly need the schooling...I'll continue. Third, Apple has been awarded money damages...in other words, they can be made whole by money. Thus, there can be no prejudice for waiting to get paid. In such situations, you just get paid more if the appeal is successful. (interest is awarded after appeal, and the 1 billion bond will be posted by Samsung) Finally, if it were even remotely possible that an injunction would be entered, and not stayed on appeal, Samsung would simply pay up now....and they might in the coming weeks. Again, you keep posting this Apple stuff as if it had any relation to NVDA, it doesn't....Tegra 2...LOL Why do you keep lobbing me softballs?....you are making a fool of yoursef.</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1346615296219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 15:48:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346617333951-21</Id><Topic><Title>EXTRA! EXTRA! -- Apple Sues Samsung Over 4 More iPatents</Title><Username>bestville_daily_gazette</Username><Timestamp>1346554228339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:50:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . Nice surrender at the end, patent_killr. Probably a document time stamper at some little municipal courtroom. . "Finally, [given] the "possibility" that an injunction would be entered, and not stayed on appeal, Samsung would simply pay up now....AND THEY MIGHT IN THE COMING WEEKS." . HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA! All those words, and patent_killr caves in at the end and admits Samsung is toast. . .</Msg><Username>plaintiff.best</Username><Timestamp>1346617333951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 16:22:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346621479452-22</Id><Topic><Title>EXTRA! EXTRA! -- Apple Sues Samsung Over 4 More iPatents</Title><Username>bestville_daily_gazette</Username><Timestamp>1346554228339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:50:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YAWN To be clear, I have always said the case will settle and money/cross licenses will be exchanged, that is how the game is played. It is just a question of timing, now or on appeal later. If the case settles soon, there certainly wont be an injunction. If the case continues on appeal, any injunction (assuming one is entered in December) will be stayed....and the case will settle down the road (assuming Samsung believes they can gain some additional leverage by continuing). Your point was that there will somehow be a magical injunction in force that pulls Samsung products off the market in the short term...aint happening....but I would change the subject too if I were you. Like I said all academic anyway, your initial premise that any of this is related to NVDA is just plain foolish, even for a clown like you. P.S. If you have to resort to "HA HA HA HA HA HA" in a debate, and you are above the age of 5 (far from certain based on your track record here) you're losing.</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1346621479452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 17:31:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346624269170-23</Id><Topic><Title>EXTRA! EXTRA! -- Apple Sues Samsung Over 4 More iPatents</Title><Username>bestville_daily_gazette</Username><Timestamp>1346554228339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:50:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . Dude. Wake up! This isn't some little garden-variety patent case here. Oh no no no. This is a Corporate Mission -- by Apple -- the most valuable corporation on the planet. . “I will spend my last dying breath if I need to, and I will spend every penny of Apple’s $40 billion [$120 billion now] in the bank, to right this wrong. I’m going to destroy Android, because it’s a stolen product.” I’m willing to go thermonuclear war on this.” -- Bill Gates, the late founder of Apple Inc. . This isn't as you purport, to be about Samsung paying mere money to Apple. Or some silly cross-licensing agreement. Oh no no no. Apple doesn't need the cash. Nor access to any of Samsung's patents. It's much iBigger than that. Much much iBigger. And no, it's not a game. Timothy Cook, the new CEO of Apple, inherited the most concise succession plan ever written. To crush Anrdoid into extinction. At any cost -- no matter what it takes -- no matter how long it takes. Apple will be seeking an Injunction, banning virtually every one of Samsung's mobile devices from being imported or sold in these United States. Including, by the way, the nvidia powered Samsung Captivate Glide. Now Samsung might be begging and pleading to merely write a Giant Check and sweep their willful patent theft under the rug. "ain't happening" As the #1 largest manufacturer of Android devices in the world, Samsung is Apple's #1 iTarget. In their thermonuclear war against the stolen product called Android. Your dream of "cash being exchanged down the road"? Forgetta 'bout it. Apple is going for Total Thermonuclear Destruction of Android. Not Samsung's mere cash. . . .</Msg><Username>ibest.here</Username><Timestamp>1346624269170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346630999000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Can this be true?</Title><Username>miss_iona15</Username><Timestamp>1346605052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:57:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thats true</Msg><Username>tomiko_rosalia68</Username><Timestamp>1346630999000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:09:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346632314000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Can this be true?</Title><Username>miss_iona15</Username><Timestamp>1346605052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:57:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I followed your picks since last week. Nice work...</Msg><Username>noriko_aubrey47</Username><Timestamp>1346632314000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:31:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346632442022-26</Id><Topic><Title>I just bought another Nexus 7</Title><Username>buddha541995</Username><Timestamp>1346611974761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:52:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What? U mean a gift has to be more expensive to mean love? This guy bought a present and u wanna insult him? Fine. Let's see.... Did u buy a $100 mil place to stay with your loved ones or just a normal place ? No? Shameful Did u buy super cars or normal? Normal? Shameful Did u sent your kids to ivy league schools or normal? Normal? Shameful Now's the Best! Did your father marry a super pretty model to give birth to u or did he marry a 'bixxxtch' to have u? No super model? Well we all know. Cos u are the BEST Son of a Bitxxxch around! Shameful, shameful, F shameful !!!</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1346632442022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:34:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346633231607-27</Id><Topic><Title>Stock gonna pop. NVDA</Title><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1346608409512</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 13:53:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lenovo And nvda can work also.</Msg><Username>markasmith58</Username><Timestamp>1346633231607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:47:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346635842099-28</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen to NVDA stock price if</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1346610872872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you seem like a slithering snake; posting inaccurate dribble... analyst estimates put NVDA's forward EPS at around $1.10 - $1.20... take out the $5.3 per share in pure, wholesome, appreciating US dollars and you have a business equity value trading at 7.9x.... less than half of what the snake BEST just posted...</Msg><Username>baseball_angel_45</Username><Timestamp>1346635842099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:30:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346636024818-29</Id><Topic><Title>EXTRA! EXTRA! -- Apple Sues Samsung Over 4 More iPatents</Title><Username>bestville_daily_gazette</Username><Timestamp>1346554228339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:50:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Patent took you to the woodshed again...LOLZ</Msg><Username>snakeplizkn</Username><Timestamp>1346636024818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:33:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346636065768-30</Id><Topic><Title>I just bought another Nexus 7</Title><Username>buddha541995</Username><Timestamp>1346611974761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:52:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Snake seems to be too endearing a term for a twot like you..... I see you post here religiously, as if you lost a bet with mephastopheles himself... run into a talking poodle lately??</Msg><Username>baseball_angel_45</Username><Timestamp>1346636065768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:34:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346641266908-31</Id><Topic><Title>I just bought another Nexus 7</Title><Username>buddha541995</Username><Timestamp>1346611974761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:52:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nexus sux. wait for Surface</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1346641266908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:01:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346642927436-32</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen to NVDA stock price if</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1346610872872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If nvidia not in Apple Mac pro = huge plunge If nvidia not in Microsoft surface = huge plunge If Kepler not in many laptops but instead loses to AMD = huge plunge If nvidia not in nexus 7 = huge plunge Now Nvidia is already in all those, yet even if, even if they are not in kindle = still huge plunge. What stupid Best logic is that? Best Crap Logic??!!! Lol</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1346642927436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:28:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>