<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-24"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351051541827-1</Id><Title>In the Year 1233...</Title><Msg>In the Year 1233... -- Floris IV, The Count of Holland, was killed in tournament -- The Formulary of Adjudications is promulgated -- Earl Otto II van Gelre of Tielerwaard grants Arnhem state justice -- Ferrand of Portugal, Earl of Flanders, dies at 45 -- Emperor Chukyo of Japan was born -- The Project of Denver was trumpeted. Ha ha ha ha!</Msg><Username>ct.bestula</Username><Timestamp>1351051541827</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:05:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351051956717-2</Id><Title>Apple wants to be the creme de la #$%$</Title><Msg>Too many scumball tablets will be vying for click strokes this holiday selling season, and doubt very much that Apple will get away with premium pricing in the entry level market. The Macs with NVDA discrete graphics look like winners in the creme de la creme segment.</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1351051956717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351051965353-3</Id><Title>Apple wants to be the creme de la #$%$</Title><Msg>Too many scumball tablets will be vying for click strokes this holiday selling season, and doubt very much that Apple will get away with premium pricing in the entry level market. The Macs with NVDA discrete graphics look like winners in the creme de la creme segment.</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1351051965353</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351052068750-4</Id><Topic><Title>Apple wants to be the creme de la #$%$</Title><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1351051965353</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The title should read, creme de la $kum</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1351052068750</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:14:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351054579824-5</Id><Topic><Title>nvidia's 2012 market share for smartphones? -- 00.90% -- Ha ha ha ha!</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1350912820996</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:33:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? I looked at that highly educational chart from EE Times. ("Analysts clash over Marvell's apps processor sales - EE Times") Which shows Smartphone Application Processor Shipments (millions of units), for the First Half of 2012. Here. I'll graciously provide it again for Our fine readers. 96.5 million __ Qualcomm, THE King of smartphone application processors 65.6 million __ Apple's self-designed iProcessors 29.9 million __ Samsung processors 23.2 million __ Marvell processors (who would have thought, right boys?) 18.4 million __ Texas Instruments 12.6 million __ Broadcom smartphone processors + on-board cheerleaders 10.9 million __ Mediatek processors 4.6 million __ ST processors 2.4 million __ nvidia 1.1 million __ Spreadstrum So Best? With the first five (5) smartphone processor makers, -- Qualcomm, Apple, Samsung, Marvell and Texas Instruments -- having an iron grip on Eighty Eight percent (88%) of the entire smartphone market, and little nvidia with a miniscule 00.90% of the processor market, is nvidia really IN the smartphone processor market? Ranked #9 out of 10? Or is it just a diversion for Wall Street -- while Jen desperately tries to figure out how to come up with a Real business to replace his dying business of making Graphics Processors -- 80% of which get attached to PC's.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1351054579824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:56:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351055956643-6</Id><Topic><Title>nvidia's 2012 market share for smartphones? -- 00.90% -- Ha ha ha ha!</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1350912820996</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:33:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jeepers Best, Did any of the longs here see that chart Before putting their hard-earned cash into this crap shoot? I didn't think so.</Msg><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1351055956643</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 01:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351058381603-7</Id><Topic><Title>nvidia's 2012 market share for smartphones? -- 00.90% -- Ha ha ha ha!</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1350912820996</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:33:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a confounding wonderment, right boys? It sure is. How Marvell Technology can make Ten Times (10x) the number of smartphone application processors than nvidia does, with 1/1,000th of the carnival barking. It's a confounding wonderment.</Msg><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1351058381603</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 01:59:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351061796264-8</Id><Title>Surface vs Clovertrail</Title><Msg>'The only other user experience issue I have with Surface has to do with CPU utilization when using Office 2013. Surface, like all Windows RT tablets, comes with a free installation of Office 2013 Student &amp; Home Edition. Surface also happens to use a quad-core NVIDIA Tegra 3 SoC, featuring four ARM Cortex A9 cores running at up to 1.3GHz. At least for the Cortex A9 generation, I don’t know that Microsoft could’ve used anything slower. Simply typing quickly in Microsoft Word maxes the single threaded performance of Tegra 3’s ARM Cortex A9 cores. I’ve seen CPU usage a high as 50% when typing very quickly, but mostly it tends to sit between 20 – 40%. Switch to notepad and max CPU utilization drops to sub 10%. This says more about Office 2013 than the performance of NVIDIA’s Tegra 3, but there are not a whole lot of spare CPU cycles to go around with Surface. On the user experience side alone, the Clovertrail tablet is noticeably quicker than Surface. Surface isn’t slow by any means, but had it used Atom hardware it would’ve been even more responsive. The large files used in the workload do a great job of showing Atom’s memory controller advantages over that used by the Cortex A9. The results here likely overstate the Clovertrail performance advantage a bit (I’m not sure how much 1080p video transcoding you’re going to be doing on Surface as compared to web browsing) but the results tend to agree with what our browser based JavaScript tests show: Intel’s Atom Z2760 is considerably faster than Tegra 3 here. I understand that Microsoft needed a good launch vehicle for Windows RT, however I really would have liked to have seen an Atom version of Surface. An Ivy Bridge version is in the works, but it’s also a bit larger. An Atom version could retain the same chassis size/weight, but deliver tangibly better CPU performance. Again we’ll have to wait to see what battery life looks like for these Clovertrail tablets before really deciding whether or not Atom would’ve been a better fit.' anandtechDOTcom/show/6385/microsoft-surface-review/10</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351061796264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:56:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>26</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351069745920-9</Id><Title>Strong earnings preview from MPartners - Reporting a Milestone quarter today after market</Title><Msg>- Interdigital ( NASDAQ:IDCC ) is about to explode, check out the reasons for the $45 Price target from MPartners ( last night ) - This quarter IDCC recognized revenue from its first batch of patent assets sold to Intel for $375M (announced in June 2012) and also received positive ruling from the CAFC regarding its appeal of a 2009 ITC decision in favor of Nokia with respect to two 3G essential patents. - The recent good news has been undermined by underperformance of its core 3G licenses. Particularly revenue from per unit licensees continued to erode because handset vendors in Japan, along with RIM, and HTC continued to lose market share to Samsung and Apple. Samsung and Apple are both fixed-term licensees where revenue streams are unaffected by volumes. OUTLOOK SHOULD BE SOLID We believe that due to the timing of asset sales, as well as license renewals and outcomes of litigation, that quarterly results are difficult to forecast. However, we should continue to see an annualized trend towards growth through licensing, partnerships, and asset sales. This is reflected in our sum-of-the-parts analysis below. Our estimate of cash includes our estimate incremental cash that resulted from the sale of the patents to Intel. We reiterate our BUY recommendation and our 12-month share price target of $45.00. Our estimate excludes licensing revenue from Nokia, Huawei, ZTE, and LG, which are all involved in litigation with Interdigital currently. Yesterday's the stock closed with a gain of 5% in the after hours trading. Calls are also very active lately</Msg><Username>patentsaddicted</Username><Timestamp>1351069745920</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 05:09:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351078005355-10</Id><Topic><Title>Surface vs Clovertrail</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351061796264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:56:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vs a two year old $20 ARM processor??!! Go rub out your daily intc hard on..</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1351078005355</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:26:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351082452534-11</Id><Topic><Title>Surface vs Clovertrail</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351061796264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:56:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Office??!! You want to do content creation, get a real notebook.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1351082452534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:40:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>23</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351082771605-12</Id><Title>Shorts getting fried in FB! NVDA next!</Title><Msg>Keep selling dip wits! More deals than you can shake a stick at. Face it . Apples hug says it all. We are the best!</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1351082771605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351083330381-13</Id><Topic><Title>Engadget publishes a rave review on Surface RT, with special praise on its performance and Tegra 3 processor</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1351080547815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one!</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1351083330381</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:55:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351083366464-14</Id><Topic><Title>Surface vs Clovertrail</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351061796264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:56:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra 3 has been on sale for less than a year and if they have a more later version perhaps they should have been kind enough to supply MSFT with it ! Atom is the truly old design, unchanged micro-architecture in 4 years now, only advances have been on the SoC side.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351083366464</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:56:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351083615203-15</Id><Title>lol, winRT you can have any browser you want, as long as...</Title><Msg>it's IE. installation of other browsers NOT allowed. windoz dead, long live windoz.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1351083615203</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:00:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351085228975-16</Id><Topic><Title>Surface vs Clovertrail</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351061796264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:56:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is rumored that Ron "Typewriter" Mingo melted his new Tegra-powered Microsost Surface in just 57 seconds. "It's just junk." "Maybe okay for students -- or if your arm is in a cast -- but not for any kind of serious typing." Check it out. Google this : Ron "Typewriter" Mingo - Real People The World's Fastest Typist.</Msg><Username>bestnfastest.wins</Username><Timestamp>1351085228975</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351085649821-17</Id><Topic><Title>nvidia's 2012 market share for smartphones? -- 00.90% -- Ha ha ha ha!</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1350912820996</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:33:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Attention. Attention. Will the Owner of the Green 1995 nvidia Please Remove Your Doors from the Race Track. Thank You.</Msg><Username>good_one_best</Username><Timestamp>1351085649821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:34:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086358026-18</Id><Topic><Title>Surface vs Clovertrail</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351061796264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:56:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Be the best in whatever you do". -- Ron "Typewriter" Mingo Oh, and buy a decent tablet too -- like one of those iPads.</Msg><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1351086358026</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:45:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087875220-19</Id><Topic><Title>Surface vs Clovertrail</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351061796264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:56:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you want 'fast', you can get a $1200 i5 tablet. That will be 'fast'. So we really need to take into account pricing and purpose, non? $600 for a tablet winAnything, with a keyboard. You want to do serious content creation, $600 will buy you a 15" i3 that will run circles around any Atom or ARM. No company will pay for that. Win tablets are DOA because of pricing, regardless of CPU.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1351087875220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:11:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351088699249-20</Id><Topic><Title>Surface vs Clovertrail</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351061796264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:56:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If you want to do serious content creation, $600 will buy you a Genuine Intel® Core™ i3 Processor Laptop that will run circles around any Atom or ARM." Agreed. It is neither fitting nor proper to write the Great American Novel on a cheap Chinese tablet powered by a chip made in some Taiwanese job shop. Genuine Intel® -- It's The American Way.</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1351088699249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:24:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351088933447-21</Id><Topic><Title>TADF BIG OCTOBER NEWS.TADF 2000% GAINS POSSIBLE ON ACQUISITIONS ANNOUNCED. Undervalued and CHEAP@ 0.0007.READ</Title><Username>dollarmultiplier</Username><Timestamp>1351008065839</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 12:01:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Going to give this a try with 6 million shares at 0.0008. Don't think it Can go any lower, can only go up from here. 6 million shares X .20 cents = $1,200,000 profit. The profit potential on the upside is massive. This could help RECOVER all my losses for the YEAR. After purchase remember to Add TADF to your Watchlist to maximize gains to the upside on more news and to buy more on news.</Msg><Username>hugemargins</Username><Timestamp>1351088933447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351090546340-22</Id><Topic><Title>Surface vs Clovertrail</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351061796264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:56:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quite a pathetic review for that Tegra-powered Microsoft Surface, boys. And girl too. "I don’t know that Microsoft could’ve used anything slower. Simply typing quickly in Microsoft Word maxes the single threaded performance of Tegra 3’s ARM Cortex A9 cores. I’ve seen CPU usage a high as 50% when typing very quickly." Maybe it's going after a niche market? The slower folks, don't u know.</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1351090546340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:55:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094199642-23</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA is bad. This is the reason why.</Title><Username>garypogue21</Username><Timestamp>1351094112628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Checking it out as we speak.</Msg><Username>colton.vierra</Username><Timestamp>1351094199642</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:56:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351100388013-24</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA is bad. This is the reason why.</Title><Username>garypogue21</Username><Timestamp>1351094112628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already signed up. They are good.</Msg><Username>danielwix951</Username><Timestamp>1351100388013</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351106055744-25</Id><Title>Almost in the elevens again.</Title><Msg>It really deserves single digits. It has to greatly increase sales to reach 1% market share in its chosen field of concentration, while still losing money in it(?), and touting itself as a market leader in the field. To top it off, nobody in the market trusts anyone in management any more, in my opinion. IMHO</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1351106055744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:14:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106662839-26</Id><Topic><Title>US disavows Apple patent in center of legal dispute of Apple vs Samsung - major legal defeat for Apple</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1351052692840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:24:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now if only they could get the same kind of ruling against those other dozen Apple patents, but they can't. And this is an initial ruling, anyway, that will be challenged for years, and it does not affect at all the remaining declared valid patents in the Samsung case. BoiiiiiiiiiiiiY</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1351106662839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:24:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351112439983-27</Id><Title>BEST you still involved in RMBS</Title><Msg>Well at least you are still here with us.. could have been worse... am i right?</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1351112439983</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:00:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351117405966-28</Id><Topic><Title>US disavows Apple patent in center of legal dispute of Apple vs Samsung - major legal defeat for Apple</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1351052692840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:24:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess they will appeal to overturn the radius corner verdict as well.</Msg><Username>pennyforabuck</Username><Timestamp>1351117405966</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:23:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351119847492-29</Id><Topic><Title>US disavows Apple patent in center of legal dispute of Apple vs Samsung - major legal defeat for Apple</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1351052692840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:24:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>justice...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351119847492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:04:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351128955921-30</Id><Topic><Title>In the Year 1233...</Title><Username>ct.bestula</Username><Timestamp>1351051541827</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:05:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, okay. So it was a muted trumpet. ( Doot, do do dooooo! )</Msg><Username>my_favorite_best</Username><Timestamp>1351128955921</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:35:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351129077074-31</Id><Title>In the Year 1217...</Title><Msg>In the Year 1217... -- The Second Battle of Lincoln is fought near Lincoln, England, resulting in the defeat of Prince Louis of France by William Marshal, 2nd Earl of Pembroke. -- In the Battle of South Foreland, the English fleet beats France -- French Prince Louis of France and King Henry III of England sign peace treaty. -- The Estonian tribal leader Lembitu of Lehola was killed in a battle against Teutonic Knights. -- Earl Jen of Tegratonia claims receipts will double "any day now." Ha ha ha ha!</Msg><Username>ct.bestula</Username><Timestamp>1351129077074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351132525789-32</Id><Title>Kindly reminder to Jen : It's Ten (10) trading days forward notice.</Title><Msg>"Public companies must give adequate advance notice of their conference calls, including time, date and dial-in information", so says the SEC. Remember a few quarters ago, when Jen screwed-up? Right after his Chief Investor Relations person quit. Leaving Jen to figure things out for himself. Like the Calendar. And he set the date of his quarterly confessional too close. Yep, he did. And Best kindly reminded Jen of the Ten (10) day forward notice rule. Right here on Our board. And "someone" at nvidia hastily revised the nvidia earnings announcement date. Like Pronto. "Thank you, Best." So here we are, the evening of October 24th. Well, it'll be October 25th, right after Best quaffs a couple more Dos Equis. Yes, Best doesn't always drink beer, but when I do, I prefer Dos Equis. Anyway... the well-established convention for setting earnings announcement dates is Ten (10) trading days forward notice, boys. ALL respectable companies that aren't trying to slide one by give at least Ten (10) trading days notice, don't u know. So let's assume that someone reminds Jen tomorrow, Thursday October 25th. That then becomes "announcement day for earnings announcement day." Ten (10) trading days forward notice from that is what? Friday, November 9th. Assuming Halloween isn't considered a Holiday by the exchanges, of course. Somebody remind Jen, okay? To set the earnings date no earlier than Friday, November 9th. Oh, also remind Jen to update his Investor Relations website page too. It currently shows "No Scheduled Events" "Thank you, Best."</Msg><Username>thanks.best</Username><Timestamp>1351132525789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:35:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351133039261-33</Id><Topic><Title>Kindly reminder to Jen : It's Ten (10) trading days forward notice.</Title><Username>thanks.best</Username><Timestamp>1351132525789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:35:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? Jen could announce his earnings Later than Friday, November 9th, right? But then, seeing how nvidia stock is plunging every day in anticipation of the Eminent Bad News, it would be both expensive and silly to wait, right? It sure would be.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1351133039261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:43:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351134193975-34</Id><Topic><Title>Kindly reminder to Jen : It's Ten (10) trading days forward notice.</Title><Username>thanks.best</Username><Timestamp>1351132525789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:35:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have been lokin back at your posts here and on IV.. this is a over rmbs losing to nvda.. you go back years.. such a waste.. well, this is how you deal with it..better than the poor guy who ended it all..</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1351134193975</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:03:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351134194480-35</Id><Topic><Title>Kindly reminder to Jen : It's Ten (10) trading days forward notice.</Title><Username>thanks.best</Username><Timestamp>1351132525789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:35:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have been lokin back at your posts here and on IV.. this is a over rmbs losing to nvda.. you go back years.. such a waste.. well, this is how you deal with it..better than the poor guy who ended it all..</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1351134194480</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351135353929-36</Id><Title>Forbes: 5 Reasons You Shouldn't Buy An iPad Mini</Title><Msg>1: The Resolution 1: The Resolution Apple’s hardware engineers get all the credit in the world; the iPad mini is a thin, beautiful piece of kit. However, the company was eager to draw direct, wholly unflattering comparisons to the Google Nexus 7. I have some comparisons of my own to share. Visit the official iPad Mini product page, and you’ll see it touted as being “Every Inch An iPad.” Unfortunately the 7.9″ screen’s 1024 x 768 resolution is identical to the iPad 2 — a device now two generations old following Apple’s unveiling of a fourth-generation iPad today. (The iPad 3 boasts a Retina display of 2048 x 1536.) iPad Mini &amp; iPad 4th Generation: What CIOs Need To Know Forrester ResearchContributor Are You Annoyed That Your iPad 3 Is Now Obsolete? Adrian Kingsley-HughesContributor Is the iPad Mini Cheap Enough? Dave ThierContributor Google’s Nexus 7 Android tablet has 1280 x 800 resolution in a 7” screen. Notably, the Nexus 7 display packs in 216 PPI (pixels-per-inch) compared to the iPad Mini’s 163 PPI. I find it baffling that Apple is aggressively pushing their Retina technology (and rightly so), while simultaneously producing what is clearly an inferior display experience for their iPad mini. Newcomers to the iPad will not be impressed, and existing iPad owners will be underwhelmed should they choose to purchase the iPad Mini as a second device. Oh, even Amazon’s Kindle Fire HD has a better resolution. 2: The Price Arguably, $299 would have been the sweet spot. The actual MSRP of $329, however, is Apple asking the usual premium price — but this time for an inferior product. Google’s Nexus 7 is priced at $249 for the 16GB model, and the search giant includes a $25 Google Play Store voucher. Add to this a noisy rumor mill pointing to an imminent price drop on the Nexus 7, and you have a clearer picture of why Apple was deriding its closest competitor at today’s keynote. It used to be enough for Apple to pull back the curtain on a new product, inspire oohs and ahhhs, and watch the pre-orders roll in. Now the competition is so fierce that they’ve subjected themselves to dirty marketing. 3: The Planned Obsolescence Factor Apple has now demonstrated they have no qualms about introducing a new revision of their products every six months. Much to the chagrin of new iPad 3 owners, Apple has seemingly reduced their yearly iterative cycle to a six-month one. With the 4th generation iPad available next month, it’s nothing less than a slap in the face to Apple loyalists. We should expect a similar treatment of the iPad Mini. By summer 2013, expect Apple to roll out an iPad Mini 2 with a Retina display and a more competitive pricetag. 4: The A5 Chip I’d be kinder to Apple if the hardware inside the iPad mini matched the hype they’re trying to generate. Again, crucial to the pricing discussion is Apple’s inclusion of their dual-core A5 chip. This is the same chip powering the iPad 2 – a device now two generations old — and the iPod Touch. Furthermore, Apple’s A5X chip found in iPad 3 (aka “New iPad”) has a quad-core graphics processor compared to the A5’s dual-core graphics processor. Google’s Nexus 7 manages extraordinary battery life even with the inclusion of NVIDIA’s Tegra 3 processor, which beats the A5 chip handily in GeekBench tests, and destroys it in raw graphical processing power. Again, something Apple neglected to point out in their comparisons. 5: Windows 8 RT (The Wildcard) Look, I acknowledge that Android is a splintered platform, but don’t expect Amazon and Google to give up the fight so easily. Both companies will continue to iterate on their respective signature tablets, and they will do so with extremely aggressive pricing. But it’s actually Microsoft‘s Windows 8 that may throw a curve ball into this tablet game. We’ve seen a myriad of companies (like Dell and Asus) debut inspired tablet/ultrabook convertibles based around Windows 8. The “RT” variant of that operating system (ARM-processor powered) is perfect for tablets 7 inches and larger. It’s only a matter of time before hardware manufacturers release 7″ Windows 8 RT tablets. In fact, if Microsoft’s in-house Surface finds a decent audience, we may even see smaller tablets coming from Redmond in the near future. Here’s the bottom line: Apple is a brilliant technology company. Some may call them a lifestyle company. The iPad (revolutionary when it was released) deserves every bit of praise and success it has garnered thus far. But today, Apple didn’t debut an innovative product. Today they debuted a clone which is inferior to the vast majority of products it’s attempting to copy.</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1351135353929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:22:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351135643532-37</Id><Topic><Title>Almost in the elevens again.</Title><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1351106055744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:14:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Señor Miguel, The low of 52 week, she is coming, sí? Right after confessional por Jen. ¡Boomba! ¡Boomba! ¡Boomba! ¡Boomba! Down she go, to nuevo mínimo. Digits de la single, sí?</Msg><Username>senor.best</Username><Timestamp>1351135643532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:27:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351137092591-38</Id><Topic><Title>Almost in the elevens again.</Title><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1351106055744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:14:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rmbs...</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1351137092591</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>