<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-14"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350187734355-1</Id><Title>Apple going quad-core and 20 nm in late 2013</Title><Msg>Apple Reportedly Tapping TSMC for 20-nm Quad-Core Chips with Late 2013 Production Source: wwwDOTmacrumorsDOTcom/2012/10/12/apple-reportedly-tapping-tsmc-for-20-nm-quad-core-chips/</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1350187734355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 00:08:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350198697292-2</Id><Topic><Title>Who would buy AMD? A tough question with no easy answers</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1350174187641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jeepers Best ! Imagine an AMD mobile x86 CPU + ATi's superb Mobile Radeon™ Graphics Processor + Qualcomm's legendary multi-mode radio + Windows 8 -- the genuine x86-64 version that can run the Hundreds of Millions of Windows x86 programs, not the little stripped-down RT version. All nestled right there together on the same tiny piece of silicon. Quite a winning combination, boys. A Winning Combination for sure. Could be the Intel Clover Trail's one and only Competitor. In a post-android world.</Msg><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1350198697292</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 03:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>19</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350214793509-3</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T all set to introduce ASUS vivo Tab RT. At $599, it is much cheaper than similarly configured ipad 3</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1350190332455</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 00:52:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>roflol... trying to 'justify' a $600 tablet.... you forgot, it does Office too!!!! Read my lips, ain't no market for a $600 tablet, winRT Surface or Zoom.... stillborns! Again, who is going to come out with a decent $350 10" and fill that big market void? ah no one.... until el goog does that with the Sanpdragon quad. Gool ramping down production of T3 in Q4. T3, like T2 and OMAP, are all 2 Quarter wonders. And since there ain,t no T4, that round will soundly and rightfully will belong to the Sanpdragon quad with LTE. qcom's engineers won that round handily. nvda's cpu design engineering stinks. There you have it, aapl high end, goog mid market, amzn mops up the bottom. WinRT will sell even less than ultrabooks.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1350214793509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 07:39:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350214903901-4</Id><Topic><Title>Apple going quad-core and 20 nm in late 2013</Title><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1350187734355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 00:08:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>late 2013? I doubt tsmc will have that process ready by then, especially if they try to do finFets.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1350214903901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 07:41:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350215336901-5</Id><Topic><Title>LIKE AN APPLE: MICROSOFT WILL DESIGN THEIR OWN ARM CHIP INTEL DOOMED</Title><Username>eastofeastside</Username><Timestamp>1350062580700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure why you keep harping on BOM cost. BOM cost is only relevant for loss calculations when they have to dump their initial built because of no sell through. It is also relevant when msft is charging their msft tax. It's about market positioning. msft has decided to not fight the challengers heads on, abandon the mass market, and concentrate on their version of 'ultrabooks'. And there goes the franchise. No more wintel tax... go, el goog GO!</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1350215336901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 07:48:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350223833722-6</Id><Topic><Title>LIKE AN APPLE: MICROSOFT WILL DESIGN THEIR OWN ARM CHIP INTEL DOOMED</Title><Username>eastofeastside</Username><Timestamp>1350062580700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From your own quoted text "... Microsoft *may* have first and last rights of refusal to purchase the stock." (emphasis mine). Try reading it again. So do you have any info on what the conditions would be that would give ROFR or ROLR? No?Then are you shorting/bashing "somewhat blindly"? I'm long Nvidia. Not blindly. The darn thing has a market cap of $7.8B, with $3.26B in net cash and $900M in guaranteed future payments from Intel. The enterprise is being valued at less than $4B, which is less than 1x trailing revenue. In my opinion, the risk to the lower end might be just below 12, but the upside is far higher ($20+ by mid Feb if Q4 is strong like the current quarter).</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1350223833722</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 10:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350224464510-7</Id><Topic><Title>Who would buy AMD? A tough question with no easy answers</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1350174187641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not arguing Nvidia is going to be acquired. That said what you've posted above is not necessarily accurate. Jen Hsun's ego and confidence in his vision/abilities aside, he owns just ~3.5% of the company and has a fiduciary responsibility to consider any and all reasonable offers. Sometimes even offers with huge premiums to market are still rejected (like MSFT's offer for YHOO) but I think it's impossible to think there's no offer that Jen Hsun Huang would accept. Imagine the same 65% premium Google paid on Motorola, brining an offer to $20, with the condition that the current management stay in place and the company be run as a wholly owned subsidiary (like Motorola, if Jha had been promised to keep his position at the top).</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1350224464510</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 10:21:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350226143768-8</Id><Topic><Title>LIKE AN APPLE: MICROSOFT WILL DESIGN THEIR OWN ARM CHIP INTEL DOOMED</Title><Username>eastofeastside</Username><Timestamp>1350062580700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cash in company's coffers is worth a whole lot less of cash in your or my pocket. Reasoning is simple and nvda is a good example of it. The company can easily waste that cash, like nvda is blowing through hundreds of millions at a time 'investing' in a market, which when you strip out the unreachable part like aapl and samsung, is really a very small market. That reachable TAM will never suupport such an overblown R&amp;D program. nvda is the only company losing money in app processors. mediatech, qcom, brcm, aapl, samsung are all making money with their SoC programs. nvda's program does not have a chance.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1350226143768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 10:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350232591145-9</Id><Topic><Title>LIKE AN APPLE: MICROSOFT WILL DESIGN THEIR OWN ARM CHIP INTEL DOOMED</Title><Username>eastofeastside</Username><Timestamp>1350062580700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear theblindtrader50, That "$900M in guaranteed future payments from Intel" of which you speak? You DO realize, I hope, that Intel's LAST annual payment of $300 million is coming up really quick. January 15, 2013 to be exact. Then there's only three (3) little annual payments of just $200 million left. January 15, 2014 / January 15, 2015 / and January 15, 2016. Then Intel is Done paying for the use of ALL of nvidia's Existing patents, and ALL Future patents that nvidia receives thru March 31, 2017. With No additional Intel payments to be made to nvidia -- like Forever. And Intel will make rapacious use of those nvidia patents, until the very last one expires. Probably killing-off a few more of nvidia's businesses. Like the Tesla. While the $200 million annual handout from Intel might Look like a big deal in your pocket or mine, or even whosunw's pocket -- and she's filthy Rich -- it really isn't. Oh no no no. Not with Jen's CPB (Tegra) Division on track to LOSE over $400 Million per year. The Tegra HAS INDEED lost ($191,641,000.00) for the six (6) months ended July 29, 2012 -- right boys? It sure has. And the Tegra losses are Growing Exponentially, quarter after quarter after quarter. So losing ($400,000,000.00) PER YEAR will be a walk-in-the-park for the Tegra. In short, the Tegra will be Losing TWICE (2X) the amount of the annual Intel handout. Yes, just blowing the cash. TWICE as fast as it's coming in. And blowing it Badly. Did I mention? While the $200 million annual handout from Intel might Look like a big deal in your pocket or mine, or even whosunw's pocket -- and she's filthy Rich -- it really isn't. Nope. Not with The Tegra around.</Msg><Username>best.warning</Username><Timestamp>1350232591145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 12:36:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350233606099-10</Id><Topic><Title>Who would buy AMD? A tough question with no easy answers</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1350174187641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD comes with crushing debt... I'm sure there would be buyers if AMD could be sold in divisions... But just no way around their debt... And the Rats just keep jumping ship...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1350233606099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 12:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350233744420-11</Id><Topic><Title>LIKE AN APPLE: MICROSOFT WILL DESIGN THEIR OWN ARM CHIP INTEL DOOMED</Title><Username>eastofeastside</Username><Timestamp>1350062580700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ill-gotten treasures are of no value, but righteousness delivers from death. -- Proverbs 10:2</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1350233744420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 12:55:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350237263886-12</Id><Topic><Title>Who would buy AMD? A tough question with no easy answers</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1350174187641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Best ! For sharing with us that PATENT CROSS LICENSE AGREEMENT BETWEEN ADVANCED MICRO DEVICES, INC. AND INTEL CORPORATION, Dated January 1, 2001. Why, that's the Single Most Valuable License Ever Written in the History of Mankind. The the History of Mankind, boys. Available for your perusal, right here on Our board. Courtesy of Best. And it shows that Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. CAN INDEED assign their rights. To some lucky Assignee. Thanks a Million, Best.</Msg><Username>thanks.best</Username><Timestamp>1350237263886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 13:54:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350237971941-13</Id><Topic><Title>Who would buy AMD? A tough question with no easy answers</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1350174187641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So the new owner of AMD would need to refinance what, $1.532 bil of debt? Not a problem, boys. I bet these nice folks could help. Google this : Our Advantage - Intel Capital "Intel Capital can help you reach your potential." They could kinda help their parent out too.</Msg><Username>i_know_best</Username><Timestamp>1350237971941</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 14:06:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350238995637-14</Id><Topic><Title>Who would buy AMD? A tough question with no easy answers</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1350174187641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Creepers Best, Yes, it's in INtel's best interest to keep AMD alive... wouldn't want to be sole supplier of x86 now... maybe you count VIA... but no one else does... but if AMD does go for sale, I could see INtel buying their graphics division. Maybe even the whole company for their graphics division... But could they ?? #1 buying #2 ... not sure that would be allowed...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1350238995637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 14:23:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350239507142-15</Id><Topic><Title>Who would buy AMD? A tough question with no easy answers</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1350174187641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IC Banker : "So Mr. Best, in applying for a loan from us, what do you have for collateral? Best : "Well, I have the Most Valuable License Ever Written in the History of Mankind." Best : "To make those Intel x86-64 processor chips." Best : "That's worth a Lot, right?" IC Banker : "And Mr. Best, where would you like your funds wired?"</Msg><Username>in_best_we_trust</Username><Timestamp>1350239507142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 14:31:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350239876956-16</Id><Topic><Title>Who would buy AMD? A tough question with no easy answers</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1350174187641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad the x86 license isn't transferrable... So who would buy AMD ???</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1350239876956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 14:37:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350244578555-17</Id><Topic><Title>Who would buy AMD? A tough question with no easy answers</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1350174187641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Mr. Best? Now that you've saved Intel's hide from the M word, they should be deeply thankful for all of your best efforts. Deeply Thankful. Maybe you should go back to Intel and talk about some last-minute license issues. Like Lt. Columbo and his "Just One More Thing". Like reducing the per-item x86 licensing fee? What AMD agreed to pay in the past is, well, just not relevant anymore. Forgetta 'bout it. What with that Moore's Law thing and this and that. EVERYTHING keeps getting cheaper. And ask Intel to fab your chips too. Like maybe one node behind their best. So that's what, 18 nanometers. And if they whine and complain -- just remind them about the unspeakable M word.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1350244578555</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 15:56:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350248812789-18</Id><Topic><Title>LIKE AN APPLE: MICROSOFT WILL DESIGN THEIR OWN ARM CHIP INTEL DOOMED</Title><Username>eastofeastside</Username><Timestamp>1350062580700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So $3.26B in net cash currently, and $900M in guaranteed payments -- like I said. Take the NPV of the future payments if you'd like -- it still leaves an enterprise value less than $4B, for a company doing about $850M in FCFO. I don't think the valuation makes any sense, and certainly don't understand the short thesis at this valuation.</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1350248812789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 17:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350249387709-19</Id><Topic><Title>Who would buy AMD? A tough question with no easy answers</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1350174187641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Master? When you become the new owner of AMD, will you have a Board of Directors? You know -- like Jen does. Me and the clones would like to be Directors. We would be good Directors too, Master. We would always on time. And always vote Yes! to everything. Just like Jen's do. Well that, and not pinch all the nice Cubans out of the cigar box. Just don't ask us to approve something like the Tegra though. We are fed-sushi-aries, u know. .</Msg><Username>best.clone185</Username><Timestamp>1350249387709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 17:16:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350254284931-20</Id><Topic><Title>LIKE AN APPLE: MICROSOFT WILL DESIGN THEIR OWN ARM CHIP INTEL DOOMED</Title><Username>eastofeastside</Username><Timestamp>1350062580700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>let me try to paint a scenario that will void your current analysis. An extremely likely scneario, BTW. This CEO is an egomanic. There is simply zero way for him to admit he is wrong and par back the Tegra program to something reasonable given the small size of his reachable TAM. He is extremely likely to double down. That probably means wasting $2B cash to take over Infineon. So with $2B cash flushed, loses widens even more, what do you think the stock will look like? The current price is nowhere near where this stock can get down to.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1350254284931</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 18:38:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350262326053-21</Id><Topic><Title>LIKE AN APPLE: MICROSOFT WILL DESIGN THEIR OWN ARM CHIP INTEL DOOMED</Title><Username>eastofeastside</Username><Timestamp>1350062580700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This CEO is an egomanic. There is simply zero way for him to admit he is wrong and pare back the Tegra program to something reasonable given the small size of his reachable TAM. He is extremely likely to double down. That probably means wasting $2B cash to take over Infineon." Since all of Infineon Technologies AG has a market cap of $7 Billion Dollars, I presume you mean the Infineon RF Group -- which does exactly what the acquisition of Icera was supposed to do -- but clearly couldn't. And wouldn't The Street view Jen acquiring yet another cheap radio maker as an Admission that he screwed-up the first time? And screwed-up Badly. And that the acquisition of Icera was just a total waste of $367,000,000.00 of undistributed nvidia shareholder's cash. Further, Infineon is a bunch of German guys, where Icera is mostly Englishmen. Does this look like a good mix to be working on radio communications together? I think not. "Ich denke nicht." "我不这么认为。"</Msg><Username>bestogram</Username><Timestamp>1350262326053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 20:52:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350264687777-22</Id><Topic><Title>LIKE AN APPLE: MICROSOFT WILL DESIGN THEIR OWN ARM CHIP INTEL DOOMED</Title><Username>eastofeastside</Username><Timestamp>1350062580700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How are you sizing the TAM? If this is the short thesis, as a long I like that it *could* be proven invalid in a matter of weeks. Q3 is the first quarter with substantial unit shipments of a Tegra SoC fabbed on a mature process (40nm) -- so we'll see whether or not margins are actually negative, as you suggest. If selling Tegra at scale actually hurts Nvidia's profitability, I agree the stock will likely languish or move down more.</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1350264687777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 21:31:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350265769592-23</Id><Topic><Title>Alleged Apple Mini models, pricing leaked: from €249 ($320) to €649 ($840)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1350264644122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 21:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The #$%$-bot whosunvv must love the ipad mini price points a lot better than the ASUS RT's $599. LOL</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1350265769592</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 21:49:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350265769639-24</Id><Topic><Title>Alleged Apple Mini models, pricing leaked: from €249 ($320) to €649 ($840)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1350264644122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 21:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The #$%$-bot whosunvv must love the ipad mini price points a lot better than the ASUS RT's $599. LOL</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1350265769639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 21:49:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350266316256-25</Id><Topic><Title>Alleged Apple Mini models, pricing leaked: from €249 ($320) to €649 ($840)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1350264644122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 21:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They're gonna sell like Belgian waffles, boys. Yes, Belgian waffles.</Msg><Username>bestogram</Username><Timestamp>1350266316256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 21:58:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350271761634-26</Id><Topic><Title>Apple going quad-core and 20 nm in late 2013</Title><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1350187734355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 00:08:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep target Q4 2013. But not volume production. Even Citi analysts chirped in here. Source: wwwDOTcensDOTcom/cens/html/en/news/news_inner_41728.html</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1350271761634</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 23:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350271958007-27</Id><Title>Long article in Chicago Tribune: As PC era fades, good times may be over at Intel</Title><Msg>Marsavian, where are you? AMD, done! Intel, in the process of being done! Reference: .chicagotribuneDOTcom/business/sns-rt-us-intel-glorydaysbre89d0e0-20121014,0,1534942.story</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1350271958007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 23:32:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350273101753-28</Id><Topic><Title>Long article in Chicago Tribune: As PC era fades, good times may be over at Intel</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1350271958007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 23:32:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Intel acts quickly enough on Jen Hsun's advice by opening up its manufacturing processes to nvidia/qualcomm/apple before TSMC takes them all, Intel can become a manufacturing power house in the USA. This is Intel's chance to make "Made In USA" happen with products designed by nVidia in USA. lol</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1350273101753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 23:51:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>