<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351311090726-1</Id><Topic><Title>what are we missing? investor confidence is so low</Title><Username>neo_trinity1020</Username><Timestamp>1351281706702</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:01:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amd -70% since nvda earning report nvda -20% is reasonable</Msg><Username>close_below_9</Username><Timestamp>1351311090726</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 00:11:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351312643567-2</Id><Topic><Title>what are we missing? investor confidence is so low</Title><Username>neo_trinity1020</Username><Timestamp>1351281706702</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:01:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed with you and the same here I don't know why the stock price is so depressing. I wonder if people see NVDA prospect is not promsing, esp in the mobile market. The reasons for that are (1) TXN is exiting the mobil market. That tells investors that making chips for mobile markets is not easily profitable (2) Samsung starts making their own mobile chips based on ARMH core as NVDA, QCOM, and AAPL.. Samsung chips will be used in the new product lines e.g. Nexus 10. Another niche that NVDA has is to design graphic chips for PCs or laptops. And it seems to me that they are ahead of their competitor (ATI/AMD) now. But PC market is shrinking and Intel intergrated graphic chips are very decent for normal graphic use and they will get even better. However, I still think with higiher resolution display for laptop and games, a lof of people still want to have a dedicated graphic that is where NVDA crowns right now. I hope to hear others'opinion.</Msg><Username>dragon_horse_0002</Username><Timestamp>1351312643567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 00:37:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351313066523-3</Id><Topic><Title>Android grabs 41% of tablet market</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1351309606710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 23:46:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey ibbey? You quoted the first 3 paragraphs of a very short 5 paragraph story. So how come your didn't quote the next 2 paragraphs? Hummm? Here's what ibbey deliberately omitted -- probably so he wouldn't scare even more nvidia sheep into selling. "Overall, the entire market was up by 43% from 17.2m in the same quarter last year to 24.7m this year - although the analyst firm said that growth was "SLUGGISH" compared to the previous years' growth. THIS QUARTER WAS THE WEAKEST FOR TABLET SALES GROWTH since the iPad arrived in 2010, suggest the market was maturing. "DEMAND FOR TABLETS SLOWED DUE TO ONGOING ECONOMIC UNCERTAINTY AND CONSUMERS HOLDING OFF PURCHASES IN ANTICIPATION OF MULTIPLE NEW MODELS, LIKE THE iPAD MINI, during the upcoming Q4 holiday season," said Neil Mawston, executive director at Strategy Analytics." My my my. -- The WEAKEST quarter for tablet sales growth in the History of Tablets. -- Demand for tablets Slowed due to the crummy economy. -- Folks held-off tablet purchases in anticipation of the Genuine Apple iPad Mini. -- All 24 models of the Mini. You can read the WHOLE TRUTH -- not ibbey's redacted version of the truth, here: Android grabs 41% of tablet market | News | PC Pro</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1351313066523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 00:44:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351314065223-4</Id><Topic><Title>Android grabs 41% of tablet market</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1351309606710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 23:46:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Best, Thanks for bringing the Whole Truth to our paid propaganda controlled board. I for one am appalled -- yes Appalled -- at the lies and half-truths from this ibbey guy. 24 hours a day, 364 days a year. This time he deliberately omitted that this quarter was the WEAKEST quarter for tablet sales growth in the Entire History of Tablet Sales? That's it, Best. I'm DONE reading the lies and mis-truths from ibexx88. And on IGNORE he goes. Permanently. Thanks again Best, for your invaluable service to Our board.</Msg><Username>thanks.best</Username><Timestamp>1351314065223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 01:01:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351315530629-5</Id><Title>3Q : THE Weakest quarter for tablet sales growth in the Entire History of Tablets.</Title><Msg>3Q : THE Weakest quarter for tablet sales growth in the Entire History of Tablets. Read it and weep, boys : Android grabs 41% of tablet market | News | PC Pro This fits with the Google 3Q conference call, right? It sure does. Where they apologized for selling only $666 million of Nexus 7 tablets. Which is what, maybe only 1 million units for the quarter. Contributing to THE Weakest quarter for tablet sales growth in the Entire History of Tablets. Hopefully Jen can come clean regarding those disappointing tablet sales during his conference call confessional on November 8th.</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1351315530629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 01:25:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>36</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351320816740-6</Id><Topic><Title>3Q : THE Weakest quarter for tablet sales growth in the Entire History of Tablets.</Title><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1351315530629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 01:25:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Overall, the entire market was up by 43% from 17.2m in the same quarter last year to 24.7m this year - although the analyst firm said that growth was "Sluggish" compared to the previous years' growth. THIS QUARTER WAS THE WEAKEST FOR TABLET SALES GROWTH since the iPad arrived in 2010, suggest the market was maturing. "DEMAND FOR TABLETS SLOWED due to ongoing ECONOMIC UNCERTAINTY AND CONSUMERS HOLDING OFF PURCHASES IN ANTICIPATION OF multiple new models, like THE iPAD MINI, during the upcoming Q4 holiday season," said Neil Mawston, executive director at Strategy Analytics." So tablet sales had the Weakest growth in the Entire History of Tablets. The sale of new PC's was the worst in eleven (11) years. And nvida has a miniscule 00.90% of the cellphone market. And the reason to hold nvidia is what again?</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1351320816740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 02:53:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351337381778-7</Id><Topic><Title>Android grabs 41% of tablet market</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1351309606710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 23:46:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do we put all your foolish aliases on ignore..</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1351337381778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 07:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351346324827-8</Id><Topic><Title>what are we missing? investor confidence is so low</Title><Username>neo_trinity1020</Username><Timestamp>1351281706702</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:01:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>qcom has quad A15 products out in market, with full LTE integrated no less. looks like samsung Exynos A15 will be in Nexus 10. Where's Wayne? If 1 yr chip announce to device out, nvda is sitting out the while A15 generation while incurring R&amp;D costs of $250M/Q, $1B/yr. it is evident that nvda does not know how to do cpu, even just linking up cpu with somebody else's proven cores. nvda needs to dump the whole Tegra program and just license their graphics cores.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1351346324827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:58:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351349062429-9</Id><Title>Jeepers Best, Everybody else pays a dividend.</Title><Msg>Jeepers Best, Everybody else pays a dividend. Except current nvidia CEO Jen Hsun Huang. Take a look. 4.10% __ Intel Corporation 3.50% __ Dell Inc. 3.20% __ General Electric (The #1 Most Held Stock by Members of Congress) 3.10% __ Marvell Technology Group Ltd. 3.00% __ Texas Instruments Incorporated 2.60% __ Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Corporation 2.50% __ Sony Corporation 2.01% __ The Average Dividend Return of the 500 Stocks in the S&amp;P 500. 1.70% __ Apple Inc. 1.70% __ Qualcomm Incorporated 1.33% __ Microsoft Corporation 1.30% __ Broadcom Corp. 0.80% __ Oracle Corporation 0.40% __ ARM Holdings Plc 0.00% __ nvidia So nvidia stock has plunged from a year ago, there is no stock buyback, Dear Leader is afraid to make any acquisitions after the icera disaster, and it pays Zero Dividends (0.00%) to its hapless shareholders. Despite an absurd cash hoard of over $3 Billion Dollars of unemployed shareholder's cash. For a company with less than $4 Billion of Annual Gross Revenues. Enjoy your illogical nvda "investment".</Msg><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1351349062429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:44:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>57</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351350308788-10</Id><Topic><Title>Jeepers Best, Everybody else pays a dividend.</Title><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1351349062429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya, I also took a look at RMBS - it pays a huge negative dividend at the rate of -70% ever since we took you advice to buy at $25+. And you promised the stock would go to $30 in 2 weeks in July of 2010. LMAO!</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1351350308788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:05:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351350545351-11</Id><Topic><Title>Jeepers Best, Everybody else pays a dividend.</Title><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1351349062429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Creepers Best, Ya know... NVDA is the only stock I own that doesn't pay a dividend... the REITs have done me right... when will your darling RMBS start to pay dividends ???</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351350545351</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:09:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351352203608-12</Id><Topic><Title>Jeepers Best, Everybody else pays a dividend.</Title><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1351349062429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"So nvidia stock has plunged from a year ago, there is no stock buyback, Dear Leader is afraid to make any acquisitions after the icera disaster, and it pays Zero Dividends (0.00%) to its hapless shareholders. Despite an absurd cash hoard of over $3 Billion Dollars of unemployed shareholder's cash. For a company with less than $4 Billion of Annual Gross Revenues. Enjoy your illogical nvda "investment". Jen calls them "Barbarians at the Gate." And has 'em chased off the property. Those Institutional Investors. With their Halloween bags open. Just looking for some alpha. On the Hundreds of Millions they each invested in Jen's company.</Msg><Username>ct.bestula</Username><Timestamp>1351352203608</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:36:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>33</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351354694128-13</Id><Topic><Title>Strong earnings preview from MPartners - Reporting a Milestone quarter today after market</Title><Username>patentsaddicted</Username><Timestamp>1351069745920</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 05:09:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UBS analysts reiterated BUY rating for NVDA.</Msg><Username>borderescalade</Username><Timestamp>1351354694128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:18:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351355450860-14</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg : Microsoft’s Surface Tablet Lacks Apps to Rival IPad</Title><Username>in_best_we_trust</Username><Timestamp>1351174062142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:07:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>------------------------------------------------------------------- 275,000 __ Genuine Apple iOS apps 000,100 __ Surface RT apps (est.) ------------------------------------------------------------------- So Master? Investing your hard-earned cash in nvidia is kinda like a crap-shoot bet that the Surface RT apps can someday catch-up with Apple, right? Hummm. I'll stick with those scratch-off Loto cards, thanks. Looks like better odds.</Msg><Username>best.clone185</Username><Timestamp>1351355450860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:30:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351356407737-15</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg : Microsoft’s Surface Tablet Lacks Apps to Rival IPad</Title><Username>in_best_we_trust</Username><Timestamp>1351174062142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:07:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I tried to get MS office for the iPad... NOT Available Guess I'll just have to get RT...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351356407737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:46:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351357663515-16</Id><Topic><Title>what are we missing? investor confidence is so low</Title><Username>neo_trinity1020</Username><Timestamp>1351281706702</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:01:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>on A15s, nvda is not the only guy who can't heck it. aapl does not have it, txn does not have it, not even brcm has it. The only difference, the other guys are running profitable or minimally profitable businesses. Nvda is the only one who ran up the tab like no tomorrow and can't deliver. nvda needs to close their Tegra business and just license their graphics.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1351357663515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 13:07:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351360310642-17</Id><Topic><Title>what are we missing? investor confidence is so low</Title><Username>neo_trinity1020</Username><Timestamp>1351281706702</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:01:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I did look at Marvell in that highly educational chart from EE Times. ("Analysts clash over Marvell's apps processor sales - EE Times") Which shows Smartphone Application Processor Shipments (millions of units), for the First Half of 2012. Here. I'll graciously provide it again for Our fine readers. 96.5 million __ Qualcomm, THE King of smartphone application processors 65.6 million __ Apple's self-designed iProcessors 29.9 million __ Samsung processors 23.2 million __ Marvell processors (who would have thought, right boys?) 18.4 million __ Texas Instruments 12.6 million __ Broadcom smartphone processors + on-board cheerleaders 10.9 million __ Mediatek processors 4.6 million __ ST processors 2.4 million __ nvidia 1.1 million __ Spreadstrum Marvell sells Ten Times (10x) as many smartphone application processors as nvidia. 23.2 million sold by Marvell, and just 2.4 million for piker nvidia. AND Marvell pays a nice dividend to their shareholders too. Which nvidia has never done. Nope. Jen just hoards all of the shareholder's cash, for no specific purpose. Marvell looks like the best pick to me.</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1351360310642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 13:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351361294447-18</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg : Microsoft’s Surface Tablet Lacks Apps to Rival IPad</Title><Username>in_best_we_trust</Username><Timestamp>1351174062142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:07:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sick.. deranged ... lunatic.... is the your whole life?</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1351361294447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 14:08:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351363381279-19</Id><Title>Besty_pest, how much dividend did Rambus pay?</Title><Msg>Negative dividend doesn't count, albeit a high number. I hope you know the difference between positive and negative LMAO!</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1351363381279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 14:43:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351364174431-20</Id><Topic><Title>Jeepers Best, Everybody else pays a dividend.</Title><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1351349062429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's Jen's fear of the Chinese, right? The reason why Jen is hoarding nearly One Year's Gross Revenues -- in cash. He knows that on any random Tuesday, the People's Republic of China can start hostilities to reclaim their rogue state of Taiwan. Like they reclaimed Hong Kong. But with the Chinese Red Army, Air Force and Navy involved this time. And with 100% of Jen's semiconductor chips being fabricated by Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company, -- located IN Taiwan, don't u know -- well, things might not turn out swimmingly well for the Green Team. Hence Jen's need to hoard absurd amounts of unemployed shareholder's cash.</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1351364174431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 14:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351366771771-21</Id><Title>Does the CEO expect shareholders to thrown in the towel?</Title><Msg>maybe, maybe not. He does not talk to us much....I never as a shareholder received even one shareholder letter... Yes, not one letter or reward for investing in his company. so he probably does expect shareholders will bail as evident in the share price action over the last 5 years.</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1351366771771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:39:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351367031984-22</Id><Topic><Title>Does the CEO expect shareholders to thrown in the towel?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1351366771771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:39:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is stopping you? - go ahead and throw in the towel. Cry baby!</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1351367031984</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351370292654-23</Id><Topic><Title>Jeepers Best, Everybody else pays a dividend.</Title><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1351349062429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best, In the clash between Chinese Red Army, Air Force and Navy and the rogue state of Taiwan's National Guard, let's say a Chinese Red Army smart bomb has a bad day and goes down the chimney of the Taiwanese Semiconductor Manufacturing Company's plant -- by accident of course. Rendering TSMC's class 5 clean room, well, not so clean any more. The formerly class 5 clean room that formerly made 100% of nvidia chips. "Collateral damage" the military folks call it. Where's fabless Jen gonna get all his chips made? Like for the next three years. Hummm?</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1351370292654</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:38:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351371574673-24</Id><Topic><Title>Does the CEO expect shareholders to thrown in the towel?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1351366771771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:39:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>smallstock1, Jensen is a focused man who doesn't worry about things he can't control, such as the stock price. Good Luck with your investing !</Msg><Username>pastdue99</Username><Timestamp>1351371574673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351374878117-25</Id><Topic><Title>Does the CEO expect shareholders to thrown in the towel?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1351366771771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:39:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>others have thrown in the towel...I want a return and expect it based on potential... jen can control the share price by making things happen...Again, he would fire himself if he worked for himself..... I demand some return on investment....and stop issuing stock options until the performance of the stock turns around...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1351374878117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 17:54:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351376875725-26</Id><Title>Upgrade Nexus 7: 32 GB RAM and 3G!!!</Title><Msg>That's the rumored. All for the price of $249!!! A steal for the Christmas holidays.</Msg><Username>toisletsat</Username><Timestamp>1351376875725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 18:27:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351381802457-27</Id><Topic><Title>Does the CEO expect shareholders to thrown in the towel?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1351366771771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:39:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Jensen is a focused man who doesn't worry about such things as the stock price." HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA! HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA! Oh my God, that has to be the FUNNIEST line of the month! Past due dude, Jen's entire undiversified net worth, trusts, stock options, proceeds from stock sales and EGO is determined by the nvidia stock price. And what, he hires a whole crew of paid nvidia pumper boys for his grins, hilarity and personal amusement? "Jensen is a focused man who doesn't worry about such things as the stock price." Now THAT's priceless!</Msg><Username>good_one_best</Username><Timestamp>1351381802457</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 19:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351391200325-28</Id><Topic><Title>Upgrade Nexus 7: 32 GB RAM and 3G!!!</Title><Username>toisletsat</Username><Timestamp>1351376875725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 18:27:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>7 ... 3G.... T3 with quad A9.... that's so 'yesterday'. X'mas belongs to 10 .... 4G .... A15s!</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1351391200325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 22:26:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>