<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353564046310-1</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA FLYNG UP UP AND AWAY TODAY!</Title><Username>better_than_bestie</Username><Timestamp>1353514948140</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 11:22:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean 'domesticated' turkey not 'domestic' you dumb sack.</Msg><Username>best_the_turkey</Username><Timestamp>1353564046310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 01:00:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353597999262-2</Id><Topic><Title>Was Otellini pushed???</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1353523512617</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 13:45:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel is challenged in the mobile arena, with handsets and tablets cannibalising core PC sales, and with Intel not achieving solid success in handsets or tablets. Otellini’s departure could be related to the immense challenges Intel faces in competing in the mobile space." ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- A bit of history: from 2006: "Marvell To Purchase Intel’s Communications And Application Processor Business For $600 Million"</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353597999262</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 10:26:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353606749053-3</Id><Title>Notice How Quiet Management Has Been?</Title><Msg>Notice how quiet Nvidia's management has been? My goodness they even pay a 2.6% dividend. Will they start stock buybacks too as they hinted at in last quarters conference call. What in the world has brought about this sudden and swift change in Nvidia's personna. Has some magic internal metric finally been hit by AMD's demise in GPUs? Gross margins climbing. Texas Instruments exiting the mobile application market puts up 8% of the market for grabs with only Qualcomm and Nvidia left to compete for it. Can Nvidia actually get the Kindle Fire and Nook processor slots? Will Nvidia get their Icera LTE modem integrated with Tegra 4 in time to challenge Qualcomm? I bought this week for the potential growth and income. Suspect some growth and income mutual funds are doing the same. I for one am thankful for the change in Nvidia's investor face. But maybe it's just Jen Hsung trying out for the top slot at Intel when they purchase Nvidia.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1353606749053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 12:52:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353607790460-4</Id><Title>Intel acquires ZiiLabs, jumps into ARM processors.</Title><Msg>Another acknowledgment that Intel is feeling the heat of the bloated x86, and the dominant success of ARM. Any thoughts about the ramifications? "The ZMS processors redefine the landscape for high-performance, low-energy computing. The latest ZMS-20 combines ZiiLABS' proven Stemcell media processing array with dual 1.5GHz ARM Cortex-A9 MPCore to deliver stunning 1080p high profile video playback, immersive OpenGL ES 2.0 gaming, HD video calling and a rich desktop browsing experience including Adobe Flash player support." With multi-core application acceleration and dynamic power management for longer battery life the ZMS processors deliver efficient, high-performance computing across a broad range of devices, from Tablets and Smartphones to video conferencing and digital home solutions. The latest ZiiLABS processors featuring Stemcell Computing include: ZMS-40 : Quad 1.5 GHz ARM Cortex A9 + 96 Core Stemcell Array ZMS-20 : Dual 1.5 GHz ARM Cortex A9 + 48 Core Stemcell Array ZMS-08 : 1GHz ARM Cortex A8 + Stemcell Array</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1353607790460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 13:09:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353608838080-5</Id><Topic><Title>Notice How Quiet Management Has Been?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1353606749053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 12:52:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess Jen finally understands that publicly releasing details on the next generation chip during the prime-time selling season has no advantages. They will announce T4 at the CES show in early Jan. just around the time the phone/tablet makers are focused on the next generation. Whatever the reason, I do like the new style of not informing the competition, and the public who might forgo a purchase now, and wait for the new improved performance.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1353608838080</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 13:27:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353611045234-6</Id><Topic><Title>Notice How Quiet Management Has Been?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1353606749053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 12:52:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Whatever the reason, I do like the new style of not informing the competition, and the public who might forgo a purchase now, and wait for the new improved performance." I agree. Grownups have entered the room! One other point. Nvidia is now saying Maxwell GPUs in 2014 instead of next year. This means further margin expansion and higher profits next year for GPUs. Let's face it.....AMD is dropping out of the GPU picture at an alarming rate. GPU operating income percent has been climbing steadily...19.5% in the Jan. 2012 quarter to 26.1% last quarter. Should go over 30% in 2013. And if Nvidia wins the Kindle fire processor slot that would make the Consumer Products Division (Tegra) profitable for the first time in it's history. Hence the dividend. Now what kind of dividend policy will they pursue? Typically semiconductor companies hike dividends on a yearly basis, but there have been a few that start small and raise slightly every quarter. See Microchip Technology's dividend history. Let's hope they stop the absurd share dilution of the last 3 years by stock buy backs. Even potentially reversing the trend by 30 to 40 million shares. All the employees have more than enough options....but their not in the money. I'm sure they want to be able to cash some someday.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1353611045234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 14:04:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353611286732-7</Id><Topic><Title>Notice How Quiet Management Has Been?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1353606749053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 12:52:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>amzn is price only, so nvda or even qcom would not be able to underbid samsung, who has a fab sitting there with a lot of empty wafer starts now that aapl is moving out. Samsung will own that socket, unless that is, the day when they can fill that fab all by themselves. Forget about nvda fabbing at samsung and selling to amzn, samsung will see to that pronto by undercutting the price.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1353611286732</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 14:08:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353615580646-8</Id><Topic><Title>Notice How Quiet Management Has Been?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1353606749053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 12:52:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nvidia is now saying Maxwell GPUs in 2014 instead of next year. " It means Maxwell is late, for TSMC 20nm is late, and NVidia Project Denver is late... GPGPU computing will turn into something different when it has the full programability of a CPU(s).... a full SOC for HPC... "This means further margin expansion and higher profits next year for GPUs." Hope so... Their current high-end part appears more geared for Tesla than Quadro... But next year they'll release new improved Kepler parts for graphics... new AMD CEO really shaking things up, in a bad way, at AMD... morale must really suck over there these days...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353615580646</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 15:19:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353621491995-9</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel acquisition of Nvidia possible?</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353430809659</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 12:00:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What hemorrhaging? Intel is still making $20 billion cash each year from x86 (in spite of the cost of building the World's best Fabs at the same time) and Nvidia is still losing hundreds of millions each year from ARM. So what and where is this fantasy world you guys all inhabit, x86 is the most financially successful computer architecture of all time and it isn't done yet ! Atom still sells more than Tegra so if Atom is not successful than neither is Tegra which you want Intel to waste its money on. Clovertrail makes Tegra 3 look slow and hot and will abort the WinRT market at birth. No-one in their right mind would want Huang to manage their company unless deception and incompetence were part of the requirements. He is a laughing stock amongst Intel employees and investors, there is more chance of AMD's ex CEO Jerry Sanders being the CEO of Intel lol ! Totally forget this pipe dream you all have of Intel and Nvidia, Nvidia has nothing Intel wants.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353621491995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 16:58:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353622524814-10</Id><Topic><Title>Notice How Quiet Management Has Been?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1353606749053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 12:52:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One would think Intel has spare fab capacity.....one would think qcom is too big for Intel to warn up with....Nvidia is their darling...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1353622524814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 17:15:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353622607617-11</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel acquisition of Nvidia possible?</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353430809659</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 12:00:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have seen ARM's own performance numbers for the 64-bit ARM A57 and it's not going to be threatening any Core processor, even the 65nm Core 2 Duo would beat it in single thread performance and how old is that chip ! ARM64's competition will still be the Atom line and Atom is the one starting out with the tiny marketshare on tablets and phones so ARM is going to be the one being threatened. As to Project Denver Qualcomm thought they could build a better performing triple-issue out of order processor than ARM A15 with its S4 Krait, sure has not turned out that way. Let's wait until we see the specs and benchmarks before proclaiming PD the 2nd coming as you guys have been pumping it for as many years as it has been delayed !</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353622607617</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 17:16:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353622631853-12</Id><Title>I smell a gap up tomorrow morning</Title><Msg>despite what best has dialed in...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1353622631853</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 17:17:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353631034605-13</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel acquisition of Nvidia possible?</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353430809659</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 12:00:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"As to Project Denver Qualcomm thought they could build a better performing triple-issue out of order processor than ARM A15 with its S4 Krait, sure has not turned out that way. " Hmmm...find any representative from Qualcomm, NVidia, ARMH, or INtel... that will claim that Qualcomm's Krait has a shred of anything to do with Project Denver... Project Denver will be as much to do about NVidia's compilers working with Project Denver... than just plugging Project Denver into an ARMH compiler... At least that's my understanding after reading interviews with Bill Daly... "Let's wait until we see the specs and benchmarks" We'll be here...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353631034605</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 19:37:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353633519396-14</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel acquisition of Nvidia possible?</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353430809659</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 12:00:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You missed the point I was making, just because you are doing your own bespoke processor does not meant it will automatically better than the effort from the company who designed the ISA. Compilers also can't get out performance that is not inherently there. Frankly we know nothing about Project Denver architecturally wise, at least we have seen detailed ARM A57 and Applied Micro X-Gene specs. Yes you can hope it will be great and awesome but it is not remotely a given. Have no fear though if it does have traits of goodness or even greatness in it I will not be shy in informing you about them ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353633519396</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 20:18:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353634200380-15</Id><Title>When will this dog have it's day???</Title><Msg>I have owned this stock for over a decade and am DISGUSTED that is goes nowhere year after year. Granted, I doubled my money and sold half my position a number of years ago but since then it has done nothing. They should give us a whopping stock dividend. Long term stockholders need a reward. Hell, I am tempted to throw in the towel and put my money where I get a strong dividend. What do you think?</Msg><Username>wftglo</Username><Timestamp>1353634200380</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 20:30:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353634888128-16</Id><Topic><Title>When will this dog have it's day???</Title><Username>wftglo</Username><Timestamp>1353634200380</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 20:30:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>decade huh? a buy in the later 2002 thru 2003 time frame figures to a 3 to 5 bagger .. not a bad return eh ??? what are you kvecthing about ?LOL</Msg><Username>best_the_turkey</Username><Timestamp>1353634888128</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 20:41:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353640038847-17</Id><Topic><Title>Notice How Quiet Management Has Been?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1353606749053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 12:52:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"new AMD CEO really shaking things up, in a bad way, at AMD... morale must really suck over there these days..." First rule of Silicon Valley----never never never put a Marketeer in charge of Technology company! Finance guys and gals are bad enough but Marketing types must always be kept on a tight leash. Want more proof look no further than HP with that crybaby Meg Whitman. LOL Hey Nvidia can make good use of the $300M a quarter AMD graphics revenue that will have to go Nvidia when AMD folds within 12 months!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1353640038847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 22:07:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353641211624-18</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel acquisition of Nvidia possible?</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353430809659</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 12:00:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You missed the point I was making, just because you are doing your own bespoke processor does not meant it will automatically better than the effort from the company who designed the ISA. " NO, I don't think I missed your point. But my point was that results of Krait, relative to the company that designed the ISA, have zero relevance to how the results of Project Denver will turn out... "Compilers also can't get out performance that is not inherently there" True, they cannot. And I will also add I can only speculate on what NVidia is up to... But that doesn't mean you can automatically discount their claims of looking at multi-issue 'fixed'-length instructions, data dependencies, and branch miss/prediction working with new compilers is to be entirely discounted... I personally am very drawn to this for it was something I wanted to pursue... but was never allowed to... Anyway, probably why it makes total sense to me... "Yes you can hope it will be great and awesome but it is not remotely a given. Have no fear though if it does have traits of goodness or even greatness in it I will not be shy in informing you about them ;-)." And you can hope it will be like Qualcomm and NOT deliver bragging right improvements... So where are now: I cannot produce any evidence it delivers... You cannot produce any evidence it underwhelmed...or another 'me too' But we both agree that you are NOT shy...:) And I think that you will be over every scrap of info there will be about Project Denver... far more than any other ARM CPU...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353641211624</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 22:26:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353643803615-19</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel acquisition of Nvidia possible?</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353430809659</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 12:00:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I’ve noticed there are 21 replies on this topic which shows quite an interest. It seems investors here are worried about Nvidia’s doomed fate and its diminishing prospect. What is so odd is Nvidia’s management has been very quiet recently which is always not a good sign.</Msg><Username>ali_next_play</Username><Timestamp>1353643803615</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 23:10:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353644488420-20</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel acquisition of Nvidia possible?</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353430809659</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 12:00:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I’ve noticed there are 21 replies on this topic which shows quite an interest. It seems investors here are worried about Nvidia’s doomed fate and its diminishing prospect. What is so odd is Nvidia’s management has been very quiet recently which is always not a good sign." ---------------------------------------- weak... Good Luck with your short...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353644488420</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 23:21:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>