<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-13"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347516505031-1</Id><Title>How bashers could be so stupid?</Title><Msg>They kept bashing this with it not in IPad or amazon kindle fire. But please, it is in 2 major companies tablet. 1. Is google ! A proven successful sales. 2. Is Microsoft surface. Though not on sale but it has fantastic design. These 2 are behemoth companies. It shows nvidia is a good contender in the mobile space. Period. It doesn't have to win all. As long as the tech sector rises in the mobile space, rising tide raises all good contenders. Qcom , Texas, Intel, Brcm, Nvidia will all rally together.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347516505031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 02:08:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347529357572-2</Id><Title>Per Bloomberg, new iPhonee will be fastest selling tech device ever</Title><Msg>Just like Senor Best and I have been saying for months. Sell NVDA and buy AAPL. IMHO</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1347529357572</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 05:42:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347529495931-3</Id><Topic><Title>How bashers could be so stupid?</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347516505031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 02:08:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see you conveniently left off the fact that they still lose many many millions a year on the Terga and it looks like it may never be profitable at all.</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1347529495931</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 05:44:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347529690291-4</Id><Topic><Title>That settles it! - EETimes says A6 includes a quad-core A9 processor</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347495435355</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:17:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Senor Ibex, you are investing under the wrong impression. People do not care about chip size as long as the chip fits in the phone, it is fine. Companies that can't compete on performance brag about small chips because they can't compete on other specs.</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1347529690291</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 05:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347529985590-5</Id><Topic><Title>No IPAD mini! haha! what idiots.</Title><Username>tradingguy1111</Username><Timestamp>1347477093036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny, because it will be the fastest selling gadget ever, and, unlike Nvidia's poorly thought out mobile offerings, everything Apple releases is EXTREMELY PROFITABLE!</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1347529985590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 05:53:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347530717551-6</Id><Topic><Title>Apple lost Cheyer, the second co-founder of Siri Voice Unit</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347430990551</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 02:23:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Best, his Apple bashes are getting so ridiculous, Surprised Senor Jen even let him post so much from work. Might be time to invest in a real PR department and cut down on the message board pumpers. imho</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1347530717551</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 06:05:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347534839343-7</Id><Topic><Title>That settles it! - EETimes says A6 includes a quad-core A9 processor</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347495435355</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:17:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'which was **expected** to include' Regardless, even if it is a quad-core it will match the Tegra 3 on cpu and absolutely destroy it in graphics and as Apple is selling a phone and not a cpu die it really doesn't matter how big it is. Apple has the best all round performing mobile SoC again !</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347534839343</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 07:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347540063382-8</Id><Title>Downgraded again!!!! Darn it</Title><Msg>The screws love to kill this stock this time by Citi. Cuts AMD NVDA and intc</Msg><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1347540063382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:41:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347541116746-9</Id><Title>Apple’s Latest IPhone Set to Become Best-Selling Gadget</Title><Msg>. Google this, boys: Apple’s Latest IPhone Set to Become Best-Selling Gadget In excerpts. "Apple Inc. (AAPL) unveiled a taller, lighter and speedier iPhone that’s poised to become the fastest selling technology gadget in history -- even as competition accelerates in the $219.1 billion smartphone market. “This is going to be the best-selling consumer electronics device of all time, bar none,” said Carl Howe, an analyst at Boston-based Yankee Group, who predicted that Apple will sell more than 10 million by month’s end, surpassing the record set last year by the predecessor device, the iPhone 4S. Chief Executive Officer Tim Cook took the stage in San Francisco yesterday to tout iPhone 5, which runs on faster wireless networks, boasts a bigger screen and has a chip that handles tasks more quickly than past versions. “Apple has never been stronger,” Cook said during the presentation. Apple may sell as many as 58 million units of the iPhone 5 by the end of the year, according the average estimate of analysts surveyed by Bloomberg. That could generate as much as $36.2 billion in sales for Apple, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. Going Global Sold with a wireless contract, the iPhone 5 will cost $199, $299 or $399, depending on how much memory it contains. The device will be available for orders on Sept. 14 and lands on store shelves Sept. 21 in the U.S., Australia, Canada, France, Germany, Hong Kong, Japan, Singapore and the U.K. It goes on sale in another 22 countries on Sept. 28. The iPhone, introduced in 2007, has helped make Apple the world’s most valuable company. Once a niche computer maker, Apple now generates higher profit than technology competitors Hewlett-Packard Co. (HPQ), Microsoft and Google Inc. (GOOG) Having popularized handheld touch-screen devices that offer swift Web downloads and a range of games, entertainment and productivity tools, Apple is now battling with manufacturers led by Samsung for dominance of a market that leaped 62 percent last year. ‘Radical Revision’ The new iPhone, Apple’s sixth, works with so-called long- term evolution, or LTE, data networks being introduced by companies including AT&amp;T Inc. (T) and Verizon Wireless. LTE is designed to enable quicker Web browsing as well as faster download speeds for video and music than existing networks. Even though using faster networks can drain a phone’s power supply, Apple said iPhone 5’s battery lasts longer than earlier models.The iPhone 5 also comes 18 percent thinner and 20 percent lighter than the iPhone 4S, Apple said. To make the device more svelte, Apple changed the design of the charging-dock connector. To accommodate the slew of accessories that are available for the older dock design, Apple said it will sell an adapter. “The iPhone 5 represents the most radical revision yet to the biggest-selling smartphone,” Mike Gikas, an editor at Consumer Reports, said in an initial review of the product. “It has enough improvements and enhancements that even satisfied owners of the last-generation iPhone 4S will want to consider upgrading.” ‘Blowout, Home Run’ “There’s more attention than ever on Apple,” Schiller told reporters after the event. “That’s a great thing.” “They have built a juggernaut,” said Matt Murphy, a partner at Kleiner Perkins Caufield &amp; Byers, a venture capital firm that invests in iPhone application companies. “This is going to be an absolutely blowout, home-run product.” Apple also enhanced the speech-command service Siri, adding features that let users search for sports scores and make dinner reservations by speaking to the smartphone. A new application called Passbook gives users one application to store their loyalty gift cards, as well as digital tickets to movies, concerts and sporting events. “When you look at each of these, they are incredible, industry-leading innovations by themselves, but what sets them apart and puts Apple way ahead of the competition is how they work so well together,” said Cook." .</Msg><Username>bestonica</Username><Timestamp>1347541116746</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:58:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347541727779-10</Id><Topic><Title>Apple’s Latest IPhone Set to Become Best-Selling Gadget</Title><Username>bestonica</Username><Timestamp>1347541116746</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:58:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. "Apple may sell as many as 58 million units of the iPhone 5 by the end of the year, according the average estimate of analysts surveyed by Bloomberg. That could generate as much as $36.2 billion in sales for Apple, according to data compiled by Bloomberg." It is truly a shame, right boys? That there are no nvidia parts in the Genuine Apple iPhone 5 None. Nada. Goose egg. Not even the baseband radio part -- which nvidia/icera now purports to make. Truly a shame to have lost such a whale of an order.. .</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1347541727779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:08:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347542866470-11</Id><Title>The downgraders will have their face slap today</Title><Msg>Nvidia just made a hedge fund buy signal with yesterdays close.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347542866470</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:27:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347543084515-12</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon's new $199 tablet gets tepid reviews</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347542629497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. “This is going to be the best-selling consumer electronics device of all time, bar none,” said Carl Howe, an analyst at Boston-based Yankee Group, who predicted that Apple will sell more than 10 million by month’s end, surpassing the record set last year by the predecessor device, the iPhone 4S. "Apple may sell as many as 58 million units of the iPhone 5 by the end of the year, according the average estimate of analysts surveyed by Bloomberg. That could generate as much as $36.2 billion in sales for Apple, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. “They have built a juggernaut,” said Matt Murphy, a partner at Kleiner Perkins Caufield &amp; Byers, a venture capital firm that invests in iPhone application companies. “This is going to be an absolutely blowout, home-run product.” Google this, boys: Apple’s Latest IPhone Set to Become Best-Selling Gadget .</Msg><Username>ibest.here</Username><Timestamp>1347543084515</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:31:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347543440217-13</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon's new $199 tablet gets tepid reviews</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347542629497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seekingalpha has a nice objective but very negative writeup on FireHD. One more thing that they never told you. Besides paying $15 to get rid of the ad, you even have to pay $10 - $20 to buy a charger??!! Like I said, don't turn your back on Bezos, keep a very close eye on him if you do business with him, he'll nickel and dime you to death. OK, all eyes on Ballmer' winRt, he's going to seize the moment as the man who brought msft back from mobile oblivion? or the guy who charges $500 because he's 'worth it'.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1347543440217</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:37:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347544314747-14</Id><Title>Sell NVDA downgraded by Citi &amp; Buy GDOT Upgraded by Piper Jaffray</Title><Msg>Piper Jaffray has upgraded GDOT from Neutral to Overweight and the price target is $20/share ... Now Citi has downgraded NVDA ... Is it worth hanging on to NVDA ... isn't it better to sell NVDA and buy GDOT? GDOT is presenting at Goldman Sachs Financial Technology Conference at the Goldman Sachs Conference Center in New York, NY</Msg><Username>delphioracle2009</Username><Timestamp>1347544314747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:51:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347545198727-15</Id><Title>New Kepler graphics boards announced today</Title><Msg>SANTA CLARA, CA--(Marketwire - Sep 13, 2012) - NVIDIA today introduced two new high-performance GPUs, the NVIDIA® GeForce® GTX 660 and GeForce GTX 650. These new gaming GPUs deliver the exceptional performance and power efficiency of the award-winning NVIDIA® Kepler™ architecture at price points that will allow more gamers to experience the richness of next-generation PC gaming. The GeForce GTX 660 and GeForce GTX 650 GPUs set a new benchmark for high-performance, remarkably-priced gaming available now</Msg><Username>schmenkle321</Username><Timestamp>1347545198727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347545530745-16</Id><Title>They presented at think equity this mOrning</Title><Msg>Guided rev in line and said Tegra Kepler doing well Supply fine less constraint. Think equity is buying today</Msg><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1347545530745</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:12:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347545572306-17</Id><Topic><Title>Apple lost Cheyer, the second co-founder of Siri Voice Unit</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347430990551</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 02:23:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. "Best, ibbey's Apple bashing is getting Sooo ridiculous. Might be time for Jen to invest in a real PR Department, and pink-slip the nvidia pumper crew." . Jen probably is probably still thinkin' he gets more mileage from a cheap pair of speakers. Always behind the times that guy. .</Msg><Username>good_one_best</Username><Timestamp>1347545572306</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:12:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347547354027-18</Id><Title>Two new graphics cards...and the stock tanks? only you...NVDA,,,only you</Title><Msg>I think I'll actually buy a new card for 109$ ... that's an awesome price for the power.</Msg><Username>tradingguy1111</Username><Timestamp>1347547354027</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:42:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347547959335-19</Id><Title>NVDA downgrade</Title><Msg>Chips Chopped: Citi Cuts Ratings On Intel, AMD, Nvidia Citing the ongoing weakness in PC demand, Citigroup analyst Glen Yeung this morning cut his ratings on Intel, Advanced Micro Devices and Nvidia to Neutral from Buy. “While these names are down noticeably in recent days, prompted by a noticeably weak August and punctuated by Intel’s recent pre-announcement our downgrade today reflects our checks in Asia that stoke our concerns that the intermediate term prospects for PC’s do not look optimistic,” he writes. “Robbed of catalysts, we see limited likelihood PC-related shares will appreciate meaningfully in coming months, despite valuations.” For 2013, he now sees PC units shrinking 1% – his old forecast was for 4% growth – despite the upcoming launch of Microsoft Windows 8. Here’s Yeung list of reasons for the more bearish view: Yeung asserts that touch-based solutions will comprise less than 5% of production in the 2012 second half, “negating the benefits of the Metro UI.” He says ASP’s of touch-enabled solutions “are apt to remain high, adding $50-$100 to system costs. He also notes that high license fees for Windows RT-based solutions – which are required to bundle Office – are likely to elevate ARM-based notebook prices. “Macro uncertainty is clouding demand and likely limits tolerance for high ASP devices.” Tablet cannibalization also will be an ongoing issue. “After an initial build recovery in September and October, we suspect PC-related builds will again soften from November onward,” he writes. In addition to the downgrades, he also cut his price targets and EPS estimates for the PC chip stocks: Intel: New target is $25.75, down from $32. For 2012, he now sees profits of $2.07 share, down from $2.25. AMD: New target $4.25, down from $6.50. For 2012, Yeung now expects a loss of 72 cents a share; his previous forecast was a loss of 65 cents. Nvidia: Target goes to $15.25, from $16.50. For 2012, Citi now sees profits of 89 cents a share, down from 92 cents. Marvell: Yeung maintains his Neutral rating on the stock, while cutting his target to $11.50, from $14. His EPS estimate for the company are unchanged.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347547959335</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:52:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347548646444-20</Id><Title>carnival bark board!!!</Title><Msg>bottom line.....</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1347548646444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:04:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347549462108-21</Id><Topic><Title>carnival bark board!!!</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1347548646444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:04:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Matches the CEO.</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1347549462108</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:17:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347554675556-22</Id><Title>shorts in trouble here</Title><Msg>eomeom,:)</Msg><Username>daysofshred30000000000</Username><Timestamp>1347554675556</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347555053373-23</Id><Title>shorts taking mm's hostage, breaking news!!!</Title><Msg>they will hang them soon w/o coop</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1347555053373</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:50:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347555613246-24</Id><Title>breaking news!!! shorts going after long's mothers!!!</Title><Msg>children being rounded up as well</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1347555613246</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:00:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347556498236-25</Id><Title>Stop WHINING Nvidia fans. Apple is a winner. Nvidia is junk.</Title><Msg>Wake up and stop whining because you put it all on the wronng horse. Apple is $680. Nvidia is $13. When Nvidia was $26 Apple was $345 You blew the best investing opportunity of your generation so hush with all that WHINING. Nvidia Historical Prices Feb 2, 2011 24.33 26.17 24.33 25.58 40,165,400 25.58 Apple Historical Prices Feb 2, 2011 344.45 345.25 343.55 344.32 9,248,400 342.85 Your horse has been running backwards. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1347556498236</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:14:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347557364373-26</Id><Topic><Title>Stop WHINING Nvidia fans. Apple is a winner. Nvidia is junk.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1347556498236</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks, you're wonderful...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1347557364373</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:29:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347558148682-27</Id><Title>Apple sets another NEW ALL TIME HIGH. Over $684 today.</Title><Msg>You can't bash the RICHEST stock on earth while its setting NEW ALL TIMES HIGHS without making yourself look like a fool, can you? Can you? lol Get over it Nvidia fans. This market likes its Apples. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1347558148682</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347558581189-28</Id><Title>Apple added $14 today or over $13 BILLION in market cap which is more than you know who is worth.</Title><Msg>And they did that in ONE DAY. Another $13 BILLION in shareholders pockets in ONE DAY. Are you sure you want to waste your time bashing iPhone 5 or iAnything? Really? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1347558581189</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347561173808-29</Id><Title>Dow up 220 points. Nvda UP</Title><Msg>ten cents! This is a POP?</Msg><Username>alwasontop</Username><Timestamp>1347561173808</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347563436844-30</Id><Topic><Title>Dow up 220 points. Nvda UP</Title><Username>alwasontop</Username><Timestamp>1347561173808</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:32:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barely up....but it's up at least....I should have held my BAC ...</Msg><Username>tradingguy1111</Username><Timestamp>1347563436844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:10:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347564092348-31</Id><Title>Always tanks EOD, like clock work.....close of 13.60 max</Title><Msg>......watch</Msg><Username>tradingguy1111</Username><Timestamp>1347564092348</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:21:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347564149901-32</Id><Topic><Title>Dow up 220 points. Nvda UP</Title><Username>alwasontop</Username><Timestamp>1347561173808</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:32:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flat lining here at +0.05, could close with a red candle. This stock is an empty suit or a full garbage can.</Msg><Username>alwasontop</Username><Timestamp>1347564149901</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:22:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347565432832-33</Id><Title>Oh well, I'm wrong again....wow</Title><Msg>Nice run EOD, it's about time!!</Msg><Username>tradingguy1111</Username><Timestamp>1347565432832</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:43:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347565824395-34</Id><Title>come on close above 50ma of 13.68 ,go go go go!!!</Title><Msg>go go go!</Msg><Username>tradingguy1111</Username><Timestamp>1347565824395</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347568360798-35</Id><Title>Market up 200+, Everything super-up, how about NVDA ??</Title><Msg>Every freakin stock is way up, including QCOM, BRCM and others and NVDA is up only 9 penny ?? What is happening guys ? With adecent market gain of 20-30 points, 9-10 pennies are usually what NVDA goes up. How about when market is up big way like today ? On the other side, when NVDA is down it does not go down by 10-15 penny but by 30-40 pennies. I am wondering what type of catalyst they need to gain 10 % on one day, Buyout ? Really frustrated the way it is trading. With Dow trading over 13,500 and Nasdaq close to 3200,Market does not seem to have much room to gain. What does NVDA need to go over $15, DOW 15,000 ? No way Jose.</Msg><Username>fraihan64</Username><Timestamp>1347568360798</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:32:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347570483535-36</Id><Topic><Title>Market up 200+, Everything super-up, how about NVDA ??</Title><Username>fraihan64</Username><Timestamp>1347568360798</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:32:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NVDA is way over sold ... investors confidence down? need some good news...Tegra 4 news would make it pop, but what will really move this...is quarterly results....that's when I'll sell this FAT PIG....have avg of 14 now....waiting and waiting...and waiting...so boring ...but it's bounced off 50MA and it's trending up....just have to stay away from those -5% days...those are behind us IMO</Msg><Username>tradingguy1111</Username><Timestamp>1347570483535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:08:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347571120086-37</Id><Title>AT&amp;T HTC One X+ 4G LTE with Tegra 3 spotted at FCC</Title><Msg>Source: Android Community Rumors of an HTC One X+ have been floating around for some time now, some even stating a model arriving for T-Mobile. Today however a new and improved Tegra 3 powered quad-core 4G LTE One X+ has hit the FCC en route to AT&amp;T. NVIDIA’s Icera modem recently was approved for AT&amp;T 4G LTE too, so this makes perfect sense. We still aren’t fully sure what to expect from the folks at HTC but they have an event coming up next week where we’ll be learning about what they’ve been brewing. These recent FCC filings have all but confirmed the device exists, and rumors have suggested it will be designed very similar if not the same as the previous One X. I’m hopeful for a larger battery though myself. We’ve seen reports that the NVIDIA Tegra 3 has been boosted to 1.6 GHz on all four cores, as well as 1.7 GHz for the fifth “ninja core” that does the simpler tasks at hand to preserve battery life. The folks from Engadget uncovered this FCC filing earlier today so now we just need to wait for HTC to make a formal announcement. NVIDIA has stated their quad-core Tegra 3+ with 4G LTE radios would make it to market before the end of 2012, and they look to be right on track. Hopefully HTC is aiming for an October launch — which also lines up with a few recent rumors although nothing can be confirmed at this moment. For now it appears that an improved HTC One X+ is for sure headed to AT&amp;T, and possibly to the folks at T-Mobile too. Stay tuned for details from next weeks event.</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1347571120086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:18:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347571842065-38</Id><Topic><Title>Market up 200+, Everything super-up, how about NVDA ??</Title><Username>fraihan64</Username><Timestamp>1347568360798</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:32:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I still remember the days back when NVDA was around $26. I know they are trying to ramp up icera baseband chip which they have to fiercely compete with QCOM and come out with a superior product. But, they need to focus more on smartphone compared to tablets. PC's are really in downtrend.So, few design wins in smartphone and lauch of Icera baseband chip, in my point of view, will turn the boat for NVDA. Any thoughts or comments ?</Msg><Username>fraihan64</Username><Timestamp>1347571842065</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:30:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347572864329-39</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T HTC One X+ 4G LTE with Tegra 3 spotted at FCC</Title><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1347571120086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:18:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Bro, When is the event next week ? any specific time ?</Msg><Username>fraihan64</Username><Timestamp>1347572864329</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:47:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347578080298-40</Id><Topic><Title>Apple added $14 today or over $13 BILLION in market cap which is more than you know who is worth.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1347558581189</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That has more to do with a higher valued company... Apple can also subtract 13B from shareholders pockets in in 0NE Day! Is their really anything bad to say about a improved tech that will be leapfrogged in a few months. Its called progress.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1347578080298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347578710242-41</Id><Topic><Title>Is there room in Apple's lineup for an ipad Mini? - a lot less likely than a couple of days ago</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347576164515</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know if I'd agree the iPad Mini would be better than the Google Nexus 7. No doubt, it would be better then the Fire, but I think the Fire will prove to be a bust, maybe even short-term. And based on what I've read and heard about the iPhone 5, it seems like Apple is starting to lose an edge or maybe it's just not possible to innovate anymore than they have without getting lawsuits for copyright infringement themselves. I mean couldn't the decision about a 4" screen be because there are already the larger 4.3" screens by Samsung out there . . seriously!</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1347578710242</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:25:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347578828262-42</Id><Topic><Title>Is there room in Apple's lineup for an ipad Mini? - a lot less likely than a couple of days ago</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347576164515</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As long as Apple maintain its tablet market share it does not want to release iPad mini. There is not going to be a competition between iPad mini and Nexus 7. But there is definitely going to be a competition between iPad mini and New iPad and it is going to hurt the latter big time and will reduce overall pad profit. Why would Apple want to do that?</Msg><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1347578828262</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347580914593-43</Id><Topic><Title>Is there room in Apple's lineup for an ipad Mini? - a lot less likely than a couple of days ago</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347576164515</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>come on Ballmer, $350 win RT will take home all the bacon and lift you out of the shadows of Bill. I know you can do it!</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1347580914593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347581151831-44</Id><Topic><Title>Is there room in Apple's lineup for an ipad Mini? - a lot less likely than a couple of days ago</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347576164515</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and if you, Ballmer, goes for a $300 winRT, that will get you the knighthood from the queen herself. The queen of Castro Street, that is.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1347581151831</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:05:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347582816088-45</Id><Topic><Title>Is there room in Apple's lineup for an ipad Mini? - a lot less likely than a couple of days ago</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347576164515</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you 'think' like Ballmer, nose in the air, you will not be destined for greatness. Besides, giving that away won't cost one penny. WinRT not selling will be a real disaster. Tough times require tough men making touch decisions. Ballmer, show yourself a real man, stand up from behind the shadows of you know whom!</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1347582816088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:33:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347590561753-46</Id><Title>Reiterate guidance. Think equity conference</Title><Msg>1. Ard $1.25 b rev for third quarter 2. Gaining mkt share in notebook 3. Maintains gross margin 52% 4. Second half growth from Kepler and tegra 5. Supply situation improved</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347590561753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:42:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347594614042-47</Id><Topic><Title>Apple added $14 today or over $13 BILLION in market cap which is more than you know who is worth.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1347558581189</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. "Look as us now", crows Jen and his pumper crew. nvidia closed up $00.09 today. Which, times 619,480,000 nvidia shares outstanding, created Fifty Five Million ($55,753,000) of new market cap. Today. "Look as us now", crows Jen and his pumper crew. And it sounds pretty good, right boys? $55,753,000 of new market cap created today. Hooray for the green team, right? Until you compare it to a Good company -- like Apple. Apple closed Up $13.19 per share today -- on news of the phenomenal new iPhone 5. Which, times 937,410,000 aapl shares outstanding, equals Twelve Billion Dollars ($12,308,683,000.00) of new market cap. Created between the Opening bell and the Closing bell. Just today. $12,308,683,000 of new market cap created today by Apple #$%$753,000 of new market cap for nvda. Apple outperformed nvidia by 219.8 Times today, in the Value Creation Department. 219.8X, boys. In just one day. Truly iAwesome, right boys?. So, you ask, what would nvidia's stock price have needed to be today to match Apple's iAwesome increase in market cap? Well, $12,308,683,000.00 of new market cap created by Apple today, divided by 619,480,000 nvidia shares outstanding equals $19.87. Plus the nvda closing price of $13.67 means that to replicate what Apple did today in the Value Creation Department, nvidia stock price at the close would have needed to be $33.53. $33.53 Did your precious nvidia close anywhere in the neighborhood of $33.53? Hummm? Speak up now, boys. You're mumbling at your shoes again. Maybe you boys can pick a better stock next time. One that creates iAwesome Value for its fortunate shareholders. .</Msg><Username>bested.again</Username><Timestamp>1347594614042</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:50:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347594940436-48</Id><Topic><Title>Apple added $14 today or over $13 BILLION in market cap which is more than you know who is worth.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1347558581189</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. $12,308,683,000 of new market cap created today by Apple $55,753,000 of new market cap for nvda. Juuuuuuust a bit of a difference, right boys? .</Msg><Username>bested.again</Username><Timestamp>1347594940436</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:55:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>