<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354599065315-1</Id><Topic><Title>Barrons on AAPL; Sundal Collier says "Sell", target $400, "cycle of vogue" ending....</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354566113077</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 15:21:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's time to fess-up IBEXX88, what group do you work for?" Yes, the reading public deserves to know who our 24/7 nvidia propagandist works for.</Msg><Username>bests.people</Username><Timestamp>1354599065315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 00:31:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354602653286-2</Id><Topic><Title>Barrons on AAPL; Sundal Collier says "Sell", target $400, "cycle of vogue" ending....</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354566113077</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 15:21:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most importantly ibexx88: In a large, complex and democratic community like the Yahoo! Message Boards, paid shills and compensated propagandists who post 100% nothing but sunbeams 24/7 for their employer are eventually discovered and outed publicly. Yes, discovered and outed publicly. And pushed with a click of a mouse into obsolence -- by putting the paid shills and propagandists on IGNORE. 'Cause folks have tired of the messages of paid shills for nvidia on Our board. { Click } No more propaganda from ibexx88. Oh, and ibexx88? You haven't posted your reply to Best's challenge yet. You know, about publicly denying to be paid to post here. Is there some reason? You've posted 4 little fluff pieces about nvidia since. One right here on this very thread. So you Must have Seen Best's challenge, right? What's the matter -- can't honestly do it?</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1354602653286</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 01:30:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354614953599-3</Id><Topic><Title>Barrons on AAPL; Sundal Collier says "Sell", target $400, "cycle of vogue" ending....</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354566113077</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 15:21:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'ibex' is somebody who supposedly lives in NJ, but he knows the geographic in and outs of silicon valley. 'ibex' only posts by cut and paste and hurls personal insults, but he will never ever reply with reasoning, cause this is personal thinking. 'ibex' supposedly successfully invested in qcom, but as you have found out, he knows nothing about qcom's LTE. 'ibex' supposedly successfully invested in brcm too, but his knowledge of brcm's baseband is exactly 180 degress diffeerent from what brcm is doing. but 'ibex' offers you a mirror of what is actually going on inside nvda. eg. he might insinuate this and that with cut and paste, but he will never ever go out and say directly what nvda is going to do in the future. In the rare occasions that he slips, you can take it to the bank that is the gospel truth. like when dreamers says nvda might benefit when txn got out and I said amzn is only about cheap and samsung will probably get it for fab fills, ibex stayed totally silent. then he posts that amzn going mediatek. You can bank on that being the truth, nvda is NOT in the running for the amzn socket. eg. he offers a picture of the environment inside nvda right now. Jen has so misguided the whole Tegra program, they are so way late on A15, nvda is really out of the picture now. So instead of spending his time singing his own glorifications, Jen simmers and hurls venomous barbs at all his successful mobile competitors, real or imaginary. Hence ibex's lack of +ve nvda posts and posts nothing but insults at the likes of aapl, samsung, qcom. Jen is getting so irrelevant in the app space, Jen even will hurt insults at potential customers like hp or dell. Tegra failed, just fold it. nvda can't even string ARM cores together, and there are fools here who drank so much koolaid, they still expect nvda to out-ARM ARM in processor designs. 100M$ loss in tegra this Q, nothing in the product pipe for the whole of 2013. care to take a guess how big the loses will be at the end of 2013? In silicon, no chips, no talk.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1354614953599</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 04:55:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354629176365-4</Id><Topic><Title>Barrons on AAPL; Sundal Collier says "Sell", target $400, "cycle of vogue" ending....</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354566113077</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 15:21:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good points, whosunw. Oh so many many good points. So who do you think pays ibexx88 to hurl venomous barbs at all of nvidia's more successful mobile competitors, real or imaginary? And even insults at potential customers like hp or dell? Is it, 1.) nvidia directly. 2.) nvidia indirectly, like via some independent social media management firm. 3.) some very long but haplessly under-water fund or institutional investor. 4.) Jen is paying for ibexx88, directly or indirectly. Clearly, he's a paid venomous-barb-hurling mouthpiece for somebody. Which ibexx88 has never denied. Ever.</Msg><Username>good_point_whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1354629176365</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 08:52:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354632572389-5</Id><Title>more sellers</Title><Msg>oh wow! now NVDA is attracting sellers even as the market recovers. INTC +1.5% NVDA is begging to be punished, not a safe long until it breaks 12.70 on large volume. Just good for scalping here.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354632572389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:49:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354632921585-6</Id><Topic><Title>more sellers</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354632572389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:49:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now NVDA in the green nicely and it looks like shortie here is going to be seriously soiling his big biy diapers byu and of day. Lookit, are you really going to cheerlead this stock every few pennies up or down bestie? Like I said: What a Loser.</Msg><Username>nvda_4_ever</Username><Timestamp>1354632921585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:55:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354633380857-7</Id><Topic><Title>more sellers</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354632572389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:49:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's perfectly fine - selling covered calls to greedy people, not unlike shorts, lowers my cost basis. Sold calls and bought puts on the pre 10:15 am pop and now I am in at less than 11.50. A lot less risk using this strategy albeit it does limit your upside potential some - but who cares it's trading sideways right now with plenty of support above it's 52 week low. I see little downside risk right now and considering; 1.trading at a respectable 15 PE (lower than the industry average). 2. Increasing revenues and margins in all major product lines, 3. soon to be the only high-end GPU desktop provider (once AMD divests it's assets) and possibly consoles. 4 exception levered free cash flow 5. Half of its market cap in cash and growing 6. Diversified product portfolio with superior brand recognition 7. Emerging competitor in the mobile market 8. Leader in cloud based GPU initiatives. There is a lot of upside potential! Now that being said I do agree the chart stinks but who cares the best long term strategy are to buy great companies as low as you can and sell them as high as you can. Sorry shorty, there really isn't a ton of downside here right now other than a #$%$ chart and once the chart starts to look good that is when all the retail suckers would have bough on hype and it's time to sell.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1354633380857</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 10:03:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354633649470-8</Id><Topic><Title>more sellers</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354632572389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:49:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Make sure you have your diaper changed before you take your nap and medicine.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1354633649470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 10:07:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354633873783-9</Id><Title>intc buying back she</Title><Msg>bottom in for semis same thing happened two yrs ago... they pick up shs for the dividend now nvda's turn they rise as fast as they fall.......COVER!!!!!!</Msg><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1354633873783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 10:11:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354633991477-10</Id><Topic><Title>more sellers</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354632572389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:49:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey "brokeagain" - you are a long term perma-bull, why are you wasting your time on the message boards? You should be happy with your beliefs and conviction. My negativity is not keeping this stock down. I just say it like I see it. I started looking into NVDA after their earnings report - which on surface seemed bullish. I so wanted to be long this stock. After digging into the underlying facts I see this company facing many headwinds. I am sure you are frustrated with NVDA underperformance but can't come to grips with it and keep lashing out at people who may suggest otherwise. I hardly ever post on message board of stocks that I have conviction long on, whats the point? so - I hope your NVDA long position makes you tons of money. I am going to keep swing trading it for now. I don't see any point in getting big time behind this stock with so many challenges and macro uncertainty. good luck to you</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354633991477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 10:13:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354634231919-11</Id><Topic><Title>intc buying back she</Title><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1354633873783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 10:11:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not NVDA - volume too low INTC - sure looks like bottom is in. same with MRVL.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354634231919</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 10:17:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354634442566-12</Id><Topic><Title>more sellers</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354632572389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:49:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1 year price target is $15 , that puts NVIDIA at respectable industry average trailing PE. Now - assuming revenues stay flat as well as margins, in the upcoming year which btw is simply not going to happen; with 3.5 billion in cash and growing, at WORST, this stock loses 5 bucks (which can mitigated by option play) it would be trading at 7x current PE and less than book. So, near to medium term with the same but MORE likely 50% upside potential I just can't see why you'd be short considering it could go a lot higher than 15 - dumb move in my opinion.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1354634442566</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 10:20:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354635058869-13</Id><Topic><Title>more sellers</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354632572389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:49:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, I appreciate your backdoor niceties but I am not a perma-bull at this point nor am I lashing out due to poor performance - I simply want to join in on the fun. Honestly, I just bought in, when the stock dropped recently and as I do see there are headwinds facing NVIDIA, I believe these headwinds are not isolated to NVIDIA alone. So, do you care to share your perspective on negative forces and their impact NVIDIA? As I see it they are a well branded, decently managed company with a diversified portfolio, growing revenue and income, a great balance sheet, who has expanded into growth markets which is ripe for the taking. There are many on this board who post exaggerated downside perspective none of which is empirical but rather conjecture at best if not an out right lies.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1354635058869</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 10:30:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354635091561-14</Id><Topic><Title>more sellers</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354632572389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:49:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not currently short but due to my negative sentiment and reading charts, I am making money shorting any spike-up, I have been regularly posting my positions. Btw, I am in this just to make money - if I thought NVDA was near bottom I would go long. I have seen action in the last month. NVDA sells of harder than market and underperforms market on recovery. Some of this has to do with semi sector, most of it has to do with NVDA. I still think single digits are possible when weak hands are shaken. That would be a time I would consider going long. Also, most other weak performing companies have cut expenses and had lay-offs. AMD, TXN. I dont think NVDA operating expenses justify the declining revenue stream they are supporting.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354635091561</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 10:31:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354635880542-15</Id><Title>We live in the United Cliff of America</Title><Msg>we elected the same people to do the same thing</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1354635880542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 10:44:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354636373150-16</Id><Topic><Title>more sellers</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354632572389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:49:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well, I am not going to regurgitate the whole litany of reasons. You can see some of the past postings. NVDA has a great balance sheet which tends to cloud judgement. NVDA gets its lions share of revenue from PC market. There are double negatives in this market for NVDA: 1. PC market is declining 2. NVDA is being designed out by integrated solutions from INTC and AMD NVDA is OK in the high-end GPU market but you can count on competitors and challengers. NVDA has become the King of FUD in mobile market. They over-promise and under-deliver. You can see the story on Tegra-2, Tegra-3, Denver etc. They seem to be trying to correct their behavior as they have been quiet so far on Wayne and Grey. It may also be that the projects are in bad shape and hence CEO's reluctance to opine on the subject (see how quickly the last analyst call ended when the subject came up). Meanwhile, Nvidia mobile head Mike Rayfield recently quit the company (not a good sign) and so has Icera head Stan Boland. Remember the competition in Mobility is intense, QCOM, BRCM, Mediatek etc. are the clear leaders. 2nd Tier like TXN, FSL are getting out. 3rd Tier like NVDA and MRVL need to either get big or, get out.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354636373150</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 10:52:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354636462741-17</Id><Topic><Title>more sellers</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354632572389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:49:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>O - I guess I simply don't understand most of your comments and essentially where you are getting your information from. As I said before, in my prior post, when the fundamentals and charts show strong support at or around your short target I am not sure how you justify or mitigate the risk for such little gain. The beta is 1.8 which is not flat by any means but it seems to me there are many other higher beta stocks out there that would contribute to a better risk/reward outcome. You say it is possible to go to single digits - yeah just like it is possible it will go to 15 but less likely, again as I said before. In fact I believe you yourself said that you covered at 11.80 right, so how do you think that at its current price it has not bottomed - please explain? Why would you cover if you truly believed there was little risk in holding till single digits? I think I have the answer and, despite you WANTING it to go down, you see they same fundamentals regarding price and valuation I have have mentioned prior and aren't willing to take the risk. Now on to some of the fundamentals; 1. "Also, most other weak performing companies have cut expenses and had lay-offs. AMD, TXN" Ahh yeah but neither of those are NVIDIA - NVIDIA is growing and hiring...so not sure what your point is here and I hope you AREN'T extrapolating the the current conditions of poor performing companies in the industry and deriving that NVIDIA will have the same fate - that is an opinion non of which is based in fact and if anything is a reason to buy NVIDIA as they will likely benefit from industry consolidation via attrition. 2. "I dont think NVDA operating expenses justify the declining revenue stream they are supporting." Again, can you please post numbers or statements to support your claims. I really am having a hard time understanding this statement as revenues have increased in almost all segments not near end of life as well as their margins. Have you read any of their investor literature or the quarterly's? Like I said before it is statements like that I seem to be compelled to respond to- mostly because they are posting an inaccurate picture in order to justify a position - feel free to respond. Thanks and Happy Holidays. :-)</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1354636462741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 10:54:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354636786667-18</Id><Title>BMO reiterates Market Perform on NVDA, PT $13</Title><Msg>analyst call this morning</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354636786667</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 10:59:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354636813415-19</Id><Title>Down in a up mkt Up in a down mkt</Title><Msg>What gives??</Msg><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1354636813415</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:00:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354636875100-20</Id><Title>I'm Sure All You Traders Have seen the Large 100K Bids</Title><Msg>Now what could that mean? Nvidia is buying back shares! JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354636875100</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:01:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354637069075-21</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Sure All You Traders Have seen the Large 100K Bids</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354636875100</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:01:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt NVDA is going to buyback shares without a CFO. As you may know, NVDA has not had a CFO for some time. They have an interim CFO and I doubt share buyback function will be handled by an interim CFO.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354637069075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:04:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354637112679-22</Id><Topic><Title>more sellers</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354632572389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:49:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BRagain73: thank you for posting here good stuff! it saveds me a lot of time having to comment on others. Bottom line is we have a self professed 'swing trader' who - in all the posts I have read- bascailly is saying well whole ship sector kind weak now and, uh, I dunno, it seems like there are like some, uh, challenges or something for NVDA. Look folks if you cannot be specific then youa re just a grunt hoping to scalp a few nickels up and down. Hey if that works for you go for it. But if there is no real meat to offer then stop with the contstant silly attempt to 'cheerlead' down the price give you tiny short shares. It just sounds follish and sad with no content. Btw posting that one is long or short is kind of silly too without any info about size. Not tht anyone belives shorts lies here anyhow LOL</Msg><Username>nvda_4_ever</Username><Timestamp>1354637112679</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:05:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354637188298-23</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Sure All You Traders Have seen the Large 100K Bids</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354636875100</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:01:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL - She is doing a whale of a job and Jensen said she has passed her tryout. Besides before her promotion she was the Treasurer is the person that directs the handling of the cash.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354637188298</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:06:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354637532357-24</Id><Topic><Title>more sellers</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354632572389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:49:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. PC market is declining Yes, I agree but mostly for consumer based segment. The PC market will shrink but the highend gaming market is stable and growing some both of which are high margin, and the mainstay of NVIDIA's GPU sales. 2. NVDA is being designed out by integrated solutions from INTC and AMD. This is not true and in fact it is quite the contrary. INTC and AMD both have solutions but market segments where they have a foothold (one which is declining) is a different than the market segment NVIDIA reaches. NVIDIA is poised to take the remainder of the high end market from AMD as AMD becomes further burdened, by cash flow issues, brain drain, and poor product recognition - NVIDIA is way better branded and much more developer-centeric. They have outperformed AMD despite AMD having comparable, possibly better, and new GPU technology - kepler will change that. 3. NVDA has become the King of FUD in mobile market. They over-promise and under-deliver. Not sure how growing revenues by almost 50% yoy is under performing. If you are solely commenting on the perceived performance of their chips let me say this; despite having the perception that they have an inferior product, which I agree is outdated, they keep getting wins and growing revenues in this segment - again brand recognition and loyalty often outweigh other intangibles and to be honest by all standards their mobile products are still quite good despite needing an upgrade which we will see this year. They have a proven track record of innovating and setting the bar for performance and with the amount they are set to spend on R&amp;D I have no reason to believe that trend won't continue. Their are all but a few players left in the mobile space and their is plenty of opportunity for NVIDIA to gain more market share, improve their margins (which includes going to smaller footprint) and be on track for a higher profits.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1354637532357</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:12:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354638126555-25</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Sure All You Traders Have seen the Large 100K Bids</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354636875100</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:01:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope it was not a "Brownie, you're doing a heck of a job" moment. Don't know about her specifically but an internally promoted CFO is not a good sign, nor not having a CFO for almost 2 years, and it would have already happened if she was the first choice. Maybe a strong minded CFO would not allow such poor ROE in CPB division. aka TXN lopping OMAP. YTD SOX : +2% NAZ: +14% NVDA: -14%</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354638126555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:22:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354639037770-26</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Sure All You Traders Have seen the Large 100K Bids</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354636875100</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:01:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Company Gross margins up 5 percentage points since she took over. But what the heck...she is buying shares and I like it. Don't you?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354639037770</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:37:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354639411380-27</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Sure All You Traders Have seen the Large 100K Bids</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354636875100</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:01:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe - but we will only know for sure about share buyback when NVDA announces next qtrly results in Feb. Until then its all pure conjecture. NVDA did not buy any shares in 2012 so far and going by that I don't think they are buying any here.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354639411380</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:43:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354639871064-28</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Sure All You Traders Have seen the Large 100K Bids</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354636875100</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:01:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"NVDA did not buy any shares in 2012 so far and going by that I don't think they are buying any here." But remember they never had issued a dividend but they did!!! and during the cc Jensen said they would start buying back shares again. "We will be active from time to time"</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354639871064</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:51:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354644445109-29</Id><Topic><Title>New SeekingAlpha article has advice for chips stock investors</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354642037513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 12:27:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SeekingAlpha market articles have minimal impact on stock prices. Any positive opinion by a Alpha analyst of NVDA is meaningless.</Msg><Username>enteaupuzi</Username><Timestamp>1354644445109</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 13:07:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354646127817-30</Id><Title>Market action</Title><Msg>Good volume, up on a down day; good news coming or just a head fake?</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1354646127817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 13:35:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354646205739-31</Id><Title>Nvidia's Secret Weapon</Title><Msg>Karen Burns - CFO handling the stock buyback. Picture this: Karen: hey Jensen how did you like your dividend? Jensen: Yea it's nice $600K a year but heck that won't even buy me a new car. Karen: Well watch this - Hits buy on 100K shares and the stock pops 3 cents. Check your account now Jensen. Jensen: Wow that's nice another $600K. Do it again Karen LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354646205739</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 13:36:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354646487592-32</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's Secret Weapon</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354646205739</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 13:36:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.03 cents x 100,000 shares = $3,000... What are you talking about???</Msg><Username>bobdavis4</Username><Timestamp>1354646487592</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 13:41:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354646646378-33</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's Secret Weapon</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354646205739</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 13:36:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia's CEO has 20M shares mostly in his blind trust. $.03 X 20,000,000 = $600,000</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354646646378</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 13:44:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354647457443-34</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's Secret Weapon</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354646205739</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 13:36:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jensen: Hey Karen I just got off the phone with Larry Ellison and he said something about the Fiscal Cliff (What in the world is that) and then mentioned the words special dividend. He said it was a great way to avoid taxes. Hung up quick too. Can we do something like that? Karen: Sure Jensen How much do you want. My treasury is full and I can't stuff anymore money in it for heaven's sake. Jensen: Wink, Wink...this conversation never took place but I have my eye on this new $3M car so how about $1.50 a share.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354647457443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 13:57:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354648046446-35</Id><Topic><Title>New SeekingAlpha article has advice for chips stock investors</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354642037513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 12:27:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seeking alpha is a site for ultra biased opinions by stockholders...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1354648046446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 14:07:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354648877244-36</Id><Topic><Title>Market action</Title><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1354646127817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 13:35:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you are a strong sell?</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1354648877244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 14:21:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354649580213-37</Id><Topic><Title>Market action</Title><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1354646127817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 13:35:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh #$%$, I marked the wrong bullet!</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1354649580213</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 14:33:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354651369698-38</Id><Topic><Title>Market action</Title><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1354646127817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 13:35:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you metrosexual #$%$.?</Msg><Username>juapanial</Username><Timestamp>1354651369698</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 15:02:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354651939725-39</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's Secret Weapon</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354646205739</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 13:36:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jensen: Hey Karen I got a question. OK Karen: Sure what is it? Jensen: Do all those restricted shares we have been giving ourselves collect dividends. Karen: Yes Jensen: Super....That Ellison guy sure knows what's what. Call his CFO and let's get cracking.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354651939725</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 15:12:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354653322037-40</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA sellers @12.12</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354303907821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 14:31:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nailed it again! 12.12 has become big resistance low volume to overcome 12.12</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354653322037</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 15:35:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354653449696-41</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA's stock action doesn't surprise me...</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354653261216</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 15:34:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK - you are full of it, complete rubbish. Pray, how do you know about Institutional vs retail money flow on a day to day basis ?</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354653449696</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 15:37:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354653715161-42</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA's stock action doesn't surprise me...</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354653261216</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 15:34:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Susquehanna downgraded NVDA on 9/4/12 and not 12/4/12 - why don't you check your sources before posting.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354653715161</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 15:41:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354654568914-43</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA sellers @12.12</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354303907821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 14:31:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You gonna hold your small lot short overnight? LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354654568914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 15:56:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354655129026-44</Id><Title>Nice close - reversal?</Title><Msg>nice close near day high - hmm... is there a reversal in works? Someone please fire Maria B. on CNBC - I can't stand her anymore, please oh please fire her. This is supposed to be a financial news network! not a fiscal cliff drama network, she has made it into a soap opera.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354655129026</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 16:05:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354655268749-45</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA's stock action doesn't surprise me...</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354653261216</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 15:34:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And 'o.investor' posting like crazy during times like this is also not surprising. He's on ignore for me but I see his name posting 'ghosted' everywhere. He talks out of two sides of his mouth simultaneously and is completely spineless. He can't handle being wrong or admitting he loses a challenge . . he just disappears when it doesn't go his way. He appears to know what's happening but it's all misinformation and misdirection. Not worth the trouble of engaging him . . ignore him.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1354655268749</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 16:07:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354656999167-46</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA's stock action doesn't surprise me...</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354653261216</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 15:34:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you looked at the Chalkin Money Flow chart. Sellers have the upper hand.</Msg><Username>kunmgzi</Username><Timestamp>1354656999167</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 16:36:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354657506793-47</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA's stock action doesn't surprise me...</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354653261216</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 15:34:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That chart is all about what's behind you, not what's in front.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1354657506793</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 16:45:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354665836430-48</Id><Title>What's Wrong With Apple?</Title><Msg>I went to the yahoo message board and it's going ballistic about Communist Plots led by CNBC to tank the stock. Someone is trying to drive the world into an IRecession. LOL By the way, does anyone know what happened to endanger all these IFans? something about Android #$%$ but I can't understand what they are saying.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354665836430</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 19:03:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354673257602-49</Id><Topic><Title>JUST IN from iSuppl: global semiconductor market shares ranking, top 20</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354655682004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 16:14:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Best has read the rest. And what is clear is what an irrelevant rounding-error nvidia really is. In the Global Semiconductor Industry. Get out your magnifying glasses, boys, and take a look. 1 __ Intel ______ $47,543 Billion in 2012 Semiconductor Revenues 2 __ Samsung ___ $30,474 3 __ Qualcomm __ $12,976 4 __ Texas Inst __ $12,008 5 __ Toshiba ____ $10,996 9 __ Broadcom ___ $7,940 15 __ nvidia _____ $3,823 nvidia has just 1.3% of the Global Semiconductor Market. Ha ha ha ha! "We're the Global Leader in this and that don't u know." With a mini-scule 1.3% of the Global Market. What a bunch of pathetic carnival barkers.</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1354673257602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 21:07:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354675786171-50</Id><Title>So shines a good deed in a naughty world.</Title><Msg>Happy days are here again! Still in strong buy territory folks.</Msg><Username>nvda_4_ever</Username><Timestamp>1354675786171</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 21:49:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354676149751-51</Id><Topic><Title>JUST IN from iSuppl: global semiconductor market shares ranking, top 20</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354655682004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 16:14:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiot best too stupid to realize he needs to look, inter alia, at rankings, change in rankings, growth of market in total, growth of nvda relative to it and... wait for it... the realtive market cap, profit, etc ratios REALTIVE to their share. Gawd you are one dumb shortie! You have been warned bestie but here is my prediction for you and your sock puppets for years to come: PAIN Cover now or be assimilated! LOL</Msg><Username>best_the_turkey</Username><Timestamp>1354676149751</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 21:55:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354676240535-52</Id><Title>Grey finally came to life</Title><Msg>at brcm: quad A9s + everything under the sun integration, not just SoC + cheap radio. Analyst also is predicting brcm will show LTE integrated app processor at CES, with announcement of oem partners to boot. And of course, being brcm, that means full integration, not just SoC + cheap radio. And everything will come with just-slap-yours-together reference designs. Being totally integrated, I would not be surprised that amzn will go that way in the future - very cheap BOM cost + fast to market. nvda, where's Grey? Where's Wayne??</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1354676240535</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 21:57:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354680069386-53</Id><Title>OH MY ASIA ABSOLUTLEY POPPING! China up over 3%!</Title><Msg>Looks like shortie is going to be 'trapped' once again at the gap up. Ouchie! Nice to be long and strong through the attempted shakeouts. 4ever!</Msg><Username>nvda_4_ever</Username><Timestamp>1354680069386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 23:01:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354680515045-54</Id><Topic><Title>JUST IN from iSuppl: global semiconductor market shares ranking, top 20</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354655682004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 16:14:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"__ nvidia _____ $3,823" They are still highly profitable, so who cares? I really don't see your point. Does the company state publicly that they are the global leader in semi revenue? I certainly never heard that. Additionally, you'd be stupid to buy a company solely based on gross revenues as compared to it's competitors or the industry. Where it ranks in distribution or revenue has little to do with the companies performance or future growth potential. I agree the top four controlling a 100 million is huge but that is just more lunch for Nvidia to eat in the coming years - keep in mind revenues, profits, margins and market share is indeed growing, so again I don't see your point.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1354680515045</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 23:08:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354680590063-55</Id><Topic><Title>JUST IN from iSuppl: global semiconductor market shares ranking, top 20</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354655682004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 16:14:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is clear is IF nvidia Doubled in size, -- Yes, 100% growth in semiconductor revenues -- they Still would not make it to the #9th smallest. Up from #15th smallest today. And being the #9 smallest in a 5 company industry is no where to be investing your hard-earned cash. Face it -- She's nothing but a rounding-error, boys. 1.3% of the Global Market. Ha ha ha ha!</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1354680590063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 23:09:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>