<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349323408240-1</Id><Topic><Title>After hours volume</Title><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1349321608767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I should have told you, that was a small trade I made.</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1349323408240</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 00:03:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349327333083-2</Id><Title>Google Surrenders. Withdraws entire ITC complaint against Apple.</Title><Msg>"Apple does what Apple does and Nobody else is going to compete with them." -- Jen Hsun Huang, MobileBeat, March 4, 2011. Google/Motorola finally came to their senses, boys. And realized that Nobody is going to compete with Apple in a Court of Law. Nobody. And accordingly, just two (2) weeks into the estimated sixteen (16) Month legal battle, Google/Motorola WITHDREW THEIR ENTIRE ITC COMPLAINT against Apple. Which had accused Apple of infringing on seven non-standard-essential patents. It's a classic, Total and Absolute Surrender by Google/Motorola, boys. Following Apple's thermonuclear attack on Google. Well, except for the Navy battleship and signing ceremony and flags and this and that. Google's sudden surrender to Apple has left many, well, searching for words. Which can be found here: Google's Motorola Mobility withdraws its entire second ITC complaint against Apple Foss</Msg><Username>ibest.here</Username><Timestamp>1349327333083</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 01:08:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>35</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349355287289-3</Id><Title>Breaking news. Amazon orders 10,000 Tesla k10</Title><Msg>Key pts: no doubt gpgpu is becoming big business Nvidia net $25-28 mil from a single customer, amazon Source: vrzone</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349355287289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349356762517-4</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news. Amazon orders 10,000 Tesla k10</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349355287289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Outstanding find! Amazing the deals some people will talk about? This is setting up quite a bear trap!</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1349356762517</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349357424046-5</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news. Amazon orders 10,000 Tesla k10</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349355287289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Key pt mentioned also that despite Intel saying the otherwise, big company like amazon decided to use Nvidia GPU processors. Others like Samsung etc that needs to access fast memory will use tesla too! When a leader like amazon use, others follow suit.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349357424046</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:30:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349357430774-6</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news. Amazon orders 10,000 Tesla k10</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349355287289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Amazon's tough negotiating stance did drive the price down. While we expected that the boards would be discounted down from $4,999 from $2,499 to $2,999 range, truth was a little bit different. Amazon allegedly paid as low as $1,499 to $1,799 per card, bringing a value of the order between 15 and 18 million U.S. dollars. Tesla comes with an interesting subscription warranty program, which sets the customer back for additional $500 per board per year. That money guarantees immediate replacement should the board fail. Our sources implied that the company took that option in a heartbeat [Amazon had probably heard about nvidia's reputation for shoddy goods] , expecting to pay around $1000 to $1,500 per board (2-3y lifespan). All in all, with this one deal, Nvidia should net between 25 and 28 million U.S. dollars from a single customer. Naturally, the success of GK104 die in the HPC space and the limited supply from TSMC have another consequence - potential shortage in the consumer segment." So nvidia sold out cheap to Amazon -- like Really Dirt Cheap -- and threw the high margin consumer gamers under the bus, since the razor-thin Amazon order will cause "limited supply and potential shortage" for the high profit consumer segment. And this is somehow a good deal for nvda shareholders? Hummm? Looks like Desperation by Jen to get some hollow revenues NOW to show The Street.</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1349357430774</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:30:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349358007175-7</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news. Amazon orders 10,000 Tesla k10</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349355287289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? With the P&amp;L for the Tesla start to look like the P&amp;L for the Tegra? Black and white and RED all over.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1349358007175</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349358152889-8</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news. Amazon orders 10,000 Tesla k10</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349355287289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lol, knew u would say this. Everybody knows in business, bulk and big enterprises get better deals than retail. Plus once u get a major customer, u have leverage over others .</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349358152889</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:42:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349358649164-9</Id><Title>I adore Best, he spins a bash well and he clicks 35 self thumbs up in 30mins!</Title><Msg>With all his multiple IDs. Amazing how he does that! I witness his fast actions hours ago.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349358649164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:50:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349359767607-10</Id><Title>A tale of 2 semis, intel vs armh</Title><Msg>Intc continues to breakdown, Armh breaking out.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349359767607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:09:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349359770802-11</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news. Amazon orders 10,000 Tesla k10</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349355287289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With the subscription fee, the article that you both cite says the deal should still end up being $25-28M in revenue from Amazon on this order alone, even after accounting for the supposed discount priced -- the key being the subscription revenue that you mention critically but don't include in your revenue number. The more important thing, though, is that it sets two important an important precedent that could/should have two key consequences: 1) Amazon making large unit orders for Tesla products... as suggested in the article you both site, it seems likely that Amazon will also being purchasing K20s, and those should be closer to MSRP given supply constraints (aka, the Kepler GPUs are still being sold as quickly as they can possibly be produced) 2) Other companies building AWS competitors that want to compete in high performance computing will also consider Tesla... getting the "design win" in AWS HPC is tantamount to a massive reference design win for the performance computing market. Last quarter, the company reported 15% sequential top line growth in GPU, 35% growth in Consumer Products (Tegra + Icera), and a single digit decline in their Professional Solutions segment. Seems as though we can now expect to see Q3 showing sequential growth in Professional Solutions (as management suggested on the Q2 call). Remember, the midpoint of their raised guidance is $1.2B -- lots of ways getting there, but if they post another 15% Q/Q growth for GPU (thanks to increased supply) and 35% growth in Consumer products (an acceleration from Q2, based on a full quarter of providing Tegra for nexus 7 and the pre-launch ramp of the Surface RT, among others) -- that'd imply expectations of Professional Solutions to show 6% sequential growth. Or maybe the counter argument by "best" et al is that the GPU and/or Consumer Product businesses are actually going to show even stronger sequential growth (which seems to be at conflict with the bear case).</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1349359770802</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:09:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349359776254-12</Id><Topic><Title>I adore Best, he spins a bash well and he clicks 35 self thumbs up in 30mins!</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349358649164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris is a belated new member of the Best Fan Club. 'Cause he appears to be a little slower. But hey, Welcome anyway!</Msg><Username>friends_of_best</Username><Timestamp>1349359776254</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:09:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349360003392-13</Id><Topic><Title>I adore Best, he spins a bash well and he clicks 35 self thumbs up in 30mins!</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349358649164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it seems like a first step to filtering noise out of the NVDA message board is to realize that you just have no choice but to ignore each "best" account as they pop up.</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1349360003392</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:13:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349363258874-14</Id><Title>Texas Instruments OMAP 5 slips to 2013</Title><Msg>Could not make it in 2012 Despite the rumors started by Reuters who stated that Texas instrument is giving up on the mobile market and halts the OMAP 5 development, TI is continuing to fight in this market, at least for another year. TI has a quite long gap between OMAP 4 and OMAP 5 but it is expected to see the OMAP 5 early next year. The company thinks that slight speed bump of OMAP 4 parts that launched at 1.0GHz to 1.2GHz with very successful OMAP 4430 in Q1 2011 the got to 1.2 to 1.5GHz in Q4 2011 with OMAP 4460 can reach over 1.5GHz with OMAP 4470 that gets to launch with Archos tablets, Nook HD and Kindle Fire HD 8.9. Mass availability of OMAP 4470 is expected in Q4 2012, the quarter we live since this is the timeframe when we expect the increased production of tablets based on OMAP 4 especially the new Kindle and Nook flavors. Some people are even claiming that OMAP5 might be the first Cortex A15 chip to market, but somehow we think that Nvidia might beat them to it. We have a funny feeling that we might see both chips at CES and at the latest in early February 2013 at Barcelona based Mobile World Congress. Despite the small delay TI and OMAP 5 still coming to market and we would be very surprised if we don’t see at least some major design wins. Texas Instruments is doing fine with design wins of the Barnes &amp; Noble and for two consecutive years with Amazon Kindle tablets too, and we see that this partnership is here to stay, unless challenged by some offer from the competition that Amazon or Barnes &amp; Noble could not resist. It is quite certain that we will see at least a few OMAP 5 design wins in 2013, but we also reportedly heard that Texas Instruments will be late to market with its OMAP 4 and OMAP 5 based Windows 8 tablets and notebooks, mainly due to driver related issues. There is no doubt that Qualcomm and Nvidia will fight for the crown in ARM market but let’s also don’t forget that two big ones Samsung and Apple make their own chip leaving a very tight space for fearsome competition. It remains to be seen if Texas Instruments continues to develop high performance mobile chips after OMAP 5 and has good parts for a competition with many quad and octa cores in 2013 and beyond.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349363258874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:07:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349364459829-15</Id><Topic><Title>Texas Instruments OMAP 5 slips to 2013</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349363258874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:07:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think TXN has fallen on the list of competitors for Nvidia, and the top 3 in the SoC space (outside of Apple and Samsung) are Qualcomm, Mediatek, and Intel. If Nvidia fails to gain/maintain significant share (I think Jen-Hsun Huang has state on CCs that they need it to get to $1B+ a year to be sustainable) then I think they can have a successful business licensing their GPU IP to the other SoC makers... this could even re-open the doors at Samsung and Apple. Intel is paying $1.5B Nvidia over six years based on their 2011 settlement ($900M in 4 annual payments still owed). A few licensing deals near that scale could add up very quickly. This of course is a back-up plan. Plan A is leveraging their strength in graphics to become a dominant SoC provider to all non-Samsung/non-Apple devices, from smartphones and tablets (Tegra) through notebooks/pcs (Denver) and up through supercomputers (Boulder).</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1349364459829</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:27:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349365023030-16</Id><Topic><Title>I adore Best, he spins a bash well and he clicks 35 self thumbs up in 30mins!</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349358649164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When will we see best on YouTube!?</Msg><Username>lifesuckswhenstocksaredown</Username><Timestamp>1349365023030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:37:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349365802861-17</Id><Topic><Title>Texas Instruments OMAP 5 slips to 2013</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349363258874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:07:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If Nvidia fails to gain/maintain significant share " On Tegra, NVidia is investing heavily in Windows. 70% of Android tablets Phones next year with integrated LTE "I think they can have a successful business licensing their GPU IP to the other SoC makers... " Only INtel for a five years... "Plan A is leveraging their strength in graphics to become a dominant SoC provider" 64-bit Project Denver will be more important to NVidia's growth than anything they are doing now... Tegra Stark in 2 yrs...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349365802861</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349366359884-18</Id><Title>The nvda BOD, "yes men" are not effective fiduciaries IMO</Title><Msg>for shareholders that is... Someone needs to put some pressure on the CEO to perform better. Right now he is "King".</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349366359884</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:59:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349366668675-19</Id><Title>what does Brooke Seawell do but sell shares?</Title><Msg>how did he get shares @ $3.5...Come on Brooke! what about the shareholders that buy in at market? why are you on the BOD? What is your contribution?</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349366668675</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:04:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349366780890-20</Id><Topic><Title>Texas Instruments OMAP 5 slips to 2013</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349363258874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:07:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel for 6 years, actually. If you assume a hypothetical scenario where they are focusing on licensing their graphics IP rather than designing and selling SoCs, they could actively license their IP or sell GPUs as components for other SoC providers. Kepler (which hasn't yet come to market in Tegra SoCs) should be very compelling to companies that currently are left to ARM or Imagination Technologies' GPUs.</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1349366780890</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349367364884-21</Id><Title>shareholders' lack passion, just want a buck or two!</Title><Msg>that is what complacent management counts on...NVDA is not a kingdom, it's a publicly owned company...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349367364884</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:16:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349367672434-22</Id><Title>Are the board idiots still talking about a Head N Shoulder for NVDA?</Title><Msg>LOL Board idiots include pseudo idiots SmallCock, Chrisizaass etc etc</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1349367672434</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349367757425-23</Id><Title>Finnaly, our baby fires</Title><Msg>go go go Baby is on fire</Msg><Username>jasonhustock</Username><Timestamp>1349367757425</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:22:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349368275132-24</Id><Topic><Title>shareholders' lack passion, just want a buck or two!</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349367364884</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:16:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, traders want a buck or two. Investors see waaaay more potential than that. Look, you're here to trade. The channel is defined, so pick your opportunities well. It's very clear there are lots of 3% gains on both sides. Long term investors are not phased by recent action or the muck spread around by detractors. Traders are gamblers and your challenge is to time your moves with the big boys. Quit complaining.</Msg><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1349368275132</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349368320662-25</Id><Topic><Title>Texas Instruments OMAP 5 slips to 2013</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349363258874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:07:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If you assume a hypothetical scenario where they are focusing on licensing their graphics IP rather than designing and selling SoCs, they could actively license their IP or sell GPUs as components for other SoC providers. " Who makes more $$... ARMH that uses a licensing model... or NVidia who doesn't ?? Licensing NVidia's IP would be giving competitiors NVidia's advantage on the cheap...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349368320662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:32:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349368436727-26</Id><Topic><Title>I adore Best, he spins a bash well and he clicks 35 self thumbs up in 30mins!</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349358649164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well they are start out slow, and then end up braindead. This guy appears to believe this is a 20 dollar stock, after he's been here as long as the rest of the pumpers he'll soon realize it is a 30 and 50 dollar stock and think Best Buy top 10's and Amazon sell outs mean nvda is destined for greatness. lol.</Msg><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1349368436727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349368488159-27</Id><Topic><Title>shareholders' lack passion, just want a buck or two!</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349367364884</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:16:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not complaining, just exercising my rights as a shareholder. Are you Brooke Seawell?</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349368488159</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:34:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349368538821-28</Id><Topic><Title>I adore Best, he spins a bash well and he clicks 35 self thumbs up in 30mins!</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349358649164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What price was AMD at when you created your yahoo screen name..??</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1349368538821</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:35:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349369651742-29</Id><Title>company buyback could take stock to 20 easy!</Title><Msg>what are they waiting for? are they selling calls? what's going on here? what's the issue against unlocking some value in this company?</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349369651742</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:54:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349370253279-30</Id><Title>Jen Hsun's lack of shares owned makes him vulnerable to being forced out</Title><Msg>unless he keeps his BOD intact!!!!! No more stock options should be given at shareholders' expense.</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349370253279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:04:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349370258350-31</Id><Topic><Title>Google Surrenders. Withdraws entire ITC complaint against Apple.</Title><Username>ibest.here</Username><Timestamp>1349327333083</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 01:08:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>iDiot, Google intends to checkmate Apple in 2013 with such a move! ================== The complaint can be re-submitted. Florian Mueller, who was first to report the withdrawal on his blog, said he believed that Google withdrew the complaint to prevent it from being consolidated with an earlier case, thus slowing that case down. In that case, an ITC judge had said in a preliminary ruling that Apple infringed on a patent for eliminating noise and other interference during voice and data transmissions. A final decision is due next April. ==================</Msg><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1349370258350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:04:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349370811094-32</Id><Topic><Title>Texas Instruments OMAP 5 slips to 2013</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349363258874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:07:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I argued this as a back-up plan, in a "bear-case" where their SoCs aren't able to grab/maintain enough share and provide sustainable margins. What do you think they should do in that case? Or do you assume it's impossible?</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1349370811094</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349371627076-33</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news. Amazon orders 10,000 Tesla k10</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349355287289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Given this latest news I am upgrading to overweight with a price target of $40.50 By January.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1349371627076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:27:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349372304468-34</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news. Amazon orders 10,000 Tesla k10</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1349355287289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The gross profit margin for NVIDIA CORP is rather high; currently it is at 51.80%. It has increased from the same quarter the previous year. Regardless of the strong results of the gross profit margin, the net profit margin of 11.40% trails the industry average. NVDA's revenue growth trails the industry average of 13.9%. Since the same quarter one year prior, revenues slightly increased by 2.7%. This growth in revenue does not appear to have trickled down to the company's bottom line, displayed by a decline in earnings per share.</Msg><Username>lobseerque</Username><Timestamp>1349372304468</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:38:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349373094206-35</Id><Topic><Title>Jen Hsun's lack of shares owned makes him vulnerable to being forced out</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349370253279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:04:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>enough of the boy scout club meetings....unlock value and earn your pay...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349373094206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:51:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349373353154-36</Id><Topic><Title>Jen Hsun's lack of shares owned makes him vulnerable to being forced out</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349370253279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:04:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stop the freebies....no zero cost options. these people who get zero's just turn around and sell them. People they're free they don't care they;'ll get more next time.</Msg><Username>anitoirnet</Username><Timestamp>1349373353154</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349373604010-37</Id><Title>shareholders do not need positives from analysts, value already locked in</Title><Msg>we need responsible management to unlock the value and use it to become the company it was meant to be...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349373604010</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:00:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349375490035-38</Id><Topic><Title>Texas Instruments OMAP 5 slips to 2013</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349363258874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:07:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I argued this as a back-up plan, in a "bear-case" where their SoCs aren't able to grab/maintain enough share and provide sustainable margins. What do you think they should do in that case? Or do you assume it's impossible?" It's not even in NVidia's business model... The INtel royalty is a settlement from a breach of contract by INtel...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349375490035</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:31:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349376508593-39</Id><Title>who the heck cares about TI, the problem is NVDA CEO</Title><Msg>he is the one that has power to unlock value to shareholders...why he has not is beyond me. he needs to be held accountable. We know the "yes men" BOD are not going to do it. It must ultimately come from institutional investors....but they are to busy collecting their fees from their clients....</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349376508593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:48:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349376724030-40</Id><Title>that ceo stock sale @22 15 months ago must be recognized!</Title><Msg>unlock it for the rest of us.....</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349376724030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:52:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349377707077-41</Id><Topic><Title>who the heck cares about TI, the problem is NVDA CEO</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349376508593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:48:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe the BOD should look into hiring someone from Apple.....CFO, etc?</Msg><Username>foonegier</Username><Timestamp>1349377707077</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349377894772-42</Id><Topic><Title>who the heck cares about TI, the problem is NVDA CEO</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349376508593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:48:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not a chance with this board.... our shares have been used as their atm machine...would you want to make a change if in their place...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349377894772</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349378073977-43</Id><Topic><Title>what does Brooke Seawell do but sell shares?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349366668675</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:04:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got them $3 shares for his Board directorship . Sells and sells and sells, driving down stock price. Sells indicate no confidence in company future. IMHO. Should be voted off the Board or somehow place his free shares in a lock box for a few years.</Msg><Username>foonegier</Username><Timestamp>1349378073977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:14:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349378423810-44</Id><Topic><Title>Texas Instruments OMAP 5 slips to 2013</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349363258874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:07:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I remember correctly TI is just not coming up new designs. They are just finishing the stuff that's been mostly developed already, if not finished, and will not really stop making them for another few years. It's not an immediate exit but they are in the process of yielding to Nvidia and Qualcom.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1349378423810</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349378648667-45</Id><Topic><Title>what does Brooke Seawell do but sell shares?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349366668675</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:04:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they will keep doing this crap until someone call them out on it....institutional shareholders do not care, they are busy counting their fees from AUM...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349378648667</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:24:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349380373976-46</Id><Topic><Title>Technical Chart Shows Upside on NVIDIA Corporation</Title><Username>marlacatalan40</Username><Timestamp>1349379375562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is interesting, all of the sudden, is there a catalyst or new information out?</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1349380373976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:52:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349380889032-47</Id><Title>who cares about what barrons says, value already locked up</Title><Msg>it's up to the ceo and board to make it happen for shareholders..</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349380889032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:01:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349381338228-48</Id><Title>Is this the Problem?</Title><Msg>Jen-Hsun Huang Co-founder, President and Chief Executive Officer Jen-Hsun Huang co-founded NVIDIA Corporation in April 1993 and has served as President, Chief Executive Officer, and a member of the Board of Directors since its inception. Under his leadership, NVIDIA has become the world leader in programmable graphics processing technologies and one of the semiconductor industry’s largest fabless companies. Mr. Huang serves on the RAND Corporation’s Board of Trustees and is a member of the Committee of 100, an organization that addresses issues concerning the Chinese-American community and U.S.-China relations. In 2004, the Fabless Semiconductor Association honored Mr. Huang with the prestigious Dr. Morris Chang Exemplary Leadership Award, which recognizes a leader who has made exceptional contributions to driving the development, innovation, growth, and long-term opportunities of the fabless semiconductor industry. Additionally, Mr. Huang is a recipient of the Daniel J. Epstein Engineering Management Award from the University of Southern California and was named an Alumni Fellow by Oregon State University. Prior to founding NVIDIA, Mr. Huang held engineering, marketing, and general management positions at LSI Logic, and was a microprocessor designer at Advanced Micro Devices. Mr. Huang holds a #$%$.E.E. degree from Oregon State University and an M.S.E.E. degree from Stanford University. No business degree. Business experience? Running NVDA? Result=bad job, need a new CEO/COB!</Msg><Username>anitoirnet</Username><Timestamp>1349381338228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:08:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349388577673-49</Id><Topic><Title>Is this the Problem?</Title><Username>anitoirnet</Username><Timestamp>1349381338228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:08:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nothing personal Ibexx on the ceo... He's not worried much about me as an investor as well. If nvda is about growth, then put the cash to work and make it happen. a growth company sitting on 1/2 cash for yr after yr is light years in today's global marketplace. do you think IBM did that in the 60's? Mircrosoft in the early 90's? He needs to hire a CFO to boot. I want to see a reward for my investment. Time to get tough...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349388577673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 18:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349388741054-50</Id><Title>Big AH trade again today</Title><Msg>Today and Yesterday the after hours volume has been much larger than normal. It looks like two huge block trades, yesterdays was just over 1.6M shares and today's was just under 1.25M shares. Coupled with the price action today, there's some institutional buying going on?</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1349388741054</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 18:12:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349390517464-51</Id><Title>did obama have privey on the employ report for tomorrow?</Title><Msg>you heard it here first....</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349390517464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 18:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349393055643-52</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 32GB shows up in retailers inventory sheets, could ship October 24th</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1349392072625</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:07:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know Jen Hsun can execute the business plan, but 3B sitting around, not working at a 30% internal ROI vs 2% is giving up a .50/sh profit yearly profit. years today, is a long time in economic light years. He needs to be pressured to produce a better return... otherwise, pay a dividend or go private. This is about money, not personal at all.</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1349393055643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:24:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349395731932-53</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news: AT&amp;T announces the availability of ASUS vivoTab RT tablet with Tegra 3/LTE for the holiday season</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1349394206700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:43:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$500+ tablet... winRT is a non-event. Guess I will be moving right along over to that $300 toshiba 10".</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1349395731932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 20:08:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349398165955-54</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news: AT&amp;T announces the availability of ASUS vivoTab RT tablet with Tegra 3/LTE for the holiday season</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1349394206700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:43:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No price has been announced except in your bubble world of ignorance. Hopefully you will be moving right along over to a Leapfrog tablet that fits your style.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber22</Username><Timestamp>1349398165955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 20:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349399691746-55</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news: AT&amp;T announces the availability of ASUS vivoTab RT tablet with Tegra 3/LTE for the holiday season</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1349394206700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:43:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The toshiba 10" tab (Excite 10) is also powered by a Tegra 3.</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1349399691746</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 21:14:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349400577755-56</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news: AT&amp;T announces the availability of ASUS vivoTab RT tablet with Tegra 3/LTE for the holiday season</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1349394206700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:43:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what's this misleading, newly invented nomenclature all about, boys? Specificially, that "Tegra® 3 TE" jive. The speed reader -- or the not-so-closely-paying-attention reader -- might be bamboozled -- yes, bamboozled boys -- by the cunningly deceptive nvidia PR Department into Thinking that the Tegra® 3 now has an integrated on-board LTE radio. Like Qualcomm's ever-growing Family of Snapdragons with integrated on-board LTE radios. Except the Tegra ® 3 doesn't. Nope. The deceptively named Tegra® 3 TE has NO integrated LTE radio. Or ANY integrated radio at All, for that matter. Maybe the cunningly deceptive nvidia PR Department deliberately Schemed to come up with a name that would Convey the Impression that nvidia/icera have finally figured out how to put both a tegra AND the on-board LTE radio side-by-side on the same little piece of silicon. Hummm? When in Fact, those than read best clearly know that nvidia/icera is still Nowhere Close to having an integrated LTE radio. Like Qualcomm's ever-growing Family of Snapdragons with integrated on-board LTE radios. So what's next from the nvidia Misleading Nomenclature Department? "The NVIDIA next-generation quad-core Tegra® 3 x68."</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1349400577755</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 21:29:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349401342687-57</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news: AT&amp;T announces the availability of ASUS vivoTab RT tablet with Tegra 3/LTE for the holiday season</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1349394206700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:43:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? What you're saying is, that nvidia is just like a wet cat. Yes, a wet cat, boys. And that under all that hyped up hair is just another rat. Yes boys, a cunningly deceptive rat.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1349401342687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 21:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349402012423-58</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news: AT&amp;T announces the availability of ASUS vivoTab RT tablet with Tegra 3/LTE for the holiday season</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1349394206700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:43:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think an even better part of this story is VivoTab RT actually uses Icera i410 LTE chip inside. So this is not only the first Windows RT device for AT&amp;T, but also the first device with Nvidia LTE chip for AT&amp;T.</Msg><Username>antims_news</Username><Timestamp>1349402012423</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 21:53:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349402690081-59</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news: AT&amp;T announces the availability of ASUS vivoTab RT tablet with Tegra 3/LTE for the holiday season</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1349394206700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:43:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe nvidia could copy Qualcomm and have a special Tegra for the Chinese market. They could call it the "next-generation quad-core Tegra® 3 ETL" And since the Chinese read from right to left.....</Msg><Username>good_one_best</Username><Timestamp>1349402690081</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 22:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349403438909-60</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news: AT&amp;T announces the availability of ASUS vivoTab RT tablet with Tegra 3/LTE for the holiday season</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1349394206700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:43:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 1985-era Icera i410 LTE non-integrated discrete radio chip. Located like 14,378 electron miles from the processor chip. Great technology there, boys.</Msg><Username>good_one_best</Username><Timestamp>1349403438909</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 22:17:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349404629037-61</Id><Topic><Title>ArsTechnica reviews the newly released Trinity APUs - billed as the future of AMD</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1349403576483</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 22:19:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So when does nvidia release their version of a quad-core x86 processor? Like AMD’s Trinity quad-core x86. Hummm? Speak up now, boys.</Msg><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1349404629037</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 22:37:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349404699206-62</Id><Topic><Title>ArsTechnica reviews the newly released Trinity APUs - billed as the future of AMD</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1349403576514</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 22:19:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So when does nvidia release their version of a quad-core x86 processor? Like AMD’s Trinity quad-core x86. Hummm? Speak up now, boys.</Msg><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1349404699206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 22:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349405736226-63</Id><Topic><Title>ArsTechnica reviews the newly released Trinity APUs - billed as the future of AMD</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1349403576514</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 22:19:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seven (7) years, boys. Seven long years the nvidia Project Denver team labored away. Trying to make an x86 processor. Like AMD. But they couldn't do it. Nope. Not even one little stand-alone x86 chip. And so the original Project Denver was Abandoned. After seven (7) long years. Maybe we'll see the Project Denver R&amp;D Charge-Off some quarter soon?</Msg><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1349405736226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 22:55:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349406512312-64</Id><Topic><Title>ASUS vivoPad LTE for ATT will use "next generation Tegra 3 TE processor"</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1349405295968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 22:48:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Does anyone have a source to describe what the heck the Tegra 3 TE processor is? Best says: Pure Marketing Spin. Deceptive named by the nvidia PR Department to make folks Think that the Tegra® 3 TE now has an integrated on-board LTE radio. When of course, it does not. But hey, a bit of Pure Marketing Spin is a whole lot cheaper than engineering, right boys?</Msg><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1349406512312</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 23:08:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349407613865-65</Id><Title>NVDA Technicals</Title><Msg>Technical Indicators Name Value Action RSI(14) 51.668 NEUTRAL STOCH(9,6) 31.362 SELL STOCHRSI(14) 100.000 Overbought MACD(12,26) -0.176 SELL ADX(14) 15.387 NEUTRAL Williams %R -30.108 BUY Name Value Action CCI(14) -1.1197 NEUTRAL ATR(14) 0.3775 Less Volatility Highs/Lows(14) 0.0211 BUY Ultimate Oscillator 53.765 BUY ROC -1.590 SELL Bull/Bear Power(13) -0.0560 SELL BUY: 3 SELL: 4 NEUTRAL: 4 Indicators Summary: SELL</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1349407613865</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 23:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349409056937-66</Id><Topic><Title>ASUS vivoPad LTE for ATT will use "next generation Tegra 3 TE processor"</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1349405295968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 22:48:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Does anyone have a source to describe what the heck the Tegra 3 TE processor is?" Well, since the General Manager of the Tegra Division quit, and there's Absolutely Nothing New close to being launched, maybe the new interim Tegra GM decided to re-name the old legacy chips, and mail out "engineering samples" to the same folks that said no last time. "Oh no no no. That's not the Tegra 3 -- it's the new Tegra 3 TE, don't u know."</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1349409056937</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 23:50:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>