<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-15"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355583097684-1</Id><Title>BEST</Title><Msg>Does everyone here know that 'best' lost all his money and what little dignity he ever possessed in RMBS stock.. for years now, he harasses an anonmous message board to soothe his pain and anguish... this is all he has left... think about it another way... if RMBS was a person, what kind of attributes would it possess?? A non productive mooch that harasses .. spot on for BEST!</Msg><Username>michaelwallsen</Username><Timestamp>1355583097684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 09:51:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355589898000-2</Id><Title>Dividend received</Title><Msg>for anyone that's been checking... Dividend posted in my account today...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1355589898000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 11:44:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355593136702-3</Id><Title>Microsoft Surface On-Line Best Buy Rankings - The 12 days before XMAS</Title><Msg>Tablet Best Selling Rank - *Highest Rank Microsoft Surface Win8 RT tablet of the 3 models. Thursday 12/13 - #70 Friday 12/14 - #37 Sat 12/15 - #17 In Store Availability in my Metropolitan Area Thursday 12/13 - 1 store out of 20 Friday - 12/14 - 12 out of 20 Sat - 12/15 - 17 out of 20 Note: All Staple stores in my metropolitan area had inventory Thursday morning. But Staples does not rank best sellers. * $599 model with touch cover and 32GB HD. Note: I know the price seems high but people forget that Office Home and Student is bundled for free in all Win8 RT tablets. This costs $99 for one PC or $119 for 3 PC's.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1355593136702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:38:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355594809236-4</Id><Topic><Title>THANKS BEST! For forcing Jen to finally pay us a Dividend!</Title><Username>thanks.best</Username><Timestamp>1352438311323</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 00:18:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes boys, Jen reluctantly sent those dividends out on Friday, December 14th. Oh so reluctantly. THANKS SO MUCH, MISTER BEST !!!! Without you publicly shaming Jen -- right here on this very board -- into paying his First Ever Cash Dividend in 19 years, why, it clearly would have never happened. Never never never. Jen would still be senselessly hoarding the shareholder's cash -- without Best's efforts. Way to GET-R-DONE, Mister Best! You have accomplished a Great Thing, sir. Yes, a Very Great Thing indeed. One of the best things to ever happen to the hapless nvda shareholders. Let the Official History of nvdia show that it was Best that forced Jen to finally pay us all a dividend.</Msg><Username>in_best_we_trust</Username><Timestamp>1355594809236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:06:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355595810554-5</Id><Title>mobile supplier giant nvda in enviable position</Title><Msg>#1 in mobile goes down and take down its suppliers, and nvda stood tall. in fact, even if #2 goes down, nvda will still stand tall since nvda is not into #2 either. in fact, even if #3 tablet amzn goes down, nvda will still stand tall cause Jen 'does not want that kind of biz'. in fact, even if #4 tablet goog goes down, it will still only barely affect nvda, cause goog is in 'spreading the wealth'. maybe nvda is really a mobile supplier midget? roflol</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1355595810554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:23:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355597068945-6</Id><Topic><Title>Patrick Moorhead's tweet: "Considering ditching iPhone.."</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1355590693341</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 11:58:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't believe it took him this long to figure out what a closed system apple realy is.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1355597068945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:44:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355597233706-7</Id><Topic><Title>mobile supplier giant nvda in enviable position</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1355595810554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:23:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you would still have to look up to look them in the gonads.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1355597233706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:47:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355599764688-8</Id><Title>Crazy rumors on INTC &amp; NVDA as a Takeover Target</Title><Msg>posted on Seeking Alpha give a shy relieve for investors. This could be a alternative avenue in providing sound return in lieu of sitting duck for years and only 2.6% return going forward. JIMHO.</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1355599764688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:29:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355600008219-9</Id><Topic><Title>Crazy rumors on INTC &amp; NVDA as a Takeover Target</Title><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1355599764688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:29:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seekingalpha is a site with self-serving biased articles from investors...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1355600008219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:33:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355607028819-10</Id><Topic><Title>THANKS BEST! For forcing Jen to finally pay us a Dividend!</Title><Username>thanks.best</Username><Timestamp>1352438311323</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 00:18:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Such the loser... RMBS cry baby... life wasting fool..</Msg><Username>michaelwallsen</Username><Timestamp>1355607028819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 16:30:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355615109296-11</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface On-Line Best Buy Rankings - The 12 days before XMAS</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1355593136702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:38:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft couldn't sell the #$%$ on its web site and its stores, so they are dumping it into retail stores. RT is creating a great deal of confusion in the marketplace, and its a SLOW DOG. Very likely Microsoft will dump it next year after getting rid of the excess inventory.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1355615109296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 18:45:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355616720866-12</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend received</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1355589898000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 11:44:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why yes, nice tidy holiday bonus did hit the accounts :)</Msg><Username>schmenkle321</Username><Timestamp>1355616720866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:12:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355621011265-13</Id><Topic><Title>Try this again - NVIDIA DARPA Contract</Title><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1355422898865</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 13:21:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DARPA is tops for advanced R@D in the US Govt. Congratulations to the research staff</Msg><Username>vanmusicblues</Username><Timestamp>1355621011265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:23:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355627162423-14</Id><Title>A Conumbrun - Apple - To Short or Not to Short?</Title><Msg>1) All the tech press praise Apple. Oh the IPad Mini at $329 Gotta have....and at the same time poo paw the Nexus 7. Yet Google stock is up. Nexus 7 sales pass a million a month and Apple's stock is cratering. Nvidia stock price is also up. 2) Absolutely no one in the tech press likes the Microsoft Surface yet retailers clamor for it and production is increased. Apple IPAD4 sales falter but it's not Android and Win8 RT fault according to the tech press. It's the Ipad Mini....LOL 3) Iphone 5 is launched in China with no clammering crowds. What is this? Walmart and Best Buy cuts the price on Iphone 5 to $127 to spur sales. What is this? 4) Gene Munster has been seen hanging around Best Buy and Staples counting Surface sales. ummmm.....What is this? 5) Several Semiconductor companies take out Full Page ads in the Wall Street Journal to state they are not in the IPhone or IPad. Gosh things change on a dime. LOL 6) but wait we have Apple ITV rumors coming through. Yes 70% of all consumers say they are interested in a 40 inch TV made by Apple and will retail for $3000.00. I guess I will have to throw out my perfectly good $500 LG 40 incher to keep up with the Jones. LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1355627162423</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 22:06:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355632303130-15</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA expects to announce Grey and Wayne at CES 2012, vendors will announce products at MWC in February</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1355629510886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 22:45:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I recommend everyone who is interested in Nvidia (Short or Long) listen and view Chris Evenden's presentation at the Raymond James Conference. A lot of data...love the tablet projections and the China Smartphone penetration sensitivity by price.Keep in mind when viewing and listening to the presentation that in 2011 Nvidia sold 20M Tegra processors and in 2012 Nvidia sold 30M Tegras. Available on the Nvidia website.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1355632303130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 23:31:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>