<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348459471667-1</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Asks Judge: More Damages, Triple the Total, Ban Samsung Devices, please.</Title><Username>ibest.here</Username><Timestamp>1348458913248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 23:55:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Jeepers Best, Apple will likely generate more iRevenue from that fine lady Judge Lucy Koh, than little nvidia's entire 2011 revenue of $3.997 billion. "Take bad boy Samsung to Court -- Grow a nvidia." .</Msg><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1348459471667</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 00:04:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348460658295-2</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Asks Judge: More Damages, Triple the Total, Ban Samsung Devices, please.</Title><Username>ibest.here</Username><Timestamp>1348458913248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 23:55:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. So Best? This new business of Apple's has really really good margins, right? Let's assume that Apple is meritorious, and receives $4,755,000,000.00 from Samsung . $4,755,000,000.00 __ Gross amount of award ($200,000,000.00) __ Estimated cost-of-goods-won -- lawyering, filing fees etc. $4,555,000,000.00 __ Net Award . That's like what? 95.8% Net Margin. Apple has a fine new iBusiness there -- Suing Patent Infringers. .</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1348460658295</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 00:24:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348461863374-3</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Asks Judge: More Damages, Triple the Total, Ban Samsung Devices, please.</Title><Username>ibest.here</Username><Timestamp>1348458913248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 23:55:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. So Master? Apple's cash-on-cash return will be really really really good, right? ($200,000,000.00) __ Cash in (Estimated cost of lawyering, filing fees etc.) $4,755,000,000.00 __ Cash out (Estimated final award) 2,377.5% __ Cash-on-Cash iReturn This is a fine new business for Apple, right Master? Maybe Apple should think about suing more patent infringers in the future. .</Msg><Username>best.clone185</Username><Timestamp>1348461863374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 00:44:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348493144982-4</Id><Topic><Title>per WSJ, Apple sold 5 million new Iphone in the first weekend, still undercut analysts estimates</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348492329423</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC had barn-burning Q2 &amp; Q3 in prep for the iPhone 5 launch (benefiting QCOM, CRCM &amp; CRUS), and forecasted slowing Q4 due to inventory correction. Looks like they are right on. No need to 'write big checks'.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1348493144982</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:25:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348493760498-5</Id><Title>alpha touts AMD, come on! pathetic journaism</Title><Msg>every day is a new surprise....</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348493760498</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:36:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348493912307-6</Id><Topic><Title>Apple A6 TRASHES the Tegra 3 says AnandTech</Title><Username>bestnfastest.wins</Username><Timestamp>1348379603777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 01:53:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. My my my. nvidia very best mobile chip -- the Tegra 3 -- gets Absolutely Trashed by the Apple A6 processor. By a factor of three (3x), mind you. Looks like whosunw was right again. The nvidia Board needs to pull-the-plug on Jen's hopelessly-in-shambles Tegra program. .</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1348493912307</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348494828829-7</Id><Topic><Title>per WSJ, Apple sold 5 million new Iphone in the first weekend, still undercut analysts estimates</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348492329423</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Apple's custom designed A6 is "still less powerful than the Tegra 3 A9 quad-core", writes ibbey, desperately ignoring the Truth. Hey ibbey! Perhaps you missed the benchmarks? Conducted by AnandTech, the gold standard of benchmarking. Of the Apple self-designed A6 processor which powers the Genuine Apple iPhone 5 vs. the nvidia designed tegra 3 processor which powers the HTC One X cellphone. Google this: The iPhone 5 Performance Review by Anand Shimpi AnandTech on 9/21/2012 . Let's take a look at those benchmarks, shall we? . 1. GL Benchmark 2.5 Egypt Classic (offscreen 1080p) Frames per second -- Higher is Best 91 __ Apple A6 processor (Genuine Apple iPhone 5) 31 __ nvidia Tegra 3 chip (HTC One X) The Apple A6 is 293% faster than the nvidia Tegra 3. . 2. GL Benchmark 2.5 -- Egypt HD (offscreen 1080p) Frames per second -- Higher is Best 27 __ Apple A6 processor (Genuine Apple iPhone 5) 9 ___ nvidia Tegra 3 chip (HTC One X) The Apple A6 is 300% faster than the nvidia Tegra 3. . 3. GL Benchmark 2.5 -- Triangle Texture Test -- Vertex Lit MTriangles -- Higher is Best 86.2 __ Apple A6 processor (Genuine Apple iPhone 5) 27.4 __ nvidia Tegra 3 chip (HTC One X) The Apple A6 is 314% faster than the nvidia Tegra 3. . 4. BrowserMark -- Score in BrowserMarks Higher is Best 191,726 __ Apple A6 processor (Genuine Apple iPhone 5) 102,640 __ nvidia Tegra 3 chip (HTC One X) The Apple A6 is 186% faster than the nvidia Tegra 3. . 5. Mobile Soc GPU Comparison -- GFlops as shipped Higher is Best 25.5 __ Apple A6 GPU (Power VR SGX 543MP3) 12.0 __ nvidia Tegra 3 GPU The Apple A6 is 212% faster than the nvidia Tegra 3. . 6. GL Benchmark 2.5 -- Fill Test MTexles/s -- Higher is Best 1,650 __ Apple A6 processor (Genuine Apple iPhone 5) 407 ___ nvidia Tegra 3 chip (HTC One X) The Apple A6 is 405% faster than the nvidia Tegra 3. . My my my. The custom designed Apple A6 is clearly much much more iPowerful than the nvidia Tegra 3 A9 quad-core. Now say it ain't so. .</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1348494828829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348495465253-8</Id><Topic><Title>Apple A6 chip: 1.2 GHz dual-core A15 and PowerVR 6</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347699166224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 04:52:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Jen's "let's make mail-order design commodity ARM chips" folly is looking, well, pretty shambly today. Compared to the superior chips that Apple is iDesigning. .</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1348495465253</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:04:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348498459018-9</Id><Title>is this the apple chearleader locker room?</Title><Msg>ya baby!!!!!</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348498459018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:54:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348499492229-10</Id><Topic><Title>is this the apple chearleader locker room?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348498459018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:54:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lol, agree. Those fools can't differentiate between apple and Nvidia. Best part, dun cheerleaders aren't even in the game. They are cheering apple but dun even own a share. They are bashing Nvidia yet also din short a share! They are like the useless many out there. We call them the NATO. No Action, Talk Only! Lol</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348499492229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:11:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348500145151-11</Id><Topic><Title>is this the apple chearleader locker room?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348498459018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:54:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>laid off jr designers maybe....</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348500145151</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:22:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348500174054-12</Id><Title>Apple on pace to sell 200 million iPhones in 2013</Title><Msg>. Apple, the World's Most Valuable Company, is on pace to sell an incredible 200 Million (200,000,000) Genuine iPhones next year. Unfortunately, none of them (000,000,000) will contain any nvidia parts. "If you want the best mobile processors, ya gotta design 'em yourself", says Apple. Google the facts, boys: Apple on pace to sell 200 million iPhones in 2013 By Neil Hughes . Monday, September 24, 2012, 08:16 am Apple on pace to sell 200 million iPhones in 2013 By Neil Hughes The strength of the iPhone 5 could help Apple buck seasonal trends in the first quarter of calendar 2013, setting the company up to sell more than 200 million iPhones next year. Analyst Katy Huberty with Morgan Stanley sees Apple achieving that lofty sum after meeting with a supplier and distribution partner of Apple in Asia. She said both suppliers and carriers are bullish on demand for the iPhone 5. Huberty sees Apple selling 25 million iPhones in the September quarter, which concludes this week, while she expects record shattering sales of 50 million iPhones in the December quarter. Even those numbers may prove conservative, she said, as Apple could see "significant upside if component constraints improve." In particular, Huberty believes that China will be a meaningful catalyst for Apple, particularly if the iPhone 5 ships with carrier China Unicom in December. Her forecast calls for the iPhone 5 to debut on China Telecom in the first quarter of calendar 2013, while a partnership with China Mobile, the largest carrier in the world, could be reached in the second half of 2013. China Mobile is said to be stocking up on nano-SIM cards that would allow customers to run the iPhone 5 on its network. And the iPhone 5 is compatible with TD-SCDMA and TD-LTE, but Huberty said it could take TD-LTE licensing agreements and broader number portability in order for a formal distribution partnership to be reached between China Mobile and Apple. In her note to investors on Monday, Huberty also noted that the anticipated launch of Apple's so-called "iPad mini" is expected to lower average selling prices for the iPad lineup. She expects the new, smaller iPad to account for between 35 percent and 40 percent of total iPad shipments, reducing the average selling price of an iPad to $483 in the December quarter, and $468 in calendar 2013. "While shipments should improve once the iPad Mini launches, we lower our near-term iPad shipments to consider the impact of the upcoming launch and potential wallet share shift to iPhone," she wrote. Morgan Stanley has maintained its "overweight" rating for AAPL stock. Its price target is $720, though the company's "bull case" scenario calls for a price of $960. Huberty said Monday that if the initial success of the iPhone 5 carriers into 2013, she sees estimates moving toward Morgan Stanley's "bull case." .</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1348500174054</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348500891783-13</Id><Topic><Title>Apple on pace to sell 200 million iPhones in 2013</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1348500174054</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:22:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see your pom poms flailing in the wind..</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348500891783</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:34:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348501988816-14</Id><Title>Nvidia is starting to outperform in the semis space and heres why</Title><Msg>Recently, its holding well against the plunge of AMD, mrvl, klac etc. The fundamental reasons are 1. Surface win rt launching in Oct 2. Earnings in early Nov</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348501988816</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:53:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348504682216-15</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is starting to outperform in the semis space and heres why</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348501988816</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:53:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NVDA Outperforming? Yeah, sure, sure. RMBS up 20% today.</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1348504682216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:38:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348504936376-16</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Iphone 5's big weekend not big enough</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348504622222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:37:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whose expectations, Apple basher/relentless NVDA pumper? From shortselling analysts that got no guidance from Apple? New Iphone is selling more than 20% faster than the Iphone 4S, which is the fastest selling gadget ever. Now, if you were smart, you would take the 1 or 2 days that they will try to keep Apple down about $10-$15 to sell out all your NVDA and buy as many shares of AAPL as you can with the proceeds. Apple's probably good for a 50% increase in 1 year, with the Ipad Mini, next gen of Ipad, Iphone China Mobile and next gen of Iphone probably all coming in the next year. IMHO</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1348504936376</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:42:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348505444641-17</Id><Title>Btw, congratulate me, I ordered the 64GB black Iphone from Sprint with the Ballistic Hard Core Series Case</Title><Msg>and Simply Everything plan. The new Iphone in black is really beautiful, and I already love IOS 6 from using it with my Ipad. Should come in 3 weeks or less, and I CAN NOT WAIT!!!!!!! Will finally be able to get rid of the Blackberry I've had for 3 years and hate so much. BTW, NVDA will close red again today, as usual. You are welcome!</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1348505444641</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348505558412-18</Id><Topic><Title>Apple aggressively poaching Google maps developers to fix IOS 6 maps issues</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348494599491</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:49:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, in your opinion, hiring the best and brightest in the field is a bad thing? I guess that's why you're such a big NVDA fanboi.</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1348505558412</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:52:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348505642899-19</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is starting to outperform in the semis space and heres why</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348501988816</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:53:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. "Rambus Inc. (RMBS +20.59%) shares jumped on Monday after the technology company said it won a "positive result" in a court case involving patents with SK Hynix Inc. (KR:000660 -1.47%). The Sunnyvale, Calif., technology company said a judge in the Northern District of California found that Rambus patents in the case are "valid and infringed." Rambus is entitled to receive royalty payments for past infringement based on reasonable and non-discriminatory rates, the company said." .</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1348505642899</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348505793857-20</Id><Topic><Title>is this the apple chearleader locker room?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348498459018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:54:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure we can differentiate between the 2. Apple is BEST in class, the largest company in the world, growing at an extremely high clip and its stock usually closes green. NVDA is closer to worst in class than BEST, and usually closes red. Oh, and 1 more thing. Apple has the best CEO in the world in Tim Cook. NVDA has a carnival barker/snake oil salesman.. IMHO</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1348505793857</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:56:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348505969529-21</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is starting to outperform in the semis space and heres why</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348501988816</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:53:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now that Judge Whyte has issued an ironclad ruling that drives a stake through the heart of the spoliation red herring, ALL memory companies, and companies that use memory controllers will have to pay Rambus royalties on every single device they make, INCLUDING NVIDIA. Boo Yah! IMHO</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1348505969529</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:59:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506053649-22</Id><Topic><Title>is this the apple chearleader locker room?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348498459018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:54:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its all the same guy, mr-pennies-per-post-best and his many, many IDs, don't let them distract</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1348506053649</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:00:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506399032-23</Id><Topic><Title>is this the apple chearleader locker room?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348498459018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:54:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong, loser, I only post on this board with this ID. Admit that you picked a rotten stock in NVDA, sell out of it, and switch into AAPL!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1348506399032</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:06:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348508694886-24</Id><Topic><Title>is this the apple chearleader locker room?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348498459018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:54:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i agree, same guy, with a grudge, and he is not making any money either..</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348508694886</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:44:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348508905983-25</Id><Topic><Title>is this the apple chearleader locker room?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348498459018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:54:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am making a ton of money in Apple. if you are long NVDA, you must have been losing money for going on 6 years? Arrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrriba!</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1348508905983</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:48:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348510350737-26</Id><Title>TegraZone Android App Tops 5,000,000 Downloads</Title><Msg>NVidia Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) TegraZone Android App Tops 5,000,000 Downloads This stocks got legs. Lots of legs. Google it.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1348510350737</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:12:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348510881699-27</Id><Topic><Title>is this the apple chearleader locker room?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348498459018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:54:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where's your broken english Miguel? Forgot about your tell, mr pennies per post, LOL</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1348510881699</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:21:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348511190828-28</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia fans bashed a $320 Apple on the way to $700 and bragged about owning a $26 Nvidia on the way to $13</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1347997308829</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 15:41:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep bashing Apple, it worked so well form when Nvidia was $26 all the way down to $13 didn't it? lol</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1348511190828</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:26:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348511553859-29</Id><Title>More post bashing Apple then anything here? They know Nvidia is JUNK and $26 to $13 proves it.</Title><Msg>BIG Apple ENVY huh? Get over it. Apple is the richest company on earth. Nvidia is a $13 stock that USE to be $26 when Apple was $345. You BLEW the best investing opportunity of your generation on wasting your money on JUNK. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1348511553859</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348512309738-30</Id><Topic><Title>You blew $400 of UPSIDE in Apple pumpng junk</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1346108578468</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:02:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You blew off the best investing opportunity of your generation while wasting your time on a message board being silly about Fermi and Kepler and all that Amazon best seller nonsense." Now say it ain't so. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1348512309738</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:45:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348512540479-31</Id><Topic><Title>Apple was your ticket to out of this dump and you blew it.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1347897700593</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 12:01:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You blew the best investing opportunity of your generation. When Nvidia was $26 Apple was $345 Now Nvidia is $13 , Apple is over $680 and the RICHEST company on earth. " Is it TRUE or not? You can't dispute ONE word in that post. You know it's true. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1348512540479</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348513102311-32</Id><Topic><Title>TegraZone Android App Tops 5,000,000 Downloads</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1348510350737</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:12:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice!</Msg><Username>daysofshred30000000000</Username><Timestamp>1348513102311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348515683725-33</Id><Topic><Title>Btw, congratulate me, I ordered the 64GB black Iphone from Sprint with the Ballistic Hard Core Series Case</Title><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1348505444641</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont sell nvda . there still polishing it .</Msg><Username>walterwlaszkiewicz</Username><Timestamp>1348515683725</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:41:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348530817014-34</Id><Title>Apple's SUCCESS is driving some over the edge.</Title><Msg>What sane person bashes the stock that added $400 since last year and praises a stock that was CUT IN HALF while Apple soared? Look at all the Apple ENVY on this board, it's insane. Apple is the RICHEST company on the planet. When was the last time ANY stock added $400? Apple has been the best investing opportunity in a generation. And NO ONE can deny that fact. NO ONE. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1348530817014</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348530928433-35</Id><Title>Dell Servers The wins keep coming</Title><Msg>Have you ever hit a screw with a hammer because you didn’t have a screwdriver at hand? No? Me neither. Each job requires using the right tool for the best results. In high-performance computing or for “big data” and hosting applications, the main job is maximizing throughput. In this case, you need the right processor for the right job: an NVIDIA Tesla GPU to provide ultra-high throughput for parallel tasks, and a high-performance Sandy Bridge CPU for single-thread jobs. The new Dell PowerEdge C8000-series systems provide both, along with a host of other tools optimized for a range of accelerated computing needs. At launch, the servers support Tesla M2090s, the only available GPU option. Best of all, later they will support the forthcoming Tesla K20 GPUs based on Kepler, the world’s highest performance, most energy-efficient compute architecture. These new Dell systems are ideal for a new class of mainstream, high-volume enterprise customers who need the power and flexibility to handle the next generation of compute-intensive apps. Integrated Design Ideal for HPC, “big data” and Hosting Dell optimized the new high-density Dell PowerEdge C8000-series systems for performance and flexibility for all types of HPC, “big data” and hosting applications. Each 4U chassis houses up to 4 C8220X double-wide sleds with two Tesla GPUs and two CPUs in each node – that’s up to 80 GPUs in a single server rack. Another standout feature is the “shared infrastructure,” which integrates the latest Sandy Bridge CPUs, NVIDIA GPUs and storage in a single chassis. With this high level of integration, users will benefit from the highperformance density — an impressive 5.3 teraflops double-precision per 4U chassis in GPUs alone. The chassis design also enables flexibility. Customers can mix and match to tailor their configuration to their target workloads. The PowerEdge C8000 series will initially ship with Fermi-based Tesla M2090 GPUs. Future systems will offer the next-generation Tesla K20 GPUs – the same GPUs that will power supercomputers such as the world-leading Titan system at Oak Ridge National Labs, the Blue Waters system at the National Center for Supercomputing Applications at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, and the Stampede system at the Texas Advanced Computing Center. If you’re running compute-intensive apps in a mixed-workload environment, what GPU-CPU density and other features would you like to see in your next server?</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1348530928433</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348530965387-36</Id><Topic><Title>Paying over $16 for a $13 stock can leave you bitter and stalking a message board EVERY DAY trying to break even.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1348270714495</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 19:38:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you rad this board YOU KNOW IT'S TRUE. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1348530965387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:56:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348531094266-37</Id><Topic><Title>Today is the first time AAPL traded below $320 since January</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1307719332000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2011-06-10 11:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A watershed event! AAPL to test $300 for sure! Keep your powder dry to nibble some Apple around $280!" Some people CAN'T ADMIT THEY WERE WRONG? Not even after $400 UP later? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1348531094266</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:58:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348531226029-38</Id><Topic><Title>You blew $400 of UPSIDE in Apple pumpng junk</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1346108578468</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:02:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was on sale for less than $320 JUST LAST YEAR wasn't it? lol Did you get in?</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1348531226029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 20:00:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348534283363-39</Id><Topic><Title>Dell Servers The wins keep coming</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1348530928433</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:55:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>, Waste your computing budget on electricity, if you wish. But the best graphics co-processor per watt is the Intel Xeon Phi. Take a look, boys. 1,381 MFLOPS/Watt __ Intel Xeon Phi ("Knights Corner") Co-processor 1,266 MFLOPS/Watt __ nvidia Tesla M2090 Conclusion: The Intel Xeon Phi is 9.1% more energy efficient than the nvidia Tesla M2090 .</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1348534283363</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 20:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348536652177-40</Id><Topic><Title>Apple on pace to sell 200 million iPhones in 2013</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1348500174054</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:22:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. "Morgan Stanley has maintained its "Overweight" rating for AAPL stock. Its price target is $720, though the company's "bull case" scenario calls for a price of $960. Huberty said Monday that if the initial success of the iPhone 5 carriers into 2013, she sees estimates moving toward Morgan Stanley's "bull case." . $960 for AAPL says Morgan Stanley's bullish case. And AAPL is now at $690. So +$270 / nvidia at $13.66 = 19 nvda's to the upside That's nice upside for AAPL, right boys? 19 nvda's. .</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1348536652177</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:30:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348538448357-41</Id><Topic><Title>Dell Servers The wins keep coming</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1348530928433</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:55:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey best, but nothing beats your best. Take a look Best's intellect : 0/ watt Conclusion : Ultra stupid ! Lol</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348538448357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:00:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348540602086-42</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's SUCCESS is driving some over the edge.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1348530817014</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:53:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't let iPhone 5 SALES drive you insane. Apple is selling MILLIIONS of iPhones. Let it go. The RICHEST company on earth doesn't care about a message board rant from the holdouts who can't admit they were wrong to bash a $320 Apple last year. We all know it was SILLY. $400 of UPSIDE Silly. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1348540602086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:36:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348543283403-43</Id><Topic><Title>Btw, congratulate me, I ordered the 64GB black Iphone from Sprint with the Ballistic Hard Core Series Case</Title><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1348505444641</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. ¡ Congratulación Señior Miguel ! The screen, she is easy on the eye, si? Like coochie coochie girl. No need for las glasses. ¡ Arriba ! .</Msg><Username>senor.best</Username><Timestamp>1348543283403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:21:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348543382545-44</Id><Title>Apple's success is indeed driving some insane!</Title><Msg>It is driving Xc3155 insane and others. They kept posting here and not in apple's board. U know why? Cos they kept saying apple is good, yet din buy a share! Understandably its driving them insane. Let's all Nvidia board members give them some airtime to blow their imaginery victorious win. They are understandably pitiful.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348543382545</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:23:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348543569459-45</Id><Title>Do you see that post from "1 year 3 months ago" bashing a $320 Apple? It's STILL good for a laugh.</Title><Msg>Some folks NEVER learn anything. Same Nvidia fanatic STILL bashing Apple. The whole world knows he was WRONG about a $320 Apple but he STILL can't admit it. Apple ONLY ADDED $400 since just last year and tthe usual suspects are STILL bashing Apple. lol Bashng Apple for what? Because Apple didn't add $500 or $600 instead of $400? lol You act like adding $400 wasn't good enough? lol When was the last time ANY stock ADDED $400? No one noticed that while they were bashing Apple for adding $400 Nvidia dropped from $26 to $13, hmm? lol Do you think Apple shareholders care about NONSENSE on a message board from bitter Nvidia bag holders? Do you? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1348543569459</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:26:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348544034264-46</Id><Topic><Title>Do you see that post from "1 year 3 months ago" bashing a $320 Apple? It's STILL good for a laugh.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1348543569459</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:26:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. "Morgan Stanley has maintained its "Overweight" rating for AAPL stock. Its price target is $720, though the company's "bull case" scenario calls for a price of $960. Huberty said Monday that if the initial success of the iPhone 5 carriers into 2013, she sees estimates moving toward Morgan Stanley's "bull case." . $960 for AAPL says Morgan Stanley's bullish case. And AAPL is $690 now. So +$270 / nvidia at $13.66 = 19 nvda's to the upside That's nice upside for AAPL, si? 19 nvda's. ¡ Arriba ! .</Msg><Username>senor.best</Username><Timestamp>1348544034264</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:33:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>