<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343449113000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcomm Snapdragon S4 Pro (APQ8064) MDP benchmarks</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1343187865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 23:44:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- "On behalf of the Board of Directors, it's my duty to inform you, Jen-Hsun, that we've set a budget -- a maximum limit, as it were -- on your Tegra folly losses. Being Prudent Men, and being conscious of our Fiduciary Responsibilities, -- and the skyrocketing cost of our D&amp;O liability insurance here -- we have accordingly set the limit on your Tegra folly losses at Two Billion Dollars ($2,000,000,000.00). That's it Jen-Hsun. Lose more than that and we're pulling the plug. 'Cause losing anything more than Two Billion Dollars ($2,000,000,000.00) of nvidia shareholder's cash would appear to be, well, entirely imprudent on our part, don't u know. -</Msg><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1343449113000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 00:18:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343451461000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Behold! The Nexus 7 [Out of Stock] Tracker.</Title><Username>ct.bestula</Username><Timestamp>1342441101000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-16 08:18:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Four days have passed since the last sale. Let's count them, shall we? Tuesday Wednesday Thursday Friday Four (4) days, right boys? And zero sales of the Tegra-powered Nexus 7. On that Out-of-Stock Tracker. Goose egg. -</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1343451461000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 00:57:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343451930000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Everyone is Chopping Guidance here. Except...</Title><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1342750131000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-19 22:08:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- LONDON – "Morris Chang, chairman and CEO of leading foundry chipmaker Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. Ltd., has warned that a slowdown is coming to the chip market and has cut his forecast for the total semiconductor market's annual growth, according to reports. Chang, speaking during TSMC's second quarter earnings conference on Thursday (July 19), disclosed a cut in the growth forecast for the global semiconductor market in 2012 to between 1 and 2 percent, the reports said. This is lower than recent forecasts from Future Horizons Ltd. (4 percent) and from International Data Corp. (4.6 percent). Chang said the slowdown is set to start in the fourth quarter and last into the first quarter of 2013, and put it down to a renewed inventory correction and deterioration in the global economy, the reports said. "We are now seeing a dip in our revenue in the fourth quarter from the third quarter," the Taipei Times quoted Chang as saying. Chang also sees a strong rebound in the second quarter of 2013 after the inventory adjustment. TSMC posted strong revenue results and soaring profits for its 2Q12. The company expects to expand sales revenue by about 7 percent sequentially in 3Q12, which is roughly in line with TSMC's historical average for the third calendar quarter. Over the last ten years TSMC has averaged sequential third quarter revenue growth of 6.5 percent. Over the same period TSMC's fourth quarter revenue has, on average, dipped sequentially by 1.8 percent although it has grown by as much as 17.2 percent and contracted by as much as 30.6 percent. Chang also confirmed that TSMC is negotiating with lithography equipment maker ASML Holding NV about investing in the company, according to a Dow Jones Newswires report. The Taipei Times said that TSMC maintained its advice it would spend between $8 billion and $8.5 billion on capital expenditure in 2012." http://eetimes.com/electronics-news/4390786/Morris-Chang-cuts-forecast Ignore Morris Chang, the Chairman and CEO of Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. -- and nvidia's sole foundry vendor -- at your own financial peril, boys. -</Msg><Username>best_was_here</Username><Timestamp>1343451930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 01:05:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343452002000-4</Id><Title>The Oracle with a blind eye</Title><Msg>He is an extension of the Qualcomm QCOM marketing pumpers always not mentioning or down playing or barely mentioning their weaknesses or misses. What can one say about people who are "in bed" at the top. http://www.cnbc.com/id/48349225</Msg><Username>qmtai2</Username><Timestamp>1343452002000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 01:06:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343483803000-5</Id><Topic><Title>The Oracle with a blind eye</Title><Username>qmtai2</Username><Timestamp>1343452002000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 01:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- "Chip executives have embraced the most professional of the benchmark reviewers and ship them samples of their new products, often ahead of their release. In return, they get objective feedback. "We literally go into every review site in the world we can find, and our teams read the reviews, and they decide internally whether it was a good review for us or a good review for the competition," Jen-Hsun Huang, chief executive of chipmaker Nvidia told investors at a conference in May." You can bet that Jen and his boys didn't like this benchmark comparison review. http://www.engadget.com/2012/07/24/qualcomm-snapdragon-s4-pro-apq8064-benchmark/ "Whaaaaaaat???!" "Qualcomm has a chip 109% faster than our Tegra #3?" "It's true, sir. We are not the best." -</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1343483803000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 09:56:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343484806000-6</Id><Topic><Title>The Oracle with a blind eye</Title><Username>qmtai2</Username><Timestamp>1343452002000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 01:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Anand Shimpi is one of the most influential tech industry figures you've never heard of. "From his start as a teenager building PCs for students and faculty at a college in his hometown of Raleigh, North Carolina, he's become one of the semiconductor industry's most closely watched reviewers. His website, AnandTech.com, is all about product performance, plain and simple. Shimpi measures exactly how fast the latest Intel processor really is, how quickly that graphics chip will render the latest video game, how long that laptop battery will last. At age 30, Shimpi is courted by technology executives and followed by Wall Street analysts keen to hear his well- informed product views. He briefs Intel executives, dines with Asian PC executives and commands a loyal following of tech enthusiasts, with AnandTech.com drawing 12 million unique visitors per month. His workbench at his home in Raleigh is cluttered with high-end storage drives, laptops and recently released tablets, one of them playing a Harry Potter movie in an endless loop. A storage room is filled with hundreds of other products shipped to him over the years, and he says UPS drops more gear off almost every day. Poor marks in one of his so-called benchmark reviews, focusing strictly on performance data, can mean trouble for a new product." http://www.cnbc.com/id/48349225/ Interesting, right? It sure is. Jen spends Billions of nvidia shareholder's cash designing and hyping those Tegra attempts. Yet a 30 year old kid working from home gives Jen his Final Report Card. "Sorry. Qualcomm wins. It was 109% faster." An odd business model, right? -</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1343484806000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 10:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343484925000-7</Id><Topic><Title>The Oracle with a blind eye</Title><Username>qmtai2</Username><Timestamp>1343452002000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 01:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- For those that might have missed the buzz. http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_N/threadview?m=te&amp;bn=13029&amp;tid=689644&amp;mid=689644&amp;tof=8&amp;frt=2#689644 -</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1343484925000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 10:15:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343485884000-8</Id><Title>OnLive coming to Ouya: ouya uses Tegra 3 in its consoles</Title><Msg>http://www.psu.com/a016292/OnLive-is-coming-to-OUYA-can-Sony-strike-back-with-Gaikai</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1343485884000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 10:31:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343486874000-9</Id><Topic><Title>OnLive coming to Ouya: ouya uses Tegra 3 in its consoles</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1343485884000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 10:31:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Additional link http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/ouya/ouya-a-new-kind-of-video-game-console/posts</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1343486874000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 10:47:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343491308000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Extreme Caution!&gt;</Title><Username>sylviamary723</Username><Timestamp>1343480524000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 09:02:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't Believe This WOW</Msg><Username>mornarws396</Username><Timestamp>1343491308000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 12:01:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343491945000-11</Id><Title>Ubitus cloud gaming uses Geforce grid</Title><Msg>http://www.theverge.com/2012/5/16/3023502/ubitus-cloud-gaming-service-gtc-2012</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1343491945000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 12:12:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343492300000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Ubitus cloud gaming uses Geforce grid</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1343491945000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 12:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/china-telecom-and-ubitus-team-up-to-build-worlds-largest-cloud-gaming-kingdom-159410875.html</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1343492300000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 12:18:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343494181000-13</Id><Title>Korea logical place to start cloud gaming</Title><Msg>http://www.koreatimes.co.kr/www/news/biz/2012/07/123_115578.html</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1343494181000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 12:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343496384000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Ubitus cloud gaming uses Geforce grid</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1343491945000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 12:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ibexx, Can you quantify that in terms of possible revenue growth for this paticular deal only?</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1343496384000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 13:26:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343499656000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Ubitus cloud gaming uses Geforce grid</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1343491945000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 12:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is the best way for an investor to profit from cloud gaming?</Msg><Username>rickwest14710</Username><Timestamp>1343499656000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 14:20:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343499678000-16</Id><Title>Jen selling his 0 cost shares.</Title><Msg>Everytime Nvda makes a move to upside, it gets beaten down. My question is who is selling...is it jen getting out before any bad news or just taking his money out before Nvda sells off again and again. There is no upside to this stock, just flat to lower. Even with good news, earnings, etc it does nothing ..;. well sometimes it hemorrhages.</Msg><Username>ffrksuyou</Username><Timestamp>1343499678000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 14:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343501217000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Jen selling his 0 cost shares.</Title><Username>ffrksuyou</Username><Timestamp>1343499678000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 14:21:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The sky is falling chicken little!</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1343501217000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 14:46:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343501775000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Everyone is Chopping Guidance here. Except...</Title><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1342750131000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-19 22:08:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://community.nasdaq.com/News/2012-07/amd-warns-taiwan-semi-projects-upside-at-qualcomm-broadcom-apple-and-others.aspx?storyid=154847 But how is AMD related to Qualcomm ( QCOM )? The answer can be seen by taking a look at Taiwan Semiconductor, or TSMC ( TSM ). TSMC, the world's leading semiconductor foundry, has as its primary customers QCOM, Broadcom (BRCM), AMD, Nvidia (NVDA), and others. And due to TSMC's status as a public company in Taiwan, it reports sales results on a monthly basis. TSMC is currently experiencing a huge revenue ramp. It just reported June unconsolidated revenues of NT$42.87B (-1.7% M/M, modestly below a 10-year average of +2.5%) -- the second highest all-time, following only May's results. (And prior to May, April results were the highest all-time). TSMC's record results in two of the past three months are even more interesting because they did not just barely eclipse the previous high -- they crushed it. TSMC's previous all-time monthly revenue record was NT$37.37B, set in October of 2010. Thus the April, May, and June monthly revenues beat the previous high by anywhere from ~7.1% to ~16.7%. TSMC's quarterly unconsolidated revenue of NT$126.5B was in line with management guidance, and represented the highest quarterly revenue that TSMC has ever reported by a wide margin (beating Q3:2009 by nearly 15%). To put the uptick in further perspective, TSMC's implied Q/Q revenue growth of +21.3% has been eclipsed just once in the past nine years -- and that was the extraordinary +91.7% Q/Q result posted in Q2 of 2009, when the entire industry was coming out of the bottom following the 2008 meltdown. These beats are all the more noteworthy because of the very high absolute levels. TSMC is the world's largest semiconductor foundry. Its June revenues were nearly 5x that of its competitor, UMC. TSMC is building a massive amount of product, more so than at any other time in its history. What is driving TSMC's strength? Clearly not AMD. AMD is a mid-single digit customer of TSMC. Nor is it Texas Instruments (TXN); TXN is a significant TSMC customer, accounting for perhaps 2-3% of its revenues. TXN narrowed its Q2 guidance on its mid-quarter revenue update back on June 11, so it is not responsible for TSMC's strength. That leaves major TSMC customers such as QCOM, BRCM, and NVDA. Let's look at NVDA, which accounts for a mid-to-high single-digit percentage of TSMC's revenues. Back in mid-May, NVDA actually guided its next quarter's revenue higher -- its midpoint of $1.02B was at the time about 4% higher than Street expectations of $976.3M. But NVDA's bread and butter is still the PC market -- whose weakness is evidenced by negative data from MU, STX, and AMD -- and in absolute terms, NVDA's upside is only about $25 million. TSMC, on the other hand, reported May revenues that were roughly $234.2 million higher than March on a U.S. dollar basis. Other, smaller TSMC customers are unlikely the source of TSMC's strength, not only because of the smaller size individually, but in aggregate, most end markets are somewhat sluggish. That leaves BRCM and QCOM, each of which accounts for a high single-digit percentage of TSMC's revenues. BRCM has significant exposure to both AAPL (low teens %) and Samsung (roughly 10%), which are the likely source of the strength, given recent data. QCOM also has significant exposure to both: it has a mid-teens percentage exposure to Samsung, and a high single-digit (and growing) exposure to AAPL. Now I wonder If everyone is Chopping guidance except NVDA well just maybe they are the one's that are actually creating this revenue for TSMC we will find out shortly. and do not forget. http://semiaccurate.com/2012/04/20/qualcomm-moves-majority-of-production-to-global-foundries/</Msg><Username>Nine_feet_underground</Username><Timestamp>1343501775000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 14:56:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343514293000-19</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC: Sell Apple and buy Google and Microsoft</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1343513475000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 18:11:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple has turned into patent trolls... NOT a good sign...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1343514293000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 18:24:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343517227000-20</Id><Topic><Title>The Oracle with a blind eye</Title><Username>qmtai2</Username><Timestamp>1343452002000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 01:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- "We literally go into every review site in the world we can find, and our teams read the reviews, and they decide internally whether it was a good review for us or a good review for the competition," Jen-Hsun Huang, chief executive of chipmaker Nvidia told investors at a conference in May." http://www.engadget.com/2012/07/24/qualcomm-snapdragon-s4-pro-apq8064-benchmark/ Oh my! My my my. On this one Jen's boys and The Best Team can agree. That was NOT a good review for the Tegra #3. Starting with the title. "Qualcomm Snapdragon S4 Pro MDP benchmarks blow away the competition." -</Msg><Username>best_design.wins</Username><Timestamp>1343517227000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 19:13:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343521725000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Jen selling his 0 cost shares.</Title><Username>ffrksuyou</Username><Timestamp>1343499678000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 14:21:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think he would risk going to jail as selling this close to reporting earnings would implicate him in insider trading crime.</Msg><Username>ghadji</Username><Timestamp>1343521725000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:28:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343521935000-22</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC: Sell Apple and buy Google and Microsoft</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1343513475000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 18:11:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RMBS was like that and did well for a while, but look at them now,. sad. I hold no position in AAPL.</Msg><Username>ghadji</Username><Timestamp>1343521935000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:32:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343522378000-23</Id><Title>Apple to Acquire AuthenTec, next NVDA</Title><Msg>Apple needs biometric Security technologies for the smart phone, but Apple needs Graphics technologies for the smart phone much more. Therefore it's almost sure that Apple's next to acquire target is NVDA.</Msg><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343522378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343522771000-24</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC: Sell Apple and buy Google and Microsoft</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1343513475000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 18:11:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple is already playing catch-up to 7" tablets...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1343522771000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343522958000-25</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC: Sell Apple and buy Google and Microsoft</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1343513475000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 18:11:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it must suck to be best or amdsfool... http://finance.yahoo.com/echarts?s=NVDA+Interactive#symbol=nvda;range=my;compare=rmbs+amd;indicator=volume;charttype=area;crosshair=on;ohlcvalues=0;logscale=off;source=undefined;</Msg><Username>daysofshred30000000000</Username><Timestamp>1343522958000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:49:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343524509000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to Acquire AuthenTec, next NVDA</Title><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343522378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Therefore it's almost sure that Apple's next to acquire target is NVDA. " NOT !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1343524509000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 21:15:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343524883000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to Acquire AuthenTec, next NVDA</Title><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343522378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>excuse the newbie</Msg><Username>qmtai2</Username><Timestamp>1343524883000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 21:21:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343525691000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to Acquire AuthenTec, next NVDA</Title><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343522378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why NOT? Post Jobs Apple needs to acquire more tech companies and convert Apple into a sophisticated tech giant. That's the only way for Apple to continue to be expanded with growth. There will be not much new inventions for Apple after Jobs. Tim Cooker knows that. Companies like QCOM is too big for Apple to acquire, but companies like NVDA is just good for Apple. Apple also needs to buy or build fabs.</Msg><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343525691000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 21:34:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343526063000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to Acquire AuthenTec, next NVDA</Title><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343522378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then you should tell Apple what they're missing...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1343526063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 21:41:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343526433000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to Acquire AuthenTec, next NVDA</Title><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343522378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, I don't need to tell Tim Cook anything. He knows what needs to do, he is not Steve Jobs, so he has to be somebody specially in doing something good: to convert Apple into a sophisticated tech giant by acquiring good tech companies and integrated. That's it.</Msg><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343526433000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 21:47:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343526659000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to Acquire AuthenTec, next NVDA</Title><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343522378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK... we'll be having this same conversation for years...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1343526659000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 21:50:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343527228000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to Acquire AuthenTec, next NVDA</Title><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343522378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's coming, just in a few days... Tim Cook is good even though he is not as good as Steve Jobs. Tim is very efficient and productive, he will get it done quickly. You guys expecting Intel or MSFT to acquire NVDA, that will take many years, Paul O. or Steve B. is not kind of getting it done quickly man.</Msg><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343527228000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343527934000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to Acquire AuthenTec, next NVDA</Title><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343522378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's coming, just in a few days..." what time frame will you admit defeat ?? a month ? 6 months ? a year ?</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1343527934000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:12:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343528192000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to Acquire AuthenTec, next NVDA</Title><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343522378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a month. I even think it could happen before NVDA Earning day.</Msg><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343528192000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:16:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343528550000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to Acquire AuthenTec, next NVDA</Title><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343522378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, end of August then... Thank you for having the guts to give a date... sorry for the inconvenient truth...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1343528550000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:22:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343528681000-36</Id><Title>Another false lead??</Title><Msg>Why would they want to use T3 or T3+? Perhaps to fill a certain lower price point? Or is it because of DX11? http://www.phones-online.org/new-samsung-nvidia-tegra-chip-cell-phone.html</Msg><Username>qmtai2</Username><Timestamp>1343528681000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:24:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343528863000-37</Id><Topic><Title>Another false lead??</Title><Username>qmtai2</Username><Timestamp>1343528681000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:24:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope it's true...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1343528863000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343529020000-38</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to Acquire AuthenTec, next NVDA</Title><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343522378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NVDA is in the merchant semi biz - what's apple going to do with that part of the biz? NVDA is worth $10B because of the sum total of it's biz not because of it's ip. To another semi company like intel or brcm - they can use the revenue and the margins - for apple?? For &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt; $10B they can pay NVDA $$ to do a custom T4 with Power VR and have them produce it for apple. They can do other derivatives too T4+Power VR + LTE all for a lot6 less than $1B!</Msg><Username>qmtai2</Username><Timestamp>1343529020000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:30:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343533375000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to Acquire AuthenTec, next NVDA</Title><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343522378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 20:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Business as usual. AUTH has business with Samsung, AUTH will continue to do business with Samsung after AUTH become part of Apple.</Msg><Username>hus108</Username><Timestamp>1343533375000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>