<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352626059374-1</Id><Topic><Title>"Project Denver going great!" says Jen Hsun Huang</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1352521041877</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 23:17:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's curious that you think Project Denver processors are only for the server market. 64 bit ARM is needed in the very next generation of premium mobile products, and in the bulk of the market a generation later. If you look at the configuration of tablets and smartphones, they are currently being shipped with 1GB or 2GB of DRAM. That#$%$ the architectural limit. A 2GB DRAM configuration is the maximum addressable with 32 bit ARM, since the other 2GB of address space is assigned to non-DRAM devices. The obvious PAE-like extension to expand the addressable memory has been introduced, but it's not yet in use. The other obvious market evolution is the leap in display resolution, after being stalled for years. This is adding to the demand for larger directly addressable main memory (PAE doesn't help here) and powerful GPUs. Of course GPUs are second nature to nvidia, since they and ATI have split 90% of the market for the past decade. I don't think nvidia can be a profit-making leader without a 64 bit product. The follow-on question is "did they need to build their own". Like Apple' with A5X and Qualcomm with Krait, nvidia must have decided that they did. Up to a year ago I considered Krait a losing bet by Qualcomm. They invested tens of millions, and ended up with a product that wasn't quite as fast as a drop-in ARM designed core that could be licensed by anyone for under a buck. But it has become clear what it gave them, and now Apple: control. They can introduce products on their own schedule, switch fab lines as needed, and customize bus bandwidth to the product. That's such a huge product integration advantage that no one questioned Apple's recent decision to switch to their own processor core design.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1352626059374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 04:27:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352626905817-2</Id><Title>Options Trickery</Title><Msg>Obviously all the institutions who sold calls to the gamblers didn't actually want to give up their shares. The "lowered" guidance (still up Y/Y) was a great excuse. This company has grown Y/Y and executed like mad. What more does Wall Street want?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1352626905817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 04:41:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352635146519-3</Id><Topic><Title>"Project Denver going great!" says Jen Hsun Huang</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1352521041877</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 23:17:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>weak... surely, you can spin better than that....</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1352635146519</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 06:59:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352635571313-4</Id><Topic><Title>"Project Denver going great!" says Jen Hsun Huang</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1352521041877</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 23:17:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cj_observer, Dude, you are so far removed from the industry... but yet attempting to convince others to uninformed spin...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1352635571313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 07:06:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352645190724-5</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P 500 Stocks Biggest Weekly Changes in Target Price -- NVDA is the #3 Biggest Loser.</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1352582382016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 16:19:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Remember that fine question from the polite analyst from FBR Capital Markets &amp; Co? "Jen-Hsun, did you say how much was Fermi versus Kepler in the quarter just ended?" And the reply from the interim CFO was, "Well, we don't really disclose that." "Jen continues to play his little cat-and-mouse games with the analyst's questions. Basically not answering Any of them." So here's Best's idea to end Jen's stonewalling of the analysts. Since Jen clearly responds to Yahoo posts -- witness Best's demand for a dividend -- maybe the analysts should post their fine questions right here on our board, -- like maybe three or four days before the conference call -- giving Jen and his interim Plenty of time to find the answers to Wall Street's questions. And then on the day of the conference call each analyst asks their question again. And for each question NOT answered openly, honestly, truthfully, painstakingly fully and completely during the conference call, each analyst chops his price target by a buck. Follow-on questions not answered are maybe fifty cents each. Might get the current CEO of this publicly-owned company speaking publicly, right? Either that, or we're looking at a $6 buck stock. And since the analyst questions have been posted in advance right here on Yahoo, the listeners at home can follow along with their own scorecards of how the conference call is going to be received by Wall Street the next day. Kind of a group-participation conference call for the entire investor community. A Great Idea, right boys? It sure is.</Msg><Username>bests.idea</Username><Timestamp>1352645190724</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 09:46:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352646025696-6</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P 500 Stocks Biggest Weekly Changes in Target Price -- NVDA is the #3 Biggest Loser.</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1352582382016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 16:19:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SUKS 2 B A BAGHOLDER! PASS THE LOBSTER Barry.</Msg><Username>jiinxstank</Username><Timestamp>1352646025696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 10:00:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352649545961-7</Id><Title>nvda investors buy more then 40 millon shares last 2 days are not going sell at loss!!!</Title><Msg>will buy more to average down cost which should drive the price up above 13.00---who agree ???</Msg><Username>clintelkins</Username><Timestamp>1352649545961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 10:59:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352650465978-8</Id><Topic><Title>nvda investors buy more then 40 millon shares last 2 days are not going sell at loss!!!</Title><Username>clintelkins</Username><Timestamp>1352649545961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 10:59:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe those nvda investors that Sold 40 million shares in the last 2 days have more nvda to sell? Like "sold 30%" daysofshred.</Msg><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1352650465978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 11:14:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352650525130-9</Id><Topic><Title>"Project Denver going great!" says Jen Hsun Huang</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1352521041877</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 23:17:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Am I really out of touch? Let’s examine the market dynamics. There are only two markets out there, desktop and server. The demise of PC industry due to consumer preference of tablets over laptop/desktop will put additional pressure on Nvidia to become profitable in a shrinking consumer PC market. Further, according to IDC: “Worldwide server market revenues decline 4.8% in second quarter as market demand softens. On a year-over-year basis, volume systems experienced a 2.5% revenue decline. At the same time, demand for midrange and high-end systems experienced year-over-year revenue declines of 11.2% and 7.6% respectively in 2Q12. All three segments were impacted by difficult year-over-year compares combined with transitions in the technology refresh cycles.” The worldwide server market will continue to decline because companies are cutting down their costs by consolidating into the “cloud”. This trend has actually started back in 2000 when large companies started to rationalize their costs of maintaining large pools of in-house servers. During that time, networks have been also converged to provide server centric (flat network storage) environment called “server-farm”. Today, the same server-farm has now graduated into an Internet-WAN based “cloud server architecture” but the concept remains and has now been expanded to every enterprise, not just to large companies. The reason why 64-bit based ARM chip is attractive in the server arena is mainly due to its inherent low power consumption which is most suited for datacenter. But, now Intel has come up with their own version of low power x86 chip called Atom Gemini that’s specifically designed for server architecture. “HP chose to lead with Centerton server cartridges in its initial production server system, codenamed Gemini, due to the processor’s data-center-class features, such as 64-bit support, hardware virtualization (VTx), error correcting code (ECC) memory, lower power requirements, increased performance and broad software ecosystem. These features, coupled with the revolutionary Gemini infrastructure, make the new Centerton-based servers ideal for hyperscale workloads, where using many extreme low-energy servers densely packed into a small footprint can be much more efficient than fewer standalone servers. Traditional servers rely on dedicated components, including management, networking, storage, power cords and cooling fans in a single enclosure. However, Gemini enclosures are capable of supporting thousands of servers per rack that share these components” -hp Doesn’t this remind you of a glorified SoC? My point is, by the time Denver is in production Nvidia will be competing in the shrinking server market due to consolidations while at the same time competing against an established low energy processor like Intel Gemini. In my view, it will be extremely difficult for Nvidia to be profitable in the desktop and server arena given this market dynamics.</Msg><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1352650525130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 11:15:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352651204778-10</Id><Topic><Title>nvda investors buy more then 40 millon shares last 2 days are not going sell at loss!!!</Title><Username>clintelkins</Username><Timestamp>1352649545961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 10:59:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do not think their was any sellers last 2-days only buyers since stock was trading .50 off LOW !!</Msg><Username>clintelkins</Username><Timestamp>1352651204778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 11:26:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352651264643-11</Id><Topic><Title>Like a flag at half-staff, lowered guidance is a sad thing.</Title><Username>bestogram</Username><Timestamp>1352446269676</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 02:31:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed Best. Jen lowering his guidance is a very sad thing. And to go from revenues of $1.204 billion for the quarter just ended, to as low as $1.025 billion the Next three months, -- according to Jen's latest guidance -- is a Very Large Reduction indeed.</Msg><Username>fan_of_best</Username><Timestamp>1352651264643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 11:27:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352651862718-12</Id><Topic><Title>"Project Denver going great!" says Jen Hsun Huang</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1352521041877</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 23:17:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Am I really out of touch?" YES !!!! From the article you quoted: "The worldwide server market will continue to decline because companies are cutting down their costs by consolidating into the “cloud”." "Today, the same server-farm has now graduated into an Internet-WAN based “cloud server architecture” " But then you jump in and exclude ARM64 from cloud servers... Just be very careful declaring game over before its begun... HP didn't go with ARM server anything for ARM didn't have 64-bit (yet) "The reason why 64-bit based ARM chip is attractive in the server arena is mainly due to its inherent low power consumption which is most suited for datacenter. But, now Intel has come up with their own version of low power x86 chip called Atom Gemini that’s specifically designed for server architecture." SO... A sucker for the INtel company line... How will the ARM64 servers compare to the Atom Gemini...?? Well... you can't answer... Again, don't declare game over before it's begun...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1352651862718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 11:37:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352657035118-13</Id><Title>So how long can Jen delay releasing the 10-Q Report?</Title><Msg>So how long can Jen delay releasing the 10-Q Report? Anybody know? There's a Lot of good facts and figures in there, don't you know. Like for instance, how much did the Tegra/Consumer Products Business lose for the 3Q? Nobody knows, right? Until Jen reluctantly releases that pesky SEC required 10-Q Report.</Msg><Username>seeking.best</Username><Timestamp>1352657035118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 13:03:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352658667932-14</Id><Topic><Title>What does Jen's new dividend means to a typical holder of 100 nvidia shares?.</Title><Username>everyday_best</Username><Timestamp>1352479908826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:51:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>X X X My my my. The Yahoo Monitors are working like a well-oiled Machine today, boys. THREE -- count 'em 3 -- TOS-abusive and likely illicit Libelous messages from Badly Behaving Member "getanid61" were speedily removed from public view by the fine Yahoo Monitors. Unfortunately the new Yahoo doesn't mark the spot with an "X" like the good 'ole days. But I'll bet that they're working on it. To "optimize the user experience", don't u know. .</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1352658667932</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 13:31:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352660534399-15</Id><Topic><Title>What does Jen's new dividend means to a typical holder of 100 nvidia shares?.</Title><Username>everyday_best</Username><Timestamp>1352479908826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:51:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo! Terms of Service Section 3 -- YOUR REGISTRATION OBLIGATIONS In excerpts. "Yahoo! has the right to suspend or terminate your account and refuse any and all current or future use of the Service." Seems like a good rule, right? For flagrantly repeat violators of Yahoo's TOS.</Msg><Username>bnh.police</Username><Timestamp>1352660534399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 14:02:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352660874176-16</Id><Topic><Title>What does Jen's new dividend means to a typical holder of 100 nvidia shares?.</Title><Username>everyday_best</Username><Timestamp>1352479908826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:51:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""Yahoo! has the right to suspend or terminate your account " Is that why you have over a thousand accounts (aliases) ???</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1352660874176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 14:07:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352662395992-17</Id><Title>Will rally tomorrow to scare the shorts.</Title><Msg>Nvda may open at 12.40 and climb all day.</Msg><Username>maveric_trader1</Username><Timestamp>1352662395992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 14:33:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352663361475-18</Id><Title>UK court says Apple notice was 'false and misleading,' orders full repayment of Samsung's legal costs</Title><Msg>Justice !!!! UK court says Apple notice was 'false and misleading,' orders full repayment of Samsung's legal costs Nothing truly says "I'm sorry" like a large sum of cash, and Apple will have to open up its wallet to Samsung thanks to "false and misleading" information it published in a court-ordered statement. The decision stems from an earlier UK high court ruling ordering Cupertino to post an apology on its British website stating that the Galaxy Tab didn't copy the iPad. However, according to a new judgement by the the Court of Appeal of England and Wales, the apology it issued contained statements "calculated to produce confusion," like references to unrelated, favorable judgements. Though Apple issued a second apology, the court is taking the unusual step of forcing it to pay all of Samsung's legal fees for the entire case on an "indemnity basis" -- in other words, to compensate the Korean maker for losses suffered due to the original statement.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1352663361475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 14:49:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352663667566-19</Id><Title>Tim Cook is Tech 'Lightweight', Says Former Apple Exec</Title><Msg>David Sobotta, a former director of Apple's federal sales group, has criticized current CEO Tim Cook's lack of leadership skills, as well as being "lightweight" in terms of understanding technology. Sobotta, who published a Kindle book pertaining to his 20-year experience at Apple called "The Pomme Company" (Pomme being French for apple) spoke about Steve Jobs' successor in an interview. When asked for his thoughts of the recent firing of iOS chief Scott Forstall, which was purportedly due to his lack of apology for Apple's abysmal iOS maps app, and retail chief John Brownell, Sobotta said: "Tim will react to the numbers or his fear of being wrong quickly. Fear of being wrong is a managerial trait that runs strong and deep in Apple because of the way Steve ran the company. Even the appearance of being wrong when in the end you might be right is dreaded at Apple." "Technology-wise, I think Tim Cook is a lightweight," he added. "I never felt passion for technology from Tim like I did from Steve and some of the great engineers." Sobotta has previously been critical of Apple in a number of areas on his blog, Applepeels. The titles to some recent posts are "Do Apple Employees Need A Witness Protection Program?", "Has Apple lost its soul?" and "Will Apple Ever Figure Out the Cloud?"</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1352663667566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 14:54:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352664858296-20</Id><Topic><Title>Tim Cook is Tech 'Lightweight', Says Former Apple Exec</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1352663667566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 14:54:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's how that brand-new "lightweight" Apple A6X processor compares to the pitiful nvidia tegra 3. According to AnandTech -- the gold standard for benchmarks. Google it boys : iPad 4 GPU Performance Analyzed: PowerVR SGX 554MP4 Under the Hood Good luck competing with that "lightweight" Genuine Apple A6X processor, boys. Ha ha ha ha ha!</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1352664858296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 15:14:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352664932086-21</Id><Topic><Title>Tim Cook is Tech 'Lightweight', Says Former Apple Exec</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1352663667566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 14:54:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>glad you don't dispute the article...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1352664932086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 15:15:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352665802463-22</Id><Title>Shorts will be squeaking like a pig in the morning!!!!</Title><Msg>NVDA will rocket up at the open. $12.70 will be the close. Way over sold.</Msg><Username>maveric_trader1</Username><Timestamp>1352665802463</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 15:30:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352668302913-23</Id><Title>short frying party on Monday.</Title><Msg>Sure would not want to be short here, near the years low, could bounce up a buck in days.</Msg><Username>rigged_markets</Username><Timestamp>1352668302913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 16:11:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352669072265-24</Id><Topic><Title>short frying party on Monday.</Title><Username>rigged_markets</Username><Timestamp>1352668302913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 16:11:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps you missed this company's latest guidance? Revenues for the quarter just ended were $1.204 billion. But the current CEO gave his latest guidance of as low as $1.025 billion the Next quarter. Quite a Large reduction in revenues, yes? It sure is. From $1.204 to as low as $1.025 billion. Why, that's a 15% plunge. On a "linked-quarter" basis, as they say in the lingo of investing. { sniff sniff } Don't ya just Love the smell of those long bacon strips frying?</Msg><Username>fumbe.bapoto</Username><Timestamp>1352669072265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 16:24:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352674101637-25</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts will be squeaking like a pig in the morning!!!!</Title><Username>maveric_trader1</Username><Timestamp>1352665802463</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 15:30:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Say Goose? Do you have the number of that truck-driving school we saw on TV? I think I might need it. This nvidia carnival barking gig just ain't working out. What with Jen chopping guidance and all." .</Msg><Username>maverick.pete</Username><Timestamp>1352674101637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:48:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352684065049-26</Id><Topic><Title>short frying party on Monday.</Title><Username>rigged_markets</Username><Timestamp>1352668302913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 16:11:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NVDA more than paid for the miss and guidance, if you hold a month, it will be back over $13..</Msg><Username>maveric_trader1</Username><Timestamp>1352684065049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 20:34:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352686243249-27</Id><Topic><Title>UK court says Apple notice was 'false and misleading,' orders full repayment of Samsung's legal costs</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1352663361475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 14:49:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It could have been much worse. Even the 2nd apology is implemented on Apple's UK site in such a technologically sophiscated way to defeat search engines. Apple Execs could have been held in court comtempt and locked in jail.</Msg><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1352686243249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:10:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352688252839-28</Id><Title>Valuation is absurdly cheap</Title><Msg>Okay, so I feel like buying NVDA down here is essentially free money. $3.43B in cash, 2.4% yield, year-over-year revenue growth despite operating in a weak PC demand environment, and a ramping mobile processor segment. I've got a limit order set for $11.99 to buy even more.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1352688252839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:44:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352689715680-29</Id><Title>With HTC Patent Deal, Apple Is Going For Android’s Jugular : "Royalty stacking,”</Title><Msg>Great article, boys. On the HTC settlement with Apple. Google this : With HTC Patent Deal, Apple Is Going For Android’s Jugular TechCrunch "Now HTC will have to pay hefty royalties to both Microsoft and Apple for every Android device it sells. Lawyers call this “royalty stacking,” and it can be a big problem in complex industries like smartphones. It’s perhaps not surprising, then, that the phone hogging the most real estate on HTC’s homepage today is running Windows Phone 8. It may be that the weight of these stacked royalties will effectively push HTC off of Android entirely — something that suits both Apple and Microsoft who are used to co-existing as a duopoly, as in the desktop OS market. The HTC deal is bad news for Samsung, and even worse news for Google. Whatever royalty HTC agreed to, it sets a floor for any future deal between Apple and Samsung. It’s true that Samsung is a far larger company and has its own portfolio of patents to use as bargaining chips. But in the end, Samsung won’t be able to get around the fact that this HTC deal happened, and its price tag will carry some weight. Samsung, sooner or later, will end up paying a similar price. The big question is whether Samsung — or anyone else — will be able to still sell Android phones at a profit after paying Apple’s and Microsoft’s royalties." "Royalty stacking”. $10 bucks here, $20 bucks there -- and pretty soon those android devices can't compete with Anything. So android gets Crushed and is abandoned. Remember the National Geographic Channel, boys? Where the Lion takes down the wildebeest. Apple's mauling of HTC seems a lot like that. Same technique, right? It sure is. The Lion goes right for the jugular. Crushing it.</Msg><Username>bestonica</Username><Timestamp>1352689715680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 22:08:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>36</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352689769181-30</Id><Topic><Title>Valuation is absurdly cheap</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1352688252839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:44:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bought some at $12.21 and will also buy more at $11.90. Good luck, it shouldn't be this low, but people are panicking. I bought 6,500 shares so far and will buy up to $200K worth if it goes low enough. 6 months it will be $14.00</Msg><Username>longtrader123</Username><Timestamp>1352689769181</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 22:09:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352690278214-31</Id><Title>Jefferies Group Sets NVIDIA Price Target at $14.00 (NVDA)</Title><Msg>Jefferies Group Sets NVIDIA Price Target at $14.00 (NVDA) N, ovember 9th2012 - 0 comments - Filed Under - by Latisha Jones Filed Under: Analyst Articles - US - Stock Market Investment analysts at Jefferies Group dropped their target price on shares of NVIDIA (NASDAQ: NVDA) from $16.00 to $14.00 in a note issued to investors on Friday. The firm currently has a “hold” rating on the stock. The analysts wrote, “NVDA exceeded both consensus revs and EPS but guided 4Q revs to decline by 9% QoQ or 800bps below consensus. The company announced a $0.075 dividend or 2.4% yield and its entry into 4G LTE modem market (discrete and integrated app processor). We continue to believe that NVDA is best positioned w/ Tegra to benefit from Windows RT ramp into PCs, and could get more positive w/ success there.” NVIDIA traded down 3.47% on Friday, hitting $12.24. NVIDIA has a 1-year low of $11.63 and a 1-year high of $16.90. The company has a market cap of $7.582 billion and a price-to-earnings ratio of 16.71.</Msg><Username>maveric_trader1</Username><Timestamp>1352690278214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 22:17:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352693462661-32</Id><Topic><Title>Low Target: 12.00</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1352600855865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 21:27:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure the bozo analysts will start revising down targets to scare people.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1352693462661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 23:11:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352693903902-33</Id><Topic><Title>With HTC Patent Deal, Apple Is Going For Android’s Jugular : "Royalty stacking,”</Title><Username>bestonica</Username><Timestamp>1352689715680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 22:08:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Apple and Microsoft both view Google as a strategic threat. With patents --- which are, at their essence, a monopoly right — they are attacking Google together in a way they could not otherwise do without running afoul of antitrust laws. Their combined royalties have the potential to squeeze all the profits out of manufacturing Android devices." As the profits are squeezed-out of manufacturing those patent-stacked android devices, the manufacturers will likely put the squeeze on their component suppliers. Like nvidia. Which unfortunately for the tegra, have no profits to be squeezed-out. Nope. The tegra is already losing Huge amounts of shareholder's money. Here's what the six (6) months of 2012 look like. (The 3Q numbers should be out any day now) The nvidia 10-Q for the Six (6) months ending July 29, 2012. Page 28 $312,158,000 __ CPB (Tegra) revenue for the 6 months ($191,641,000) __ CPB (Tegra) Losses for the 6 months Like I mentioned before, the tegra is Already losing Huge amounts of money. And that's Before the impending "Royalty stacking” squeeze from the manufacturers. This could get ugly, boys. Oh so Ugly. For the tegra.</Msg><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1352693903902</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 23:18:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352695129831-34</Id><Topic><Title>With HTC Patent Deal, Apple Is Going For Android’s Jugular : "Royalty stacking,”</Title><Username>bestonica</Username><Timestamp>1352689715680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 22:08:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Royalty stacking”. "Their combined royalties have the potential to squeeze all the profits out of manufacturing Android devices." $10 bucks here, $20 bucks there -- and pretty soon those android devices can't compete with Anything. So Best? Maybe the android manufacturers -- like HTC and Asus and Samsung and ZTE -- will decide to use those perfectly good Dual core processors, rather than that extravagant and largely unnecessary Five-core tegra #3. As a way to save money, don't u know. To offset some of the increased cost created by those new stacked royalties. From Microsoft and Apple.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1352695129831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 23:38:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352695305289-35</Id><Title>Analysis: Apple and HTC Settle Patents Disputes Globally</Title><Msg>1. Bloomberg: Apple Settles HTC Patent Suits in Shift Away From Jobs’ War Plan Apple’s complaints included claims HTC copied the iPhone maker’s technology for detecting phone numbers in e-mails, allowing users to save the information or make a call without dialing. The dispute, which include a case filed in London, also included Apple accusing its rival of copying other features such as “slide to unlock,” multiple screen touches and using various alphabets when sending messages. HTC’s rebuttal included its $300 million purchase of 3G Graphics Co., a company part-owned by HTC Chairwoman Cher Wang, in a bid to leverage that company’s patent claims against Apple to bolster its own defense. The gambit failed when the ITC ruled in November 2011 that Apple’s Macs didn’t infringe two S3 Graphics patents. A separate case before the ITC may have forced Cook to the negotiating table after a judge said Apple would likely face difficulty getting a series of HTC patents invalidated. HTC bought those patents, covering technology in LTE high-speed wireless devices, from ADC Telecommunications Inc. for $75 million. “The settlement is a big surprise and is likely due to HTC’s LTE patents, which it bought from ADC last year, as Apple’s LTE patents are relatively weak,” said Jeff Pu, an analyst with Fubon Financial Holding Co. in Taipei who raised his price target for HTC today to NT$270 from NT$160. “What HTC still needs, though, is good products.” ====================== 2. In a separate interview, HTC CEO Cher Wang commented that the patent settlement shows that HTC portofolio of patents are respected due to their strengths. =========== 3. Apple has suffered a string of legal setbacks lately, including 1) forced 2nd apology to Samsung and fines to pay Samsung's legal costs, 2) US judge tossed Apple's suit againt Google out of the court in a federal cout in Wisconsin, 3) VirnetX adds iPhone 5 to new Apple lawsuit after $368m trial win, 4) Apple pays Swiss rail $21mn over clock dispute after beign caught for stealing the swiss clock design, ...</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1352695305289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 23:41:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352696173737-36</Id><Topic><Title>With HTC Patent Deal, Apple Is Going For Android’s Jugular : "Royalty stacking,”</Title><Username>bestonica</Username><Timestamp>1352689715680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 22:08:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More posts from freaky and distrubig poster who has his sock puppets 'talk' to eachother coo-coo for cocoa-puffs.</Msg><Username>better_than_bestie</Username><Timestamp>1352696173737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 23:56:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352696297090-37</Id><Topic><Title>With HTC Patent Deal, Apple Is Going For Android’s Jugular : "Royalty stacking,”</Title><Username>bestonica</Username><Timestamp>1352689715680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 22:08:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The big question is whether Samsung — or anyone else — will be able to still sell android phones at a profit after paying Apple’s and Microsoft’s royalties." Such a Big Big Question. Be sure to read that highly informative article on the HTC settlement with Apple, boys. Google : With HTC Patent Deal, Apple Is Going For Android’s Jugular TechCrunch</Msg><Username>good_point_best</Username><Timestamp>1352696297090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 23:58:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>