<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351748604627-1</Id><Topic><Title>Who Does Apple Fire for the iPad Mini Fiasco?</Title><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1351742260354</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 23:57:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Who Does Apple Fire" One bad apple...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351748604627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 01:43:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351777055700-2</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Surface RT : Microsoft's greatest hardware Fiasco ever?</Title><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1351740240087</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 23:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I don't know that the Surface RT tablet was meant to be an iPad competitor. If it's greatest value is having a keyboard -- then isn't it a laptop competitor? Then why not buy a "real" Windows laptop? Hummm? A Surface RT with Type cover keyboard will cost you $628. Over on CNET, I found over 740 genuine x86 Windows laptops for that price and below. 740 nice laptops, boys."</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1351777055700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:37:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351777882943-3</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Surface RT : Microsoft's greatest hardware Fiasco ever?</Title><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1351740240087</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 23:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't you say the same kind of thing about Nexus 7? It is selling a million a month. A lot of ppl flap their lips, day in and day out. It doesn't mean anything when they do. ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1351777882943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:51:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351778219516-4</Id><Title>NVDA can jump to 18 after earnings - here is why</Title><Msg>I studied NVDA. It has 5.29 in cash per share. Now 12.29 less 5.29 cash is 7. So the company is going for less than 6.5 forward PE. With the design wins and early success of Surface RT, several other RT machines, the ZTE phone win, the increased attach rate on x86 (presented by NVDA) recently all indicative of impressive growth ahead. This stock is ripe to fly.. I feel NVDA for next 12 months is like the Cirrus logic of last 12 months .. Thoughts?</Msg><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1351778219516</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:56:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351779073153-5</Id><Title>nvda &amp; armh merger</Title><Msg>if i was nvda ceo, i would merge with arhm to create the new power house for mobile chips. nvda has the cash and products and armh have the long term technology. win win.</Msg><Username>marktran912</Username><Timestamp>1351779073153</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:11:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351781882280-6</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA can jump to 18 after earnings - here is why</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1351778219516</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:56:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Based on your comments elsewhere, I don't see how you can be taken seriously, but the stock would go MUCH higher if it were bought . . MUCH higher. The $18 is very realistic if the current estimates by the company hold true and they go counter to the bearish view of tech for the 4th quarter.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1351781882280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:58:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351782036253-7</Id><Title>When you are not going up, you are going to go down.</Title><Msg>Ain't no plateau. Just look at the Blackberry and Nokia. Once they were on top of the clouds, now they are in the dumpster. Look at GM and Ford. Once they set the standards for cars. But that's all changed. Apple is going to be there...in the dumpster with BB and NOK and GM. What goes up, comes down. Simple as that. The market and the courts won't be fooled by round rects forever. ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1351782036253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351783153220-8</Id><Title>Apple vs Samsung in UK: Signs of Desperation?</Title><Msg>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-11-01/apple-ordered-to-change-notice-in-u-k-samsung-case.html</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1351783153220</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:19:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351784869170-9</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA SHORT INTEREST 13,979,797</Title><Username>dedrapop</Username><Timestamp>1351504851532</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 06:00:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.............</Msg><Username>dedrapop</Username><Timestamp>1351784869170</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351785111510-10</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA can jump to 18 after earnings - here is why</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1351778219516</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:56:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Okay, well, see ya. I think the whole management is the problem is WAY overplayed. You do realize that what Nvidia is doing is essentially David vs Goliath in terms of strategy, don't you? Sooo, you think the competition, the Goliaths, are just going to stand by and let them take market share by competing only legitimately? It's not just the MM and investors involved that make this a tough slog right now. And the hedge funds that use Apple as one of the main tech investments to keep their portfolio from caving during bearish times aren't about to help a company take away some of that capital income except for short-term trades. It takes time for David to become king and so it will take time for Nvidia to convince enough investors to hold long-term. I've been frustrated too but it's not because of the company's management.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1351785111510</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351786062277-11</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA SHORT INTEREST 13,979,797</Title><Username>dedrapop</Username><Timestamp>1351504851532</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 06:00:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>on ignore</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1351786062277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:07:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351786123035-12</Id><Topic><Title>Sell the Bounce</Title><Username>ertowrhy</Username><Timestamp>1351784845859</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:47:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One and done . . goodbye.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1351786123035</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:08:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351789868742-13</Id><Title>good day, but friday puts will play!</Title><Msg>as usual......</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1351789868742</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 13:11:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351796854163-14</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA SHORT INTEREST 13,979,797</Title><Username>dedrapop</Username><Timestamp>1351504851532</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 06:00:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>short interest down 6% from prior month, also less than 3% of float. If you are short you are likely to get nut punched.</Msg><Username>springer97me</Username><Timestamp>1351796854163</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:07:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351800494535-15</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA can jump to 18 after earnings - here is why</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1351778219516</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:56:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post, roundhouse_c.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1351800494535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:08:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351818576416-16</Id><Topic><Title>Apple vs Samsung in UK: Signs of Desperation?</Title><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1351783153220</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:19:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>iPad mini is another sign of desperation -- a former leader has now become a reactionary follower.</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1351818576416</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:09:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351819736953-17</Id><Title>Remember - Real Quality of Life Determined By State's Rights - Romney</Title><Msg>Federal control is the alternative</Msg><Username>mackgreene33</Username><Timestamp>1351819736953</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351822652715-18</Id><Topic><Title>Remember - Real Quality of Life Determined By State's Rights - Romney</Title><Username>mackgreene33</Username><Timestamp>1351819736953</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:28:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>amen.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1351822652715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 22:17:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351826311684-19</Id><Title>Support around $12</Title><Msg>There was quite a bit of support around $12 +/-. Traders buying on the first day of the month through earnings next Thursday are hoping for a big up move, based on options volatility. If it takes out $12.75 tomorrow, there's at least another buck left on the upside till earnings date.</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1351826311684</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:18:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351826621679-20</Id><Title>FTC Staff Said to Formally Recommend Suing Google for Antitrust</Title><Msg>FTC Staff Said to Formally Recommend Google Patent Suit Bloomberg | By Sara Forden | Nov 1, 2012 3:22 PM CT. Google Inc. (GOOG) should be sued by the Federal Trade Commission for trying to block competitors’ access to key smartphone-technology patents in violation of antitrust law, the agency’s staff told commissioners in a formal recommendation, according to four people familiar with the matter. A majority of the agency’s five commissioners are inclined to sue, according to the people, who declined to be identified because the matter isn’t public. A final decision on the staff recommendation, made last month, isn’t likely until after the Nov. 6 presidential election, they said. Google Inc. should be sued by the Federal Trade Commission for trying to block competitors’ access to key smartphone-technology patents in violation of antitrust law, the agency’s staff told commissioners in a formal recommendation, according to four people familiar with the matter. At issue are Google’s efforts to block U.S. imports of products made by Microsoft Corp. (MSFT) and Apple Inc. (AAPL) by claiming the devices, which rely on industry-standard technology, infringe patents owned by Google’s Motorola Mobility unit, the people said. “We take our commitments to license on fair, reasonable, and non-discriminatory terms very seriously and are happy to answer any questions,” Niki Fenwick, a Google spokeswoman, said. Peter Kaplan, a spokesman for the FTC, declined to comment. Formal Probe The FTC opened a formal probe into the matter in June, when it began seeking information from companies including Microsoft and Apple about whether Google offered licensing for technology under patents that help operate 3G wireless, Wi-Fi and video streaming on fair and reasonable terms, a person familiar with the matter said at the time. Industry-standard technology helps ensure that different manufacturers’ products, such as mobile phone antennas and global-positioning system software, work together. Companies that create technology that helps develop the agreed-upon industry standard pledge to license patents for those inventions on reasonable terms. The FTC is also focusing on Google’s decision to continue litigation started by Motorola Mobility over industry-standard patents before Google bought the company. Those lawsuits could end up blocking imports of popular consumer products such as Microsoft’s Xbox and Apple’s iPhone and iPad. “There is a tough emerging attitude by antitrust regulators who’ve recognized that the failure to honor standard essential patent commitments needs to be treated much more severely than in the past,” said Bert Foer, president of the American Antitrust Institute in Washington, which advocates strong enforcement of antitrust law. “The agencies want to move this issue to the forefront by speaking out and tackling these high profile cases.” Samsung Electronics U.S. antitrust regulators have agreed the FTC will focus on Motorola Mobility while the Justice Department will scrutinize Samsung Electronics Co.’s handling of industry-standard patent claims, said a person familiar with the matter June 30. The European Commission opened formal probes of Motorola Mobility and Samsung Electronics Co. for the same issues earlier this year. The investigation into Google’s use of standard-essential patents is separate from the agency’s broader probe examining whether Google’s business practices in search, advertising and mobile hurt competition, the people said. FTC investigators are also recommending the commission sue Google in that case, three people familiar with the matter said Oct. 13. A final decision hasn’t been made. " My my my. The noose tightens on Google. Steve Jobs would be so iHappy, right boys? "Google Inc. should be sued by the Federal Trade Commission for trying to block competitors’ access to key smartphone-technology patents in violation of antitrust law, the FTC's own agency’s staff told commissioners in a formal recommendation. “There is a tough emerging attitude by antitrust regulators who’ve recognized that the failure to honor standard essential patent commitments needs to be treated much more severely than in the past,” said Bert Foer, president of the American Antitrust Institute in Washington, which advocates strong enforcement of antitrust law."</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1351826621679</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:23:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>45</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351827983509-21</Id><Topic><Title>FTC Staff Said to Formally Recommend Suing Google for Antitrust</Title><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1351826621679</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:23:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Every violation of the antitrust laws is a blow to the free-enterprise system envisaged by Congress. This system depends on strong competition for its health and vigor, and strong competition depends, in turn, on compliance with antitrust legislation. In enacting these laws, Congress had many means at its disposal to penalize violators. It could have, for example, required violators to compensate federal, state, and local governments for the estimated damage to their respective economies caused by the violations. But, this remedy was not selected. Instead, Congress chose to permit all persons to sue to recover three times their actual damages every time they were injured in their business or property by an antitrust violation. By offering potential litigants the prospect of a recovery in three times the amount of their damages, Congress encouraged these persons to serve as "private attorneys general." -- The United States Supreme Court, Hawaii v. Standard Oil Co. of Cal., 405 U.S. 251, 262 (1972) Google it boys : United States antitrust law From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia My my my. Congress chose to permit all persons to sue to recover THREE TIMES (3x) their actual damages every time they were injured in their business or property by an antitrust violation. Google could be facing fines of Thermonuclear proportions, boys.</Msg><Username>plaintiff.best</Username><Timestamp>1351827983509</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:46:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>37</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>