<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346648636984-1</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen to NVDA stock price if</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1346610872872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . With a P/E of 18.48 -- nvda is already priced to perfection. Any failure to win what Jen has baked-into his questionable guidance will cause nvda to plunge off the cliff. There is zero tolerance for disappointment here. With a P/E of 18.48. . . Hey dribble boy! Check out the Inconvenient Facts for yourself. See at the top left of this page, where it says Summary Click on that. Good boy. Now see the second column of stats on nvda, to the left of the chart? What's the P/E for nvda? Hummm? Speak up now, boy. You're mumbling at your shoes again. . Your due diligence Instructor, Best wins. . .</Msg><Username>best.wins</Username><Timestamp>1346648636984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 01:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346651484883-2</Id><Topic><Title>EXTRA! EXTRA! -- Apple Sues Samsung Over 4 More iPatents</Title><Username>bestville_daily_gazette</Username><Timestamp>1346554228339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:50:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . Oops! Sorry for the typo. Best was just reading an article about how Microsoft's Windows 8 RT could very well implode right on the launch pad -- so maybe I got my tech chiefs mixed up. . “I will spend my last dying breath if I need to, and I will spend every penny of Apple’s $40 billion [$120 billion now] in the bank, to right this wrong. I’m going to destroy Android, because it’s a stolen product.” I’m willing to go thermonuclear war on this.” -- Steve Jobs, the late founder of Apple Inc. . .</Msg><Username>ibest.here</Username><Timestamp>1346651484883</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 01:51:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346652268242-3</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: Production of iPhone screens delayed at Sharp</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346564330410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 01:38:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . Looks like another epic fail at deception. By ibexx88. . .</Msg><Username>best_vs_decepticons</Username><Timestamp>1346652268242</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 02:04:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346665319371-4</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo, you will lose advertisement revenues with this new board</Title><Username>lordgaga81</Username><Timestamp>1346601309856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:55:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I completely agree ! why fix some thing that wasn't broken ! it was much easier to use the old format ---</Msg><Username>eemoss57</Username><Timestamp>1346665319371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 05:41:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346678708526-5</Id><Topic><Title>Apple iPhone 5: 50 Million + Sales Possible</Title><Username>ibest.here</Username><Timestamp>1346350218967</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 14:10:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. "Of those upgrade-eligible respondents, 45% plan to purchase an iPhone and the vast majority are waiting for the iPhone 5. The next biggest group, 31%, said that they were undecided on their next phone, and those planning to buy Google‘s (GOOG) Android devices rounded out the bottom at 22%. Power writes “Those percentages, if they held, could suggest 50 million+ iPhone 5 sales in the U.S. alone, well above current forecasts.” . Wow! "Could suggest 50 million+ iPhone 5 sales in the U.S. alone." "Well above current forecasts.” Says Robert W. Baird analyst William Power. And then there's the rest of the world that wants a Genuine iPhone 5 too. So that's what? Maybe another 100 million+ international units. Clearly, the Genuine Apple iPhone 5 will be the Fastest Selling Electronic Device in the History of Mankind -- and nvidia parts had nothing to do with it. Are we sure that nvidia is actually IN the cellphone part business? Or just a little parts hobbyist? . .</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1346678708526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 09:25:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346679524440-6</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen to NVDA stock price if</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1346610872872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The snake seems more obnoxious and angry... slithering snake best, stocks are all about the future not the past with the raised guidance and design wins and such... you never mention the cash nor the cash generated..... but what to expect from a slimy slithering snake....</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1346679524440</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 09:38:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346679627468-7</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 with 3G reportedly to arrive in six weeks</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346675414875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 08:30:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. So who did nvidia/icera lose THAT baseband radio business to? Hummm? Rather than cheering that Nexus 7 finally got 3G, astute investors are mourning that nvidia/icera lost yet another one. . .</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1346679627468</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 09:40:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346680102323-8</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 with 3G reportedly to arrive in six weeks</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346675414875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 08:30:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a worthless piece of @&amp;%@ ... you sit on a yahoo message board harassing people in Labour Day... get some self respect you RMBS refuse you..</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1346680102323</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 09:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346680276603-9</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen to NVDA stock price if</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1346610872872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. "you never mention the cash", whines mikey. Okay, let's talk about cash. nvidia has about $2b. Sitting in dry rot earning what? Half of one percent? There is no multiple applied to cash, boys. Ever. A buck is always worth just a buck. Nothing more. Folks looking for true Growth Stocks ignore the dumb cash. And focus instead on Earnings. Beautiful, glorious Earnings. Which in nvidia case, have plunged 37.4% for the First Half y-o-y. . .</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1346680276603</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 09:51:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346682216063-10</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen to NVDA stock price if</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1346610872872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First of all Nvidia PE is much less than Yahoo shows. Did you notice that they use GAAP numbers in PE calculation whereas wall street uses NON-GAAP? Last quarter Nvidia made $0.27 but they show $0.19. As far as forward view is concerned I am even more optimistic than baseball. I think Nvidia will make at least $0.35 this quarter. That is $1.40 annual run rate. With 13%-15% sequential QoQ growth for last 2 Qs the company deserves at least PE=20. That is $28 right there. Plus $5.3 per share cash makes it $33. In reality if Nvidia will show 30% YoY growth for 2 years (this year is already almost in the book) it will be easily tolerated with PE=50. Just execute and don't worry about stock price. The reason I asked about upcoming Kindle announcement is that this close to a product release it is very difficult to keep secret about component suppliers. So many people already have this product in their hands, So I am sure all big boys already know what is inside. The actual announcement should not be a surprise to them. So if Nvidia is not there (and I am sure it is not) I expect a small initial retail sell off. I have my cash ready to use this opportunity and buy around $13.50.</Msg><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1346682216063</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 10:23:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346684249628-11</Id><Topic><Title>Apple,Samsung patent battle to delay iPhone 5 launch? (another reason)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346682495056</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 10:28:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While I have no doubt Samsung will sue upon release of the iPhone5, there is zero chance that the threat of a lawsuit would EVER derail a release date. I'm sure Apple is threatened with suits with every major launch, as is any successful company. It is far more likely that supply issues are a problem for the iPhone5 (as you pointed out in another post) and Apple needs a convenient scapegoat.</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1346684249628</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 10:57:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346684575454-12</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 with 3G reportedly to arrive in six weeks</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346675414875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 08:30:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, instead of a Qcom or INTC chip where did THAT business go to? Hummmm? Rather than worrying about an add on radio chip that is sold for pennies. Astute investors realize that this is another design win for Tegra 3. RIGHT BOYS</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1346684575454</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 11:02:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346685591948-13</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 with 3G reportedly to arrive in six weeks</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346675414875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 08:30:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . So who did nvidia/icera lose THAT baseband radio business to? Hummm? Rather than cheering that Nexus 7 finally got 3G, astute investors are mourning that nvidia/icera lost yet another one. . . Three Hundred Sixty Seven Million ($367,000,000.00) of shareholder's cash, boys. Call it a Third of a Billion+ That's what Jen wasted buying icera. And for what? To make a 1985-era discrete, non-integrated radio chip. That there are no buyers for. EVERYBODY wants Qualcomm radio parts. No wonder you paid pumper boys never want to talk about nvidia's baseband radio business. It sucks. . .</Msg><Username>best.again</Username><Timestamp>1346685591948</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 11:19:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346697901724-14</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news: Is Amazon prepping a dual-screen tablet?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346644962015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 00:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so what is your own spin? is amzn prepping a dual-screen tablet or not? amzn is about cheap. dual screens ain't cheap. this will never happen. this whole patent thing in the us and europe is getting way out of hand. the only winners are the new ruling class, otherwise fondly known as the lawyers.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1346697901724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 14:45:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346698278457-15</Id><Topic><Title>Apple,Samsung patent battle to delay iPhone 5 launch? (another reason)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346682495056</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 10:28:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wouldn't be surprised to see Samsung completely cut-off Apple after their contractual agreements expire.</Msg><Username>bestisapest</Username><Timestamp>1346698278457</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 14:51:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346698670066-16</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news: Is Amazon prepping a dual-screen tablet?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346644962015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 00:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are If you place a 10 million unit blanket order. It's a great idea that fits Amazon perfectly. Just think of all the special complied ads according to your interest/lifestyle they can show constantly display on the other screen, or in the section not being used.</Msg><Username>bestisapest</Username><Timestamp>1346698670066</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 14:57:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346706977178-17</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news: Is Amazon prepping a dual-screen tablet?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346644962015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 00:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmm... could be the angle of view, but they looked like two different size devices...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346706977178</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 17:16:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346717235399-18</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news: Is Amazon prepping a dual-screen tablet?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346644962015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 00:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . So what can an Apple iAttorney do that the Tegra Superchip can't? Hummm? Come on, think about it. Ready? Contribute to the bottom line. . 笑笑笑笑笑! Ha ha ha ha ha! . .</Msg><Username>good_one_best</Username><Timestamp>1346717235399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 20:07:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346719103389-19</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 with 3G reportedly to arrive in six weeks</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346675414875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 08:30:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone can Google "Nvidia Icera" and see that the acquisition was roughly a year ago, and there are already design wins in Asus tabets and ZTE phones.....seriously, stop making a fool of yourself, it's getting really old.</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1346719103389</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 20:38:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346721274876-20</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 with 3G reportedly to arrive in six weeks</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346675414875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 08:30:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. What's getting Old is whenever nvidia has something new to launch, Asus is their one-and-only "launch partner". Time after time after time. It's like Jen can never find a Real customer will to be a guinea pig, -- and it would be plenty embarassing to launch with zero customers -- so he probably cuts a deal with his Taiwanese pals at Asus. "Same as last time, right boys? Quarter million "engineering samples" to give it a go." Sole launch partner Asus. Sole launch partner Asus. Did I mention? It's getting Old. . .</Msg><Username>perceptive.best</Username><Timestamp>1346721274876</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 21:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346721310339-21</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news: Is Amazon prepping a dual-screen tablet?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346644962015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 00:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imagine, just for a moment... RMBS had the Apple legal team... you may have lost only half your savings... and you wouldn't have been scared for life...</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1346721310339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 21:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346721529874-22</Id><Title>what if RMBS had the Apple legal team??</Title><Msg>BEST WISHES..... pun intended...</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1346721529874</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 21:18:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346721716815-23</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 with 3G reportedly to arrive in six weeks</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346675414875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 08:30:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have no clue what getting old means.. your endless, pointless banter ?? Truly a loser's loser..</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1346721716815</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 21:21:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346724610639-24</Id><Title>HTC plays hard to get.</Title><Msg>. . "HTC chairwoman Cher Wang has confirmed that her company has no plans to settle its ongoing patent lawsuit with Apple, despite Cupertino's recent legal triumph over Samsung. In May, a Delaware court ordered the two companies to begin settlement talks, but Wang says HTC has no intention to settle, and remains undeterred by Samsung's recent setback. "Samsung’s defeat does not mean that Google Inc.’s Android camp is defeated," Wang told Cynes yesterday, adding that "every company has good innovations." Wang's comments, issued ahead of an APEC Business Advisory Council meeting, suggest that HTC is willing to take the matter to court, despite the fact that such recourse now seems rather RISKY, given last week's verdict. Late last year, the US International Trade Commission banned HTC phones from entering the US. HTC responded with a custom-built workaround, though it now appears that the dispute is far from over." Google this: "Cher Wang: HTC has no plans to settle patent lawsuit with Apple" . Stubborn, fiesty defendants make for the best show, right boys? Let's hope they get that same, even fiestyier lady Judge again. ...Miaow! ....Riieeewn! ....Miaw! ....Hisssss! ....RrreoowwWOW !!! . .</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1346724610639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 22:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346724976896-25</Id><Topic><Title>HTC plays hard to get.</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1346724610639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 22:10:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . So Master? Will Ticketmaster be selling tickets? Me and the clones would like to see it. . .</Msg><Username>best.clone185</Username><Timestamp>1346724976896</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 22:16:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346725020123-26</Id><Topic><Title>what if RMBS had the Apple legal team??</Title><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1346721529874</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 21:18:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A defendant in a lawsuit involving large sums of money was talking to his lawyer. "If I lose this case, I'll be ruined." "It's in the judge's hands now," said the lawyer. "Would it help if I sent the judge a box of cigars?" "Oh no! This judge is a stickler or ethical behavior. A stunt like that would prejudice him against you. He might even hold you in contempt of court. In fact, you shouldn't even smile at the judge." Within the course of time, the judge rendered a decision in favor of the defendant. As the defendant left the courthouse, he said to his lawyer, "Thanks for the tip about the cigars. It worked!" "I'm sure we would have lost the case if you'd sent them." "But, I did send them." "You did WHAT?" said the lawyer, incredulously. "Yes. That's how we won the case." "I don't understand," said the lawyer. "I sent the cigars to the judge, but enclosed the plaintiff's business card."</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1346725020123</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 22:17:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346725205470-27</Id><Title>Intel needs to adjust ATOM roadmap for PC use</Title><Msg>Digitimes says, Intel may be forced to adjust its roadmap for PC-use Atom processors as the top-2 netbook vendors – Asustek Computer and Acer – both plan to stop manufacturing related products, according to sources from notebook players. Asustek is already set to halt its Eee PC product line and officially phase out from the IT industry after completely digesting any remaining inventory. As for Acer, so far, the company has not yet made any plans to open new netbook projects, indicating that the vendor may also plan to step out of the market. Although Atom series processors will still be adopted by handset and embedded products, the sources believe the two product lines are unlikely to be able to fill the gap created by the absent netbook products in short term due to weak shipments. .... (Sales from Intel's new mobile offerings, if any, will not be enough to bridge the gap)</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1346725205470</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 22:20:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346725542404-28</Id><Topic><Title>HTC plays hard to get.</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1346724610639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 22:10:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . And Master? Will they have those big tubs of buttered popcorn there? We clones Love buttered popcorn! . .</Msg><Username>best.clone167</Username><Timestamp>1346725542404</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 22:25:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346728555890-29</Id><Topic><Title>what if RMBS had the Apple legal team??</Title><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1346721529874</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 21:18:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The days of patent trolls have passed, the RMBS patents are being demolished in reexamination at the USPTO, right boys? How are those "Barf" patents holding up, not so well huh?.</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1346728555890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346729171405-30</Id><Topic><Title>Sept. 12th: New iPad Mini and iPhone 5</Title><Username>seeking.best</Username><Timestamp>1344143588000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 01:13:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . Heck, even Linus Benedict Torvalds, -- the chief architect of Android -- wears a tie now. This ain't 1999, u know. . Yeah, Probably one of those nice custom-made Italian silk ties. A fun, embroidered one, u know? F.U.N. __ F.U.N. __ F.U.N. __ F.U.N. . 笑笑笑笑笑! Ha ha ha ha ha! . .</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1346729171405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:26:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346730044206-31</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 with 3G reportedly to arrive in six weeks</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346675414875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 08:30:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really, that's what you come back with?? I honestly dont know why you bother.</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1346730044206</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:40:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346730134789-32</Id><Topic><Title>Intel opens up about its "Knight's Corner" parallel superputing coprocessor</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1346728651514</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:17:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . Wow! Extraordinary! You gotta see the benchmark graph, boys. Google this: "Intel opens up about its 'Knights Corner' supercomputer co-processor" . 1,381 MFLOPS/Watt __ Intel Knights Corner 1,266 MFLOPS/Watt __ nvidia Tesla</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1346730134789</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346730507770-33</Id><Topic><Title>what if RMBS had the Apple legal team??</Title><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1346721529874</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 21:18:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So who was it that filed the "Barf" patent reexamination requests that devastated the Rambus portfolio, causing our pal Best to lose his life savings.....you guessed it Nvidia. Paid basher LOL....no, not at all, just a bitter and crazed fool. Mystery solved. Patent wins again!</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1346730507770</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346730524828-34</Id><Topic><Title>Intel opens up about its "Knight's Corner" parallel superputing coprocessor</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1346728651514</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:17:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . An impressive leap-frogging by Intel, right boys? It sure is. And if Jen is done spending R&amp;D on those teeny-tiny volume Tesla chips, it looks like Intel has captured yet another market -- supercomputer chips. . .</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1346730524828</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:48:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346731137201-35</Id><Title>BEST ...just how much does NVDA pay RMBS annually??</Title><Msg>Just curious.. do you know?</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1346731137201</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:58:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>