<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353820304750-1</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Bay Trailer-T, A Next Generation Mobile SoC (January 2013)</Title><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1353685413211</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 10:43:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? Since Intel will no longer be needing any of nvidia's graphics attachment parts, maybe Jen and his boys can come up with something else to attach. Like a little joy stick maybe. To make playing Every shoot-em-up game ever written for the x86, even more enjoyable on the new Genuine Intel Bay Trailer-Tablet gaming rig.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1353820304750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 00:11:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353863928528-2</Id><Title>NVDA ready to take off? NVDA tegra based Surface RT is the top holiday Gift</Title><Msg>Now, this is getting really hot!!! http://live.wsj.com/video/surface-tablet-tops-holiday-wish-lists/A75792D8-BEDE-43CE-A826-F6B9651FF9D4.html#!A75792D8-BEDE-43CE-A826-F6B9651FF9D4</Msg><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1353863928528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 12:18:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353865863871-3</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra/CPB Loses more than Twice (2x) what it Lost last year!</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1353375883620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:44:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the Nine Months ending October 28, 2012 the Tegra/Consuming Profits Division wiped-out 32.5% of nvidia's Operating Income, as follows: $434,818,000 __ Operating Income, GPU Business $283,520,000 __ Operating Income, Professional Solutions Business __________ $718,338,000 __ Operating Income without the Tegra/CPB Business ($233,545,000) __ Operating Loss, Tegra/Consumer Products Business ($233,545,000) / $718,338,000 = (32.51%) So Master? This is quite an odd company, right? One Third (33%) of their profits are wasted on the CEO's tegra folly. Yes, Wasted, boys. Yet "somebody" spends a Lot of money on a paid pumper crew. Which hype the "virtues" of the horrendously loss-making tegra 24/7. To make the CEO's tegra folly sound, well, not so bad. When clearly the numbers show that it's Really Really Really Bad. Like, on pace to Lose about ($311,000,000.00) this year. ($311,000,000.00), boys. That's what the Jen's tegra folly is likely to lose -- just this year alone. Why, that about equal to the City of Pittsburgh's entire annual Operating Budget. A city of 307,484 people, don't u know. Which requires expenditures of about the same amount as the tegra loses. Oh so many many expenditures to run a city of 307,484 people. Police, Fire, Building Inspection, Emergency Medical Services, Animal Care &amp; Control, Public Works, Parks &amp; Recreation, City Clerk's , Mayor's Office, City Information Systems, Commission on Human Relations, Controller's Office, Finance Office, Office of Municipal Investigations, Equal Opportunity Review Commission, Personnel &amp; Civil Service Commission, City Planning, Public Safety Administration, Citizen Police Review Board, Departmental Expenditures, Pension, Health Benefits and Workers' Comp, Utilities, Judgments and Tax Refunds, Misc. Other Non-Dept. Operating Expenditures and Non-Departmental Operating Expenses. So remember boys, when you think of Jen's tegra folly, think of the City of Pittsburgh. Wasted. Did I mention? This is quite an odd company, right Master?.</Msg><Username>best.clone185</Username><Timestamp>1353865863871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 12:51:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353865977438-4</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Bay Trailer-T, A Next Generation Mobile SoC (January 2013)</Title><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1353685413211</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 10:43:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. as of now, nvda is and will be for a long long time, awol in this fight. Jen ain't got no chips "for mktg reasons", roflol 2. #1 &amp; 2 will always use their own chips, #3 is cheap only, #4 is into 'spreadiing the wealth', as per txn noted when they exited, there just ain't a big enough available TAM to win to justify the investment. Jen is fool in continuing to throw good shareholders money after bad. 3. I have noted that you have always avoided my question: you can sing intc's praise all day long, but is intc ready to sell $20 SoCs?</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1353865977438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 12:52:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353867170767-5</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Bay Trailer-T, A Next Generation Mobile SoC (January 2013)</Title><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1353685413211</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 10:43:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If anybody can afford to sell $20 SoCs, it's Intel. They have plenty of excess fab capacity, don't have to pay for an external foundry's profits or ARM's license. So...yes.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1353867170767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:12:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353867984264-6</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Bay Trailer-T, A Next Generation Mobile SoC (January 2013)</Title><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1353685413211</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 10:43:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Is Intel ready to sell $20 SoCs?" As always, thinking-between-the-lines whosunw asks the Billion Dollar question. "Is Intel ready to sell $20 SoCs?" ANYBODY can play Jen's sell-'em-at-a-loss game in mobile processors. If they decide to. Anybody can. And with Texas Instruments gone from the game, it's even more interesting now. Could Intel deliberately sell their superior 22nm mobile processor at a loss? In order to finally conquer the mobile processor business. They sure could. If the new guy at Intel decides to do so. For long-term strategic reasons, don't u know. Like finally killing-off nvidia. So when you think about it, the very future of nvidia rests with the new guy at Intel Corporation.</Msg><Username>perceptive.best</Username><Timestamp>1353867984264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:26:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353868174784-7</Id><Title>HTC One X Plus - Back to Nvidia</Title><Msg>I thought it was interesting that as soon as HTC could use Tegra 3+ with LTE they kicked Qualcomm to the curb and went back to Nvidia. Price wasn't an issue because both processors cost the same. Perhaps they looked at how well the HTC One X internationally version was selling and went with Nvidia for the US market.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1353868174784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:29:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353868659460-8</Id><Topic><Title>HTC One X Plus - Back to Nvidia</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1353868174784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:29:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's like with intc, the chinese, especially the mainland chinese, have a distinct dislike for qcom because of the royalties that qcom demanded before. On the same beat, if they can use local, I am sure they will.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1353868659460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:37:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353871572140-9</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra/CPB Loses more than Twice (2x) what it Lost last year!</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1353375883620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:44:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>60 % of content is, well, empty lines. Congratulations!</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1353871572140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:26:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353873931532-10</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra/CPB Loses more than Twice (2x) what it Lost last year!</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1353375883620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:44:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Congratulations Best!" Yes yes yes. Dr. Bester has studied the labyrithine, abtruse, complex and special inner-workings of the new Yahoo! format. Yes, the labyrithine, abtruse, complex and special inner-workings, boys. And has discovered -- yes Discovered -- the secret Yahoo Magic involved in making blank lines, also known as "spaces", if you will. And other cool things too. To VASTLY improve the readability of the best messages, don't u know. Yes yes yes, I know. That's why Best is called "Doctor Bester" by his many many fans.</Msg><Username>dr.bester</Username><Timestamp>1353873931532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:05:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353878438420-11</Id><Title>AMD Wins the new Nintendo Wii U game consoles!</Title><Msg>AMD's HD GPU for Nintendo's Wii U - Analyst Blog Posted 11/23/2012 1:45 PM by Zacks Equity Research Advanced Micro Devices Inc. announced that it is supplying custom AMD Radeon HD GPUs to Nintendo 's newly-launched Wii U home consoles. This custom graphic processing unit (GPU) will enable Wii U to support high-definition (HD) video for games. The Wii U is Nintendo's first offering with HD graphics. Moreover, this is the first console upgrade by Nintendo in six years since the release of Wii. Gamers appear enthusiastic about the new console, as evident from the fact that Wii U is already sold out in many U.S. stores. Research firm IHS is also optimistic, expecting Nintendo to sell 3.5 million Wii Us in the U.S. this year. Nintendo launched the AMD-powered gaming consoles just before the holiday season. This makes sense, as the holiday season is usually the time when demand goes up. The gaming hardware market is currently reeling under competitive pressure from emerging social network sites and competing hardware platforms such as smartphones and tablets. Gamers are switching to these platforms or devices as they also provide free games. Gaming apps are also providing various fun-filled and thrilling games, which are successfully enticing gamers. A study conducted by DFC Intelligence suggests that the global gaming market is expected to Increase from $67.0 billion in 2012 to $82.0 billion in 2017. Further, IDC is expecting that there will be 257 million active consoles worldwide by 2015. These estimates suggest that there are opportunities for gaming companies to increase their stakes." 257,000,000 active home gaming consoles on the planet by 2015, boys. A QUARTER OF A BILLION GAMING DEVICES. And Advancing Micro Devices might capture them all. Yes boys, ALL of them. With their Genuine AMD Radeon HD custom graphics GPUs. This might explain why AMD sprinted ahead by +4.28% on Friday, November 23rd -- the day the news of AMD's key win with Nintendo came out.</Msg><Username>bestnfastest.wins</Username><Timestamp>1353878438420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:20:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353881601086-12</Id><Topic><Title>HTC One X Plus - Back to Nvidia</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1353868174784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:29:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you just posted about the HTC One+ is very old news - at least 3 months old. The One plus has been on market in Europe for several weeks, and is being released in US now, but pre-order started sometime ago. Noticed you've been away (or on short side) for awhile. Perhaps some refreshing would help.</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1353881601086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:13:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353881985688-13</Id><Title>Investing 101: The Art of Selling Short - Yahoo! Finance</Title><Msg>"What is Short Selling?" "It's the opposite of long buying," Smith says in the attached video, explaining that when people buy securities, they think the price may go up. But when they sell a security short, he says "they do that because they think the price may go down." On Wall Street, there are several different iterations of shorting, but they all essentially mean the same thing; that a stock or index is Overpriced and expected to go down in value. "It's another investment management technique,'' Smith says." Google it boys : Investing 101: The Art of Selling Short | Breakout - Yahoo! Finance</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1353881985688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:19:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353882165333-14</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Bay Trailer-T, A Next Generation Mobile SoC (January 2013)</Title><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1353685413211</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 10:43:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Selling chips at $20 per clip would cut in Intel's profit margin severely. Don't think those folks are willing to do it...they've been spoiled for too long. It is not a technical decision, but a business one.</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1353882165333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:22:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353884394906-15</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Bay Trailer-T, A Next Generation Mobile SoC (January 2013)</Title><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1353685413211</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 10:43:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's a business decision whether Intel wants to conquer and capture the non-Apple part of the mobile processor market." Ya gotta spend money to make money, right? Like advertising. First you spend -- and then you make. So Intel burns-off a couple or three billion on getting their newest mobile chip, -- The Genuine Intel Bay Trailer-T for tablets -- firmly established in the market with the OEM's. So what? It's no different that what Jen has attempted to do with the tegra. Selling tegra chips at an Enormous Loss. Losing Hundreds of Millions of shareholder's cash each year trying. But Intel Corporation will get it right, and thereby OWN the mobile chip market. Like they do those Intel x86 processors. I think you're kidding yourself if you think Intel is not willing to do it, or that it's not going to happen. It clearly appears that Intel is ready and willing to spend whatever it takes to own mobile computing too.</Msg><Username>valley.part</Username><Timestamp>1353884394906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:59:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353886445791-16</Id><Topic><Title>HTC One X Plus - Back to Nvidia</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1353868174784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:29:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I tend to go away when things look bad, but come back when things look goo. If your Long should be happy for that. Peace</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1353886445791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 18:34:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353888780208-17</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Bay Trailer-T, A Next Generation Mobile SoC (January 2013)</Title><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1353685413211</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 10:43:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What if Intel and Qualcomm teamed-up to make a 64-bit mobile chip? With on-board connectivity, of course. They both have something to contribute, right? And they both could benefit. Intel is unsurpassed in making great CPU's, and now graphics, and those teeny-tiny processed little chips -- all with really great yields. But they don't yet have the modem connectivity part down yet. Qualcomm on the other hand is the undisputed KING of connectivity. THE Absolute King, boys. The whole World pays licensing iTribute to Qualcomm. But Qualcomm could use a little help on the chip-making side of things. They've got no fabs, so they have to wander the streets like a homeless person looking for somebody to make their chips for them. And nobody has the teeny-tiny process technology that Intel has. Nobody. So, what if they teamed-up, and made their mobile chips Together? Intel could design everything except the mobile connectivity part of things. And make the chips too. With the aforementioned really really great yields. And Qualcomm could bring over their blueprints for the ever-changing radio modem end -- 4G LTE, 5G, 6G etc. -- and Intel churns-out the chips which are then sold by both of them. Why, it would be the best of both worlds, right? It sure would be. Sure, they might squabble over what to call it -- whether an Intelcomm or a Qualtel chip -- but it would be the absolute Best mobile technology on the planet. Hey! Maybe they could call it "The Best I-Q Mobile Processor". After the guy that thought of the great idea.</Msg><Username>bests.idea</Username><Timestamp>1353888780208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 19:13:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353892036283-18</Id><Title>NVDA = POS - worst stock in my port........</Title><Msg>Cannot wait to dump to #$%$ stock....................... hope it move up some so I can get the helllll out!!!!!!!!!!! Fri even rimm went up 11% and this POS went up 8 cents???</Msg><Username>longtrader123</Username><Timestamp>1353892036283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:07:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353893788004-19</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA = POS - worst stock in my port........</Title><Username>longtrader123</Username><Timestamp>1353892036283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:07:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>weak...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353893788004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:36:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353894151249-20</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA = POS - worst stock in my port........</Title><Username>longtrader123</Username><Timestamp>1353892036283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:07:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>btw, how many aliases you got ?? You're kinda obvious....</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353894151249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:42:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353895649141-21</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA = POS - worst stock in my port........</Title><Username>longtrader123</Username><Timestamp>1353892036283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:07:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Futures down ! NVDA is going to tank Monday - short the hell out of this Pile Of shiiiittt</Msg><Username>longtrader123</Username><Timestamp>1353895649141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 21:07:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353895847876-22</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA = POS - worst stock in my port........</Title><Username>longtrader123</Username><Timestamp>1353892036283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:07:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your last post said you were holding... but you're a bad actor... Good LUck on your short...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353895847876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 21:10:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353896286710-23</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Bay Trailer-T, A Next Generation Mobile SoC (January 2013)</Title><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1353685413211</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 10:43:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Either Intel takes the profit or someone else does...I think Intel will take it.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1353896286710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 21:18:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>