<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356671159291-1</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fact that clovertrail beats tegra3 by 30-50% in power consumption, says that even at 28nm, the tegra4 won't have a 50% power advantage over 40nm tegra3. tegra3 is a power hog, and tegra4 will be even more so, because of the A15 and 72 core GPU. 28nm doesn't add that much to power savings.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1356671159291</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 00:05:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356671781012-2</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jeepers Best, Did the new nvda shareholders see those stunning and colorful charts from AnandTech BEFORE plunking down $12.00+ for a ten dollar stock? I didn't think so.</Msg><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1356671781012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 00:16:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356673186076-3</Id><Topic><Title>I have doubts tegra4 will be power efficient enough to beat Clovertrail.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1356665581835</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 22:33:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are funny.. love it...</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1356673186076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 00:39:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356676896125-4</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To quote Mr. Anand Lal Shimpi, the Founder of the world-renowned benchmarking firm AnandTech: "Intel's role in the industry has started to change. It worked very closely with Acer on bringing the [probable CES award winning] W510, W700 and S7 tablets to market. With Haswell, Intel will work even closer with its partners - going as far as to specify other, non-Intel components on the motherboard in pursuit of ultimate battery life. The pieces are beginning to fall into place, and if all goes according to Intel's plan we should start to see the fruits of its labor next year. The goal is to bring Core down to very low power levels, and to take Atom even lower. Don't underestimate the significance of Intel's 10W Ivy Bridge announcement. Although desktop and mobile Haswell will appear in mid to late Q2-2013, the exciting ultra mobile parts won't arrive until Q3. Intel's 10W Ivy Bridge will be responsible for at least bringing some more exciting form factors to market between now and then." With the future of Windows RT devices, well, iffy at best, it looks like Intel is on exactly the right track with their super-low energy efficient Atom processors. Build fast, 22nm, highly energy efficient processors -- and conquer the mobile world.</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1356676896125</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 01:41:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356678087114-5</Id><Topic><Title>CES Opening Keynote Address -- Dr. Paul E. Jacobs, Chairman of Qualcomm</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1356618317954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 09:25:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Dr. Paul Jacobs is over in the Gentlemen's Poker Room. Perhaps you would like to try bluffing him into thinking you have some cards?" Ha ha ha ha! Good one, Best.</Msg><Username>good_one_best</Username><Timestamp>1356678087114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 02:01:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356678937465-6</Id><Topic><Title>I have doubts tegra4 will be power efficient enough to beat Clovertrail.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1356665581835</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 22:33:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An AMD fan talking about power efficiency! What a joke! Hey man, when will AMD start to sell a bundle of its chip and a power plant for it? ;-)</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1356678937465</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 02:15:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356679451246-7</Id><Topic><Title>Easy short above 12.20</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1356641311091</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 15:48:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For getanid61 -- pretending not to have seen the article entitled, "'Nvidia: Project Denver Will Not Compete for Micro-Servers". "Nvidia Corp. continues to reveal additional details regarding its highly anticipated project code-named Denver, a general-purpose fully-custom ARMv8 architecture compliant microprocessor core with a “secret sauce”. As it appears, despite all the hype around micro-servers these days, Nvidia will NOT make a special chip for that part of the market and will position Denver for high-performance computing instead. “Right now we are very focused on high-performance computing. Strategy for Denver, which is a fully-custom ARM core…, is to find a way into Tesla applications. It makes a lot of sense on the server side to put it into Tesla so that to have a differentiation on the HPC market. Today we are not looking to attack the general-purpose server market, that market is looking quite crowded... it will be a tough place to be", said Chris Evenden, director of investor relations Nvidia, at Raymond James IT supply chain conference." Looks like Project Denver could not cut it in the the general-purpose server market. So Jen will look for something -- anything -- to use the seven (7) years of R&amp;D wasted on Project Denver, rather than take a horrendous write-off.</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1356679451246</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 02:24:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356686798604-8</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is on a growth path</Title><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1356655922552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 19:52:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is not really into mobile devices but is earning a lot of money selling CPU's to the data centers serving the mobile devices. Nvidia will have a similar experience selling GPU to the cloud and data centers serving VGX and cloud Gaming and cloud HPC computing. Still Tegra will keep selling . Still hard core gamers will still buy discrete GPU's. Hence, Apple laptops are not the deciding factor for the succes of Nvidia imho. With PD Nvidia can compete and even take on Intel down the road regarding selling general-purpose processing power to the data centers. As the world transform Nvidia transforms with it and probably even facilitates the change. Don't forget the Cloud GPU will have a much larger TAM than Nvidia's current TAM. The New 2013 LG televisions come with Onlive Cloud gaming. Onlive is partly powered by Nvidia GPU's, Samsung TV's come with Gaikai (now bought by Sony) and powered by Nvidia GPU's. Oh - why do you think Sony bought Gaikai??? ... /Frank.</Msg><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1356686798604</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 04:26:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356687650195-9</Id><Topic><Title>Random musings about O.Investor`</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1356660653537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:10:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cloud Gaming will be huge down the road for the casual gamers that use consoles today. I have tried it and it works better than expected, but I would not trade it for my hardcore PC. However for the living room with my TV I would have a more relaxed experience and could easily use the TV app for Cloud gaming and have an experience similar to consoles. An analogue example: The convinience of Cloud gaming can be compared to using Netflix. Would you rather go rent a movie in blockbuster or buy a dvd and insert into your DVD player or just stream the film from Netflix?? People are getting still more lasy and choose the path of least resistance. Also Netflix provides a big library of movies (games) so I can easily try out a lot of series. Netflix is not Bluray quality so movie lovers (aka hard core gamers) will still make the extra effort to get the best experience. Besides many games needs to be patches and kept up to date - Cloud gaming takes care of all this for you. Just start the game and play. How convinient. /Frank.</Msg><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1356687650195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 04:40:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356690821902-10</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That just is not true, multiple users across the Web have received their Clovertrail tablets, reported on them and posted user reviews using them ! The driver was also officially certified this quarter. What you are reporting is an erroneous rumor, the only problem is demand is exceeding supply as you would expect from the World's first fully functional and competitive Windows tablet design.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356690821902</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 05:33:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356692781993-11</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC's 28nm HPL (HKMG) process is much better than its bulk 40nm G process. However the A15 is more power hungry than A9, the dual-core 32nm HKMG 1.7 GHz Samsung Chromebook has similar power numbers to this quad-core A9 Surface tablet so it will take some design effort to make a quad-core fit in to the same power envelope but it maybe possible if you are willing to sacrifice some clockspeed.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356692781993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 06:06:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356693830581-12</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'heck even I don't think Nvidia will be so dumb to produce a next-gen product that is not competitive power efficiency wise.' Nvidia has no experience designing competitive cpu solutions so don't mistake inexperience for dumbness. I think Nvidia was planning to keep shrinking Tegra 3 (e.g. 28nm) for its low power mobile efforts and Tegra 4 was supposed to attack the low end PC market. Trouble is Intel's 7-10-13W Ivy Bridge/Haswell will stop that attack in its tracks leaving Tegra 4 as a high end Android tablet solution. Tegra 4 as a design will probably not peak until the 16nm FinFET process because only around then will quad-core A15s have the power efficiency and clock speed headroom to fit well into all mobile form factors. Intel has kind of ruined all these slow ARM roadmaps with their current very competitive 32nm products and even more competitive 22nm products coming in a year's time which will introduce the first Atom micro-architecture redesign (e.g out-of-order processing). Intel is going to improve more quickly than ARM from here as they have a one year design/process cadence as opposed to ARM's 2 year one. This Tick-Tock system was put in place to defeat AMD, which it has done, but will equally serve to defeat ARM in its traditional mobile markets.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356693830581</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 06:23:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356699309965-13</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mars, Nvidia has hundreds of ex Stexar (ex Intel) and Transmeta cpu engineers that have been working away on a cpu for the past years and will start showing itself next year sometime. As Intel gets closer to competitive power efficiency, ARM chips will also advance the performance envelope. The issues that you ignore and gloss over is that Intel chips are more expensive so they can pay for their world class R&amp;D and foundry's. You are very naive If you think that manufactures and developers will suddenly drop ARM that has been the ultra mobile standard since the start, and change over to the bloated x86. Unless Intel reverts back to the anti-competitive illegal activities of the past, they will be relegated to the AMD of the mobile market.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1356699309965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 07:55:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356703455629-14</Id><Title>mellanox stock long strong bullish today</Title><Msg>long strong</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1356703455629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:04:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356703770561-15</Id><Topic><Title>Reversing My Short</Title><Username>barrieguagnano135</Username><Timestamp>1327154677000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-01-21 09:04:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great return</Msg><Username>evangelinesara786</Username><Timestamp>1356703770561</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:09:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356705196854-16</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is on a growth path</Title><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1356655922552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 19:52:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of having a very limited vision and understanding of Nvidia's products and pipeline, frankduxbusborg clearly missed nvidia's important news announcement about Project Denver ABANDONING the general-purpose server market. Here it is. "Nvidia: Project Denver Will Not Compete for Micro-Servers". "Nvidia Corp. continues to reveal additional details regarding its highly anticipated project code-named Denver, a general-purpose fully-custom ARMv8 architecture compliant microprocessor core with a “secret sauce”. As it appears, despite all the hype around micro-servers these days, Nvidia will NOT make a special chip for that part of the market and will position Denver for high-performance computing instead. “Right now we are very focused on high-performance computing. Strategy for Denver, which is a fully-custom ARM core… is to find a way into Tesla applications. It makes a lot of sense on the server side to put it into Tesla so that to have a differentiation on the HPC market. Today we are NOT looking to attack the general-purpose server market, that market is looking quite crowded... it will be a tough place to be", said Chris Evenden, director of investor relations Nvidia, at Raymond James IT supply chain conference." Clearly, Project Denver could not cut it in the the general-purpose server market. "A tough place to be", concedes Chris Evenden, director of investor relations at nvidia. The home-made Project Denver chip was probably too slow, or consumed too much power -- or both -- to compete with today's general-purpose server processor chips from Intel Corporation and AMD. So Jen will look for something -- anything -- to use the seven (7) years of R&amp;D wasted on Project Denver, rather than take a horrendous write-off. "Nvidia: Project Denver Will NOT COMPETE for Micro-Servers". Hope that helps improve your very limited vision and understanding of Nvidia's products and pipeline, frankduxbusborg.</Msg><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1356705196854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:33:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356705301864-17</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'As Intel gets closer to competitive power efficiency, ARM chips will also advance the performance envelope. ' Not as much. A15 is about half the performance of a modern Core processor per clock and their A57 64-bit chip is only about a third improvement over the A15 and still years away so it will fall short of Core processors which are a moving target anyway as there are new ones every year. OTOH Atom is right in the mix power wise and Core processors will be joining in it thin tablets next year due to the 7-13W low power versions coming out. 'they will be relegated to the AMD of the mobile market.' This is the fate that awaits ARM chips as Intel products will clearly be the premium high margin products in the mobile world due to superior everything.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356705301864</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:35:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356705556154-18</Id><Topic><Title>mellanox stock long strong bullish today</Title><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1356703455629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:04:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if anybody still wonders how big is HPC market, take a look at mlnx. mlnx/intel is the infini band equivalent of intel/amd in pc. just take a look at how much sales mlnx has. warning - if you know how much nvda is sinking into Denver to get a slice of the HPC market, better sit down first before you go dig out mlnx's sales. One quarter of Tegra loses is bigger than whole year of mlnx's IB sales into HPC.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1356705556154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:39:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356706406902-19</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is on a growth path</Title><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1356655922552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 19:52:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are talking about things not happening overnight. When Nvidia has successfully attacked and conquered a lot of the HPC market with PD and Tesla they will broaden their focus to more general-purpose data center functions. I am talking 5-10 years in this regard for more general-purpose data center functions..</Msg><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1356706406902</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:53:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356707091276-20</Id><Topic><Title>mellanox stock long strong bullish today</Title><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1356703455629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:04:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more to what nvda will be up against in HPC: intel got their 'AMD' position in IB by buying it off qlgc's hands for $130M. Intention: put the connectivity right inside the CPU silicon ala Atom core. when you are running tens or hundreds of thousands of cores, the connectivity is very important. No, nvda will never be able to buy that connectivity - ain't a third company with the IB IP. nvda just does not have enough IP to integrate into their projects - not for Tegras to attack the absolutely monstrous feature phone market, not for HPC.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1356707091276</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:04:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356707392776-21</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is on a growth path</Title><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1356655922552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 19:52:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Today we are NOT looking to attack the general-purpose server market, that market is looking quite crowded... it will be a tough place to be", said Chris Evenden, director of investor relations Nvidia, at Raymond James IT supply chain conference." "I am talking 5-10 years in this regard for more general-purpose data center functions", writes frankduxbusborg, quite desperately. You sir, are a wild-eyed, dreaming, uninformed nvda bagholder. The home-made Project Denver chip was probably too slow, or consumed too much power -- or both -- to compete with today's general-purpose server processor chips from Intel Corporation and AMD. It's over for that dream about nvidia ever making general-purpose server chips.</Msg><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1356707392776</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:09:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356707788521-22</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA is looking really delicious. Don't miss out on why!</Title><Username>melvinfrazier54</Username><Timestamp>1356699900205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 08:05:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>check up</Msg><Username>erickelley14</Username><Timestamp>1356707788521</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:16:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356708609258-23</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is on a growth path</Title><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1356655922552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 19:52:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The more I read here the more I see it true. "If your not getting your information from Nvidia your getting wrong information". Appreciate you trying to counter the lies from best and the rest. But you've got it right Frank.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1356708609258</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:30:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356709889845-24</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is on a growth path</Title><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1356655922552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 19:52:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Today we are NOT looking to attack the general-purpose server market, that market is looking quite crowded... it will be a tough place to be", said Chris Evenden, director of investor relations Nvidia, at Raymond James IT supply chain conference." "I am talking 5-10 years in this regard for more general-purpose data center functions", writes frankduxbusborg, quite desperately. Still waiting for that "no train to nowhere", right Frank? You know, like years ago when the railroads abandoned a lot of train lines. Yep. They pulled-up the rails, the track metal, the bridges, the switches -- everything. And left only the abandoned train stations. Frank's dream of nvidia someday going into general-purpose server chips is like waiting at the abandoned train station. It's "no train to no where", Frank. Enjoy your nvidia dream.</Msg><Username>best.again</Username><Timestamp>1356709889845</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:51:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356710153818-25</Id><Title>oh look its green</Title><Msg>struggling though to stay above 12.25 I have doubled my short position at 12.27 taking profits on other long position today. Pols will be talking again about fiscal cliff, all a dog and pony show.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1356710153818</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:55:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356710748387-26</Id><Topic><Title>oh look its green</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1356710153818</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>unless for something like the fiscal cliff where the politicians can point at each other, there will be no way for the US to get its finance under control. long term, the US is better going over the cliff - government spendings get under control a little, taxes get raised a little to cover the spendings, military gets cut like it should, people go back to work instead of drawing 2yr no-work pay, taking back jobs that the immigrants fill right now while killing the illegal immigration problem.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1356710748387</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:05:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356711613335-27</Id><Topic><Title>oh look its green</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1356710153818</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh its just the beginning - debt ceiling is coming up, more fun to come. and those who were mocking ryan's medicare plan will only wish they could get a voucher.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1356711613335</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:20:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356712031986-28</Id><Topic><Title>shareholders must check it out!</Title><Username>jeffwatson412</Username><Timestamp>1356471527249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-25 16:38:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks very much !</Msg><Username>petersen.effie</Username><Timestamp>1356712031986</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:27:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356712994095-29</Id><Topic><Title>shareholders must check it out!</Title><Username>jeffwatson412</Username><Timestamp>1356471527249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-25 16:38:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>amazing news</Msg><Username>willardjones927</Username><Timestamp>1356712994095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:43:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356713167810-30</Id><Topic><Title>oh look its green</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1356710153818</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many shares you short now and what's your current cost basis? it's important information you know. tia!</Msg><Username>nvda_4_ever</Username><Timestamp>1356713167810</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:46:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356713931428-31</Id><Topic><Title>oh look its green</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1356710153818</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well... since you asked nicely. I am short 5k at cost basis 12.26 and I have $28k trading profit on Nvidia this year, it was my 4th most profitable stock.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1356713931428</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:58:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356715062390-32</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA is looking really delicious. Don't miss out on why!</Title><Username>melvinfrazier54</Username><Timestamp>1356699900205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 08:05:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>okay dude</Msg><Username>blackjames175</Username><Timestamp>1356715062390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:17:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356715101298-33</Id><Topic><Title>oh look its green</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1356710153818</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well it wasnt that 'nicely' I was kinda mocking you for NOT posting it until asked LOL But I am in a good mood having made money on nvda as I posted real time for all to see. I find this particular point in time a tough one for the quick scalp trade but also understand where your negativity comes from in this market. This should be very interesting. It's too bad we dont have a way to know if folks are telling the truth or not on size but at least you posted so we will see. happy trading both ways!</Msg><Username>nvda_4_ever</Username><Timestamp>1356715101298</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:18:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356717200532-34</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Anandtech is a pro Qualcomm shop" Pro INtel... !!! "But nothing tops Nvidia hatred as semiaccurate." I've heard NVidia marketing can be very arrogant... With Charlie... it's personal...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1356717200532</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:53:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356717817754-35</Id><Topic><Title>Random musings about O.Investor`</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1356660653537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:10:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Frank, did you notice lag when tried cloud gaming ??</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1356717817754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:03:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356719038711-36</Id><Title>Is Nvidia share buyback keeping this up today</Title><Msg>I see the pattern of buying below 12.20 and it tells me that Nvidia may be dipping its toes in share buyback. If so, I think Nvidia will retest 12 later today and once again underperform the market after the buyer steps away. I am using stop-loss around 12.50</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1356719038711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:23:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356719808549-37</Id><Topic><Title>Is Nvidia share buyback keeping this up today</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1356719038711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:23:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're boring. Please, start a blog or a diary, but don't flood this board with the neverending list of your deeds and achievements.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1356719808549</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:36:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356726124199-38</Id><Topic><Title>Random musings about O.Investor`</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1356660653537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:10:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I tried with a racing game and it was very responsive. Lag was not too obbvious. And it was probably not the new Grid I tried but version one.</Msg><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1356726124199</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:22:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356726201344-39</Id><Topic><Title>Random musings about O.Investor`</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1356660653537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:10:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I tried with a racing game and it was very responsive. Lag was not too obbvious. And it was probably not the new Grid I tried but version one." Encouraging to hear...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1356726201344</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:23:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356729876244-40</Id><Title>6th straight red day going into CES</Title><Msg>now that is unusual - I wonder why? also, interestingly Nvidia is not blasting away with PR releases pre-CES. usually its as porous as a sieve when it comes to keeping upcoming launches under wraps. Where is i500 and Wayne and Grey and PD ? Have you guys noticed how Intel is smacking Nvidia around as a poster child for ARM? very concerted effort by Intel. Intel is not going after Qualcomm or, Samsung solutions in the same way. It may be that they have identified the weakest link and are hammering away. Tom's hardware has some details on T3 memory controller (again sort of related to single memory channel but higher clocking) that causes higher power drain under complex activity.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1356729876244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:24:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356737265471-41</Id><Title>One thing is for sure, Tegra4 will be a power hog, worse than tegra3</Title><Msg>Even with 28nm. It will probably have better performance than 5 year old clovertrail, but will lag badly in power.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1356737265471</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:27:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356737777904-42</Id><Topic><Title>One thing is for sure, Tegra4 will be a power hog, worse than tegra3</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1356737265471</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:27:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You a such a worthless punk</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1356737777904</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:36:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356756509837-43</Id><Title>The Grim Reaper has arrived for nvda.</Title><Msg>The Grim Reaper has arrived for nvda. Yes, the Grim Reaper, boys. A tired, elderly, declining old bearded man, dressed in an old dusty robe and carrying a scythe and an hourglass. The veritable symbol of nvidia's entropy. The state of steady deterioration and inevitable demise. Let's take a look at nvda since the Grim Reaper arrived, shall we? $12.65 __ Wednedsay 12/19. The Grim Reaper arrives for nvda. $12.64 __ Thursday 12/20. $12.35 __ Friday 12/21. He may be old, but his scythe is sharp. $12.25 __ Monday 12/24. Volume was 3.184 million for the entire day. The lowest pulse rate for the year 2012. There were no signs of buyers. $12.24 __ Wednesday 12/26. $12.15 __ Thursday 12/27. $12.10 __ Friday 12/28. nvda hits a low of $12.03, on a pathetic 5.515 million shares (-4.35%) gone, boys. In just the six (6) trading days since the Grim Reaper arrived. Did I mention? nvidia's entropy : The state of steady deterioration and inevitable demise. But look at the bright side. Come April 15, 2014, you boys might have a nice long-term capital loss deduction. Well, might. Given Washington's looming Fiscal Cliff, that tax deduction might be gone too.</Msg><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1356756509837</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 23:48:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>