<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-29"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356760921211-1</Id><Title>here is what will happen to Nvda in 2013 - simple logic</Title><Msg>In January, the company will start its stock buybacks thus moving up the price. Intel will be watching very closely, then within a few months, Intc will not be able to stand it any longer. With their newly borrowed $6 billion and their other cash hoard they will buy Nvda and let Nvidia's ceo run the company. So who cares about Nvda's stupid trading noise in a down market right now. We'll get $19 before summer and the idiot shorts trying to make a few pennies can go away getting what they deserve for shorting a company with $4 billion in domestic cash, and no debt.</Msg><Username>dutchref</Username><Timestamp>1356760921211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 01:02:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356761642627-2</Id><Topic><Title>here is what will happen to Nvda in 2013 - simple logic</Title><Username>dutchref</Username><Timestamp>1356760921211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 01:02:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia will give up on the ARM/tegra #$%$, buy ATI from AMD, and focus on high end graphics. In 2014, they'll be bought by some chinese company.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1356761642627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 01:14:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356780941710-3</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmm, as no NVDA investors have really made a strong defense of Tegra 3 here I will do so for the sake of balance. Firstly Windows does not use the fifth helper core. The 40G process is also the performance variant not the low power one and is a bulk silicon process not HKMG. A lot of the performance difference is the 400-500 MHz clock deficiency to Clovertrail (1.3/1.4 to 1.8 GHz). The Tegra 3 has also not peaked yet, it is worth shrinking this design all the way to 20nm as you could get the A9s up to 2 GHz at lower power than the 40nm original and the die size under 30 sq mm which would make it very cheap to profitably build, about $5. The Tegra 3 story has only just begun.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356780941710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 06:35:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356782644795-4</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The low max brightness makes the W510 not ideal for use outdoors" With most of the power going to the screen, how much of these tests have to do with power used by the SOC vs the screen... less brightness translates lower power "The Tegra 3 has also not peaked yet, it is worth shrinking this design all the way to 20nm as you could get the A9s up to 2 GHz at lower power" Grey is still supposed to use A9s...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1356782644795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 07:04:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356791003277-5</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nvda does not have enough IP to integrate T3 into anything other than highest end part. T3 is no longer highest end part. nvda also does not have a fab like samsung who can do fab fills at cost. Hence T3 is eof. Best example of former is samsung, while having its own exynos, is introducing a handful of feature phones using integrated solutions from brcm. you, like pretty much everyone here, have forgotten that the mobile segment is segmented, and that #1, 2 in mobile will never use anything other than their own processors. Atoms, like Tegras, will never go into any high end aapl or samsung products. I will also say the same about intel as nvda - intel does not have enough IP for integrated solutions, which is really the bulk of the mobile market, not the iPads or Nexus 7 that one talks about all the time.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1356791003277</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 09:23:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356791157934-6</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Grey is still supposed to use A9s..." wow, is this guy out of touch or what??? getanid is always good for a laugh.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1356791157934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 09:25:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356793185761-7</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So in summary, the nvidia tegra program is in shambles. ■ nvidia is trying to sell a 5 core chip to a customer that only wants 4 cores. ■ This is a dunder-headed business proposition for both nvidia and Microsoft. ■ So Microsoft will likely soon kick the tegra #3 to the curb. ■ The tegra #3 is being made on yesterday's obsolete 40 nanometer process. ■ Shrinking the tegra to 20 nm would be great, except there is nobody on the planet that can do it -- except for competitor Intel. ■ Intel has no interest in making chips for competitor nvidia. ■ The tegra chip runs too slow at 1.3 GHz, versus 1.8 to 2.0 GHz for the competition. ■ nvidia does not own a fab like Samsung who can do fab fills at cost. ■ Good luck with that. ■ Yes, nvidia needs a brighter paid pumper crew that can play some defense. ■ Like nvidia, their paid pumper crew is also in shambles. ■ nvidia does not have enough IP for integrated solutions. ■ Heck, they can't even take ARM Holding's mail-order blueprints and make a decent, competitive ARM chip. ■ Finally, what little Intellectual Property nvidia did have, Jen sold it all to Intel. ■ Intel is now using nvidia's own IP to bring the El Kabong to nvidia's business lines. Did I mention? nvidia, it's tegra program, and it's paid pumper crew are all in shambles.</Msg><Username>good_point_best</Username><Timestamp>1356793185761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 09:59:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356794562097-8</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Grey is still supposed to use A9s..." wow, is this guy out of touch or what??? getanid is always good for a laugh. ------------------------------------------------------------------- all the on-line info suggests so... maybe if you read it... "wow, is this guy out of touch or what???" 'There will be NO Tegra 4 at CES' -whosunw-</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1356794562097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 10:22:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356796973542-9</Id><Topic><Title>6th straight red day going into CES</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1356729876244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:24:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"PR releases pre-CES. usually its as porous as a sieve when it comes to keeping upcoming launches under wraps" lack of leaks usually means it's still in-house... "Have you guys noticed how Intel is smacking Nvidia around as a poster child for ARM? very concerted effort by Intel. Intel is not going after Qualcomm or, Samsung solutions in the same way. It may be that they have identified the weakest link and are hammering away." ON MIcrosoft tablets, there is NO one else to compare to except Tegra 3... "Tom's hardware has some details on T3 memory controller (again sort of related to single memory channel but higher clocking) that causes higher power drain under complex activity." HIgher clock rates need more voltage, power is a function of the voltage squared...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1356796973542</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:02:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356801694583-10</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of the low hanging performance/power fruit will be picked in the Tegra 3 28nm TSMC HPM/HPL shrink which is happening soon.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356801694583</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:21:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356801878047-11</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail vs Tegra 3 Windows 8/RT power comparison</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356663337074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 21:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>' intel does not have enough IP for integrated solutions, which is really the bulk of the mobile market' Not true, the upcoming Z2580 Clovertrail+ will have LTE etc.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356801878047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:24:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356804119018-12</Id><Topic><Title>here is what will happen to Nvda in 2013 - simple logic</Title><Username>dutchref</Username><Timestamp>1356760921211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 01:02:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not true.</Msg><Username>ksmh228</Username><Timestamp>1356804119018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 13:01:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356808430685-13</Id><Topic><Title>here is what will happen to Nvda in 2013 - simple logic</Title><Username>dutchref</Username><Timestamp>1356760921211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 01:02:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Nvidia ever gets bought, and I'm not saying it will get bought, the share price will be MUCH higher than $19/share. Nvidia would never be sold for anything less than $20/share, more like $30+/share.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1356808430685</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 14:13:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356811318376-14</Id><Topic><Title>here is what will happen to Nvda in 2013 - simple logic</Title><Username>dutchref</Username><Timestamp>1356760921211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 01:02:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if anyone makes a play for Nvidia - it will be Microsoft or, Google. They have to compete with Apple with vertical integration. I think the time to make a deal with Intel is well past. I used to also think Intel but the current trajectory doesn't converge. The more likely scenario is that Nvidia stays independent and keeps acquiring pieces to stay competitive. I think there is a likelihood now that Marvell will be broken up. Nvidia could make a play for some missing wireless pieces (avastar lineup). In this scenario, Nvidia will have to grind it out against Qualcomm and Intel. It will be a tough road and diminishing returns for shareholders. Its quite telling that Nvidia has never consistently produced winners and made money for its customers. zune, kin and quite soon surface may join the line-up of string of failures. I think the greatest success so far is Google Nexus 7 and that was a fortunate accident, right place, right time with the right product and most likely not repeatable. Analyze why TI quit this market. Cutting edge digital semi requires large investments, tremendous risk and fleeting returns. With Apple, Samsung, Qualcomm and Mediatek taking the lions share of mobile SOCs. Nvidia has a very small pie to contend with. Nvidia is at the mercy of Asus, HTC and these are not deep pocketed partners.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1356811318376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 15:01:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356824119220-15</Id><Topic><Title>The Grim Reaper has arrived for nvda.</Title><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1356756509837</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 23:48:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point, Best. About nvidia's entropy. And its state of steady deterioration and inevitable demise. If 2013 looks this grim already for nvidia -- imagine what it'll be like After the CES hype-a-thon is over. And Qualcomm and Intel take home all the CES awards for this and that.</Msg><Username>good_point_best</Username><Timestamp>1356824119220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 18:35:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356833805280-16</Id><Topic><Title>The Grim Reaper has arrived for nvda.</Title><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1356756509837</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 23:48:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Name one productive thing you have accomplished.. and losing all your money in RMBS is not one of them...</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1356833805280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 21:16:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>