<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-25"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351137903082-1</Id><Title>Intel's Paul S. Otellini : "Overall, the best chip has won.”</Title><Msg>"Overall, the best chip has won.” And you boys were thinkin' The Captains of Industry don't religiously read Best each and every day! Ha ha ha ha! Google it : Exclusive: Intel CEO Paul Otellini on Windows 8 AllThingsD</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1351137903082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 00:05:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351138339198-2</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Paul S. Otellini : "Overall, the best chip has won.”</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1351137903082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 00:05:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“We’ve been anxiously awaiting it [the Windows 8 OS],” Otellini said. “I’ve been doing this for a long time, and I haven’t seen this level of excitement and creativity within the joint Intel-Microsoft customer base in a long time.” Otellini isn’t convinced that everyone will shift to tablets. “I happen to believe that the standalone tablet is not the form factor people will (move) to,” Otellini said. “The fact everybody is now fitting tablets with keyboards suggests that real buyers have come to the same conclusion.” Hey, there's a growth Idea. May Jen could try his hand at making Keyboards!</Msg><Username>bestonica</Username><Timestamp>1351138339198</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 00:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351138925497-3</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Paul S. Otellini : "Overall, the best chip has won.”</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1351137903082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 00:05:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The standalone tablet is not the form factor people will move to.” -- Intel's Chief Executive Officer and God of the Valley, Mister Paul S. Otellini So Best? If folks don't like the tablet form factor -- and prefer Intel PC's with those easier-to-use keyboards -- Jen's mobile cloud idea is probably Toast, right?</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1351138925497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 00:22:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351138976449-4</Id><Topic><Title>BEST you still involved in RMBS</Title><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1351112439983</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>also best investor in AMD</Msg><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1351138976449</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 00:22:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351139987084-5</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Paul S. Otellini : "Overall, the best chip has won.”</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1351137903082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 00:05:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The standalone tablet is not the form factor people will move to.” -- Intel's Chief Executive Officer and God of the Valley, Mister Paul S. Otellini "When Prophet Paul approached the camp and saw the touching and this and that, his anger burned and he threw the tablets out of his hands, breaking them to pieces at the foot of Mount Intel."</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1351139987084</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 00:39:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351142688372-6</Id><Topic><Title>Kindly reminder to Jen : It's Ten (10) trading days forward notice.</Title><Username>thanks.best</Username><Timestamp>1351132525789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:35:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The nvidia accounting folks have been Really Really Really touchy about all those SEC public disclosure and reporting requirements and this and that. Ever since nvidia's last brush with the SEC in 2003. Where nvidia, "agreed to entry of an administrative Cease and Desist Order prohibiting any future Violations of certain non-fraud financial reporting, books and records, and internal control provisions of the Federal Securities laws." Here. You can read all about it. From the nvidia Press Release. SANTA CLARA, CA—SEPTEMBER 11, 2003—NVIDIA Corporation (Nasdaq: NVDA), the worldwide leader in visual processing solutions, today announced that the Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”) has concluded its investigation of NVIDIA. The SEC and NVIDIA have reached a final agreement resolving an investigation undertaken by the SEC's staff. That investigation was disclosed by NVIDIA in February 2002. As announced by NVIDIA earlier this year, NVIDIA and the SEC staff had reached an agreement in principle to end the investigation, subject to review and approval by the SEC. Under the final agreement NVIDIA, while neither admitting nor denying any wrongdoing, agreed to entry of an administrative cease and desist order prohibiting any future violations of certain non-fraud financial reporting, books and records, and internal control provisions of the federal securities laws. The order has no impact on NVIDIA’s reported financial results, and no penalty or fine has been assessed against the Company. This order arose out of an inquiry by the SEC regarding certain accounting matters. That inquiry was announced by NVIDIA on February 14, 2002. In accordance with the suggestion and advice of the SEC staff, NVIDIA at that time launched an internal review of the accounting matters. On April 29, 2002, the Company announced that the Audit Committee of its Board of Directors had, with assistance from outside legal counsel and outside forensic auditors, concluded its review and determined that it was appropriate to restate NVIDIA’s financial statements for fiscal 2000, 2001 and the first three quarters of fiscal 2002. NVIDIA cooperated with the SEC throughout this process.</Msg><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1351142688372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 01:24:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351143209966-7</Id><Topic><Title>Kindly reminder to Jen : It's Ten (10) trading days forward notice.</Title><Username>thanks.best</Username><Timestamp>1351132525789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:35:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia "agreed to entry of an administrative Cease and Desist Order prohibiting any future Violations of certain non-fraud financial reporting, books and records, and internal control provisions of the Federal Securities Laws." So Best? That part about, "prohibiting any future Violations." How long does "any future" last? Hummm?</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1351143209966</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 01:33:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351156804659-8</Id><Topic><Title>Intel has no process advantage in mobile, says ARM CEO</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1351090683836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:58:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Globalfoundries intends to have 14nm finfet in volume manufacturing in 2014, the same timescale as Intel has for introducing 14nm finfet manufacturing.' They currently have no 28nm production, no 20nm production yet by 2014 their 14nm finfet on 20nm planes hybrid process will be in full volume ! LOL</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351156804659</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 05:20:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351158375987-9</Id><Topic><Title>Surface vs Clovertrail</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351061796264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:56:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>arstechnicaDOTcom/gadgets/2012/10/now-that-its-here-is-there-a-place-for-windows-rt/ There are a few differences between Windows RT and Windows 8. Some of them are just the usual SKU differences that Microsoft enjoys creating. A lot of enterprise-oriented features are omitted (just as they are from the base Windows 8 SKU). Windows RT can't join a domain, be a Remote Desktop host, or boot from VHDs, for example. It also has a few omissions of its own. In particular, it lacks Windows Media Player and Windows Media Center. Then there are the two major differences. First the big bonus feature: Windows RT comes with four Office 2013 applications. Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and OneNote all ship as an integral part of Windows RT. They're not quite full versions of those applications—they lack macros and certain other extensibility features—but they're very close. These applications run on the desktop, and although Microsoft has attempted to make those applications touch-capable, you'll really want a keyboard and pointing device to use them. And the big missing feature: Windows RT can't run third-party desktop applications. At all. Office is the only desktop application allowed. The only third-party applications allowed on Surface will be Metro-style applications bought from the Windows Store. In this way, Microsoft made the problem I alluded to much worse—developers can't even port their applications to run on ARM. At the same time, however, it also provided a platform for the creation of new, touch-friendly applications. There is one final wrinkle. The Office apps that ship with Windows RT are not licensed for use in any commercial fashion, whether for profit or otherwise. In a practical sense it's hard to see how this would ever be enforced, and it's inevitable that someone somewhere will end up breaking the rules, even if unwittingly. In fact, I daresay it's already happened: I'm sure some of the reviews of the Asus VivoTab RT and Microsoft Surface were written in whole or in part on Word in Windows RT. Commercial organizations wishing to use Windows RT in a BYOD (bring your own device) fashion can still do so, but they must purchase suitable licenses (for example, by switching to one of Office 365's corporate plans) to enable this. This is presuming that they don't need macros or add-ins to do their work. So what about ARM's power advantage? That may still exist, but it's nowhere near as clear-cut as it was two years ago. Back then, Intel had nothing even vaguely comparable to the high-end ARM processors. But today it does, with its Medfield smartphone processor and Clover Trail tablet processor, both sold under its Atom brand. In the time it has taken Microsoft to bring Windows on ARM to market, ARM's once overwhelming battery life advantage has been erased. The ARM CPUs may still have a slight power use edge, but the difference will typically be dwarfed by the power consumption of the screen. The Intel processors, in turn, bring CPU performance that is probably best in class (or close to it), and most importantly of all the ability to run the full version of Windows 8 and existing Windows applications. The hardware could look identical to the user, but if it has Intel inside, the user experience will be quite different. Pricing still isn't known for all the Atom-powered Windows 8 PCs, but indications are that it won't be far off the price of the ARM machines. This all puts Windows RT in a very awkward spot. The downsides I described in 2010 are a reality, making it hard to see what Windows RT devices will do better than comparable Windows 8 ones. Windows RT devices are beholden to the Windows Store, and while that may one day be fully populated, right now it isn't. Windows 8 systems can fill any functional gaps with legacy desktop applications; Windows RT ones can't. Were it not for the licensing oddities, Windows RT devices might be useful as companion devices and in BYOD scenarios. Even if Atom machines cost the same as ARM ones, the presence of a "free" version of Office would give the ARM devices a useful advantage. But the licensing situation essentially eradicates the value of the bundled Office applications. To use them commercially requires a commercial license, and if you're buying a commercial license, you're better off with x86 Office—you get the full application suite (including Outlook), and you get the full set of functionality (including macros). No clear purpose With these constraints and limitations, it's hard to see who exactly Windows RT is for. I acknowledge that there are certainly some users who will be content to use the browser, mail app, and perhaps type the occasional letter in Word or balance their checkbook in Excel: people for whom the Windows Store's current gaps do not matter. But I think a much wider selection of users will be ill-served by Windows RT. While I think it's likely that developers will produce Windows Store apps, I don't know how quickly they will do so, or how well: Google Play, the Android store, is still substantially bereft of high quality tablet applications, even with many millions of devices already in users' hands. Without a thriving store, Windows RT is just too limited to recommend. ARM may end up being a little cheaper than Atom, but Atom ensures that your investment will not be diminished through a lack of software. Even if you're bullish on the Store and believe it will quickly be packed with desirable applications, going the Windows RT route forces a commitment to and a gamble on the Windows Store. Play it safe with Windows 8 instead.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351158375987</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 05:46:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351159914845-10</Id><Topic><Title>Surface vs Clovertrail</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351061796264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:56:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gizmodoDOTcom/5953866/microsoft-surface-rt-review-this-is-technological-heartbreak 'But it's Windows on Surface RT that's the greatest letdown of all, the lethal letdown, because it's not Windows 8, but Windows RT. You can't tell the difference by looking at them, but you certainly will once you use it. Windows RT is underpowered (everything opens and syncs slightly too slowly), under-functional (you cannot install a single app that's not available through the Windows RT app store, which offers a paltry selection), and under-planned (the built-in apps can't feel like Lite versions of something better). You'd be right to note that many of those limitations apply to the iPad as well, but no one could mistake iOS for OS X the way RT apes Windows 8. And even if it's a plight common to tablets, Microsoft—for better or worse—has hyped Surface RT as being so much more. In the end though, this is nothing more than Microsoft's tablet. And a buggy, at times broken one, at that, whose "ecosystem" feels more like a tundra. There's no Twitter or Facebook app, and the most popular 3rd party client breaks often. The Kindle app is completely unusable. There's no image editing software. A People app is supposed to give you all the social media access you'd ever need, but It's impossible to write on someone's Facebook wall through the People app, Surface's social hub; the only workaround is to load Internet Explorer. Blech. Something as simple as loading a video requires a jumbled process of USB importing, dipping in and out of the stripped-down desktop mode, opening a Video app, importing, going back into the Video app, and then playing. What. The app selection, overall, is worse than the already pathetic Windows Phone app fare, looking like the software equivalent to a barren Soviet grocery store. The difference is that Windows Phone, used in quick, informative bursts, skates by on the strength of its excellent with integrated features. At the moment, there's just not that much to do with Microsoft's über-tablet. Surface is weak because Windows RT is weak; a tepid tablet OS pretending to be a computer's. You can do work, yes. But productivity is limited to a "preview" (beta) version of Microsoft Office. It also hurts that Office requires plunging into Windows RT's Desktop mode, where users of actual Windows 8 are able to install a decade's worth of legacy software. Normally, this would compensate. But RT users can't install any of this older software. None of it. Desktop mode is entirely worthless in RT, a cruel tease of non-functionality. It'll only remind you of how much you can't do with your Surface, and is going to confuse the living hell out of most people who buy one—especially when Surface Pro, built on x86 architecture and perfectly compatible with all of those legacy programs, steps in a few months from now. I pity Microsoft's retail staff. Should you buy it? No. The Surface, with an obligatory Touch Cover, is $600. That's a lot of money. Especially given that it's no laptop replacement, no matter how it looks or what Microsoft says. It's a tablet-plus, priced right alongside the iPad and in most ways inferior. That could change. Maybe there will be a new Touch Cover that retains the original's terrific physical qualities while actually allowing good typing. Maybe the quasi-vaporware Surface Pro, which eschews Windows RT in favor of the real-deal Win 8, will make all the difference, opening itself up to the open seas of PC software (for several hundred dollars more). Maybe the app store will look different in a month, or a year, and have anything to offer. Maybe. But remember that Windows Phone—which has swelled from mere hundreds, to tens of thousands, to over a hundred thousand app offerings over the past two years—is still a wasteland compared to iOS and Android. Poor precedent. Maybe Windows RT will be different. Maybe. But those maybes aren't worth putting money on. As much as it looked (and even felt) like it for a bit, the future isn't here quite yet.'</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351159914845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 06:11:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351166296359-11</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA is bad. This is the reason why.</Title><Username>garypogue21</Username><Timestamp>1351094112628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope it contains great info. I just joined. Many thanks</Msg><Username>gonzalezkyle480</Username><Timestamp>1351166296359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 07:58:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351169195656-12</Id><Title>NVDA stockholders ought to sue Goldman Sachs</Title><Msg>for all the years of manipulating this stock, but the attorneys are the ones who always become the winners. A whistle-blower ought to sic the Feds on those crooks!</Msg><Username>audiogenx</Username><Timestamp>1351169195656</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 08:46:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351169999104-13</Id><Topic><Title>Kindly reminder to Jen : It's Ten (10) trading days forward notice.</Title><Username>thanks.best</Username><Timestamp>1351132525789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:35:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"That part about, "prohibiting any future Violations." How long does "any future" last?" Dunno. The SEC definitions of time are, well, a little vague. So we can only hope that "interim" lasts longer than "any future".</Msg><Username>best.replies</Username><Timestamp>1351169999104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 08:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351174062142-14</Id><Title>Bloomberg : Microsoft’s Surface Tablet Lacks Apps to Rival IPad</Title><Msg>Microsoft’s Surface Tablet Lacks Apps to Rival IPad By Dina Bass - Oct 25, 2012 8:38 AM CT. Microsoft Corp. (MSFT) will be constrained in a contest against Apple Inc. (AAPL) in the market for handheld computers by unveiling a tablet that doesn’t work with some of the most widely used downloadable applications. The Surface RT, a tablet that runs the latest version of Microsoft’s flagship operating system and goes on sale tomorrow, won’t feature applications for Facebook Inc. (FB)’s social-networking service or Apple’s iTunes music store. Microsoft packed the new Windows with touch-screen capabilities, gave it a new look and feel and ensured that it’s compatible with some popular apps, including Hulu LLC and Netflix Inc. (NFLX) Still, the company won’t say how many apps are available for the operating system, and the lack of a broad range of games, tools and other downloadable software will detract from the Surface in a head-to-head comparison against the iPad and its plethora of more than 275,000 apps. “Part of me had hoped that we’d see more killer apps,” said Wes Miller, an analyst at Directions on Microsoft in Kirkland, Washington. “Consumers who buy into the platform on Friday -- unless we start seeing an abundance of apps -- are buying into a promissory note that the apps will arrive.” "Buying into a promissory note." We've seen this bad movie before, right?</Msg><Username>in_best_we_trust</Username><Timestamp>1351174062142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:07:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>30</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351175603134-15</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg : Microsoft’s Surface Tablet Lacks Apps to Rival IPad</Title><Username>in_best_we_trust</Username><Timestamp>1351174062142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:07:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The company won’t say how many apps are available for the operating system." So Best? If the number of Surface RT apps at launch is more than 100, it beats the android honeycomb, right? Ha ha ha ha! Take a look : Android 100 honeycomb apps | Obama Pacman</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1351175603134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:33:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351178491650-16</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg : Microsoft’s Surface Tablet Lacks Apps to Rival IPad</Title><Username>in_best_we_trust</Username><Timestamp>1351174062142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:07:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Times being what they are and all, maybe Apple could just re-use the old Powerpoint slides? ------------------------------------------------------------------- 275,000 __ Genuine Apple iOS apps 000,100 __ Surface RT apps (est.) -------------------------------------------------------------------</Msg><Username>best.again</Username><Timestamp>1351178491650</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:21:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351179304361-17</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg : Microsoft’s Surface Tablet Lacks Apps to Rival IPad</Title><Username>in_best_we_trust</Username><Timestamp>1351174062142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:07:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Master? What ever happened to that android honeycomb that had just 100 apps at launch? We don't hear Anything about that honeycomb operating system anymore. Must not have been one of those "killer bees."</Msg><Username>best.clone185</Username><Timestamp>1351179304361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351180424080-18</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA is bad. This is the reason why.</Title><Username>garypogue21</Username><Timestamp>1351094112628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The staff at this newsletter in reality fully grasp how the stock market keeps going.</Msg><Username>raulphillips835</Username><Timestamp>1351180424080</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:53:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351180967039-19</Id><Title>NVDA should be spanked for being in surface</Title><Msg>how dare they get that business.....now we need Jen to make something of it for shreholders and not just for officers and BOD's....</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1351180967039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:02:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351181454579-20</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA should be spanked for being in surface</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1351180967039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude, Emotions have got the best of you... Re-read your own post and look at what you've been reduced to...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351181454579</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:10:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351182496022-21</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg : Microsoft’s Surface Tablet Lacks Apps to Rival IPad</Title><Username>in_best_we_trust</Username><Timestamp>1351174062142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:07:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you think it's a crap-shoot Buying one of those app-lite Surface RT toys, -- where the company won’t even say how few apps are available -- just think of the gamble made by the programmers. They spend months -- yes Months -- of their life, time they'll never get back again, writing and treaking and debugging and cursing obscenities to get their program to run on the Windows RT operating system -- and the fickle Market, she flips her hair back and says, nah, I'll stick with Apple, thanks.</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1351182496022</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:28:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351182890800-22</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA should be spanked for being in surface</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1351180967039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>come on, have a laugh....</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1351182890800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:34:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351183103839-23</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA should be spanked for being in surface</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1351180967039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure... please post something funny... and I will... promise but what you're hoping for won't happen till 2013... maybe even 2014...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351183103839</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:38:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351183212450-24</Id><Title>Break out the Purplesaurus Rex boys, she's up a penny.</Title><Msg>Break out the Purplesaurus Rex boys, she's up a penny. Yes, a whole $00.01 "Just rip 'em and snort 'em, boys." "This doesn't happen every week, you know."</Msg><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1351183212450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:40:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351186076447-25</Id><Topic><Title>Break out the Purplesaurus Rex boys, she's up a penny.</Title><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1351183212450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A penny is $6.2 million in market cap. That's some seriously dough, fool.</Msg><Username>fuzz_head</Username><Timestamp>1351186076447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:27:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351186989913-26</Id><Topic><Title>Break out the Purplesaurus Rex boys, she's up a penny.</Title><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1351183212450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just one year ago today -- October 25, 2012 -- nvidia was where? $14.45 per share. So it's lost how much in exactly one year's worth of Jen's management? $14.45 - $12.18 - ($2.27) Which is How much market capitalization, gone? ($2.27) x 619,480,000 shs = ($1,406,219,600) market cap -- Gone from the planet. Minus One Billion, Four Hundred Six Million U.S. Dollars. That's some Seriously dough. You fuzzy-headed Fool.</Msg><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1351186989913</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:43:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351187640147-27</Id><Topic><Title>Break out the Purplesaurus Rex boys, she's up a penny.</Title><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1351183212450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical day in nvda pumperland. The lads are celebrating the pennies. While Best is keeping an eye an the amounts so large they'll crash the Fed's wire transfer system.</Msg><Username>everyday_best</Username><Timestamp>1351187640147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351188248864-28</Id><Title>CC announced without warning. How big the beat?</Title><Msg>It's not rocket science girls! Here comes the beat and raise. Short at your own risk. Stupid is as stupid does.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1351188248864</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351188615359-29</Id><Topic><Title>CC announced without warning. How big the beat?</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1351188248864</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jen gave an abbreviated nine (9) trading days notice this time, right? Which is still Plenty of Time to do his "pre-earnings confessional." Remember the quarter he chopped his forward guidance like what, three (3) days before the scheduled nvidia earnings date? Plenty of Time, boys.</Msg><Username>best.warning</Username><Timestamp>1351188615359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351189342313-30</Id><Topic><Title>Break out the Purplesaurus Rex boys, she's up a penny.</Title><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1351183212450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Just one year ago today -- October 25, 2011 -- nvidia was where? $14.45 per share. So it's lost how much in exactly one year's worth of Jen's management? $14.45 - $12.18 = ($2.27) Which is How much market capitalization, gone? ($2.27) x 619,480,000 shs = ($1,406,219,600) market cap -- Gone from the planet. Minus One Billion, Four Hundred Six Million U.S. Dollars. That's some Seriously dough." Well, All of that ($1,406,219,600) of nvda market cap didn't disappear, right? A bunch of it went to the astute shorts. Forklift loads actually. Isn't that right, Best? Beep! Beep! Beep! Beep!</Msg><Username>barjonicats</Username><Timestamp>1351189342313</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:22:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351190617135-31</Id><Title>bought a little</Title><Msg>I like these guyses numbers. Great balance sheet, excellent PE ratio if you back out cash on the balance sheet, and good projected business performance going forward. If they stumble, I'll be buying more.</Msg><Username>bot_feeder</Username><Timestamp>1351190617135</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:43:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351191344635-32</Id><Topic><Title>Review of ASUS vivoTab RT tablet</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1351183240818</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only a #$%$ would "thumb down" such a nice find! Thank you!</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1351191344635</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:55:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351191500580-33</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC Q3 earnings hit record high</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1351187460789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:51:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, that definitely bodes well for nvda. The average analyst estimate is 30 cents, this stock is so far undervalued it's ridiculous.</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1351191500580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:58:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351192088379-34</Id><Topic><Title>CC announced without warning. How big the beat?</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1351188248864</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess 'o.investor' is still hoping for a warning before earnings despite the announced CC . . or he just doesn't want to admit he was wrong . .</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1351192088379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:08:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351193051568-35</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC Q3 earnings hit record high</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1351187460789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:51:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>holy smoke. TSMC earning record high submarine first to Surface</Msg><Username>sbcballpark</Username><Timestamp>1351193051568</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:24:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351198062895-36</Id><Topic><Title>Break out the Purplesaurus Rex boys, she's up a penny.</Title><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1351183212450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Just one year ago today -- October 25, 2011 -- nvidia was where? $14.45 per share. So it's lost how much in exactly one year? $14.45 - $12.18 = ($2.27) Which is How much market capitalization, gone? ($2.27) x 619,480,000 shs = ($1,406,219,600) market cap -- Gone. Minus One Billion, Four Hundred Six Million U.S. Dollars. That's some Seriously dough. Well, All of that ($1,406,219,600) of nvda market cap didn't disappear, right? A bunch of it went to the astute shorts. Forklift loads actually. Isn't that right, Best? Beep! Beep! Beep! Beep! Beep!" Don't bother me now, boys I'm clearing out the mezzanine level and stacking the pallets of cash higher towards the rafters. Jen's 3Q confessional is November 8th, don't u know. And I've gotta make room for all that incoming cash. See ya later, boys. Beep! Beep! Beep! Beep! Beep!</Msg><Username>best.short</Username><Timestamp>1351198062895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 16:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351198801453-37</Id><Topic><Title>Apple sold 14 million ipads in Q3 (WS expected 17-18 million units), 16.9 million iphone, 5 million imacs</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1351198096624</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 16:48:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many astute shoppers held off buying the Genuine Apple iPad to see what the brand-new Genuine Apple iPad Mini looks like. All 24 models. And with the Genuine iPad Mini launched, the delighted iShoppers can make their final decision on which model of the growing iPad Family most exquisitely meets their needs. And the Apple people -- in those 500 conveniently located Apple Stores -- can politely ring up their delighted iShoppers's orders. And Apple's revenues will resume their skyrocketing performance.</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1351198801453</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:00:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351199810563-38</Id><Topic><Title>Break out the Purplesaurus Rex boys, she's up a penny.</Title><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1351183212450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your apple's now down 100 bucks from recent highs... howzat?:)</Msg><Username>daysofshred30000000000</Username><Timestamp>1351199810563</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:16:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351199999105-39</Id><Topic><Title>Break out the Purplesaurus Rex boys, she's up a penny.</Title><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1351183212450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So apple lost 100 billion in market cap this year. How much "dough" is that? And the fun as just started.</Msg><Username>daysofshred30000000000</Username><Timestamp>1351199999105</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:19:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351201394123-40</Id><Title>Microsoft's Steve Ballmer has plans for more hardware</Title><Msg>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-20072497</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1351201394123</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:43:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351201915955-41</Id><Topic><Title>Break out the Purplesaurus Rex boys, she's up a penny.</Title><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1351183212450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is entirely natural that Apple's share price has backed-off a bit. Entirely natural. Since Apple declared that $10.60 per share dividend. Yes boys, $10.60 per share. Which, times 937.4 million Apple shares outstanding, equals $9,936,546,000.00 of cash to be distributed to those lucky Apple shareholders this year. Call it a cool Ten Billion Dollars, shall we? U.S. Dollars, cash in-the-mailbox. So, how much cash will Jen distribute this year to his starving nvidia shareholders? Hummm?</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1351201915955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:51:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351207041488-42</Id><Topic><Title>Surface vs Clovertrail</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351061796264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:56:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmm, I believe that review is flawed. He is assuming that the processor clock rate remains fixed, and that 50% CPU utilization is a bad thing. Modern power management controls power and clock rate to the individual cores. Perfect power management would drop the clock rate, allowing a lower operating voltage, so that the CPU is 100% busy. But since it takes a bit of time to raise the voltage, thus delaying increasing the clock rate, a good strategy is setting the clock and voltage so that the active cores are about 50% utilized. So a reported value of 50% means a CPU core is being used, not that the application is using 50% of the machine's capability. You might argue that it's therefore a pointless number to report. I would only weakly protest. This actually points to a bigger issue: the x86 is at a disadvantage in the power-sensitive market. Because of the PC legacy, it presents a simple management model to the OS. ARM systems grew up in the power-sensitive embedded world, and expose many more, and more complex, options to the OS. It's a major PITA for the OS people, taking years of development and tuning to do a good job, but the potential for power efficiency might make it worthwhile.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1351207041488</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351212515894-43</Id><Topic><Title>Surface vs Clovertrail</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351061796264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:56:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" "50% utilization of cpu" was probably a software issue, not hardware." for typing in MS WORD... GEESH !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351212515894</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:48:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351221608301-44</Id><Topic><Title>interesting tidbits about NVIDDIA/MSFT collaboration on Win 8 RT and Surface RT</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1351186620136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:37:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep. They better zip the mouth on Wayne until CES 2013.</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1351221608301</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 23:20:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351223938072-45</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Pop-up Store Pops up in Times Square, New York City</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1351195006794</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:56:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only a tablet with SoC Tegra 3 deserves this kind of nation-wide pop-up stores with a commercial blitz. Kindle Fires has stinky cheap guts and should be tossed out.</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1351223938072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 23:58:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>