<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-09"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347163591740-1</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese iPhone 5 knockoff uses Tegra 3</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1347088898147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 03:21:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. It appears that nvidia has demonstrated to the world what an ethically bankrupt place it really is. Again. Selling tegras to power an illegal Chinese knock-off of the Genuine iPhone 5 -- based on leaked photos of the iPhone 5. nvidia is taking on dispicable business partnere here. .</Msg><Username>best.short</Username><Timestamp>1347163591740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 00:06:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347169313207-2</Id><Title>NVDA coud be down to mid 12 this week</Title><Msg>Doesn't look good for NVDA .... Weak PC market Amazon's use of other chips Apple's future new releases, iphone 5 and 7" ipad Option expiry Samsung's loss to Apple ....</Msg><Username>nitavviev</Username><Timestamp>1347169313207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 01:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347170403223-3</Id><Title>Why kindle will lose to nexus 7 by a wide margin</Title><Msg>Kindle HD is sloppy. Bezos has made a mistake to go with a dual core. Most importantly, you can download amazon app on a Nexus 7 but not the other way round! Hence u can enjoy amazon benefits on nexus but not Google's benefits on kindle. The maths is simple. Who buys kindle? Only the hardcore readers should. As kindle screen is more suitable for reading. But how many gamers and casual readers vs hardcore readers? I guess there are more former ;)</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347170403223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 02:00:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347171172812-4</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese iPhone 5 knockoff uses Tegra 3</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1347088898147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 03:21:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>douchiness cemented</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1347171172812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 02:12:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347192871035-5</Id><Title>Monday's NVDA will stay in between 13.3~13.8</Title><Msg>most probably</Msg><Username>spacerunning</Username><Timestamp>1347192871035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 08:14:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347193874644-6</Id><Title>To the fools who says nvdia is crashing, take note. Valuation Matters</Title><Msg>Nvidia will earn at least $1 a share this year. Excluding $5 cash, at $13 = PE 8, at $18 = PE 13 ! Such valuation is at its lower end of historical valuation matrix. Hence nvidia ain't crashing. Market is pricing it at end of world scenario. Any upside surprise will shoot it up fast. It makes lots of cash from Kepler. With tsmc supply problems ending, nvidia future quarters will show good profit growth as yields improve. Valuation matters folks. Conversely, Facebook was touted as a must own stock. But its valuation is a big joke. Price to sales was 100 times, PE was worst. Hence FB crashed ! Nvidia already crashed from $36 to now $13, it ain't crashing anymore. Only way is up. Short term may drop to shake weak holders. But bigger picture still up. Qn is how high? My bet is min $20 by first quarter next year. Best case? $42 or $36! Why? 1. In the past, it rally 3x past its bottom during a bull market. It's 52 week low is $11.5. Three times is around $36. 2. Nvidia is due to update its project Denver during year end, I expect it to #$%$ its way. Nvidia loves to #$%$ cos they are marketing guys. But its exorbitant valuation happens during their #$%$. Hence remember to sell then. Cos its gonna crash back down when that happens. Lol.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347193874644</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 08:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347201999459-7</Id><Topic><Title>MUST READ: Computerworld on Kindle Fire HD - caveats behind PR and Bezos presentation</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347149105822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:05:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUMP BUMP</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347201999459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 10:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347205673755-8</Id><Title>Whaaaaat!? "Jim Cramer's Best Blogs"</Title><Msg>. Google this, boys: Jim Cramer's Best Blogs The iPhone 5 Still the De Facto Winner By Jim Cramer 09/08/12 - 11:56 AM EDT . Can you believe it? "Cramer's Best Blogs"? What and absolute and total friggin' rip-off of Best's concept. First, this bald talking-head guy Cramer captures the television market. And now has decided to Try to horn-in on Best's blogging hobby? No doubt a result of Mr. Baldy watching Best take a sleepy little Yahoo MB and convert it into the #1 Most Popular Board on Yahoo's entire global venue. The guy is clearly desperate to stem the tide on his plunging TV rating points. "Why I oughta...." Hey! Maybe Best should go post a few choice messages on Cramer's cheap, swarthy, knock-off "Best" blog. A little "viewer feedback", don't u know. Booyah! .</Msg><Username>bestnhighest.wins</Username><Timestamp>1347205673755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 11:47:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347206461487-9</Id><Title>TSMC July sales: 37% increase y/y, 11.7% m/m</Title><Msg>Q3 will see a further increase of 6-8%, another new record. No doubt, contributing to the surge of TSMC shippings are (but not limited to): **Tegra 3 (Nexus 7 in particular) **Kepler parts **QC Snapdragon S4 Also reflecting the fact that TSMC is catching up with its huge backlog.</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347206461487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:01:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347206791959-10</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC July sales: 37% increase y/y, 11.7% m/m</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347206461487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:01:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Probably all those thousands of test wafers for Apple's A6. They said they wanted to prove both the yield and the quality before signing-up. Right boys? .</Msg><Username>bestnhighest.wins</Username><Timestamp>1347206791959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:06:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347206990370-11</Id><Topic><Title>Why kindle will lose to nexus 7 by a wide margin</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347170403223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 02:00:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of the books available on Amazon models are also available via Google Play. Content-wise, Android uses have access to an equally large content base, if not larger (per many web pundits) Besides, the size of truly hard-core readers is shrinking while size of game players (including casual game players such as students and the entire younger set) is increasing very fast.</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347206990370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:09:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347207179460-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why kindle will lose to nexus 7 by a wide margin</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347170403223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 02:00:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In my view, Tegra 3 would have been overkill for a utility tablet like Kindle Fire 2 HD. Why would you need a quad-core for day-to-day functions such as book-reading, watching movies, email, web-browsing, and etc? Obviously, Amazon would be targeting the largest demographic. As noted in CNN article, the gaming industry as a whole has been steadily declining for the past few years and most gamers would still prefer console such as Xbox, PlayStation, Nintendo, etc over PC or tablet, in addition to the lack of games that are being developed for the PC/tablet market is also another concern. [A decade ago the PC was the system of choice for many video gamers who wanted the best graphics, the most cutting-edge gaming experience and the ability to play with friends online. Before the arrival of the Xbox from Microsoft and the PlayStation from Sony, the PC was the dominant system for multiplayer action-based games. Times changed. And as traditional gaming companies expanded their reach with new products from Nintendo's family friendly Wii to Microsoft's Kinect motion controller, the PC was relegated to a niche mainly for the hardcore.</Msg><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1347207179460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347207380643-13</Id><Topic><Title>Why kindle will lose to nexus 7 by a wide margin</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347170403223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 02:00:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>contd ... [While the top-selling games are now dominated by multi platform titles available for the consoles and PC, the shift has been increasingly away from the PC completely. It also spawned an industry of PC makers that responded by creating systems capable of meeting the demands of the latest games. But with the arrival of the Xbox 360 and PS3 in 2005 and 2006 respectively, and the greater availability of HDTV and broadband in most U.S. homes the PC gaming market declined.] -cnnMoney</Msg><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1347207380643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:16:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347207427196-14</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC July sales: 37% increase y/y, 11.7% m/m</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347206461487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:01:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Apple's first-ever order with TSMC is no doubt the Largest Semiconductor Order in the History of Mankind. And no, they're not going to base it on a piddly 50 test wafers or so. Oh no no no. Not Apple -- thousands of test wafers boys -- Thousands. Heck, just Apple's test wafers might have already cut into chip production shipped to nvidia. .</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1347207427196</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:17:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347210046585-15</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC July sales: 37% increase y/y, 11.7% m/m</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347206461487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:01:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this was well discussed/researched in a previous thread: NOT nvda, especially for Kepler, that is just trading AMD wafers. Increase due to iPhone launch: QCOM, not S4, but cheap radios, BRCM, and espeiclly cirus logic. BRCM and cirus logic have forcasted banner 2H due to aapl launches. BRCM has been making noises for about a year now, saying now that they have a foothold in the mobile market, and they don't mean the losing your shirt kind, they will be coming out with product for the high end soc market as well. We should be seeing some product announcements from them soon. Where's Wayne??? That chip is so late, meaning nvda will not have early design in advantage like they had with T3. As for Gray, I said when they announced that chip that by the time it comes out, it would be way obsolete and I still go with that, especially now that everything at nvda is delayed by over a year. Denver, Denver is s total joke, everybody else would have 64bit ARM too. This whole Tegra program is a run away wreck, the breakeven is rising faster than sales and the loses are multiplying. Market is high now and nvda is nowhere. Wait till market corrects.....</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1347210046585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:00:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347210138964-16</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC July sales: 37% increase y/y, 11.7% m/m</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347206461487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:01:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>btw, tsmc already forecasted inventory correction at their customers comes Q4.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1347210138964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:02:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347210241235-17</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese iPhone 5 knockoff uses Tegra 3</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1347088898147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 03:21:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Just as Apple is now moving their A6 chip production out of Korea and into Taiwan, Apple should mention to the Chinese politburos that they don't have to assemble their iStuff in China. And provide jobs for thousands upon thousands of high-tech workers there. Oh no no no. "Fix your crapola Chinese patent system, or we're outta here." And Apple's got the iClout to do it, right boys? You bet they do. .</Msg><Username>seeking.best</Username><Timestamp>1347210241235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:04:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347210691606-18</Id><Topic><Title>Why kindle will lose to nexus 7 by a wide margin</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347170403223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 02:00:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. I look at my gamer friends, they are all on PCs eg. 6 cores massively overclocked i7 etc. 2. never enough cpu horsepower. when I go from my Xenon desktop or i5 laptop to my overclocked i7, web surfing is so much more satisfying. 3. one last point about the Kindle. It looks cheap. In the world of fashion and design and solidly built Nexus and iPads, I am afraid the more expensive Kindles will go nowhere. I had a chance to play with the Nexus, very impressive build. Likewise for the iPads, the Galaxy looked like nothing next to an iPad. if Ballmer comes out with his nice looking winRT at $300 to $350, it will sell like hotcakes. Goog hit a homerun. amzn hit head fake, now we'll see what aapl and Ballmer do.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1347210691606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:11:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347211210325-19</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese iPhone 5 knockoff uses Tegra 3</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1347088898147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 03:21:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Well that, and this is an election year. A modest campaign contribution by Apple, and we'll have a full-bown Senate Investigation into the crapola Chinese patent system. "Protecting American Jobs" don't u know. .</Msg><Username>good_point_best</Username><Timestamp>1347211210325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:20:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347212453025-20</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese iPhone 5 knockoff uses Tegra 3</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1347088898147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 03:21:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Jeepers Best, Just wait until Apple hears about this. Jen deliberately selling tegras to power that "Goophone I5." A clearly illegal Chinese knock-off of the Genuine iPhone 5 -- based on leaked photos of the iPhone 5. Maybe it's high time for Apple to take a look and refresh those few aging Apple MacBook and Air models that still use nvidia legacy parts? Hummm? .</Msg><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1347212453025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:40:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347213352915-21</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese iPhone 5 knockoff uses Tegra 3</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1347088898147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 03:21:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. That would be hysterically funny. Jen "wins" the Goophone I5 -- an illegal Chinese knock-off copy of the Genuine Apple iPhone 5 -- and then loses pizzed-off Apple as a customer. Completely. . 笑笑笑笑笑! Ha ha ha ha ha! .</Msg><Username>frankenbest</Username><Timestamp>1347213352915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:55:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347217594157-22</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA coud be down to mid 12 this week</Title><Username>nitavviev</Username><Timestamp>1347169313207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 01:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was thinking the same thing, It's going to tank 5% Monday morning...because I bought more....it will do that, I should short every stock I buy from now on...I can't afford to buy more...I don't see NVDA ever touching 14 or 15 for the rest of my life.</Msg><Username>stocktrader4444</Username><Timestamp>1347217594157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347217737695-23</Id><Title>Apple had to pay huge sums to a Chinese co. for copyright infringement on "ipad"</Title><Msg>and delayed product launch for months. This is no joke, Apple has no territorial advantages in China - unlike the Apple vs Samsung litigations. Expect Chinese courts to issue injunctions against iphone 5 as the Goophone 15 is already patented, in design as well as some engineering aspects. Stop stealing Tim Cook! Retribution at its best! My turn to Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347217737695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347218540383-24</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA coud be down to mid 12 this week</Title><Username>nitavviev</Username><Timestamp>1347169313207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 01:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get your popcorns ready, it's gonna be a great show! GooPhone 15 maker sues Apple for iphone 5 patent infringement, and requests injunction in China.... Love it!</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1347218540383</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:22:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347218575545-25</Id><Topic><Title>Apple had to pay huge sums to a Chinese co. for copyright infringement on "ipad"</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347217737695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. I presume you saw that Both candidates for the President of the United States, -- Barack Hussein Obama II and that other Mormon guy -- both mentioned Steve Jobs' inventions and Apple's priceless contributions to America. Yep. Right there in their keynote speeches. The audience clapped wildly too. We'd hate to see the United States of America join Apple, right? And go thermonuclear on that crapola Chinese patent system. Along with the swarthty little companies -- like nvidia -- that aid and abet the patent theives. .</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1347218575545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:22:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347219090763-26</Id><Topic><Title>Apple had to pay huge sums to a Chinese co. for copyright infringement on "ipad"</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347217737695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. What's that? You missed the video of Both candidates for the President of the United States, -- Barack Hussein Obama II and that other Mormon guy -- praising the accomplishments of Great American Steve Jobs and Apple? Google this: Topeka's White: IPhone 5 to Be Biggest Upgrade Ever .</Msg><Username>best.again</Username><Timestamp>1347219090763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:31:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347219327657-27</Id><Topic><Title>Apple had to pay huge sums to a Chinese co. for copyright infringement on "ipad"</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347217737695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Thanks Best, For posting how the readers here can witness that epic video. Of Both candidates for the President of the United States, praising the accomplishments of Steve Jobs and Apple. Epic. Truly epic video. Thanks again, Best. .</Msg><Username>thanks.best</Username><Timestamp>1347219327657</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:35:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347219442327-28</Id><Title>NBC news also says the Kindle Fire HD is "sluggish" - lagging at odd moments</Title><Msg>Amazon seems to have gotten the body right. What about the guts, though? Those might be a mixed bag. Perhaps our expectations were too high or perhaps we'd been spoiled by the Nexus 7 and iPad, but the Kindle Fire HD seemed downright sluggish at times, lagging at odd moments. WAIT..... How can you stream movies effectively if the processor is sluggish? Source of information: NBCNews/GadgetBox: hands on with the new Kindle Fire HD</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1347219442327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:37:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347222723773-29</Id><Title>So why aren't shorts invited to the Annual Meeting?</Title><Msg>. So why aren't shorts invited to the nvidia Annual Meeting? Hummm? The shorts are probably Jen's best source of future stock buyers. Someday. Yet he excludes them from his Annual Meeting. Shorts have the right to hear whatever hype follows the reading of, "these forward-looking statements are not guarantees of future performance and speak only as of the date hereof. NVIDIA disclaims any obligation to update these forward-looking statements to reflect reality or future events or circumstances." . You know why I think Jen excludes the shorts from the Annual Meeting? To avoid having one of the shorts strike-up a conversation over coffee with like Jen's third (3rd) biggest shareholder. Perhaps regarding the lack of ethics in nvidia selling tegras for that illegal Chinese knock-off Goophone I5. So Jen thinks it's best and safest to exclude 'em. - .</Msg><Username>good_point_best</Username><Timestamp>1347222723773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:32:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347226014778-30</Id><Topic><Title>NBC news also says the Kindle Fire HD is "sluggish" - lagging at odd moments</Title><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1347219442327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:37:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Give it up, boys. The nvidia tegra #3 lost. And lost Badly. To the superior Texas Instruments OMAP 44-series SoC family of processors. For the reasons Amazon clearly stated in their Kindle press release. Give it up, boys. While you pumper boys where cheering about that "all but certain win" for tegra 3, consumate mobile chip designer TI waltzed-in, and took nvidia's Thanksgiving dinner right off your table. Maybe go sit by the Fire? And enjoy reading on that Texas Instruments-powered Amazon iReader. . .</Msg><Username>bestonica</Username><Timestamp>1347226014778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 17:26:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347226099289-31</Id><Topic><Title>So why aren't shorts invited to the Annual Meeting?</Title><Username>good_point_best</Username><Timestamp>1347222723773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:32:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget to hit enter after each word! You, multi-alias #$%$</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1347226099289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 17:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347226136951-32</Id><Topic><Title>So why aren't shorts invited to the Annual Meeting?</Title><Username>good_point_best</Username><Timestamp>1347222723773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:32:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only a simpleton would make an issue of a safe harbor statement.</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1347226136951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 17:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347226651299-33</Id><Topic><Title>Why kindle will lose to nexus 7 by a wide margin</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347170403223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 02:00:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like The K2 may not be able to back up Bezos claims and the poor user experience would be obvious. Top that up with the closed eco system of the K2 - most remotely knowledgeable buyers would move on to the N7 - "you can do everything the K2 can do and more and faster" for $25 to $50 more - it's future proof. The K2 is beginning to sound like a cheapo Archos Android system - Apple folks would have the last laugh - Nvidia folks would have to bite their nails in disbelief "why is Bezos so dumb"! Good Job Bezos - the PR and the Slides can't back up the mediocrity of the K2s - sad - it can't even keep the performance halo before the lights went off at the roll out ceremony.</Msg><Username>n20lte</Username><Timestamp>1347226651299</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 17:37:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347227658491-34</Id><Topic><Title>Why kindle will lose to nexus 7 by a wide margin</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347170403223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 02:00:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Bezos didn't care about performance - why would he had even bothered to compare the performance of the Omaps to the Tegra3 and make himself look extremely foolish! His foolishness had been confirmed by multiple independent observers that the K2s are indeed "laggish" - now that is extremely sad for any new device coming into the market today - it's totally unacceptable to have a "Laggish" device today - ok for the 1st gen where there is no choice for a good performance CPU - today there are many that would have eliminated the laggish performance of basic tasks. If it's Laggish performing BASIC tasks that would be extremely irritable to ALL users. What happens when a user performs multiple tasks simultaneously??? Looks like the user will have to tweedle his thumbs proportionately or exponentially longer with the number of tasks running simultaneously. Gone are the days where users are expected and confined to running one or two tasks at a time. When a tablet performs very well in a game environment - it generally performs even better in a non game environment - that's the benefit of a "GAME OPTIMIZED" machine - MACBOOK Pros have the most powerful Nvidia NB GPUs inside - I don't know of any Macbook Pro users who are gamers! However it allows the user to perform a multitude of tasks singly or simultaneously - simple as well as complex ones to perform fluidly by keeping up and offloading complex operations from the CPUs.</Msg><Username>n20lte</Username><Timestamp>1347227658491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 17:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347230250370-35</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA coud be down to mid 12 this week</Title><Username>nitavviev</Username><Timestamp>1347169313207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 01:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Market may drop this week after it reached multi year high.</Msg><Username>soranicvij</Username><Timestamp>1347230250370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 18:37:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347236655890-36</Id><Topic><Title>Bezos retreated - now charging $15 more for FK2 buyers who opt out of ads</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347229148868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 18:19:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just watch, he will have to retreat from that one too - it will come 'unlocked' for free. But will not matter, he will be branded, rightfully, as somebody to keep a very close eye on cause he will nickel and dime you behind your back while you are not looking.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1347236655890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 20:24:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347244238226-37</Id><Title>Predictions for Monday?</Title><Msg>I say open at 13.10 , down to 12.25, then close at 12.60....god I hope I'm wrong....jesus, god I hope I'm wrong, LOL</Msg><Username>stocktrader4444</Username><Timestamp>1347244238226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 22:30:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347246208871-38</Id><Topic><Title>Kindle Fire HDs: a roundup of early impressions, specs and reviews///</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347231518941</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 18:58:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Garbage, good, that makes me feel better, I wouldn't buy it, but glad to hear, they should have gone with NVDA</Msg><Username>stocktrader4444</Username><Timestamp>1347246208871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 23:03:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347246260517-39</Id><Title>Prediction for Monday: Hight 13.25 Low 12.95 Close 13.10</Title><Msg>Open? Just a prediction.</Msg><Username>nitavviev</Username><Timestamp>1347246260517</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 23:04:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>