<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347077333821-1</Id><Topic><Title>i predict a close if 13.78, based on max frustration theory</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347027243461</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 10:14:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lol, looks like my revised max remote close was spot on ! Great close. Next week look for a super long white candle!</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347077333821</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:08:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347077772755-2</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia slides after downgrade and Intel guidance</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1347050228612</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 16:37:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cloud computing needs lots of processing power and they will need to upgrade over time as well, at least until people somehow fail to make use of ever increasing processing power. Or if they hit an absolute limit on the technology. (something like not being able to shrink past the atomic level + Design issues) Then there could be trouble on margins at that point. A processor is needed for each device that is receiving/sending data. Like phones and tablets. How often do people swap to a new phone or tablet. Its quite a bit more than PCs right? I don't see Nvidia or Intel going anywhere unless ARM manages to kill Intel somehow. Which I highly doubt since Intel can always make one of their own or buy some company. Or a major new tech comes out that kills semi's.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1347077772755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:16:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347082569646-3</Id><Topic><Title>htc one x+ specs: tegra3?</Title><Username>inthemoney69</Username><Timestamp>1347046698046</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 15:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the final version model (production model). HTC One X specs: General: 2G Network GSM 850 / 900 / 1800 / 1900 3G Network: HSDPA 850 / 900 / 1900 / 2100 Announced: 2012, February Status: Available. Released 2012, May Features: OS Android OS, v4.0 (Ice Cream Sandwich), upgradable to v4.1 Chipset: Nvidia Tegra 3 CPU: Quad-core 1.5 GHz GPU: ULP GeForce Clearly, the HTC One X smartphone is targeting T-Mobile USA. If you look at the HTC One X specs you can see that it supports GSM (2G), HSDPA (3G) but not 4G. The reason why HTC One X is not supporting LTE is because T-Mobile currently does not have LTE (4G) network running and it will only be available in late 2013. T-Mobile mainly uses GSM (2G) network on 900 MHz band in Europe and in U.S. T-Mobile runs GSM on 1900 MHz band. For HSPDA (3G), T-Mobile runs on 1700 MHz and 2100 MHz bands.</Msg><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1347082569646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 01:36:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347084304576-4</Id><Topic><Title>htc one x+ specs: tegra3?</Title><Username>inthemoney69</Username><Timestamp>1347046698046</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 15:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are talking about HTC One X+ here, not HTC One X - the One X is almost one year old, and One X+ is still in the pipeline. You don't know what you are talking about, bud</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1347084304576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 02:05:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347088390285-5</Id><Topic><Title>Three horsemen hit new highs - Apple, Amazon, Google</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347051196134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 16:53:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. I think nvidia longs should be invited to the party too. As Jen always says -- the ability to celebrate failure is an important part of nvidia's culture. And no, Best doesn't make this stuff up. Check it out for yourself. A New York Times interview with Dear Leader. . Google this: I’m Prepared for Adversity. I Waited Tables. . Ya gotta love that little company history part, right? "When Nvidia was founded, we were the first company of our kind, but we rapidly almost went out of business. It turned out the technology didn’t work at all. We raised all this money. We hired 100 people. We built the technology and it just didn’t work." Now granted, the history of nvidia doesn't inspire a lot of investor confidence, -- and it's not nearly as enduring as Colonel Sanders' secret recipe of 11 herbs and spices -- but "it is what it is", right boys? "When Nvidia was founded, we rapidly almost went out of business." "We built the technology and it just didn’t work." . .</Msg><Username>elf.best</Username><Timestamp>1347088390285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 03:13:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347088898147-6</Id><Title>Chinese iPhone 5 knockoff uses Tegra 3</Title><Msg>Memo to Samsung (005930): Now this is how you get away with copying Apple (AAPL)! GizChina reports that a Chinese manufacturer has used leaked photos of Apple’s next-generation iPhone to slap together a quick knockoff of the device called the Goophone I5 and release it before Apple has a chance to launch the genuine article later this month. What’s more, the company has actually patented the knockoff design in China and is poised to sue Apple if it launches the next-generation iPhone in China later this year. For any Chinese readers who are interested in buying a not-quite-iPhone, GizChina says that the Goophone will feature “a Nvidia Tegra 3 quad-core 1.4Ghz CPU, 1GB RAM, Android 4.0 ICS with an iOS 6 theme, 8 megapixel rear camera and a 4-inch screen with an impressive retina display resolution of 1280 x 720.”</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1347088898147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 03:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347089565498-7</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese iPhone 5 knockoff uses Tegra 3</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1347088898147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 03:21:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Do nvidia sales people seek out these swarthy little illegal knock-off manufacturers, or is that all they can get an appointment with? All the decent customers -- like Google's Kindle #2 -- are going Elsewhere. . .</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1347089565498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 03:32:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347108853966-8</Id><Topic><Title>Anadtech says Amazon prohibits benchmarking by tech journalists of their newly announced models</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347047726453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 15:55:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would anyone name their product paper-weight? Unless that's what they expect it to be.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1347108853966</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 08:54:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347110568830-9</Id><Topic><Title>htc one x+ specs: tegra3?</Title><Username>inthemoney69</Username><Timestamp>1347046698046</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 15:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are missing my point. My point is that the target (T-Mobile) will not have FD-LTE (4G) network anytime soon (late next year). HTC One X+, just like its processor, still targets T-Mobile regardless. Wouldn’t you think the 2nd generation HTC One X+ would also be serving its existing customers? As stated in this article that HTC One X+ is specifically built for T-Mobile: [“We’ve heard on-and-off rumours of the highly-anticipated HTC One X+ for months now, but it seems that product is going to be announced in the very near future. Designed for AWS networks such as T-Mobile, Mobilicity and Wind Mobile, HTC’s One X+ will, according to reliable XDA Developer source Football, sport a 1.6Ghz quad-core Nvidia Tegra 3 Plus chip, with 1GB RAM, 32GB internal storage, 8MP camera, 42Mbps HSPA+ baseband and the same 1800mAh battery that exists in the current version.”] –mobilesyrub</Msg><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1347110568830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:22:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347111401006-10</Id><Topic><Title>htc one x+ specs: tegra3?</Title><Username>inthemoney69</Username><Timestamp>1347046698046</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 15:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typo: HTC One X+, just like its predecessor, still targets T-Mobile regardless. Anyway, it would be ludicrous to believe that HTC One X+ would include functionality (i.e. LTE) that cannot be tested on its target carrier’s network. In summary, HTC One X+ does not have T-Mobile LTE specs, neither does T-Mobile.</Msg><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1347111401006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:36:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347114896161-11</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese iPhone 5 knockoff uses Tegra 3</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1347088898147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 03:21:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. If nvidia was an ethical company that wasn't desperate for sales, they would say, look -- what you Chinese bums are doing is illegal. Taking leaked photos of Apple’s next-generation iPhone to slap together a quick knockoff of the device, and release it before Apple has a chance to launch the genuine article later this month. And then to apply for a Chinese "patent" for it. "That's slimy and unethical and we're not going to sell you our tegras for it". That's what "intellectually honest" Jen should say. But, Jen desperately desperately needs the sales.... so the "Goophone I5" is added to the list of Tegra 3 "SuperPhones". It's despicable the way nvidia operates -- "we'll do anything for a buck." . .</Msg><Username>truly.best</Username><Timestamp>1347114896161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:34:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347115188696-12</Id><Title>Why some analysts are wrong. The PC mkt equation on nvidia</Title><Msg>Yes PC sales are slowing. But PC gaming is actually growing! Go google search. You have nvidia and AMD competing in this segment. But nvidia has the cash to innovate. AMD doesn't. Which explains why Kepler is stealing mkt share from AMD. This will likely worsen going forward. What happens when nvidia is in near monopoly?</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347115188696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347115341209-13</Id><Topic><Title>AMD down 4.4%, INTC down 3.5%, NVDA down 3.2%, TXN down 1.7%</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347037721576</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 13:08:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why? The have inferior products all-round, and Intels manufacturing prowess are going to leave them in the dust. I would not touch AMD with a ten feet pole</Msg><Username>razorgarf</Username><Timestamp>1347115341209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:42:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347115820251-14</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia responds to Amazon's Kindle Fire performance claims</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347041202879</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 14:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe when they get to Tegra 12, they'll manage to get it right. If Nvidia manages to survive till then. But, I betcha Tegra line will still be unprofitable then, too. imho</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1347115820251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:50:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347117572198-15</Id><Title>AMZN began emailing for Preordering new KIndles</Title><Msg>Just got an email from AMZN for preorder of new Kindle Family, 8.9 4G LTE 32GB, 7 WiFi 16GB $199, Paperwhite $119, and the cheapest Kindle $69 - ALL powered by TI Qmap. IMHO - All these Kindles sales potentially amounts to more than the total sales of Tegra. This does not include future prospect of mobile phone from AMZN.</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1347117572198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347118398527-16</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia responds to Amazon's Kindle Fire performance claims</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347041202879</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 14:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No doubt talented engineers work on Tegra, but it is getting clipped by competititors going into the mass market - Investors are more concerned with how the people who run this company with ammunition of design wins can penetrate the mass market. Never know a few months from now what GOOG and MSFT partners would be - for now other behemoths - APPL &amp; Samsung have their own mobile processors. Perhaps putting NVDA on the auction block .............and let the behemoths make a bid.....</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1347118398527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:33:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347118795206-17</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia slides after downgrade and Intel guidance</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1347050228612</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 16:37:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, for the cloud computing , it may need a lot of devices on the receiving sites, but it definitely not GPU or CPU, It just like the main frame of IBM in 1975, it does not need a lot of CPU or GPUs for the single mainframe which distribute data to the users, and that is why Intel and nvidia, AMD will dies slowly, and Intel's warning proved my point. For the cloud computing, it needs a software compression and decompression software for wireless transmission of wirless video where the bandwidth is very expensive . Intel slowdown, but Apple is booming, it told me that the slowdown of Intel is just because people shifted from PCs to Tablets, and I remember Apple bought an IC fabless company many years ago called PA semiconductor which designed the CPU for handheld devices and founded by DEC employee, well, if all the IPAD used internal designed CPU , and most consumers shift to IPAD, well, of course INTEL will die</Msg><Username>edward_3141</Username><Timestamp>1347118795206</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:39:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347120796442-18</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia slides after downgrade and Intel guidance</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1347050228612</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 16:37:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When the cloud computing comes to the market , there will be a consolidation in the market, some companies will disappear over night, some will survive, and some new companies will prosper. INTC, AMD, NVDA, DELL, HPQ will die, while GOOG, AMAZ, MSFT AAPL...will survive, and many new companies offer the cloud service by providing the computing service, application based software service will prosper.</Msg><Username>edward_3141</Username><Timestamp>1347120796442</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:13:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347122692171-19</Id><Title>New Video Coding Standard H.265 will Greatly Benefit TegraX Tablets/Smartphones</Title><Msg>With the introduction of H.265 HEVC standard with 2X the compression of H.264 and a 67% improvement in streaming Nvidia TegraX will have the opportunity to gain significant market shares (imo). The new HEVC standard is specifically designed to support ULTRA HDTV at resolution of 4320p (33M-pixel). Instead of macroblocks, HEVC divides the picture into coding tree blocks. Because of the enormous amount of pixels that are presence (33M-pixel at 120 frames/sec) a 1-hour streaming will require 1-TB data for its transmission at "100 mb/s". So, the H.265 which has been specifically designed to accommodate HEVC ULTRA HD will actually consume enormous bandwidth and CPU power specifically on parallel processing. It will require quad-processors or better and a robust GPU to handle large amount of parallel decoding almost full time which is well suited for TegraX type processors for tablets and smartphones.</Msg><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1347122692171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:44:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347137127869-20</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia slides after downgrade and Intel guidance</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1347050228612</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 16:37:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cloud computing is already here. What remains is "Who will power the cloud?". Someone needs to make the processors that provide the proceeding power. INTC and NVDA are among the beneficiaries of that war. There are also reasons to not be connected to the internet all the time anyway due to power consumption from an online connection. Until PHOTO REALISTIC RENDERING is done on the cheap. They have little to worry about... I predict that until real-time interactive movies, with variations in them from AI that allow slightly different experiences every time come out, HIGH MARGIN TECH shall continue to be sold. Also on a side note, I predict that some time in the next 40 years, this tech allows robots to ruin our current economic system by flooding it with cheap and relatively intelligent robot labor.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1347137127869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:45:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347137330323-21</Id><Topic><Title>New Video Coding Standard H.265 will Greatly Benefit TegraX Tablets/Smartphones</Title><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1347122692171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:44:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. nvidia's already badly memory bandwidth constrained processors will be even more constrained with 1-TB of data struggling to get through at HDTV resolutions. But there IS a solution for nvidia's fundamental engineering problem, boys. Rambus designed XDR or XDR2 Mobile Memory. THE fastest memory on the planet, don't u know. By a mile. "The Rambus XDR™2 memory architecture is the world's fastest memory system capable of providing more than twice the peak bandwidth per device when compared to a GDDR5-based system. Further, the XDR 2 memory architecture delivers this performance at 30% lower power than GDDR5 at equivalent bandwidth." Which is why Samsung has used it for years in their HDTV applications. Heck, Samsung liked it so much they bought $100 million of stock in Rambus. And Sony has used it for years in their PlayStation gaming consoles. And Advancing Micro Devices uses it in their lightning-fast high-end graphics cards. Handily beating the pants off of nvidia's best. And with Jen finally paying for a Rambus license too, they might as well use it, right? 'Cause their best competitors already do. .</Msg><Username>bests.idea</Username><Timestamp>1347137330323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:48:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347138691789-22</Id><Topic><Title>New Video Coding Standard H.265 will Greatly Benefit TegraX Tablets/Smartphones</Title><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1347122692171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:44:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Rather than nvidia's wasting their time trying to convince folks that gaming on a teeny tiny 5" or 7" or 10" screen isn't such a a God awful experience, they need to improve their own badly constrained data transfer through-put, and nvidia could some day take a seat at the big boy table. Google this boys: Samsung UN75ES9000 75" Class LED 3D HDTV - 1080p, 1920 x 1080, 240Hz So how many years behind the cutting edge is nvidia in graphics? .</Msg><Username>valley.part</Username><Timestamp>1347138691789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:11:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347145406781-23</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Dropping like the Titanic! Need some Relief</Title><Username>adaholder911</Username><Timestamp>1336653611000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-05-10 08:40:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Ha ha ha ha ha ha! Ya gotta Love it, right? The Nigerian credit card rip-off spammers have been put out of business by Yahoo's new prohibition against URL links in new messages. So the starving spammers are now recycling those few spammy posts that didn't get deleted before the prohibition. This one is from four months ago -- brought back to the top one more time. "Play it again, Spammy" . .</Msg><Username>barjonicats</Username><Timestamp>1347145406781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347155256348-24</Id><Topic><Title>Why some analysts are wrong. The PC mkt equation on nvidia</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347115188696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You get it. Analysts don't, it's that simple.</Msg><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1347155256348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 21:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347155286098-25</Id><Title>Bloomberg video: IPhone 5 to Be Biggest Upgrade Ever</Title><Msg>. Topeka Capital's Brian White: "The Genuine Apple iPhone 5 will be the Biggest Consumer Electronics Upgrade in the History of the World." Their price target for AAPL: $1,111 -- 40% higher than today. Brian White was THE Blue Chip Analyst Survey Winner for 2009. To witness the complete Bloomberg interview with Brian White, including highly educational charts and graphs, Google this, Topeka's White: IPhone 5 to Be Biggest Upgrade Ever .</Msg><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1347155286098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 21:48:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347157066101-26</Id><Topic><Title>MUST READ: Computerworld on Kindle Fire HD - caveats behind PR and Bezos presentation</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1347149105822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:05:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this dog and pony show is going to get interesting. That $4/mo 4G - that's 250M a MONTH.... right folks, not a day, but a MONTH!. So for $500, you pay for a slow poke and pay more for a real 4G plan. this pig ain't gona fly. Now let's see if Ballmer is going to be 'exotic' or smart enough to take real advantage of this and go $300 to $350 10" winRT. Or else a goog 10" at $200 - $350 will also do the job.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1347157066101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347157959114-27</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg video: IPhone 5 to Be Biggest Upgrade Ever</Title><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1347155286098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 21:48:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. So Best? With that Top rated analyst Brian White putting a price target on Apple of $1,111.00 -- and the stock is at a mere $680 per share today -- that's a gain of what, $431.00 per share. Couldn't the down-and-out nvidia bagholders here make their crushing nvda losses back, and then some, simply by switching to the other more successful ARM chip manufacturer -- Apple Inc? They make basically the same chips -- only better. So it would simply be an intra-sector rotation of their investment. Out with the struggling nvidia, and in with the iBest. .</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1347157959114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:32:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347158500838-28</Id><Title>TSMC to get Apple orders in 2012 (for 20nm process)</Title><Msg>besty needs a new script. Everytime Apple changes partners or enemies, this idiot bashbot gets a new script to copy from.</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347158500838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347158603831-29</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to get Apple orders in 2012 (for 20nm process)</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347158500838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: TSMC to get Apple orders in 2014, not 2012. (Google the news, it's been circulated all over the web)</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347158603831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:43:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347159506990-30</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to get Apple orders in 2012 (for 20nm process)</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347158500838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. So if Apple gets access to TSMC's new 20 nanometer process in 2014, nvidia will need to stand in line until when? 2015 or 2016? This might be the worst thing to happen to nvidia yet. No doubt payback time from Jen publicly bashing TSMC's Chairman Peter Chang. .</Msg><Username>big_dog.wins</Username><Timestamp>1347159506990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347159612856-31</Id><Topic><Title>Why some analysts are wrong. The PC mkt equation on nvidia</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1347115188696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. PCs are upgradeable and next gen gaming is around the corner. Graphics cards are easier to upgrade than a possessor, so PC sales don't necessarily reflect the buying of new likely higher end cards. Steam is more popular than ever. Likely attracting new gamers that may want better graphics at a later date.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1347159612856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:00:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347160634514-32</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to get Apple orders in 2012 (for 20nm process)</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347158500838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It doesn't work the shiaty as you described. No everyone is like you. TSMC already turned down Apple and refused any suggestion of exclusivity despite a fat check. Morris Chang has moral character - which is something totally alien to you obviously. LOL</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347160634514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:17:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347160635016-33</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to get Apple orders in 2012 (for 20nm process)</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347158500838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It doesn't work the shiaty as you described. No everyone is like you. TSMC already turned down Apple and refused any suggestion of exclusivity despite a fat check. Morris Chang has moral character - which is something totally alien to you obviously. LOL</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347160635016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:17:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347161593883-34</Id><Title>Retribution for Apple patent troll....love it!</Title><Msg>Goophone manufacturer may sue Apple for patent infringement once Apple launches iPhone in China. Goophone, powered by Tegra 3 at 1.4 GHz, is now under Chinese patent protection.</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347161593883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347161593984-35</Id><Title>Retribution for Apple patent troll....love it!</Title><Msg>Goophone manufacturer may sue Apple for patent infringement once Apple launches iPhone in China. Goophone, powered by Tegra 3 at 1.4 GHz, is now under Chinese patent protection.</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1347161593984</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>