<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348291137833-1</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA up 0.4%, AAPL up 0.2%, INTC down, QCOM down</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348263576728</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:39:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. So Best? Which happened first? nvda falling. Or the Big Institutional Holders dumping massive quantities of nvda. Or did they both kinda coincidentally.happen together? .</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1348291137833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 01:18:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348293383415-2</Id><Topic><Title>gaming sales</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1348283644887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 23:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. The Good News! The new Nintendo Wii U gaming console is selling like hotcakes. Yes hotcakes, boys. The Bad News for nvidia: There are Zero (0) nvidia parts inside. None. Nana. Goose egg. "One of the Wii U's strengths is its custom AMD 7 series GPU." Which is based on AMD Radeon HD 5000 “Evergreen” series, don't u know. . Yet another huge, high volume opportunity -- Lost by nvidia. Read it and weep, boys. Google this: Game dev talks Wii CPU .</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1348293383415</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 01:56:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348294224278-3</Id><Topic><Title>gaming sales</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1348283644887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 23:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. So Best? How is Jen ever gonna make his overblown "guidance" if nvidia keeps losing the really Big, Elephantine-sized orders? Hummm? Just this month nvidia has lost, -- The Genuine Apple iPhone 5 -- The Amazon Kindle 2 -- The co-processer order for the Cray Cascade system for the Swiss National Supercomputing Centre (CSCS) in Lugano. -- And now, the GPU order for that selling-like-hotcakes Nintendo Wii U gaming console Looks like yet another Really Bad Quarter shaping-up here. -</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1348294224278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 02:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348294268516-4</Id><Topic><Title>gaming sales</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1348283644887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 23:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U fool. Point is PC gaming not dying. Which is good for nvidia. Plus, they just hired the console guru from AMD. U r not guru. U r goondoo! Lol</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348294268516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 02:11:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348308266593-5</Id><Title>Another Tegra 3 in China. Kungfu K3. Galaxy S3 type. Its china. Cloned phone is normal.</Title><Msg>Samsung is becoming the first Android smartphone manufacturer in the market today, thats why there is another manufacturer who built the same form factor. After Samsung released Galaxy S III on the market, there is another manufacturer who built smartphone look like Galaxy S III. After we’ve cover HDC Galaxy S III , It’s now another manufacturer who built the Galaxy S III knock-off thats called KungFu K3. The KungFu K3 is as powerful and stylish smartphone. POwered by quad-core NVIDIA Tegra 3 chipset running 1.4GHz clock-speed frequency, it run any task smoothly, in addition there is 8.0 megapixels rear camera and 1.3 megapixel front-facing camera for video call feature. This phone is packed with 4,7-inch QHD screen size display and support for HD playback video, running Android 4.1 Jelly Bean operating system and support for downloading multimedia content from Hulu Plus and thousand of application from Google Play Store. While we write this article, there is no information about the price, but this smartphone will be available on the Chinese market on the-end of October. Here are the quich specs of KungFu K3 Android smartphone : Size : 137.6 x 70.6 x 9.8 mm Weight : 145g with battery Display : 4.7-inch QHD screen with 1280 x 720 pixel (HD, 720p) CPU Speed : 1.4 GHz, quad-core NVIDIA Tegra 3 Operating System : Android™ 4.1 OS (Jelly Bean) Memory: Total storage : 16GB; RAM: 1GB Network : HSPA/WCDMA: Europe/Asia: 850/900/1900//2100 MHz , GSM/GPRS/EDGE: 850/900/1800/1900 MHz Sensors : G-Sensor, Digital compass, Proximity sensor, Ambient light sensor Connectivity : 3.5 mm stereo audio jack Bluetooth with aptX™ enabled (Bluetooth® 4.0) Wi-Fi®: IEEE 802.11 a/b/g/n DLNA® for wirelessly streaming media from the phone to a compatible TV or computer micro-USB 2.0 (5-pin) port with mobile high-definition video link (MHL) for USB or HDMI port Camera : 8 megapixel camera with auto focus, smart LED flash, support for 1080p HD video recording, 1.3 megapixel front camera (720p for video chat), Dedicated imaging chip Capture a photo in the midst of recording HD video High quality slow motion video capture and playback Multimedia: Audio supported formats: Playback: .aac, .amr, .ogg, .m4a, .mid, .mp3, .wav, .wma (Windows Media Audio 9) Recording: .amr Video supported formats: Playback: .3gp, .3g2, .mp4, .wmv (Windows Media Video 9), .avi (MP4 ASP and MP3), Recording: .mp4 Battery Capacity : 2500 mAh (Removable)</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348308266593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 06:04:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348316106290-6</Id><Topic><Title>Another Tegra 3 in China. Kungfu K3. Galaxy S3 type. Its china. Cloned phone is normal.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348308266593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 06:04:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. nvidia shareholders should be shocked -- Shocked I say -- to learn that their company has become The #1 Supplier of parts to the swarthy, illegal, deliberate patent infringing Chinese knock-off trade. First it was that Goophone I5 -- a swarthy, illegal, deliberate patent infringing Chinese knock-off of the Genuine Apple iPhone 5 -- powered by the nvidia tegra #3. And now this. The KungFu K3 -- a swarthy, illegal, deliberate patent infringing Chinese knock-off of the Genuine Samsung Galaxy S III phone -- powered by the nvidia tegra #3. "We don't care if the end use is illegal -- a sale is a sale and a buck is a buck", apparently say the morally bankrupt nvidia Sales Department. "Besides, it's the only way we can make Jen's otherwise unattainable revenue "guidance". Did I mention? The business practices of this company are Shocking. .</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1348316106290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 08:15:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348318626976-7</Id><Topic><Title>Another Tegra 3 in China. Kungfu K3. Galaxy S3 type. Its china. Cloned phone is normal.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348308266593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 06:04:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. So Best? It shouldn't be too long, right? Before Samsung -- the world's largest semiconductor manufacturer with 18 globally located fab plants -- starts cranking-out those counterfeit "Tegra 3" chips, right? For the Chinese knock-off trade, don't u know. Where "anything goes", and it's okay. -</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1348318626976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 08:57:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348320981936-8</Id><Topic><Title>Why nvidia will at least trade to $20 during this bull run</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348133186330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 05:26:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>totally delusional. nvda stock ain't going nowhere but down down down until Jen can trim back his losing Tegra program and cut his ballooning $750M/yr and growing loss in that division. If Jen announces the end of the Tegra program, the stock will shoot up overnight.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1348320981936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 09:36:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348323051207-9</Id><Topic><Title>gaming sales</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1348283644887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 23:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Quite a Crushing Loss for sure. Losing that selling-like-hotcakes Genuine Nintendo Wii U gaming console. To AMD. But hey! Maybe some swarthy, illegal, deliberate patent infringing Chinese company will make a knock-off of the Genuine Nintendo Wii U? And nvidia can win that. "nvidia: Powering the knock-offs is what wii do best." .</Msg><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1348323051207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348325017549-10</Id><Topic><Title>Another Tegra 3 in China. Kungfu K3. Galaxy S3 type. Its china. Cloned phone is normal.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348308266593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 06:04:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nexus7 runs a 1.2G T3 only. yet this phone runs a 1.4G T3. No doubt because of the lack of a cheap radio, nvda has to drop T3 prices to compete against qcom's integrated Sanpdragons = those Tegra loses are ballooning still.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1348325017549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:43:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348326315401-11</Id><Topic><Title>Another Tegra 3 in China. Kungfu K3. Galaxy S3 type. Its china. Cloned phone is normal.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348308266593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 06:04:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, mediatek is the biggest supplier to China cloned phones. It's share price is at 52 weeks high. I like such strategy. Oh, if Nvidia does something and makes its share prices rocket for a while and then comes crashing down, I am fine. I am only looking for that rocket moment.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348326315401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:05:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348326614534-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why nvidia will at least trade to $20 during this bull run</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348133186330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 05:26:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Totally delusional? Maybe . If it crashes from here, I will admit mistake and be man about it. But if it rallies to $20, just be man about it bashers and dun whine.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348326614534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:10:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348326781472-13</Id><Topic><Title>Another Tegra 3 in China. Kungfu K3. Galaxy S3 type. Its china. Cloned phone is normal.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348308266593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 06:04:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the wins keep coming! What's the matter trolls don't have any insiders to give you info on sales anymore? What are you going to do when nvidia blows out the sales numbers again?</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1348326781472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348329430221-14</Id><Topic><Title>Another Tegra 3 in China. Kungfu K3. Galaxy S3 type. Its china. Cloned phone is normal.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348308266593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 06:04:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mobile is on fire. all nvda's competitors in mobile are making money - mediatek, samsung, brcm, qcom, brcm, aapl...... Nvda is wrapping a $ bill with every Tegra sales $ that goes out. Not just the sheer size of the losses is alarming, $750/yr, but it is increasing much faster than nvda can ramp sales. And you want the share price to do what?? market is at all time high and nvda lingers. when market corrects, companies like nvda who has no viable biz plan and bleeding will take the blunt of the corrections and rightly so.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1348329430221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:57:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348329513434-15</Id><Topic><Title>Another Tegra 3 in China. Kungfu K3. Galaxy S3 type. Its china. Cloned phone is normal.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348308266593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 06:04:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not sure if "swarthy" menas what you think it means. Either that, or your description of the S3 clones is a bit.... racially/ethnically charged?</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1348329513434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:58:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348330437404-16</Id><Topic><Title>Another Tegra 3 in China. Kungfu K3. Galaxy S3 type. Its china. Cloned phone is normal.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348308266593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 06:04:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mediatek has been winning in the dual core China segment. But when I search under quad core, Nvidia is showing up more. ZTE u985, v985 K touch hornet 2. Oct available Small chilli , also Oct Goophone , highly a suspect, I suspect they just want quick buck from apple. Lol Kungfu k3, Oct. All these are launched at low price points. The kai strategy. The tide may swing in Nvidia favour. Nice.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348330437404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 12:13:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348332525966-17</Id><Topic><Title>Another Tegra 3 in China. Kungfu K3. Galaxy S3 type. Its china. Cloned phone is normal.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348308266593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 06:04:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what's your plan in life? Make a career out of harassing an anonymous message board ? Will this continue as long as NVDA is in existence? Mamma must be proud....</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1348332525966</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 12:48:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348335205999-18</Id><Topic><Title>Another Tegra 3 in China. Kungfu K3. Galaxy S3 type. Its china. Cloned phone is normal.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348308266593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 06:04:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mediatek is growing sales and making money while doing it. ss iis every other nvda competitors in the mobile space. nvda is growing alright, growing their Tegra loses by the Q. This is NOT a viable business plan. eg. Grey is obsolete way before it reaches the market ala all that R&amp;D $s will get flushed down the toilet. Wayne, but the time it gets here, will be just a jelly bean part, zero chance of making back the hundreds of millions sunk in. getanid: you seriously think a 5+ or 6+ or 7+ yrs R&amp;D project has a chance?? it means nvda started out with no breakthru thinking, just a me too project, and by the time 1st silicon out, competitors have already moved beyond that and they have to s can it and start all over again, with another me too project. This is Boulder. T his is Denver. Designing a leap frog cpu core is beyond their league, they don't have that core competence. nvda has NO viable business plan for Tegra. That whole program should be shut down or sold off. Continuing under Jen is just sinking in good $s after bad.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1348335205999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:33:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348346952402-19</Id><Topic><Title>Apple A6 chip: 1.2 GHz dual-core A15 and PowerVR 6</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347699166224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 04:52:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fastest mobile chip bar none ... anandtech[dotcom]/show/6324/the-iphone-5-performance-preview anandtech[dotcom]/show/6298/analyzing-iphone5-geekbench-results</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348346952402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:49:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348348136252-20</Id><Title>Head and Shoulders Pattern</Title><Msg>Can anyone confirm the H&amp;S pattern forming on NVDA from the left shoulder on July 1, head on August 12, and right shoulder on September 13? NVDA has in recent years been a "perfect" Fibonacci conforming chart, and this time around it looks like it's headed to $12 through the current cycle.</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1348348136252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 17:08:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348352372174-21</Id><Topic><Title>If NVDA is doing great, why ain't Jen planning a stock buyback?</Title><Username>zusofbull</Username><Timestamp>1348257302217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:55:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why buy? If they plan to dilute by 40% of current oustanding float for bonuses/options!</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1348352372174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348352751229-22</Id><Topic><Title>If NVDA is doing great, why ain't Jen planning a stock buyback?</Title><Username>zusofbull</Username><Timestamp>1348257302217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:55:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GROWTH? It grew to $35 a decade back and it has been sitting duck for the level of 2000 - 12 year past - is it called GROWTH? You need to upgrade your basic math - or get a kiddie $5 calculator at TorR.</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1348352751229</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:25:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348356220356-23</Id><Topic><Title>Head and Shoulders Pattern</Title><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1348348136252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 17:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look, just short some more. You don't need any logic and legitimate reasoning to short or bash NVDA, the hired crooks on this board never did - they do it anyway. Look up a few reputed TA site and see what they say.....I believe they said just the opposite. STOXLINE STOCKCONSULTANT A free lesson to you this time....</Msg><Username>lordgaga81</Username><Timestamp>1348356220356</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348356220478-24</Id><Topic><Title>Head and Shoulders Pattern</Title><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1348348136252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 17:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look, just short some more. You don't need any logic and legitimate reasoning to short or bash NVDA, the hired crooks on this board never did - they do it anyway. Look up a few reputed TA site and see what they say.....I believe they said just the opposite. STOXLINE STOCKCONSULTANT A free lesson to you this time....</Msg><Username>lordgaga81</Username><Timestamp>1348356220478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348361987325-25</Id><Title>"NVDA and INTC are the only companies</Title><Msg>with silicon spanning from smartphones to supercomputers." * and INTC's foray into smartphones is tenuous at best with a lot of cash and arm twisting involved *favorable mention in forbes</Msg><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1348361987325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 20:59:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348368526703-26</Id><Topic><Title>"NVDA and INTC are the only companies</Title><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1348361987325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 20:59:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INtel was completely taken by surprise for the smartphone. Probably 2014 before they really get into it... With continued cash &amp; arm twisting... standard INtel MO...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1348368526703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 22:48:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>