<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342966433000-1</Id><Topic><Title>huge open interest on 13 calls, we'll see!</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1342711035000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-19 11:17:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- It's a Laffer Curve actually. With the demand and supply of call options determined by the probability or improbability of the calls expiring Worthless. If the probability of the closest-to-the-money calls expiring Worthless is 100%, time after time, then the demand for nvda calls approaches zero. 'Cause it's no fun to keep losing your hard-earned cash on Worthless nvda call options, time after time. Note however, that the demand for nvda calls might not actually reach zero, since there is always a new crop of turnip-heads that are naive and think they can make money on that rigged game of nvda calls. Those folks are called the Laffer call buyers. HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA! -</Msg><Username>bestsays9</Username><Timestamp>1342966433000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342967486000-2</Id><Topic><Title>huge open interest on 13 calls, we'll see!</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1342711035000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-19 11:17:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Jeepers Best, The expert to ask about Laffer Curves and the dying interest in buying nvda call options is amdshortsrfools. Here's the guy with an advanced degree in Economics from a school so expensive that the pumper boys couldn't afford to even visit on the weekend. -</Msg><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1342967486000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:31:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342967521000-3</Id><Title>Google halts 16gb Nexus 7 new order: demand too hot</Title><Msg>Cant catch up with demand. Underestimated it. New orders placed in email notification lists!!! Boy, Nexus 7 is hotly demanded! Asus have to work overtime to ramp up supply! Great news for all components maker and google!!!!</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342967521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:32:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>31</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342968747000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Google halts 16gb Nexus 7 new order: demand too hot</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342967521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- HALTED all new orders. Hummm. You don't think that maybe -- just maybe -- it's related to their previously reported problems with, "bad components, manufacturing, and assembly"? http://www.pcmag.com/article2/0,2817,2407422,00.asp If Google has Halted orders for the gim-crack Nexus 7, Google has probably also Halted orders for nvidia's Tegra chips too, right? So when is Jen gonna chop his bad guidance? -</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1342968747000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>36</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342970028000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Google halts 16gb Nexus 7 new order: demand too hot</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342967521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They only halted 16gb. Cos cant meet demand. 8 gb is still available. If its defect issues, all will be halted.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342970028000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342970156000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Google halts 16gb Nexus 7 new order: demand too hot</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342967521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bashers, dun bother bashing on forums. Cos big boys like funds dun read yahoo forum. No one here can influence share price. We are all small fly.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342970156000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342970217000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Google halts 16gb Nexus 7 new order: demand too hot</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342967521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- So Best? With the Nexus 7 looking like a scratch here, what with the Halt on orders and all, will the next Nexus be called the Nexus 7.1 or the Nexus 8? And will Google keep struggling with the Tegra, or will they logically switch to the more reliable Qualcomm Snapdragon? -</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1342970217000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:16:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>18</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342971858000-8</Id><Title>Childish/ignorant bashers</Title><Msg>1. No point bashing in forums. We cant influenced share price. We are small fly. Big boys like institutions and funds dun read yahoo forum. 2. Rate factual good news one star eagerly. Rate their little bashings 5 stars double eagerly!!! Lol 3. Bashers mostly have shorted the stock. Mostly shorted like 1000 shares. Yet so eager to bash! 4. Most importantly, refer to pt 1. Bashing and pumping is useless. Grow up and realise it.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342971858000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:44:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342971930000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Google halts 16gb Nexus 7 new order: demand too hot</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342967521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.guardian.co.uk/technology/2012/jul/22/google-nexus-7-16-surprise</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1342971930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:45:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342973251000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Google halts 16gb Nexus 7 new order: demand too hot</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342967521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Google halts new orders for 16GB Nexus 7, surprised by demand Heavy demand for the 16GB version of the new Nexus 7 tablet has caught Google out after it expected more customers ordering through Google Play to want the 8GB version Charles Arthur | guardian.co.uk | Sunday 22 July 2012 07.48 EDT In excerpts. Google's Nexus 7 16GB version is now Unvailable through its Play Store. Sources close to Google say the search giant seriously underestimated the demand for the 16GB version of its 7in Nexus 7 tablet, which has sold out from stockists and other sources while demand for the smaller 8GB version remains comparatively low. The company has now Halted further orders of the 16GB version of the tablet, costing £199, on its Google Play store in the US and UK. While the 8GB model, which costs £159, is shown as "in stock" and being delivered in 3-5 business days, the 16GB version only offers an option to "sign up to be notified by email" when it becomes available. The 8GB version is only being sold through Google's own store, rather than physical retailers - but online buyers appear to have Shunned it, surprising Google, which had thought that the cheaper version, despite having only half as much storage, would sell better than it has. The Guardian understands that Google's planners had thought that buyers on the Google Play store, more than from physical or online retailers, would be more committed to the company's "cloud" concept, and so would have more of their content stored online, rather than wanting to keep it on the device. But most buyers appear to have noted that the storage on the device cannot be upgraded and decided to get the larger model. Asus is believed to be ramping up production of another batch of models, but that could take some weeks to arrive. The Nexus 7 marks Google's first foray into the tablet business. The device is made to Google's specifications by Asus; the 8GB version is being sold almost at cost ($199 compared to the build cost of $157), according to estimates by IHS iSuppli. The 16GB version is more profitable for Google." So Google continues to blow-out the remaining 8GB version, for which "demand remains comparatively low", -- and on which Google makes almost nothing. While orders for the slightly more profitable 16GB version have been Halted. They have to be absolutely laughing their heads off, right? At 1 Infinite Loop, Cupertino, CA. -</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1342973251000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 12:07:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>19</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342975664000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Google halts 16gb Nexus 7 new order: demand too hot</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342967521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>msft, if they are smart, which they are not, as witnesses by their going 'exotic' on their tablets while the whole world + dog have already gone cheap, can have a winner for windoz that more than justifies the cost over free, if their tablet can readily vpn back into home networks. Work data, I couldn't care less where that is stored on. Private data.... that shall always remain private. But msft will never do that, they are under the mistaken belief that they need to make you use their clouds. Same for goog - the 8G raison d'être is for you to use their cloud, as if we haven,t lost enough of our privacy already in this digital world of facebooks and tweeters and governments scanning all emails and online communications. Now if somebody like logmein will bring out an app to do this, they will make a lot of money.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1342975664000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 12:47:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342976825000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Childish/ignorant bashers</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342971858000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:44:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you missed some pts on bashers: 1. mostly premature kids with no life. 2. there are equally premature kids who call themselves pumpers here who will engage them. 3. what you said about bashers apply to pumpers too 4. together, they have a symbiotic relation, one simply will not cannot exit without the other. they depend on each other for a life. one major point difference about pumpers - some of them are actually paid by nvda to pump/spread the company mantra/create the 'buzz' here. yahoo msg board is irrelevant to anything wrt nvda, stock price nor real product demand.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1342976825000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:07:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342976878000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Google halts 16gb Nexus 7 new order: demand too hot</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342967521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But msft will never do that, they are under the mistaken belief that they need to make you use their clouds. Same for goog " more doom from whosunw... But... "same for goog" Before your next rant... at least read the thread title that proves you wrong !!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1342976878000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:07:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342977273000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Google halts 16gb Nexus 7 new order: demand too hot</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342967521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"sold almost at cost ($199 compared to the build cost of $157) " thanks...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1342977273000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:14:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342979713000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Google halts 16gb Nexus 7 new order: demand too hot</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342967521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Before your next rant... at least read the thread title that proves you wrong !!!" sorry professor, unlike you, I don't read lines. I just read between the lines. u so smart, I'll let you figure that one out.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1342979713000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:55:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342979979000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Google halts 16gb Nexus 7 new order: demand too hot</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342967521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so did you buy one? I know somebody who bought two and let me play with one of them for a while too. Both 16G. Asked him why he didn't go for the 8G and he said not enough memory to store his data. Stupid, didn't he know he could have just stored it up on the clouds?! impressive table for the price. But I found out one thing - for people with less than perfect eyesight like myself, 7" is just not enough. I've decided to wait for either the 10" or the T3 motherboard, whichever comes first.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1342979979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342980658000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Google halts 16gb Nexus 7 new order: demand too hot</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342967521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazon should have one coming soon. But of course you will find doom &amp; gloom in that eventfully just like everything else.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber22</Username><Timestamp>1342980658000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:10:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342980706000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Google halts 16gb Nexus 7 new order: demand too hot</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342967521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"so did you buy one?" No'p... I'm waiting for Windows... "7" is just not enough. I've decided to wait for either the 10" agree...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1342980706000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342981245000-19</Id><Topic><Title>ACER Iconia A110 reaches FCC (Tegra 3 on board)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1342974669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 12:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hopefully ACER will have substantial production capabilities, and considers the initial Nexus 7 results and go with 16 GB. It's good that they are including a microSD card slot and a micro HDMI.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber22</Username><Timestamp>1342981245000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:20:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342981365000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Childish/ignorant bashers</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342971858000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:44:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't it so very special that you are above it all, and have everything figured out.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber22</Username><Timestamp>1342981365000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:22:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342982302000-21</Id><Topic><Title>ACER Iconia A110 reaches FCC (Tegra 3 on board)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1342974669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 12:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>think the winning formula is 8G on board to keep the price low, but add microSD slot for expandability. But then, you'll miss out on the added $50 charge for $4 of 8G nand...... would be a good strategy for somebody like amzn or even goog who are more interested to selling their machines than making 10% on the hardware. don't look to any of the Asian guys to have half a million on hand at launch/'build up their production capacity'. They ain't that foolish to risk $500M a throw like HP and RIMM found out the hard way when they rolled snake-eyes. as I've been saying, no socket in THE two of the hottest names in mobile, nvda is just throwing $100M/Q for the table scraps. big hit on nexus, htc 1 X, all that does is to reduce the quarterly loss from $100M/Q to $90M/Q. That's far out of whack the whole tegra project is. To all those who keep bashing qcom and aapl, I'll give you a what-if: what if qcom's lament about 28nm availability is aapl needed to hold up releasing their quad core iPhone5 so much because they both are waiting for enough 28nm qcom cheap radios. Not so easy to have 20M or more of those on hand at launch..... that's &gt;&gt;10x Nexus</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1342982302000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:38:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342982523000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Childish/ignorant bashers</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342971858000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:44:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are totally green with envy, aren't you? if you have it, flaunt it. If you don't have it..... well, just keep on bashing. BTW, what happened to that gutter mouth of yours? got censored? heheheheeh......... hot day... gona go downtown and watch them sexy french girls in very short skirts.....</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1342982523000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:42:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342987453000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Childish/ignorant bashers</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342971858000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:44:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- It's no wonder you boys are poor. "Big boys like institutions and hedge funds dun't read yahoo message boards." Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! The biggest and best hedge funds actually have automated systems which "read" the degree of negative sentiment on various venues -- such as Our fine board -- to measure relative changes in the negativity of what's being posted. So chop chop, boys. Get to work cutting-and-pasting more of your nvda sunbeams. Hate to have some hedgie's black box drop a house on your precious nvidia 'cause you boys were slacking off. Again. -</Msg><Username>i_know_best</Username><Timestamp>1342987453000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 16:04:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342988485000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Childish/ignorant bashers</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342971858000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:44:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- So Best? What you're sayin' is that what we write here DOES make a difference to the stock price? Because of the hedgie's automated "readers". So for example, when we say that the nvidia's management stinks, the dividend is pathetic, the stock is plummeting, and they are losing massive GPU marketshare to Intel and AMD -- that the hedgie's automated sniffers will "read" that and adjust the short position accordingly? Oh my! My my my. This post might have just cost nvda a quarter on the open. -</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1342988485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 16:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342989234000-25</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading patterns</Title><Username>karoleaah551</Username><Timestamp>1342980952000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:15:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great move</Msg><Username>giancarlosyn318</Username><Timestamp>1342989234000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 16:33:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342990026000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Childish/ignorant bashers</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342971858000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:44:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- So Best? When the paid nvda pumper boys say those mean, vile things about the Truthsayers here, they are actually hurting the nvda stock price, right? Let's take an example. Here's a recent message from chitownbarber22. "Didn't you know that AMD's mother abandoned him at a Wal Mart when he was a small little annoying brat. A nurse at the mental hospital comes in every morning to serve him breakfast." Now when the hedgie's automated reader sees that message it sees negative sentiment, right? A whole bunch of it actually. And it adjusts the metric for negative sentiment upwards. And the stock price of nvda downwards. So the angry pumper boys here, and their mean vile messages, are actually costing Jen money. In his woefully undiversified portfolio. -</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1342990026000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 16:47:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342990434000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Childish/ignorant bashers</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342971858000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:44:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Did I mention? It's no wonder you pumper boys are poor. -</Msg><Username>i_know_best</Username><Timestamp>1342990434000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 16:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342992204000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Childish/ignorant bashers</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342971858000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:44:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- NEW FRIENDLY PUMPERS, PLEASE!!! -</Msg><Username>amdsrf.fan</Username><Timestamp>1342992204000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 17:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342992568000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Childish/ignorant bashers</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342971858000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:44:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;if you have it, flaunt it. If you don't have it..... well, just keep on bashing.&gt; Bashing is what you do very well. Perhaps it's time to take your Pamprin.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber22</Username><Timestamp>1342992568000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 17:29:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342995448000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Google halts 16gb Nexus 7 new order: demand too hot</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342967521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a terrible disease makes you hit Enter after each sixth word or so?</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1342995448000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 18:17:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342998349000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Childish/ignorant bashers</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1342971858000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:44:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor? That is how you would describe RMBS shareholders... there is no way out if it.. best... you are a two bit RMBS punk... well documented.... living in a delusional world.. and lonely world..</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1342998349000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 19:05:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343012753000-32</Id><Title>Nexus: Google has a game changer</Title><Msg>http://www.gottabemobile.com/2012/07/22/the-nexus-7-google-has-a-game-changer/ Nice read!</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1343012753000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 23:05:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343012823000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus: Google has a game changer</Title><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1343012753000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 23:05:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.gottabemobile.com/2012/07/22/the-nexus-7-google-has-a-game-changer/</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1343012823000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 23:07:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>