<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-30"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346308128455-1</Id><Title>Unreal Engine 3 Arrives on Windows RT Running on NVIDIA Tegra 3</Title><Msg>brightsideofnews</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346308128455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 02:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346323848498-2</Id><Topic><Title>Unreal Engine 3 Arrives on Windows RT Running on NVIDIA Tegra 3</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346308128455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 02:28:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . Unreal Message Arrives from getanid61. Most of what the guy posts is, well, Unreal. . .</Msg><Username>in_best_we_trust</Username><Timestamp>1346323848498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 06:50:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346327817098-3</Id><Title>Asus unveil tegra windows rt... Asus Vivo tab rt</Title><Msg>Go google search</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1346327817098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 07:56:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346329245654-4</Id><Topic><Title>Unreal Engine 3 Arrives on Windows RT Running on NVIDIA Tegra 3</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346308128455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 02:28:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a POS... it's that simple... the worst... so tired of you..</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1346329245654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 08:20:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346331462513-5</Id><Title>Samsung $4b fab investment</Title><Msg>Shifting alliances: Samsung invests $4 billion in foundry expansion By Joel Hruska on August 21, 2012 at 11:09 am1 Comment Share This Article Samsung has stated that it intends to spend $4 billion to renovate its Austin, Texas foundry in order to boost SoC production. This latest expansion is in addition to the company’s previously announced plan to build a $1.98 billion fab in South Korea. Samsung is also adding logic manufacturing capacity. If the manufacturer’s relationship with Apple were cozy, this sort of investment would be a no-brainer — Apple’s business has driven Samsung’s foundry revenue from $1.2 billion in 2010 to an estimated $3.735 billion in 2012. That jump could make Samsung the third-largest foundry in the world behind TSMC and GlobalFoundries. But, as it happens, things with Apple aren’t hunky-dory. They’re more accurately described as terrible, and consumers will ultimately end up picking up the bill for these court cases, no matter whose devices you prefer. We’ll know soon if Apple hired Samsung to fabricate the chip at the heart of the upcoming iPhone 5, but this may not matter much in the grand scheme of things. If Apple committed to manufacturing parts at Samsung as part of a long-term contract governing both SoCs and NAND flash, it may not have a choice. Samsung is caught in a paradox; its biggest foundry customer is trying to drive it out of business through legal challenges and ridiculous up-front demands (Apple wanted $30-$40 from Samsung for every device the Korean manufacturer sold). That’s neither sustainable nor desireable and it gives the company every reason on Earth to seek additional foundry customers. One of the top names on the short list is Nvidia; the two manufacturers are rumored to have paired up on Tegra 4 (T40). Whether or not NV did more than prototype the device at Samsung isn’t clear, but there’s been interest on both sides of the fence regarding a long-term strategic partnership. Samsung's current leading-edge technology is 32nm HKMG For Samsung, building relationships with other partners makes a lot of sense. Recent comments from TSMC may have driven that foundry’s customers to seek other options as well. During the company’s last earnings call, CEO Morris Chang stated that “now it makes complete sense to dedicate a whole fab to just one customer and hold that… there are customers that are getting bigger and bigger. So it makes sense that we dedicate a whole fab or even more than a whole fab to just one customer.” Chang went on to reassure nervous investors that the company remains committed to all its partners, but the short list of companies big enough to convince TSMC to dedicate an entire foundry’s worth of output to its products is short indeed. Apple has over $100 billion in the bank, craves exclusivity, and is more than willing to pay for it. That’s more than enough to make Samsung, Qualcomm, Texas Instruments, and Nvidia nervous. We don’t expect any major short-term changes, but by this time next year, Samsung will likely be talking up its new portfolio of partners, whether its still building chips for Apple or not. Between Cupertino’s courtroom antics and Chang’s fab predictions, doing anything else would be terminally short-sighted.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1346331462513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 08:57:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346332580164-6</Id><Topic><Title>Unreal Engine 3 Arrives on Windows RT Running on NVIDIA Tegra 3</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346308128455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 02:28:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is an article there on point, why the bashing?</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1346332580164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 09:16:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346337984717-7</Id><Topic><Title>Unreal Engine 3 Arrives on Windows RT Running on NVIDIA Tegra 3</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346308128455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 02:28:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL so true. difference is he is paid to be here</Msg><Username>hendar00</Username><Timestamp>1346337984717</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 10:46:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346338151491-8</Id><Title>thank goodness for HFT providing liquidity.</Title><Msg>another big rig lie</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1346338151491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 10:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346339329733-9</Id><Topic><Title>Unreal Engine 3 Arrives on Windows RT Running on NVIDIA Tegra 3</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346308128455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 02:28:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give me an example. Not sure what you mean. I'll wait here.</Msg><Username>pennyforabuck</Username><Timestamp>1346339329733</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:08:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346342174026-10</Id><Title>Ha ha shorts win a lot</Title><Msg>Good company but kidnapped by shorts.</Msg><Username>jasonhustock</Username><Timestamp>1346342174026</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346343050384-11</Id><Topic><Title>Golden Cross Setting up</Title><Username>hendar00</Username><Timestamp>1346179971331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 14:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are now having to rely on the 200 MA at 14.01 for support now.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1346343050384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:10:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346343577782-12</Id><Title>There's no qe3,so Nvda is killed</Title><Msg>13easily</Msg><Username>jasonhustock</Username><Timestamp>1346343577782</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:19:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346344189647-13</Id><Title>Haha 13s comes</Title><Msg>This stock is controlled by shorties. Ha ha</Msg><Username>jasonhustock</Username><Timestamp>1346344189647</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:29:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346344825000-14</Id><Title>The POS never loses the opportunity to crash</Title><Msg>WTF!!!</Msg><Username>roydirect2003</Username><Timestamp>1346344825000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346344899100-15</Id><Title>Shorted</Title><Msg>Wish me good luck.</Msg><Username>jasonhustock</Username><Timestamp>1346344899100</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346345114414-16</Id><Topic><Title>Uh-oh. NVDA Yahoo board not profitable?</Title><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1334108499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-04-10 21:41:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . Under new management, boys. The Best Communications NVDA Message Board "Nothing but the Best." . . .</Msg><Username>ct.bestula</Username><Timestamp>1346345114414</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:45:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346345356000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Weakness Ahead</Title><Username>phyliss_maude</Username><Timestamp>1346329842000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 08:30:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>era_esperanza</Username><Timestamp>1346345356000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:49:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346345575870-18</Id><Topic><Title>Shorted</Title><Username>jasonhustock</Username><Timestamp>1346344899100</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:41:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will do this every 20 cents.</Msg><Username>jasonhustock</Username><Timestamp>1346345575870</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:52:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346345645869-19</Id><Topic><Title>Uh-oh. NVDA Yahoo board not profitable?</Title><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1334108499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-04-10 21:41:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . So Chairman Best? Will we be able to provide URL links again? And see the name of the last poster? And BLAST messages right off the board -- if they're really Awful? Folks would probably return to the NVDA board, if Best was the new owner.. . .</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1346345645869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:54:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346346569082-20</Id><Topic><Title>Apple: One down, dozens to go.</Title><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1346199042551</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:10:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . "Amazon's recent push into the smartphone and tablet market (starting with the Kindle Fire) is what really has Apple fuming. Seems like a lawsuit just waiting to happen. And Colin Gillis with BCG Financial expects it to come sooner rather than later. "When Amazon does its big event in September, is it going to be a phone?," he said of the scheduled product launch on Sept. 6 in an interview with UPI. "Because if it's a phone, they're going to be sued, probably on Sept. 7. No joke." . . . So Best? Apple can't sue Amazon for patent infringement BEFORE it's launched, right? I didn't think so. 'Cause no harm has been done before it's launched. So Apple probably has their court papers ready to go, and now they just have to wait. Imagine being a hapless parts supplier to Amazon? Knowing it's gonna get smacked down as soon as it launches. That can't be fun -- nor profitable. . . .</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1346346569082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346346608584-21</Id><Title>Kill it all</Title><Msg>Kill kill just kill</Msg><Username>jasonhustock</Username><Timestamp>1346346608584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:10:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346347843537-22</Id><Title>Big sell off, shorts very safe.</Title><Msg>Kill it</Msg><Username>jasonhustock</Username><Timestamp>1346347843537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:30:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346348148491-23</Id><Topic><Title>YTD Earnings Plunge 37%. And the sheep cheer?</Title><Username>truly.best</Username><Timestamp>1344577324000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 01:42:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . "they raised guidance huge" . . And if Price-to-Guidance ever becomes fashionable, let us know. Until then -- it's EARNINGS that count. Nothing else. And nvidia's Earnings have PLUNGED 37.4% for the first half of 2012. . . .</Msg><Username>truly.best</Username><Timestamp>1346348148491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:35:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346350218967-24</Id><Title>Apple iPhone 5: 50 Million + Sales Possible</Title><Msg>. . Baird: iPhone 5 ‘Poised For Lift-Off,’ 50M+ Sales Possible; Little Interest In Potential FB Phone. By Teresa Rivas | August 23, 2012, 10:30 A.M. ET. On the heels of yesterday’s survey by Piper Jaffray, today Robert W. Baird analyst William Power has his own survey out, concurring that Apple‘s (AAPL) iPhone 5, which many expect to be launched next month, will see strong demand from consumers. Power writes that of 2,000 survey respondents, 39% said they are currently eligible for an upgrade and another 6% will become so within three months. Of those upgrade-eligible respondents, 45% plan to purchase an iPhone and the vast majority are waiting for the iPhone 5. The next biggest group, 31%, said that they were undecided on their next phone, and those planning to buy Google‘s (GOOG) Android devices rounded out the bottom at 22%. Power writes “Those percentages, if they held, could suggest 50 million+ iPhone 5 sales in the U.S. alone, well above current forecasts.” Consumers viewed longer battery life, 4G/LTE, improved Siri, improved back camera and a larger screen as the most important features for them, i that order. Power also found that iPhone customers were the most loyal, with 77% of current iPhone users planning to purchase another iPhone, (18% were undecided and 5% planning to purchase an Android device). Android’s loyalty was at 48% (with 34% undecided and 17% planning to purchase an iPhone.) However, Research In Motion‘s (RIMM) customers had almost no loyalty: just 2% said they would buy a new BlackBerry. “Importantly, we would note that RIM’s base in the U.S. is likely increasingly enterprise focused, with most growth generally now overseas.” As for other possible entrants to the smartphone arena, Amazon (AMZN) substantially outdid Facebook (FB): 51% of consumers said they would be interested in the former, while only 7% expressed interest in a phone from the social network. Power concludes with a note on carriers: “Though not surprising, the high number of eligible upgrades is likely to pressure margins for the U.S. wireless carriers in Q3 and Q4, perhaps more than expected. AT&amp;T (T) appears to have the highest exposure among the iPhone carriers, with 42% of surveyed subscribers currently eligible.” . . . "Could suggest 50 million+ iPhone 5 sales in the U.S. alone -- well above current forecasts.” That could take quite a large bite out of Android sales, right boys? And they wonder why nvidia plunges day after day after day..... . . .</Msg><Username>ibest.here</Username><Timestamp>1346350218967</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 14:10:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346351625191-25</Id><Topic><Title>Uh-oh. NVDA Yahoo board not profitable?</Title><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1334108499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-04-10 21:41:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't even tell which messages the replies are replying to any more. The Yahoo message board format is terrible.</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1346351625191</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 14:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346352160155-26</Id><Topic><Title>Big sell off, shorts very safe.</Title><Username>jasonhustock</Username><Timestamp>1346347843537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:30:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, look at all that much higher than usual volume, and the rest of the market doing gangbusters and all...LOL FAIL</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1346352160155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 14:42:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346353833822-27</Id><Title>taunting republicans on this board?</Title><Msg>they are everywhere, did I miss the memo?</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1346353833822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346354362000-28</Id><Title>NVIDIA Corporation is showing historic technical movement</Title><Msg>NVIDIA Corporation looks really unstable right now. Check out this site for the latest updates in NVIDIA Corporation http://SHORTPENNYSTOCKS.INFO</Msg><Username>laraepetermann</Username><Timestamp>1346354362000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346356303174-29</Id><Topic><Title>Where will this settle short term?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1345054836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:20:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump for prediction relevance.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1346356303174</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346358197310-30</Id><Title>Reiterated buy at Nomura$18 target</Title><Msg>as many buy recs as announced deals!</Msg><Username>gwin2win</Username><Timestamp>1346358197310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:23:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346359357658-31</Id><Topic><Title>Where will this settle short term?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1345054836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:20:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . Having easily smashed thru the lower support level today, -- actually reaching $13.98 at one point, and closing at $14.05 -- it looks like the next support level is at $13.67 ± 0.21, type Double, strength 2. No support, boys. She's got no support. . . .</Msg><Username>ibest.here</Username><Timestamp>1346359357658</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:42:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346359558523-32</Id><Title>BEST is an annoying loser</Title><Msg>Waste of space... pathetic</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1346359558523</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:45:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346360448738-33</Id><Topic><Title>taunting republicans on this board?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1346353833822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:10:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you notice they all had their lips removed? That way you can't tell when they are lying! NAFR!</Msg><Username>gwin2win</Username><Timestamp>1346360448738</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 17:00:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346360697082-34</Id><Topic><Title>Apple iPhone 5: 50 Million + Sales Possible</Title><Username>ibest.here</Username><Timestamp>1346350218967</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 14:10:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good for Apple now #$%$ and move to the Apple board</Msg><Username>nine_feet_underground</Username><Timestamp>1346360697082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 17:04:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346367815654-35</Id><Topic><Title>taunting republicans on this board?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1346353833822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:10:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>anyone wishing/betting for failure right now is a republican..guaranteed...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1346367815654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 19:03:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346372903910-36</Id><Title>Bloomberg: This Will Be the Biggest iPhone Launch Ever</Title><Msg>. . Since Yahoo doesn't permit links in messages any more, surf on "This Will Be the Biggest iPhone Launch Ever." Hysterical Bloomberg video, boys! "Potential for a Facebook cellphone?" "There's very little interest in a Facebook cellphone." "Facebook has proven they don't know how to run an IPO." "What makes them think they can compete with these really entrenched and highly competitive Giants?" "You gotta be kidding me! Facebook making a cellphone?" . . Sounds like a scratch, boys. . . .</Msg><Username>bestonica</Username><Timestamp>1346372903910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 20:28:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346373566106-37</Id><Topic><Title>Where will this settle short term?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1345054836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:20:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stock Consultant gives the fixed historical support/resistance points but you can't ignore the major moving averages as support/resistance points until they are broken and the 200 MA currently at 14.01 held today so that is the next nominal support until proven otherwise.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1346373566106</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 20:39:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346379918000-38</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA very high up on WSJ "buying on Weakness" list</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1346376814000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ibexx...I saw it, too, and it was on the last trade at 4PM...there was a block of just under 1mm shares on an uptick that was the final closing price of 14.05. With these low volume days in the last week of summer, NOTHING really matters. However, with no buyers willing to step up, and the market vulnerable to at least a short term sell off after Uncle Ben speaks, tomorrow, the shorts can do what they will until we find out the truth about whether or not AMZN picked Tegra 3 or 3+ for the new Kindle Fire Coyote and/or Hollywood. As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. Best, Max</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1346379918000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:25:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>