<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-07"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354858745602-1</Id><Title>Qualcomm Resolves Chipset Crisis</Title><Msg>Qualcomm Resolves Chipset Crisis Zacks 12/6/2012 Qualcomm Inc. (QCOM), the Largest Mobile Chipset Manufacturer in the World, has almost solved its chipset supply issue as two of its biggest vendor has increased their productions. Resolving the chipset supply shortage will bring to an end a major problem for Qualcomm, as it struggles to meet with the rising demand of its popular Snapdragon S4 processor. Three of its major suppliers, Samsung Electronics Co., Globalfoundries Inc. and Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (:TSMC) are all ramping up their production to meet the growing demand of smartphone chips. The popularity of Snapdragon S4 dual-core processors is always on the rise as they are mainly used in high-end smartphones and tablets. They also support LTE technology, better graphics, high network speed and increased battery life, which make them more popular among the top smartphone manufacturers. In mid-June, Qualcomm announced that there will be a shortage of S4 chipsets for the rest of 2012. In order to avoid the crisis, the company opted for some alternative chipsets called Fusion 2, which can be used in the mid-range smartphones and tablets. The company also collaborated with a third party chipset manufacturer, TSMC to accelerate the supply of chipsets. However, TSMC failed to properly estimate the demand for chips in 2012, thus resulting in lower production of processors. Therefore, to mitigate the shortage of chips, Qualcomm not only joined hands with United Microelectronics Corp. (UMC) but also selected Samsung Electronics Co. to further boost its S4 processor supply. According to research firm Gartner, tablet device sales are expected to increase by nearly 98% to 119 million units by the end of fiscal 2012. Solving the chipset issue will be a major boost for Qualcomm to meet the soaring demand from Apple Inc. (AAPL), HTC Corp. and Samsung Electronics Co. Looks like Qualcomm's swift and decisive decision making -- and their unwaivering, constant, unqualified, steadfast, unhesitating, wholehearted and gutsy willingness to deploy shareholder's cash when and where productively needed -- will pay Huge Dividends for Qualcomm as they now have the quantities of their award winning Snapdragon S4's with on-board LTE necessary to capture the 2% of the market that nvidia was able to "win" due to Qualcomm's here-to-fore inadequate chip fabbing capabilities. Starting with the Microsoft Surface RT #2, where it was disclosed last week that Microsoft is likely to kick nvidia's tegra to the curb -- and use Qualcomm instead.</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1354858745602</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:39:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354859775507-2</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcomm Resolves Chipset Crisis</Title><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1354858745602</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:39:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hello Qualcomm! { CLINK ! .... Clink clink clink bink bink } Goodbye nvidia.</Msg><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1354859775507</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:56:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354891159556-3</Id><Title>Broadcom to make LTE chips in 2013. Stock soars.</Title><Msg>Broadcom eyes entry into LTE chip market in 2013 Reuters – 18 hours ago.. . NEW YORK (Reuters) - Broadcom Corp said on Thursday that it would provide sample chips supporting the latest high-speed wireless services to its top cellphone customers in 2013. This could help the company compete better with bigger rival Qualcomm Inc, which is Years ahead of its rivals in Long Term Evolution (LTE), the high-speed wireless technology being adopted by wireless service providers around the world. Bob Rango, the company's general manager for wireless, announced Broadcom's LTE plan during the company's annual investor meeting. Broadcom Chief Executive Scott McGregor would not provide an estimate for the timing of the production of commercial smartphones using its LTE chips, but he included LTE in a list of "signposts" investors should look for in the next year. "We need to be there. We're not there today," McGregor said. The latest hot devices, such as the Apple Inc iPhone and Samsung Electronics Co Galaxy phones, already support LTE. Broadcom already supplies Apple and Samsung with chips for short-range connectivity such as Wi-Fi, but an LTE chip would help it increase the revenue it generates from each phone. Broadcom shares were Up 77 cents, or 2.4 percent, at $33.11 on Thursday afternoon. It announced late Wednesday that it was Raising its financial targets for the current quarter. Will Broadcom's new smartphone LTE chips beat nvidia's Wayne to market? Could well happen, boys. It could well happen.</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1354891159556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 09:39:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354891723356-4</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcomm Resolves Chipset Crisis</Title><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1354858745602</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:39:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like a brilliant move by Qualcomm to use Three -- count 'em 3 -- semiconductor manufacturers to get all their Snapdragon chips made. 1. Samsung Electronics Co. 2. Globalfoundries Inc. 3. Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company 'Cause when you're the Largest Mobile Chipset Manufacturer in the World like Qualcomm is -- you can't rely on just TSMC. Oh no no no. Waaaaay to risky, boys.</Msg><Username>ct.bestula</Username><Timestamp>1354891723356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 09:48:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354892032929-5</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne news: HTC to be the first with NVIDIA Tegra 4 phone?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354804662828</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 09:37:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Best the idiot shortie has an autobot that taps 15 thumbs down whenever someone posts REAL positive news liek this. Does this littel kid think that will help as nvidia continue to grow share and his idiotic short losses his #$%$? what a loser that kid is.</Msg><Username>best_the_turkey</Username><Timestamp>1354892032929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 09:53:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354892394528-6</Id><Topic><Title>Broadcom to make LTE chips in 2013. Stock soars.</Title><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1354891159556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 09:39:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>brcm just introduced quad A9s fully integrated - HSPA+, PMU, touch circuit, bluetooth/wifi/fm/gps/nfc/blah blah blah, AND reference sw + hw design. Slap yours together in 3 weeks folks! No more 9+ months to market. And of course, being brcm, they also have partners for the chips during announcement. As for their LTE, it won't be just baseband or even processor + baseband. When it comes, it will be fully integrated with everything except flash.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1354892394528</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 09:59:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354892398040-7</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcomm Resolves Chipset Crisis</Title><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1354858745602</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:39:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since nvidia only has 00.90% of the smartphone processor market, they don't need to worry about alternate supply sources and this and that. Like Qualcomm -- THE Largest Mobile Chipset Manufacturer in the World -- does. Nope. TSMC can probably knock-out all the tegras which nvidia's short list of customers require on what, alternating every-other-week Thursday afternoons? Life is simple when you have less than 1% of the market.</Msg><Username>perceptive.best</Username><Timestamp>1354892398040</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 09:59:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354893423583-8</Id><Topic><Title>Theme song for nvda bagholders : "I'm wide awake"</Title><Username>sing_along_with_best</Username><Timestamp>1354847344823</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 21:29:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great Song, Best! Totally epic. I wish I knew then {before I bought} What I know now Wouldn't dive in Wouldn't buy down GRAVITY HURTS They made it sound so sweet 'Til I woke up on On the concrete Falling from Cloud 9 It's crashing from the high I'm letting go today I'm falling from Cloud 9</Msg><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1354893423583</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 10:17:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354893607428-9</Id><Topic><Title>Theme song for nvda bagholders : "I'm wide awake"</Title><Username>sing_along_with_best</Username><Timestamp>1354847344823</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 21:29:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiot loser wiht pants aroudn ankles wont #$%$. pathetic creepy freak. LMAO!</Msg><Username>best_the_turkey</Username><Timestamp>1354893607428</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 10:20:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354894853338-10</Id><Topic><Title>Broadcom to make LTE chips in 2013. Stock soars.</Title><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1354891159556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 09:39:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hello Siri. Hi Best, my Supreme Master! How can I inform you today, Master? When will Broadcom's fully integrated LTE chips start replacing the nvidia tegra? One moment, please... It looks like sometime next year, Best. Thank you, Siri. Anytime Best, my Supreme Master.</Msg><Username>best.again</Username><Timestamp>1354894853338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 10:40:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354895419251-11</Id><Topic><Title>Broadcom to make LTE chips in 2013. Stock soars.</Title><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1354891159556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 09:39:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pom poms, hot pants and fireworks, right whosunw? Yes fireworks too. BA BOOM !!! The day next year when Broadcom's fully integrated LTE chip kicks it's first nvidia tegra out of a device. BA BOOM !!! Pom poms, hot pants and fireworks.</Msg><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1354895419251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 10:50:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354896895388-12</Id><Title>Pardon my skepticism but this stock stinks</Title><Msg>I was right all along. Man, i should have stayed short - why would I want anything to do with this loser, my bad</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354896895388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:14:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354897510552-13</Id><Title>Nvidia Is Commiting Suicide With Its FDD-LTE Single-Mode Only Chip</Title><Msg>["Ovum's Putcha and Forrester's Gupta believe mass TDD-LTE adoption may not take that long given the surge in global industry support for this version. "Network vendors may be more focused on FDD now but chipset vendors are rapidly developing dual-mode chips that support both TDD and FDD variants of LTE," says Gupta adding that TDD shares most of the FDD designs and standards and uses a common core network, which is why, the world's top network gear vendors like Nokia Siemens Network and Huawei to chipset vendors like Qualcomm, Samsung and Broadcom are supporting the TDD-LTE platform.”] –economictimes AT&amp;T has said that, in the future, they will only carry smartphones/tablets that have LTE capability, (presumably Verizon as well). It is expected that chip makers will need to incorporate modem chip into their application SoC otherwise they will lose out to their competitors. Competitors such as Qualcomm, Samsung, Intel, Marvel, Broadcom, Sequans, and others are now focusing on dual-mode (FDD and TDD) LTE chip but obviously NOT Nvidia. If Nvidia's business plan is to produce a single-mode FDD-LTE capability (only) chip with its Icera then Nvidia would be committing a suicide in this competitive business.</Msg><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1354897510552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:25:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354898263153-14</Id><Title>That's not a lump of coal in Santa's bag</Title><Msg>IT'S NVDA STOCK! Will it be Red or Green today........RED of course, silly.</Msg><Username>rundhousrite</Username><Timestamp>1354898263153</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:37:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354899132901-15</Id><Title>Holy Grail</Title><Msg>Monty Python and The Holy Grail. The knight who loses both arms and legs in a sword fight says: It's only a flesh wound. Sounds like terp. Just a stump, and a chump.</Msg><Username>aliendaytrader</Username><Timestamp>1354899132901</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:52:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354900020442-16</Id><Topic><Title>That's not a lump of coal in Santa's bag</Title><Username>rundhousrite</Username><Timestamp>1354898263153</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:37:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's that behind Santa' sled?? Reindeershyte steeped in Nvda stock Nvda down close to 1.5%, headed for a new 52 week low. Merry Xmas bagholers (sic)</Msg><Username>rundhousrite</Username><Timestamp>1354900020442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 12:07:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354900441215-17</Id><Topic><Title>Pardon my skepticism but this stock stinks</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354896895388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:14:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then short now... Please post when you do...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1354900441215</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 12:14:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354903228790-18</Id><Topic><Title>Pardon my skepticism but this stock stinks</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354896895388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:14:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>o.investor, You're no investor, you're a trader.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1354903228790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 13:00:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354903268441-19</Id><Topic><Title>Pardon my skepticism but this stock stinks</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354896895388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:14:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The smartest shorts should've shorted" The smartest shorts already have...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1354903268441</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 13:01:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354906244284-20</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia Is Commiting Suicide With Its FDD-LTE Single-Mode Only Chip</Title><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1354897510552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:25:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not sure Jen cares about a 'cheap' radio. One 'cheap' radio is just like another 'cheap' radio, why sweat about it?</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1354906244284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 13:50:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354907364136-21</Id><Title>Who else knows better about being cheap than Besty?</Title><Msg>With all his CHEAP talk day in and day out....</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1354907364136</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 14:09:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354907486880-22</Id><Topic><Title>Pardon my skepticism but this stock stinks</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354896895388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:14:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>o.investor is not just a trader, he is a penny trader at that</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1354907486880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 14:11:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354909814581-23</Id><Title>I have GOT to start buying those dips!!!!</Title><Msg>Clearly NVDa under accumlation. all imo!</Msg><Username>mr_nimble_2_you</Username><Timestamp>1354909814581</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 14:50:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354910292985-24</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 4 coming soon, HTC first in line (a few more details)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354887678906</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 08:41:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great post thanks. As I've posted recently I have the HTC One X+ wiht the Tegra3 4+1 (I use 'ninja' core for the 5th core which does the mundane tasks to save bettery life- ingenious!) and absolutley LOVE the look and speed of this phone. LOVE IT! I cant wait to see what the tegra 4 brings! NVDA_4_ever indeed! Long and Strong! Ps thx for the dividends Jen!</Msg><Username>nvda_4_ever</Username><Timestamp>1354910292985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 14:58:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354915168963-25</Id><Title>Hell even RIMM close above $12 today</Title><Msg>What does that say for NVDA? SELL, take your lumps, thankful that some dope will buy your shares.</Msg><Username>goovnia</Username><Timestamp>1354915168963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 16:19:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354915659655-26</Id><Title>where is our special dividend?</Title><Msg>should be around a billion dollars or something like $1.50 per share. let's get it done now!</Msg><Username>dutchref</Username><Timestamp>1354915659655</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 16:27:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354915950138-27</Id><Topic><Title>Pardon my skepticism but this stock stinks</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354896895388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:14:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the stink is coming from your diaper that you probably haven't changed for a while?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1354915950138</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 16:32:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354916272851-28</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia Is Commiting Suicide With Its FDD-LTE Single-Mode Only Chip</Title><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1354897510552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:25:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, you are wrong about single mode for Nvidia and it's been documented since they acquired Icera. The excerpt below comes from an article posted in February: "The NVIDIA Icera LTE modem leverages our unique SDR technology, which enables software upgradable functions to OEMs and carriers, offering high throughput and best-in-class power and small die size. This feature also enables faster time to market for new air interface technologies and lower R&amp;D expenses for handset manufacturers. This allows us to include on our roadmap for 2012-2013 a bevy of wireless data technologies, including: LTE FDD, TD-LTE, 42Mbps Dual Carrier and TD-SCDMA in addition to existing HSPA+, HSPA and 2G technologies." I'd say nice try at knocking down Nvidia, but you comments are glaring in what you choose to omit.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1354916272851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 16:37:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354942105649-29</Id><Topic><Title>Broadcom to make LTE chips in 2013. Stock soars.</Title><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1354891159556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 09:39:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This could help the company compete better with bigger rival Qualcomm Inc, which is Years ahead of its rivals in Long Term Evolution (LTE), the high-speed wireless technology being adopted by wireless service providers around the world. Bob Rango, the company's General Manager for Wireless, announced Broadcom's LTE plan during the company's annual investor meeting." That's what nvidia needs, right? A General Manager. To replace nvidia's prior General Manager that abruptly quit. And instantly took a much better job with Micron. Where the poor guy won't be quite so micro-managed to death. More likely his employee stock options will finish in-the-money too.</Msg><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1354942105649</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 23:48:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>