<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348115225382-1</Id><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Msg>. Apple's world-class iLitigators continue to Crush the Android ecosystem. Google this and take a look: Apple continues to sue three leading Android device makers (Samsung, Motorola Mobility, and HTC), In excerpts. "In August 2011, Google announced its merger agreement with Motorola Mobility (MMI) and suggested that it would use MMI's patent portfolio to bring about patent peace. Unfortunately for the Android ecosystem, the transaction has not yet had any peacemaking impact for a lack of serious leverage. Apple continues to sue three leading Android device makers (Samsung, Motorola Mobility, and HTC), and Microsoft continues to sign up licensees who take their destiny into their own hands as they realize a need to address Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues. In May, Nokia commenced a patent assertion campaign against Android device makers (as well as BlackBerry maker Research In Motion). Other large publicly-traded companies claiming that Android infringes their intellectual property include Oracle, British Telecom (BT), Fujifilm, and eBay. There are no signs of Google's post-MMI-acquisition patent portfolio deterring anyone's enforcement." . The whole patent infringing Android ecosystem is under thermonuclear attack, boys. Hey! Maybe that's why Mike Rayfield abandoned nvidia and joined Micron? .</Msg><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348116058638-2</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. So Best? If Motorola's patents are crapola in court, and of no use to Google in fending off the patent infringement claims of Apple and Nokia and Oracle and British Telecom and Fujifilm and eBay -- Google pretty much wasted the $12,500,000,000.00 they spent on Motorola, right? .</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1348116058638</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:40:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348119053882-3</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung mass produces 128GB NAND module for smartphones and tablets</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1348066849399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:00:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. And a larger memory helps the Tegra 3's fundamental problem how? The Tegra 3 is already badly memory bandwidth constrained. Oh so badly constrained. Take a look. Comparison of memory bandwidth between TI Omap 4470 and nvidia Tegra 3: 7.5 GB/s __ Texas Instruments Omap 4470 5.3 GB/s __ nvidia tegra 3 Putting a 123GB memory module in a Tegra 3 device is like putting a 100 gallon gas tank in a golf cart. She ain't gonna run any faster, boys. .</Msg><Username>bestodon</Username><Timestamp>1348119053882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 01:30:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348123742701-4</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the patent "thermonuclear" war is actually still escalating, as you suggest, then Nvidia's IP should be going up in value. The Intel settlement established the price of $1.5B for rights to a subset of NVDA's graphics IP for 6-years. Since then, Nvidia has spent an additional ~$690M to add another portfolio of patents related to baseband technologies (to pave the way for Icera baseband). The patents licensed to Intel should be worth at least 2x the settlement amount (assuming just 1 renewal, and no similar deals with other players, e.g. qualcomm) which equates to $3B. Even if you assume Nvidia paid twice the fair price for the patents purchased from IPWireless for $690, their presumed value would still be $345M. Together that's a low-end valuation of $3.3B, which presumably serves as the floor if the thermonuclear war really is ongoing/escalating. It's worth noting that Nvidia also has $3.26B in net cash. To be conservative, one could assume only 25% of it is domestic and that a) the remaining 75% would be taxed at 35% upon repatriation b) repatriation would somehow be necessary. That math works out to a net of $2.4B after getting it all into liquid domestic dollars. So, with a low-end valuation on the IP portfolio of $3.3B the patents and cash come to $5.7B in value. With a market cap of $8.49B, that leaves $2.8B in enterprise value to be justified by the 3 business segments: the GPU business (which is supply-constrained and promising 15% Q/Q growth),, Professional Business (which has no growth but great margins), and the Consumer Product Business that's scored major design wins and is growing at over 35%Q/Q. If you believe the numbers that the company has reiterated as recently as last week, then the third quarter will come in at an upper end of $1.25B -- which will bring trailing 4 QTR rev to $4.2B -- so the market cap net of cash and patents -- $2.8B -- equates to roughly .65x trailing 12 month blended rev, with growth. Or you could think of it as 1-2x rev multiples being given to the GPU an Professional Computing segments, and the Consumer Product segment (Tegra and Icera) being valued at or below zero. Awesome time to buy, IMO.</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1348123742701</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 02:49:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348131736514-5</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Super good point! That's why the fool's never understand, valuation pays. Nvidia valuation creates good margin of safety. Any upside in surprises will propel it far. Win RT could be one catalyst. Project Denver too. Lastly when tegra 4 comes out, windows phone.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348131736514</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 05:02:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348133186330-6</Id><Title>Why nvidia will at least trade to $20 during this bull run</Title><Msg>It has $5 cash per share. It is on target to earn $1 per share. With a 15 PE multiple, it should be $15. Add $5 cash equals $20 ! If Nov quarter surprises plus they up outlook, $28 to $32. Woohoo</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348133186330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 05:26:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348137235473-7</Id><Title>Tegra 3 win rt drivers in good shape</Title><Msg>According to fudzilla. Said despite qcom doing great with its lte enabled s4 chips, it looks likeqfom is losing the driver development battle against Nvidia! Now if, only if, Samsung and Dell decide to jump ship to tegra due to qcom not getting msft certification, that will be great. Also I am glad Msft, Asus and Lenovo chose tegra. Cos they are the ones succeeding in this computing space. Not Dell. Not HP.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348137235473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:33:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348145088217-8</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Your "valuation" of nvidia's IP is hysterically funny. Clearly the guy has never actually read the the terms of the PATENT CROSS LICENSE AGREEMENT BETWEEN NVIDIA CORPORATION AND INTEL CORPORATION, dated January 10, 2011. So Google this: PATENT CROSS LICENSE AGREEMENT BETWEEN NVIDIA CORPORATION AND INTEL CORPORATION, dated January 10, 2011. I'll wait for ya to catch up. Jen has given Intel the right to make rapious use of, -- and "continue in effect until the expiration of the last patent licensed hereunder" -- ALL (100%) of nvidia's patents through the "Capture Period" of March 31, 2017. Capture 'em for a six (6) year period. And Intel can use those patents until they expire. No additional future licensing by Intel required, boys. None. Note that there are only four (4) annual payments left on the Agreement, totalling $900M. Intel will make their last payment of $200M on January 15, 2016, and their licensing fees end forever. And since there are no other Intel's standing in line to license anything, that's all that nvidia's IP is worth -- $900 million -- not your illicit drug induced, "low-end valuation of $3.3B." Poof! There goes $2.4 billion of your purported enterprise value. Separately, note that the Consumer Product segment (Tegra and Icera) is on track to Lose ($700,000,000.00) this year alone. And the losses are growing exponentially. So what's the multiple to be applied to that? Hummm? If the multiple on positive earnings is currently 18.06x, it would be intellectually honest to apply the same multiple to those negative earnings too. So ($700 million) x 18.06 multiple = a negative enterprice value of ($12.642 billion) -- just for the Tegra Division alone. .</Msg><Username>bestodon</Username><Timestamp>1348145088217</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348146094779-9</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong u fool. Cos after the capture period, if Intel wants to continue using Nvidia patent, it has to pay again!</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348146094779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:01:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348146468136-10</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Sorry pumper boy. You have clearly not read the Agreement Intel gets to use 100% of all of nvidia's existing and new nvidia patents "captured" before March 31, 2017, until "the last patent licensed hereunder expires." No additional fees required. Like, ever again. .</Msg><Username>bestodon</Username><Timestamp>1348146468136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:07:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348147050937-11</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sigh. U are clearly wrong. Yes new patents. But only for use during captured period. Ie until march 2017. After that, Intel can't use anymore. To use, they must renegotiate. And nvidia has already set the min price.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348147050937</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348147781700-12</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Besty, your past track record in predicting Rambus' patent superiority and Nvidia's demise turned out to be a bunch of empty hot air. I'm not sure anybody should place any validity in your latest legal opinions?</Msg><Username>nvidiarules22</Username><Timestamp>1348147781700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348148013592-13</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. chrisindenial, If you bother to actually Read the Agreement, I would direct your attention to Section 4.1 "4.1. Term. This Agreement and the rights and licenses granted hereunder shall become effective on the Effective Date, and SHALL CONTINUE IN EFFECT UNTIL THE EXPIRATION OF THE LAST PATENT LICENSED HEREUNDER to expire unless such rights and licenses are sooner terminated by a Party pursuant to Section 4.2. Except as expressly set forth in Sections 4.2(a) or 4.2(b), neither this Agreement nor any of the rights or licenses granted herein may be terminated for any reason." Intel pays just once -- and gets to use all of those nvidia patents until they expire. There will never be an Intel renewal license on any of nvidia's existing patents, or any new nvida patents "captured" thru March 31, 2017. Sorry pumper. That's just the bad deal that Jen made with Intel Corporation. .</Msg><Username>bestodon</Username><Timestamp>1348148013592</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:33:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348148655999-14</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually not important. $1.5 b is loads of $. I had a post on how Nvidia is going to $20. That simple valuation is good enough.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348148655999</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348148886810-15</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I could be wrong in thinking nvdia is a buy. But risk reward is good at this level. My gains is at least 3 times my stop losses. Fine for me.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348148886810</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:48:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348151344841-16</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. chrisindenial, Your surrender is accepted. Granted, not the best surrender ever received, but passable. Also note, it's not $1.5B any more. Oh no no no. $600 million has already been received in the past from Intel -- and spent by Jen. On what future profit-making Whirligigs totally unclear. It sure wasn't spent on a first-ever Dividend to shareholders, right boys? Eighteen (18) years -- and zero Dividend from this place. .</Msg><Username>bestodon</Username><Timestamp>1348151344841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:29:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152105746-17</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung mass produces 128GB NAND module for smartphones and tablets</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1348066849399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:00:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SIGH... how naive that you don't understand the benefits of more memory...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1348152105746</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:41:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152117243-18</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The court may have validated appl's patents but the jury did not consider prior art and so there is an appeal. Also, there's more than one way to skin a cat: I believe that android users can live without "four corners that are equally rounded" and that bounce you get when you get to the end of a list. All these effects are just hair spray on a wig.</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1348152117243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152390617-19</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung mass produces 128GB NAND module for smartphones and tablets</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1348066849399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:00:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just more places to put your stuff. 7.5 GB/s __ Texas Instruments Omap 4470 5.3 GB/s __ nvidia tegra 3 Would the consumer really notice the difference on a phone? I tend to doubt it. One gig is an enormous amount of data. ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1348152390617</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:46:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348153511571-20</Id><Title>we have how many CEO's on this board?</Title><Msg>unemployed ceo's abound</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348153511571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:05:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348156292829-21</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My main point was that the $1.5BM settlement value provides a great data point when trying to figure out the value of the larger IP portfolio (prior to whatever's been developed and/or acquired since then). Mind you it was INTC that sued NVDA, only to end up settling by a 6-year $1.5B license agreement. To say there's "no other Intel's standing in line to license anything", I'd point out that the SoC platform war is just heating up, and you have multiple players on the mobile device side scrambling to license and embed GPU technology in their SoC solutions. Taking 2x the settlement value from 2010 does indeed seem conservative to me... as does the rest of my brief analysis where I discounted the cash on the balance sheet assuming repatriation costs. To do it your way instead, you'd have the remaining $900M, plus a very conservative $345m (50% of the $690M spent on IPWireless' patents in May), plus a conservative estimate of $2.4B net, domestic liquid dollars after repatriation-- still leaving the market valuation of the company, less cash and IP at around or less than 1x revenues. That'd be fair if the company wasn't growing share and didn't have Tegra finally landing in some major products (Nexus 7 and Surface RT).</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1348156292829</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348157581654-22</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Regarding your points on the Consumer Product segment, I don't think I agree with your reasoning... but that shouldn't be surprising. Even if the upper end of your short bashing figure of $700M in this year is true, then the segment should actually be set to achieve operational profitability by EOY, with much upside in CY2013. Consider that R&amp;D today already represents the cost of developing and integrating Icera's tech into Tegra -- with no offseting revs. Once Icera comes to market, NVDA's share of the BOM in the devices it's in will go way up, roughly doubling. When that happens, the same number of units sold will deliver significantly more revenue, and profits should improve greatly. In CY2012, though, for consumer products, we have revs of : Q1:$132.6M Q2: $179.7M Q3: will be between $240M and $260M based on guidance (to upwards of $1.25B) and leaks from the supply chain on ramped Nexus 7 production and ramping Surface RT pre-production... LG/HTC/ZTE/Fujitsu phone sales would be an upside. Part of getting to these numbers requires assumptions on how much of the raised guidance comes from growth in the GPU and PCB segments --- which I've put at 12.5% and 5%, respectively, based on company commentary. Q4: we'll have to wait for guidance, but based on others' estimates for Q4 Nexus 7 and Windows RT tablets, as well as the many other Tegra and smartphones that have or will be announced and ship (particularly those outside of the US), Q4 will probably show additional sequential growth over Q3. That'd put Consumer Products north of $240-260M. This would mean Consumer Products would end the year with ~$800M in revenue. Far better than the bashers would like to believe, but still 20% lower than what Jen-Hsun et al were originally saying could be a $1B year for CP. But Icera will mean ASPs will nearly double in all design wins where Nvidia gets the spot both SoC and baseband connectively... meanwhile costs go meaningfully hire, since they're already being realized at this stage of the process. Personal opinion is Consumer Products does over $1.5B in sales in C2013 with roughly $250M in profits. The Market, like all the various incarnations o "BEST" seem to think this is impossible. But the market and these bashers are both being irrational in this case.</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1348157581654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348157779767-23</Id><Topic><Title>Huge AH trade: a block of $1.7 million shares crossed at $1`3.788</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348091998742</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On Nvidia's investor pages there was an audio presentation from the Citi analyst day. There Jen-Hsun talked about the cash. I listened to him while doing other stuff on the computer, so I did not really pay proper attention, but I recall him saying that they liked to hang on to that pile of cash because it would be needed for acquiring other companies. He wasn't specific regarding what to acquire, but said it would be "announced later". Seemed almost like he was negotiating a deal already. By saying this I am not trying to spread a rumor of any kind...</Msg><Username>lifesuckswhenstocksaredown</Username><Timestamp>1348157779767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348158258074-24</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure there are other typos, but in the 5th paragraph I meant: "But Icera will mean ASPs will nearly double in all design wins where Nvidia provides both the SoC and baseband connectively... meanwhile costs WILL NOT go proportionally higher, since most of the fixed costs of development are already being absorbed at this stage of the process."</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1348158258074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:24:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348161091644-25</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Saint Steve Jobs' goal of completely shutting down Android coming to fruition under Tim Cook, 1 slavish copycat at a time. Just wait till Sam-dung's penalty get tripled to over 3 Billion dollars, just as willful infringement penalties usually are.</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1348161091644</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:11:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348161098042-26</Id><Title>kindle has a great future, right!!!</Title><Msg>glad nvda did not win that business</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348161098042</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:11:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348164257315-27</Id><Topic><Title>Android's massive, court-validated patent infringement issues.</Title><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1348115225382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The jury considered everything the judge allowed into the case. Sam-dung's desperate prior art reaches FAILED, just as will their appeal.</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1348164257315</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348166214748-28</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 3 win rt drivers in good shape</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348137235473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, from yesterday. The darn message board won't let me post a link, but if you go to fudzilla soon, it should still be on the homepage, near the bottom.</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1348166214748</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:36:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348166262182-29</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 3 win rt drivers in good shape</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348137235473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>here's an attempt at posting the link... goo.gl/wvmia</Msg><Username>thetrade50</Username><Timestamp>1348166262182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348166837023-30</Id><Title>could close @ $13.3498129056984567</Title><Msg>per the rich boy's trading machine...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1348166837023</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:47:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348169483112-31</Id><Topic><Title>Cray wins contract to build cluster for Swiss supercomputer Center (Tesla GPUs)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348165397565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the wins just keep coming.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1348169483112</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:31:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170474183-32</Id><Topic><Title>Why nvidia will at least trade to $20 during this bull run</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348133186330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 05:26:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>omg.. put down the pumping machine.. we all know it's not going to 20. Even the older pumpers won't claim that anymore. nvda tried on 20 after the hype of Tegra 2 was announced and after the hype was over, it settled back to 12 bucks. Face it, this isn't the investment your looking for.</Msg><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1348170474183</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:47:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348173229451-33</Id><Topic><Title>Why nvidia will at least trade to $20 during this bull run</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348133186330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 05:26:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey trailer trash boy, your IQ score has been holding steady at 20 for the longest time. Now get lost and check your propane tanks for leaks. Make sure you use a match or a lighter.</Msg><Username>bestisapest</Username><Timestamp>1348173229451</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:33:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348177613756-34</Id><Topic><Title>Why nvidia will at least trade to $20 during this bull run</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348133186330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 05:26:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agree Chris, logical conclusion. But how do you factor in the general unfavorability of the PC sector at the moment? Whats the time window on your analysis?</Msg><Username>hendar00</Username><Timestamp>1348177613756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:46:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348179709642-35</Id><Title>NVIDIA Project Boulder Revealed: Tegra's Competitor Hides in GPU Group</Title><Msg>NVIDIA Project Boulder Revealed: Tegra's Competitor Hides in GPU Group Every company has secretive and not-so-secretive projects. For example, ATI Eyefinity multi-display technology was a hidden part of the silicon in the Evergreen series, with only two executives knowing about it. Three years later, we can now say that Eyefinity pushed both Intel and NVIDIA where they did not expect to go, and AMD reaped the rewards from that program. In the case of NVIDIA, the story is more complicated. Last year saw the official announcement of "Project Denver", its 64-bit architecture fully compliant with the ARMv7/v8 ISA (Instruction Set Architecture). The announcement saw people like John Carmack singing the words of praise. However, the history of Project Denver goes long before ARM was at play. Originally, Project Denver was an intelligent RISC architecture capable of executing ARM, x86, MIPS ISAs. The focus naturally, was on getting the x86 done right and this is where the ex-Stexar team lost years in development. The first product based on Project Denver core was a dual-core PD with a cluster set of Fermi cores, scheduled to arrive on market in 2010 and fight Intel's Arrandale, originally scheduled as the dual-core x86 part with Larrabee GPU in it. After it became clear that the future lies in low-power processors, NVIDIA Colorado-based team abandoned the work on x86 instruction set architecture and pushed through with "reinventing" the Project Denver core to work with ARM ISA, most notably to have 64-bit capable, ARMv8 compatible part. The first project based on Project Denver should be the T50 e.g. "Tegra 5", combining Project Denver cores with the Maxwell GPU utilizing 20nm-SLP process at the Samsung Electronics Fab in Austin, Texas. Roughly six months ago, NVIDIA did tapeout its first test wafers from Austin Fab. Will they keep TSMC or go with a dual-foundry approach, that is not the subject of this story nd this brings us to Project Boulder, for which interviewers are asking people to join with the question, "do you want to join the ultra-successful Tegra team in NVIDIA", only for those same engineers to find out that they're heading to work on a project inside the GeForce business unit and won't have much relation to the Tegra team. In a way, the company is doing the right thing by keeping the focus on low-power architectures in the Tegra team, and high-performance in the GPU team. According to our sources in the know, Project Boulder represents NVIDIA's "claim to fame" in the server space. This high-performance part doesn't care as much about low-power as it cares about its feeding capabilities. NVIDIA doesn't want to bundle its Tesla and Quadro parts with Intel Xeon or AMD Opteron parts, as that reduces the revenue the company receives and exposes it to risks such as Xeon Phi (Larrabee Redux) and FirePro S (server versions are finally available). In a nutshell, we're probably going to see an 8-16 core SoC with high-bandwidth interconnect, utilizing high-bandwidth memory. Given the timeframe of its arrival (2014), we'd wager it's too early for GDDR6 memory and it will probably have to rely on DDR4, expanding it with memory space on parts such as ioFX (both NVIDIA and Fusion-io recently started to work together on expanding the memory addressing directly to GPUs/SoCs). Details about the actual Project Boulder silicon are scarce right now, and we would rather wait and see instead of throwing out guesstimations. At the same time, similar story is taking place at Apple, who wants to replace Intel products from its consumer notebook and desktop products. While this won't be a possibility before iOS matures to the level of replacing the Mac OS (guesstimate would be iOS8-iOS9)</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1348179709642</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 18:21:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348195820613-36</Id><Topic><Title>Why nvidia will at least trade to $20 during this bull run</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348133186330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 05:26:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pc gaming is different from whole pc. Whole pc shrinking but pc hardcore gaming growing. In Asia more mmporg are opening arcade shops for walk ins to play. Nvidia also stealing shares from AMD. Cos spents a billion a year on r&amp;d. Huge amount. Nvidia doesn't serve the whole pc market. Intel does. Hence Intel hurting. Nvidia doesnt serve the bottom 60%. When the bottom 60 moves to tablet, Nvidia benefits too as tegra sells in that segment! While hardcore gamers remain hardcore!</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348195820613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:50:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348195923710-37</Id><Topic><Title>Why nvidia will at least trade to $20 during this bull run</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348133186330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 05:26:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U? I wouldn't entertain a fool that worships AMD when it plunged so much in 52 weeks! Fool</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348195923710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348196036255-38</Id><Title>qualcom damage control</Title><Msg>QUALCOMM Incorporated (NASDAQ:QCOM) stated that the majority of users do not need quad-core processors now, citing business decisions as the cause of the delayed release of its quad-core Snapdragon S4. Qualcomm, which was the late joiner of the quad-core SoC party while its rivals, Nvidia and Samsung, had huge design wins with devices like Google’s Nexus 7 and Microsoft’s Surface tablet, stated that most people will not find two cores necessary. The firm, informed The INQUIRER that users will not experience a noticeable performance boost going from dual-core to quad-core processors at this time. What deal did they lose?</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1348196036255</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:53:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348196036845-39</Id><Topic><Title>Why nvidia will at least trade to $20 during this bull run</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348133186330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 05:26:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Argue based on facts. Not opinion fool. Tell me my valuation simple matrix doesn't make sense based on valuation facts.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348196036845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:53:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348196556893-40</Id><Topic><Title>Why nvidia will at least trade to $20 during this bull run</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348133186330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 05:26:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I find the 5million tegrazone downloads interesting. Our inclusion in nexus7 surface and more. Want the best gaming experience? Get your games from the tegrazone where they have been optimized for tegra devices.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1348196556893</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 23:02:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348196676172-41</Id><Topic><Title>qualcom damage control</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1348196036255</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:53:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh my, sounds serious. All that time to get snapdragon4 out the door and it's broken? Heads gotta be rolling.</Msg><Username>hendar00</Username><Timestamp>1348196676172</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 23:04:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348197414345-42</Id><Topic><Title>Cray wins contract to build cluster for Swiss supercomputer Center (Tesla GPUs)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348165397565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. "And the wins just keep coming." . HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA! There is ABSOLUTELY NO MENTION of ibbey's purported Kepler GPUs in the Cray Cascade system for the Swiss National Supercomputing Centre (CSCS) in Lugano. None. In fact, the September 20th news article specificially mentions, and I quote, "The CSCS machine will NOT have either Intel Xeon Phi or Nvidia Tesla K20 coprocessors." Here's the whole Truth news of the new Cray "Cascade" parallel supercomputer ordered by the CSCS in Lugano Switzerland. Google this and weep, boys: Swiss boffins jump in Lake Lugano for Cray super Pumping water uphill A fitting title, right? "Pumping uphill." . The highlights. "The boffins at the Swiss National Supercomputing Centre (CSCS) are opening up a new supercomputing center in Lugano next year, and now they have a shiny new "Cascade" parallel supercomputer from Cray to hum away inside of it. Cray has not announced the Cascade machines yet, but here's what we do know. The new Aries interconnect links nodes together through a much-improved high-radix router that speaks to server nodes through a PCI-Express bus. Given that the initial Cascade machines are based on Xeon E5 processors from Intel, and that these processors have PCI-Express 3.0 controllers right on the chip, everyone expects that only processors that support PCI-Express 3.0 links will plug into the Cascade boxes. So that means for now, the Opteron 6200s from Advanced Micro Devices are outta luck. The Aries interconnect and Cascade system design were funded by the US Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency, so it has dibs on the first machine manufactured by Cray, which is expected to be delivered later this year. The Cascade line will be commercialized in 2013. It looks like CSCS is next in line after that, with Cray saying that its Cascade machine will be installed later this year. That machine does not yet have a nickname, but if history is any guide, it will have an Alps mountain as its namesake. This Cascade box will have in excess of 750 petaflops of peak performance, according to Cray, which tells El Reg that this particular initial configuration will be entirely based on Xeon processors. With the top-bin Xeon E5 part weighing in at 172 gigaflops per socket, and a server node having two sockets, this Cascade machine should have around 2,180 nodes. *** The CSCS machine will NOT have either Intel Xeon Phi or Nvidia Tesla K20 coprocessors . *** These two coprocessors are, of course, options on the Cascade box, and it is reasonable to assume that at some point AMD Opterons and maybe even FirePro discrete graphics cards might also be options." . In summary. Intel is naturally the Big Winner. With 4,360 Intel Xeon E5 processors (2,180 nodes @ two Xeon E5 chips each) There are Zero (0) Nvidia Tesla K20 coprocessors in the new Cray supercomputer for Lugano. None. . But ibbey -- keep trying to pump your K stuff uphill, okay? HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA! .</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1348197414345</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 23:16:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348198230835-43</Id><Topic><Title>Cray wins contract to build cluster for Swiss supercomputer Center (Tesla GPUs)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348165397565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. So Best? Since that Cray Cascade system design and the Aries interconnect were funded by the US Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency, -- the American Taxpayers -- don't ya think that the co-processor order should go to that 100% American company, Intel Corporation? The Intel Xeon Phi co-processors are bigger, better and faster than the nvidia parts. Oh so much faster. And the Intel Xeon Phi's are made right here in the U.S. of A. By American workers, don't u know. Not halfway around the world in some Taiwanese job shop -- like nvidia's are. .</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1348198230835</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 23:30:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348198324062-44</Id><Topic><Title>Why nvidia will at least trade to $20 during this bull run</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348133186330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 05:26:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Soon. After it crashed from $28 two yrs ago, it has been basing for more than a yr. It doesn't sit around without preparing for a big move. Yes, it could breakdown big. But based on history, after a big drop, its a big rally. Also based on valuation, my bet is up!</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1348198324062</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 23:32:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348198905373-45</Id><Topic><Title>Cray wins contract to build cluster for Swiss supercomputer Center (Tesla GPUs)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1348165397565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. I agree wholeheartedly, Best. It is entirely proper and fitting that the American funded supercomputer should use those superior American-made Intel parts. Supporting American jobs is Important, you know. Particularly in an Election year, such as this is. I cast my vote of support for those Intel Xeon Phi co-processors, and will send a note to our fine Senator in Washington. .</Msg><Username>mayor_of_bestville</Username><Timestamp>1348198905373</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 23:41:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>