<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-18"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350536513410-1</Id><Title>Nvidia's Top End Kepler Unveiled: Tesla K20 Comes with Disappointing Specs, Performance</Title><Msg>Nvidia is preparing to unveil its highest end Kepler at the SC'12, but a lot of details were hidden from the public… until now. Thanks to CADnetworks' premature specifications, we learned everything that was missing. REVIEW German publication Heise.de was the first to catch up with the specifications of CADnetworks' new visual workstation, ProViz W60 and the G13, G26 and G40 servers. The specifications only confirm what we were suspecting - Nvidia was coy about disclosing the amount of memory that was to be placed on the K20 boards because it will actually end up less than its predecessor, Tesla C2075. We suspected this might happen as both Samsung and Hynix refused to manufacture the 4Gbit GDDR5 chip, citing lack of interest. According to our sources, the reason was a bit different, and quite unflattering for both Samsung and Hynix - both companies requested money from Nvidia in order to get the high-density GDDR5 to market, but they refused to give out exclusivity deal to the company. At least, that's how one side of the story goes. Faced with the availability of only 1 and 2 Gbit GDDR5 chips, it doesn't take a rocket scientist to figure out that the K20 could only ship with no more than six physical gigabytes, e.g. five workable gigabytes once ECC is enabled (by default). Nvidia's Top End Kepler Unveiled: Tesla K20 Comes with Disappointing Specs, Performance Thus, the K20 board is featuring a 7.1 billion transistor manufactured in 28nm process at TSMC, once more becoming the world's largest silicon (once again, a title Nvidia held since 2006 and the G80 chip). The chip in question has 13 SMX clusters enabled, which carry 192 cores each - for a grand total of 2,496 CUDA cores. The number trounces the GK104 (available in GeForce GTX 660Ti/670/680/690, Quadro K5000 and Tesla K10) by a significant margin, as the GK104 carries "just" 1536 cores. The chip physically carries 16 SMX cores, with two being disabled for yield purposes. If TSMC improves on its 28nm process, we might see a K25 or K30 with full 2880 CUDA cores, but don't expect too much. The number of cores is not the only change, though - Nvidia was working hard on optimizing the Double Precision performance, failing short of self-imposed target of 1.5 TFLOPS DP. As it stands right now, the K20 will barely outperform the Xeon Phi (ex-Larrabee, now Knights Corner / Knights Ferry) and AMD's own FirePro S9000 (which is hidden on AMD's website so well that you can't find it unless you use a search engine). The GPU will only work at 705MHz, meaning that you can expect double-precision performance to the tune of 1.17 TFLOPS, barely double than C2075/M2075/M2090. Single-precision performance is quite solid at 3.52 TFLOPS, but still lags behind AMD's Tahiti GL GPU (4TFLOPS Single, 1TFLOPS Double). The price is set at already announced $3199, or 2950 Euro. All in all, when it comes to 2013 Accelerator / GPGPU battle, we can now say that Tesla K20 is nowhere near as impressive as the company hopes it to be - Larrabee Reborn (Xeon Phi) and FirePro S9000 are too close for comfort, and with Intel's pricing schemes, no wonder Nvidia is worrying about its neighbor on the east side of the 101 freeway</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1350536513410</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 01:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350537709185-2</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's Top End Kepler Unveiled: Tesla K20 Comes with Disappointing Specs, Performance</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1350536513410</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 01:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Getanid, You are not giving VR.ZONE credit for this article? Did you think that viewers would just assume "you" could come up with all the information? There is a name for this kind of behavior, ya know</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1350537709185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 01:21:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350537752602-3</Id><Topic><Title>The genuine Intel has let the genuine idiot besty down.....hahaha</Title><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1350532314591</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 23:51:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The one major thing that Genuine Intel Corporation has that nvidia doesn't, -- besides a Fabulous CEO in Mister Paul S. Otellini -- -- a true visionary and peerless leader -- -- the veritable Don Corleone of the Valley -- -- who's not afraid to call a spade a spade -- -- if the hapless economy spirals into a global recession -- -- and candidly and frankly and voluntarily Pre-Warns the Street -- -- while courageous and forthrightly reducing his own guidance -- -- yes, forthrightly, boys -- -- like a trustworthy, loyal, helpful, friendly, courteous, kind, obedient -- -- not to mention cheerful, thrifty, brave, clean, and reverent CEO should do -- besides All of that, Intel Corporation pays it's shareholders a Cash Dividend. They sure do. 4.10% is the current yield. Genuine U.S. Dollars Cash in the mailbox. Each and Every Quarter like Clockwork. Well that, and they own and operate Forty Two (42) chip fab plants. All of which serves as a Floor under Genuine Intel stock. Keeping it from sailing off a cliff. Like their struggling little badly managed, non-dividend paying, unfab-ulous competitors will be doing. Shortly.</Msg><Username>valley.part</Username><Timestamp>1350537752602</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 01:22:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350537927514-4</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's Top End Kepler Unveiled: Tesla K20 Comes with Disappointing Specs, Performance</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1350536513410</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 01:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>busted by the NVDA board police...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1350537927514</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 01:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350538860774-5</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's Top End Kepler Unveiled: Tesla K20 Comes with Disappointing Specs, Performance</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1350536513410</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 01:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"All in all, when it comes to 2013 Accelerator / GPGPU battles, we can now say that the Tesla K20 is nowhere near as impressive as the company hoped it to be. Intel's Xeon Phi and AMD's FirePro S9000 are too close for comfort, and with Intel's pricing schemes, no wonder Nvidia is worrying." Sounds like a scratch, boys.</Msg><Username>itsascratch</Username><Timestamp>1350538860774</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 01:41:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350563056708-6</Id><Title>GETNANID61 congrats on ur SHORT.</Title><Msg>Great Call. RED CANDLE SPECIAL!!</Msg><Username>see_you_at_the_top</Username><Timestamp>1350563056708</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 08:24:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350566185922-7</Id><Topic><Title>The genuine Intel has let the genuine idiot besty down.....hahaha</Title><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1350532314591</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 23:51:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? nvidia has some cash lounging-around on their balance sheet, right? Yes, just lounging around, boys. Watching Wheel-of-Fortune and eating Cheetos all day. Due to the lack of guts and vision by Dear Leader to put it to proper work. Maybe nvidia could buy some INTC with their unemployed cash? And the hapless nvidia shareholders could Enjoy that 4.10% current dividend yield. Without all the hassle and expense of actually trading out of nvda in into INTC. Cash. It's a terrible thing to waste, boys.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1350566185922</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 09:16:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350567575167-8</Id><Topic><Title>The genuine Intel has let the genuine idiot besty down.....hahaha</Title><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1350532314591</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 23:51:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Master? Finding Blue Chip Stocks is easy, right? They all have it right there in their emblems. Blue. General Electric -- the Most Widely Held Blue Chip Stock on the Planet -- has a blue emblem. And look at Microsoft. Right down there in the lower left corner of your screen. It's mostly blue, right? And of course Intel Corporation has that nice blue-chippy logo. Which also appears on the upper left of their Generous Dividend Checks. Each and every Quarter, like Clockwork. And how about American Express? Hummm? The Blue Box THE Most Valuable Symbol in All of Financial Services. Do pick a better stock next time, boys. Look for the Blue.</Msg><Username>best.clone182</Username><Timestamp>1350567575167</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 09:39:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350567794541-9</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA is about to Give me a HEART ATTACK!!</Title><Username>paul.mccarthy76</Username><Timestamp>1350566155887</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 09:15:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, that is really cool. I've never seen anything like that before.</Msg><Username>davis.perry62</Username><Timestamp>1350567794541</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 09:43:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350570006885-10</Id><Title>Apple loses appeal against samsung in Europe in tablet case</Title><Msg>LONDON (Reuters) - Apple has lost its appeal against a ruling that cleared rival Samsung of copying its registered designs for tablet computers, in a decision which could end the two firms' legal dispute on the subject across Europe.</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1350570006885</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 10:20:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350570927891-11</Id><Title>How big is the market opportunity for GPU MapReduce?</Title><Msg>I went to a Hadoop tutorial over the weekend in Silicon Valley (at eBay) and the speaker (Paco Nathan) mentioned that GPU's were going to be used more and more for doing MapReduce jobs on large Hadoop clusters (I suppose including Amazon's EMR). I know that companies like Google and Amazon have tens of thousands of computers running these jobs, but if everyone of those were replaced with GPUs, would it impact materially the incremental revenue that NVDA generates? Just thought this might be a good opportunity to buy here and go long.</Msg><Username>biomedstl</Username><Timestamp>1350570927891</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 10:35:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350582164048-12</Id><Title>BACK UNDER $13</Title><Msg>This stock is Krap..... Even @ $13 it's a loser. Now going for $12, it really REALLY SUKS.</Msg><Username>koncakpimps</Username><Timestamp>1350582164048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 13:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350582388964-13</Id><Topic><Title>The Nexus 7 is already the UK’s all-time best-selling Android tablet</Title><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1350504768950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:12:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And what is Nvda's stock doing today? TANKING</Msg><Username>koncakpimps</Username><Timestamp>1350582388964</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 13:46:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350585337661-14</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA is about to Give me a HEART ATTACK!!</Title><Username>paul.mccarthy76</Username><Timestamp>1350566155887</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 09:15:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds good to me.I will be sure to look into that.</Msg><Username>rhonda.browning47</Username><Timestamp>1350585337661</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 14:35:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350585862898-15</Id><Topic><Title>The Nexus 7 is already the UK’s all-time best-selling Android tablet</Title><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1350504768950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:12:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have no clue what you are talking about . . all the tech stocks are being hit today because of Google's premature earnings release . . bye bye.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1350585862898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 14:44:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350587039844-16</Id><Title>Google shares slides on prematurely announced earnings</Title><Msg>Profit dips on rising cost. The news is all over the web.</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1350587039844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 15:03:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350599961404-17</Id><Title>look at 10 year chart</Title><Msg>is this ever going anywhere</Msg><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1350599961404</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 18:39:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350602768635-18</Id><Topic><Title>look at 10 year chart</Title><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1350599961404</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 18:39:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well you aren't . .</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1350602768635</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 19:26:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350605823250-19</Id><Title>NVDA is neither a Value nor a Growth Investment</Title><Msg>No dividend and the price is at the same level as back in 2000. $13.65 high in Aug 2000. Factoring in an assumed 40% dilution, $12.86 could translate to $18.</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1350605823250</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 20:17:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350616991313-20</Id><Title>Acer's 7-Inch Iconia A110 Tablet Arrives Oct. 30</Title><Msg>Tegra Inside. Source: pcmagDOTcom/article2/0,2817,2411115,00.asp</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1350616991313</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 23:23:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350617181543-21</Id><Title>Google CEO Larry Page urges investors to buy the Nexus 7</Title><Msg>Jen Hsun did this 3-months ago :) Now ogle CEO Larry Page urges investors to buy the Nexus 7 Source: gantdailyDOTcom/2012/10/18/google-ceo-larry-page-urges-investors-to-buy-the-nexus-7/</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1350617181543</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 23:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350617438476-22</Id><Topic><Title>Google shares slides on prematurely announced earnings</Title><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1350587039844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 15:03:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's an Idea how Google could reign-in their rising cost of processor chips. Cut out the middlemen. Today the chip channel is as follows: ARM chip blueprints (1) are licensed by a middleman (2), who sends the design to the fabber (3), who makes the chips and sends 'em back to the middleman (4), who sells the chips to Google (5), who ships 'em to the device manufacturer (6), who sells the completed devices to Google (7), who finally sells them to a retailer like Best Buy (8). So that's what, Eight (8) steps involved in the process. 1. ARM Holdings 2. Middleman 3. Fabber 4. Middleman 5. Google 6. Device manufacturer 7. Google 8. Third-party retailer All taking their needless markup. Oh so needless. Google could slavishly copy what Apple and Samsung are already doing. And what Amazon and Microsoft are planning to do. Do-It-Yourself ARM chip making, boys. It's all the fashion now, don't u know. ARM chip blueprints (1) are licensed by Google's own chip design department (2), who sends the design to the fabber (3), who ships 'em to the device maker (5), who ships the completed devices to Google's own Retail Stores. Only Five (5) steps -- and Four (4) entities involved. 1. ARM Holdings 2. Google's own chip design department 3. Fabber 4. Device manufacturer 5. Google's own Retail Stores It eliminates a Whole Lot of Middlemen, right boys? It sure does. Who are mostly just standing around like a doorman with his hand out. How tough can it be, right? If music retailer Apple can do it.</Msg><Username>bests.idea</Username><Timestamp>1350617438476</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 23:30:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350617924925-23</Id><Topic><Title>Google CEO Larry Page urges investors to buy the Nexus 7</Title><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1350617181543</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 23:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is a transcript of this part of Page’s remarks: "I switch between my Nexus phone, Nexus 7 tablet and my new Chromebook that we just announced today many times a day. While this abundance causes disruption, it also creates amazing opportunity. And Google is super well-placed to take advantage of these disruptive opportunities. Why? Because our search query volumes have grown this quarter as measured year over year. And we are seeing tremendous innovation in advertising which, I believe, will help us monetize mobile queries more effectively than desktop today. Indeed our mobile monetization per query is already a significant fraction compared to desktop. In short, as we transition from one screen to multiscreens, Google has enormous opportunities to innovate and drive ever higher monetization. Just like Search in 2000. Now we took a big bet on Android back in 2005. We believed that aligning standards around an open source operating system would drive innovation across the industry. Most people thought we were nuts. Today there are over half a billion Android devices-half a billion – with 1.3 million more being activated every day. You should all run out and buy the Nexus 7 tablet for $199. It’s had rave reviews and recently won “Gadget of the Year” from T3, the gadget experts. You’ll love the integration with Google Play. It is an amazing device."</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1350617924925</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 23:38:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>