<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351398076980-1</Id><Topic><Title>Upgrade Nexus 7: 32 GB RAM and 3G!!!</Title><Username>toisletsat</Username><Timestamp>1351376875725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 18:27:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"4G-LTE is a wireless technology capable of download speeds up to 10 TIMES FASTER than 3G. That's roughly the speed of your home broadband network. Carriers are rolling out 4G over the next few years, and they're in different stages of their expansion. Verizon currently has 371 markets covered nationwide, covering 75% of the U.S population. AT&amp;T has 65 markets, covering 24% of the population. Sprint covers just 19 markets. Those numbers are in constant flux: All of the carriers plan to significantly increase their 4G coverage fairly rapidly. AT&amp;T says it will have 4G LTE in more than 100 cities by the end of 2012. Sprint says it will have its network available in 100 additional cities "in the coming months." Verizon plans to have 400 markets covered by the end of the year. Some metro areas where LTE is partially deployed do not yet appear on carriers' official coverage maps. Eventually, all three nationwide iPhone carriers say their 4G coverage will be as pervasive as 3G. Until then, users will find their iPhones shifting in and out of 4G. When your phone leaves a 4G zone, it will seamlessly move to 3G as a backup (ha ha ha!)." Be sure to check out the map : Where iPhone 5 will have 4G The iPhone 5 will be the first version to support 4G-LTE networks Verizon, AT&amp;T and Sprint all have 4G-LTE now -- in about 600 markets of the U.S. Even in places like Alaska and Mississippi have it. The Genuine Apple iPhone 5 was the first to support 4G-LTE networks, of course. Apple does ALL the cool stuff first. But even those technologically dawdling android phones can use it too now. 4G-LTE is Ten Times (10x) Faster than yesterdays 3G, boys and girl. TEN TIMES (10x) Wow! One time faster Two times faster Three times faster Four times faster Five times faster Six times faster Seven times faster Eight times faster Nine times faster Ten times faster. Qualcomm of course makes the best 4G-LTE for cellphones. 'Cause they put the 4G-LTE pieces-parts right there on the same silicon as their award-winning Snapdragon processor. And because it all right there together, the electrons don't have so far to walk. Like Ct. Bestula did. Five (5) miles to school every day when The Count was a wee lad. With book bag and everything. Up hill and dale, around the horse farms and the golf course -- which by the way had a hole in the fence, so The Count could cut across the 4th, 11th, and 16th fairways on the way to school. Skeetch on the ponds too, in the Winter. Anyway... so why on Earth would anybody buy a slow 3G phone today? You'd almost have to GIVE 'EM AWAY, right?</Msg><Username>ct.bestula</Username><Timestamp>1351398076980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 00:21:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351399532794-2</Id><Topic><Title>Upgrade Nexus 7: 32 GB RAM and 3G!!!</Title><Username>toisletsat</Username><Timestamp>1351376875725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 18:27:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ever see a deer trail? Where the deer walk the same path every day for years, and wear a permanent trail? Well, that's what we did to that poor golf course. Three or four of us kids, let see, The Count, Criag, Gary and Susan, would cut across the middle of the golf course on the way to school, each and every day. For like 8 years. Making a "deer path" that's probably still there to this day. And the ranger man didn't like it. Oh no no no. One day the ranger man zoomed over on his green ranger cart and tried to chase us off his golf course. And The Count showed him his Membership Card, and said that Craig, Gary and Susan were his Guests. The ranger man never bothered us on the way to school again.</Msg><Username>ct.bestula</Username><Timestamp>1351399532794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 00:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351405393431-3</Id><Topic><Title>Jeepers Best, Everybody else pays a dividend.</Title><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1351349062429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jeepers Best, Everybody else pays a dividend. Except current nvidia CEO Jen Hsun Huang. Take a look. Dividend Yield % 4.10% __ Intel Corporation 3.50% __ Dell Inc. 3.20% __ General Electric (The #1 Most Held Stock by Members of Congress) 3.10% __ Marvell Technology Group Ltd. 3.00% __ Texas Instruments Incorporated 2.60% __ Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Corporation 2.50% __ Sony Corporation 2.01% __ The Average Dividend Return of the 500 Stocks in the S&amp;P 500. 1.70% __ Apple Inc. 1.70% __ Qualcomm Incorporated 1.33% __ Microsoft Corporation 1.30% __ Broadcom Corp. 0.80% __ Oracle Corporation 0.40% __ ARM Holdings Plc 0.00% __ nvidia Jen calls them "Barbarians at the Gate." And has 'em chased off the property. Those Institutional Investors. With their Halloween bags open. Just looking for a little alpha. On the Hundreds of Millions they each invested in Jen's company. Jeepers Best, can't the Institutional Investors vote Jen out as their CEO? They own Way more shares than he does. And have the new hired help declare a dividend?</Msg><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1351405393431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 02:23:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351434320056-4</Id><Topic><Title>Jeepers Best, Everybody else pays a dividend.</Title><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1351349062429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So let's say that the Institutional Investors have gathered, smoked some nice Cuban cigars, told a few yachting stories, and voted. Jen is out at CEO, and the new guy is in. And let's say the new guy decides that $3 Billion of cash is Waaaay too much to be holding for no particular reason. And he decides to distribute say, $2 Billion of it as a one-time Dividend. Here's how some of the checks would look. Pay to the Order of: $280.8 million __ FMR LLC $122.0 million __ PRICE (T.ROWE) ASSOCIATES INC $112.6 million __ VANGUARD GROUP, INC. (THE) $62.4 million __ PRIMECAP MANAGEMENT COMPANY $53.2 million __ BlackRock Institutional Trust Company, N.A. $30.2 million __ AllianceBernstein, L.P. $25.4 million __ Invesco Ltd. $22.6 million __ BlackRock Fund Advisors $323.88 __ for a holder of 1,000 shares "And when is a good time to meet?"</Msg><Username>genuine.best</Username><Timestamp>1351434320056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 10:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351435300757-5</Id><Topic><Title>Jeepers Best, Everybody else pays a dividend.</Title><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1351349062429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oops. It appears I slipped a naughty on that last one. It should read: $3,228.51 __ for a holder of 1,000 nvda shares ((1,000 shs / 619,480,000 shares outstanding) * $2,000,000,000.00 One Time Dividend) Could be handy around the Holidays, right boys?</Msg><Username>genuine.best</Username><Timestamp>1351435300757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 10:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351439197553-6</Id><Title>the whole Tegra program is done, dead, burried, enterré</Title><Msg>missing out a whole A15 product generation, now that's something nvda can control, not? and that is why nvda is a sub $5 stock and will be a sub $5 stock - unlike a professionally run txn who scales back when things don't work, Jen' ego won't let him bite the bullet and swallow his pride and close the program. Instead, he will continue to blow stock holders' billions in this thing. Denver - if he can't strung other people's proven cores together, how in the world he is going to design a processor that can beat ARM's own 64 bit???? Paid bashers on here, I seriously doubt it. Paid pumpers/yes-men on this board, some of that stuff spilled here is so absurd it can be only from that type. The paid pumpers here are symptoms of what is wrong with the company - instead of hard nosed business sense running the company, you have an e.gomanic doing it BTW, even with no production for the $b salaries, they will continue to dilute shareholders' holding with ever increasing stock grants. nvda is done, you can stick a fork into it.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1351439197553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 11:46:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351442774198-7</Id><Topic><Title>Jeepers Best, Everybody else pays a dividend.</Title><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1351349062429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow! Best has received so many emails on the back-channel. Oh so many emails. Regarding having a gathering of the Big Dogs to discuss Jen's lack of a dividend. The overwhelming consensus seems to yes -- "GIT-R-DONE!" And sooner -- like before 12/31/12 -- appears to be much preferred over later. For annual return calculation purposes, don't u know. A gathering in mid-November in Boca seems to be favored by the majority. And it has been suggested that the fine folks at FMR LLC should underwrite the gathering. Since they will be receiving the Biggest check. Apparently they need to "take it to committee". Coordination of frac jet schedules by some of the lesser-check-receivers is underway. Hopefully we can get like 60% of the Big Dog owners of this company there. Keep those emails coming. Best.</Msg><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1351442774198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 12:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351443113625-8</Id><Topic><Title>the whole Tegra program is done, dead, burried, enterré</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1351439197553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 11:46:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH MY... more doom from whosunw "missing out a whole A15 product generation" it's just beginning... will last for years... "Denver - if he can't strung other people's proven cores together, how in the world he is going to design a processor that can beat ARM's own 64 bit???? " blah blah balh tell us about Project Denver... any info at all... rather you have NO CLUE...NONE !!!!!!! "nvda is done, you can stick a fork into it." how much did you short...??</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351443113625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 12:51:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351445668165-9</Id><Title>TSMC Predicts Slump, Stakes 2013 Rebound Hopes on 28 nm Mobile Chips</Title><Msg>TSMC posts record profit, but warns of slowing orders from chip designers like NVIDIA and Qualcomm Financials for Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Comp., Ltd. (TPE:2330) one of the world's largest third-party chip fabricators were impressive for the third calendar quarter of 2012. The Taiwanese chipmaker raked in T$49.3 ($1.69B USD) in profits -- a record and substantially better than the T$45.3 ($1.55B USD) prediction by 22 analysts in a Thomson Reuters I/B/E/S poll. Gross margin a measure of return on sales was 48.8 percent (higher is better) and net revenue was T$141.4 ($4.84B USD). I. From Fast-Lane Straight to Slowdown But like other large chipmakers -- like Intel Corp. (INTC) -- TSMC is offering up a pessimistic outlook for the rest of the year, warning of slowing sales. TSMC warns that end users -- like automakers and computermakers -- are reducing purchase orders to its clients -- which include Qualcomm, Inc. (QCOM), Texas Instruments, Inc. (TXN), and NVIDIA Corp. (NVDA). Those chip designers are responding by cutting production with third-party fabs like TSMC. The net result is a slowdown in the entire food chain. The last year has been very kind to TSMC's clients, but the next half-year is unlikely to be. The apparent driver of the bearish chip turn is a slow global economy, which in turn has dented expectations for consumer demand for Q4 2012 and Q1 2013. Broadcom Corp. (BRCM) and LSI Corp. (LSI) two of TSMC's fab peers, joined it in offering up pessimistic outlooks. II. Weathering the Storm While the slowdown is bad news for everyone, TSMC is confident it can weather the storm a bit better than most. It's already starting see payoff in its 28 nm logic chip lines. As TSMC was the first major chipmaker outside of Intel to hit this small a node on the logic chip production side, its stock is being hotly sought after by Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (AMD), NVIDIA, and others, both in the mobile and the traditional PC markets. In the last quarter 28 nm logic chip sales accounted for 13 percent of TSMC's total revenue, twice the sales of the previous quarter. TSMC also believes that its strong ties to the mobile industry will cause it to take less of a hit, as customers tend to turn to cheaper mobile devices, rather than traditional PCs in a struggling economy. Between those two mitigating factors TSMC predicts that while revenue will drop on a year-to-year basis for Q4 and have another "modest dip" in Q1 2013, that it will rebound by Q2 2013. Chairman Morris Chang told investors and reporters, "We think the reason (for rebound in Q2) is the strength of mobile demand. We expect mobile products to be strong for a number of years." TSMC continues to try aggressively to stay ahead of other third-party fabs and keep pace with Intel via an aggressive capital commitment to die shrinks. It plans to spend $8.3B USD in total this year, with spending next year "in the same ballpark".</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351445668165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 13:34:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351450399156-10</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC Predicts Slump, Stakes 2013 Rebound Hopes on 28 nm Mobile Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351445668165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 13:34:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It appears that Jen has chopped his orders for chips, -- from his sole chip supplier TSMC -- but didn't bother to tell his hapless shareholders. So TSMC is offering up a Pessimistic Outlook for the rest of the year. It's good that we can learn the Grim Truth from TSMC, right? In excerpts. "Like other large chipmakers -- like Intel Corp. -- TSMC is offering up a Pessimistic Outlook for the rest of the year, warning of Slowing Sales. TSMC warns that end users -- like automakers and computermakers -- are Reducing Purchase Orders to its clients -- which include... NVIDIA Corp. (NVDA). Those chip designers are responding by cutting production with third-party fabs like TSMC. The apparent driver of the Bearish chip turn is a Slow Global Economy, which in turn has Dented expectations for consumer demand for Q4 2012 and Q1 2013. A slowing global economy has TSMC warning of weak results in Q4 2012." TSMC is offering up a Pessimistic Outlook for the rest of the year, warning of Slowing Sales.</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1351450399156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 14:53:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351450770350-11</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC Predicts Slump, Stakes 2013 Rebound Hopes on 28 nm Mobile Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351445668165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 13:34:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"DRATS! -- Foiled Again!", curses Jen. "Why can't that TSMC Chairman Morris Chang just keep his mouth shut?"</Msg><Username>bestsays</Username><Timestamp>1351450770350</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 14:59:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351450896471-12</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC Predicts Slump, Stakes 2013 Rebound Hopes on 28 nm Mobile Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351445668165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 13:34:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple's future chips will be TSMC... appears nothing new from Apple for some time then...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351450896471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:01:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351451677248-13</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC Predicts Slump, Stakes 2013 Rebound Hopes on 28 nm Mobile Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351445668165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 13:34:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed Best. That TSMC Morris Chang guy is a carnival barker's worst nightmare.</Msg><Username>good_point_best</Username><Timestamp>1351451677248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:14:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351452687313-14</Id><Title>14's to 12, bad news baked in? Yes, of course..tmsc news tells the story</Title><Msg>glad I pulled back on ownership of shares, but I still expect existing shares to perform. NVDA, time to use that cash and diversify....I don't know, buy a fashion company or something..... It's time to transform!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1351452687313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:31:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351452778397-15</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC Predicts Slump, Stakes 2013 Rebound Hopes on 28 nm Mobile Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351445668165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 13:34:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, Apple's future is TSMC... obviously, no new Apple chips for some time..</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351452778397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:32:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351456176827-16</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC Predicts Slump, Stakes 2013 Rebound Hopes on 28 nm Mobile Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351445668165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 13:34:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It looks like Jen must chop his guidance now. Who's gonna believe his fanciful guidance when the guy making 100% of nvidia's chips says Jen's purchase orders are Slumping?</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1351456176827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 16:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351457216113-17</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC Predicts Slump, Stakes 2013 Rebound Hopes on 28 nm Mobile Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351445668165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 13:34:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but if Apple is going forward with TSMC... obviously, no new chips from Apple for awhile...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351457216113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 16:46:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351458142485-18</Id><Title>indilinx company own by OCZ their chip products good for Nvidia</Title><Msg>indilinx company own by OCZ their chip products good for Nvidia</Msg><Username>vietnam_microsoft</Username><Timestamp>1351458142485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 17:02:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351464861551-19</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC Predicts Slump, Stakes 2013 Rebound Hopes on 28 nm Mobile Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351445668165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 13:34:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD tried GF... I'm sure Jensen is leary... NVidia has taped out test chips from Austin fab...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351464861551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 18:54:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351473423380-20</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC Predicts Slump, Stakes 2013 Rebound Hopes on 28 nm Mobile Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351445668165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 13:34:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The lead-in sentence kinda tells it all, right boys? "TSMC warns of slowing orders from chip designers like NVIDIA." They even graciously put it in BOLD TYPE for ya. Ha ha ha ha! Ah! The sweet aroma of plunging nvda in the morning.</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1351473423380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 21:17:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351482898030-21</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: All US stock and options markets will be closed on Monday, and likely remain closed on Tuesday</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1351481672935</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 23:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Monday is a great day for Jen to finally chop his guidance. Since nobody will be around to read it. And by Wednesday, it'll be "old" news, right boys?</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1351482898030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 23:54:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>