<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-18"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345263548000-1</Id><Topic><Title>My my my. So Many options expiring Friday.</Title><Username>ct.bestula</Username><Timestamp>1345170742000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 22:32:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Versus the institutional investment management world where VWAP (Volume Weighted Average Price) and multi-day VWAP (like VWAP 3 day) are the only metrics that count -- option expirations seem like a crude game played by cave men. Fun to play and watch, but very very crude. Does it make sense to have tens of millions of dollars worth of trades focused on where the price of a stock is at one point-in-time? 4:00:00 EST on a Friday. Nope. It doesn't. Options expirations are ripe to be manipulated by the Really Big Dogs. And they are. Each and every Fryday. Options will eventually be priced on VWAP too. Maybe even a multi-day VWAP closing price. Which will remove the Friday afternoon fun-and-games of who's got the bigger wallet. And exponentially increase the amount of capital that would be required to toss a thinner stock -- like nvda -- around like a rag doll. Yes. VWAP option pricing would take much of the fun out of options. But it would result in a much fairer game of chance for the little tykes. -</Msg><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1345263548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:19:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345276854000-2</Id><Topic><Title>poll!! Is it okay to alledge manipulation?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1345223182000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 13:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- "Is it okay to allege manipulation?" Da boyz and I -- we didn't witness nuthin'. Ain't that right, boyz? Other than what sounded by a car backfiring, it was just a normal Fryday afternoon. Where the stock price makes a perfectly straight line. For four hours. Capiche? Ciao. -</Msg><Username>ciao.best</Username><Timestamp>1345276854000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 04:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>44</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345278875000-3</Id><Topic><Title>poll!! Is it okay to alledge manipulation?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1345223182000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 13:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- "Leave the gun. Take their cannoli." -</Msg><Username>mister_bnh</Username><Timestamp>1345278875000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 04:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>44</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345280255000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon Kindle Fire 2 rumors and expectations</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1345177879000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 00:31:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>back to school almost over. There's really no technical reason for any more delays. It's not like a year ago when amzn could not have come out with Hollywood even if they had wanted to since T3 was no where near ready, regardless of what lies Jen was telling. If we don't see any new T3 devices in a week, I would say there won't be any because if would mean amzn made another tactical U-turn. Again. My guess, just a $149 Fire 1. Remember now, for $5, amzn can resell Asus tablet or Acer tablet with their own amzn store app pre-loaded. Why do their own and risk &gt;&gt;$100M?</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1345280255000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 04:57:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>24</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345280809000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Barrons: HP forms new "tablet unit"</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1345225081000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 13:38:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you even have any idea what happened with MeeGoo? you are just shamelessly bashing anything non-nvda, until nvda gets in bed with them and then viola, black turned into white.... by all indications, MeeGoo was a winner in the markets that Nokia did release a MeeGoo phone into. just that elop couldn't care less about MeeGoo and simply killed it to go winphone.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1345280809000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 05:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345290287000-6</Id><Topic><Title>nVidia’s GTX 660 Ti is out still can’t beat AMD’s HD 7950 for the same price.</Title><Username>impulse9266</Username><Timestamp>1345138173000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 13:29:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My bad...key guys leaving in droves is "old news," got it. I guess I am not as tuned into the AMD death spiral as you. I guess the $300 million they borrowed last week went to putting adds on monster.com...ROTFL. Speaking of cash, they could have just borrowed it from NVDA. Oh, Oracle of all things AMD, please update on on AMDs cash posiiton, or do they not talk about that on gamersandzit-popping.com...LOL...this is child abuse, I'll stop now.</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1345290287000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345293716000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon Kindle Fire 2 rumors and expectations</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1345177879000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 00:31:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look for the low price of the Amazon 10 inch. Same reasons as the Kindle fire worked. And if it works for them how about a netflix tablet!!! Got to have the first mover advantage. I'm staying for this show. It's gonna get good! Oh! Forgot the Facebook tablet! Anyone else I should add?</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1345293716000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:41:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345300387000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Barrons: HP forms new "tablet unit"</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1345225081000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 13:38:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"by all indications, MeeGoo was a winner" That is just bovine excreta. Share what are you smoking so we can all enjoy the same dream world you must live in. By all indications MeGo was a complete and utter failure.</Msg><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1345300387000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345301034000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Barrons: HP forms new "tablet unit"</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1345225081000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 13:38:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"do you even have any idea what happened with MeeGoo? " Android killed Meego... EOM !!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345301034000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:43:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345301205000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Holding on to NVDA! Gonna Rise like Bread...</Title><Username>floydosborne976</Username><Timestamp>1345293386000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:36:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That looks awesome, glad I found this when I did.</Msg><Username>paulosborne667</Username><Timestamp>1345301205000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>27</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345303822000-11</Id><Title>MSFT to build more than 3m Surface tablets: IDC</Title><Msg>http://news.cnet.com/8301-10805_3-57495666-75/microsoft-to-build-more-than-3-million-surface-tablets-says-idc/</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1345303822000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:30:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345304947000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Barrons: HP forms new "tablet unit"</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1345225081000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 13:38:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not to nit pick, but this is a favorite quote and shouldn't be mis attributed: "Better to remain silent and be thought a fool, than to speak and remove all doubt." - by Lincoln, Abraham. http://www.quotationspage.com/quote/29375.html</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1345304947000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:49:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345307880000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Amazing !!!</Title><Username>rhodyssj460</Username><Timestamp>1345302961000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:16:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Worthless bs and nothing mofe by these noise makers</Msg><Username>thekindaguyiyam</Username><Timestamp>1345307880000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:38:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345309346000-14</Id><Title>Onlive cloud gaming, shutting down or transfer?</Title><Msg>Something weird going on there. Go google search. Some say shut down, some say changing ownership.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1345309346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345310280000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Onlive cloud gaming, shutting down or transfer?</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1345309346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OnLive, a well-known video game streaming service, on Friday unexpectedly fired all of its staff and filed an alternative to bankruptcy, a status that provides companies in financial trouble a level of protection from creditors. The company does not shut down its services, but the current legal entity behind the OnLive brand will cease to exist, while another one will be created. All Out Earlier today a report broke through claiming that OnLive popular servicer called an all hands meeting, where they fired the entire crew and, perhaps, revealed some of their next steps. One of them is, potentially, the creation of a new company that would continue with the OnLive services. Some of the employees may regain their positions in the new company, but no additional details have been revealed at this point. “I wanted to send a note that by the end of the day today, OnLive as an entity will no longer exist. Unfortunately, my job and everyone was included. A new company will be formed and the management of the company will be in contact with you about the current initiatives in place,” an unknown source told Mashable web-site. Meanwhile, the staff reportedly started to blame chief executive of OnLive for not selling the business, like competing Gaikai video game streaming service, to a big company or a strategic investor. It could provide the funds necessary to continue enhancing the data centers needed to operate the video games streaming services. Apparently, the company had been approached with takeover offers several times, but its chief executive officer rejected the idea. OnLive on Friday filed an assignment for the benefit of creditors, which according to U.S. law generally implies a contract whereby the insolvent entity (Assignor) transfers legal and equitable title, as well as custody and control of its property, to a third party (Assignee) in trust, to apply the proceeds of sale to the assignor's creditors in accord with priorities established by law. Patents Work, Services Carry On It is important to point out that OnLive reportedly holds a number of patents covering cloud-distributed content, especially in 3D graphics, a portfolio that may become tremendously important these days. Without any doubts, the investors will continue to capitalize on them even if the service itself becomes unviable. It looks like this is not the case, though. The services will remain operational as the new company takes everything over. "Let me be clear. We are not going out of business," said Brian Jaquet, OnLive’s director of corporate communications.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1345310280000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:18:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345310351000-16</Id><Title>Motorola seeks to stop Apple!</Title><Msg>http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/tech/news/hardware/Motorola-files-new-patent-case-against-Apple/articleshow/15543370.cms? Couldn't happen to a nicer company. How will it feel to not be able to sell Ipads Iphones Isucks. Beginning to look like mutually assured destruction.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1345310351000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345310557000-17</Id><Title>Gamestop to launch cloud gaming 2013</Title><Msg>GameStop to launch cloud gaming service Spawn in summer 2013, with a major tweak By Dave Tach on August 16, 2012 09:24 pm Email @dptach 8COMMENTS 0 GameStop plans to launch its cloud gaming service, Spawn, in summer 2013 on "PCs, tablets, and connected TVs," according to Tony Bartel, GameStop's president. "Based on consumer feedback, our success in selling mobile devices and the imminent launch of new consoles, we have decided to move our technology to a PC-based model," Bartel said in a conference call today. "Customers tell us that they prefer to leverage cloud gaming to power their mobile occasions, and we are in active conversations with publishers and developers to leverage our patented game virtualization technology to deliver hundreds of games to PCs, tablets, and connected TVs. We expect to launch this new service in the summer of 2013." "HUNDREDS OF GAMES" FOR PCS, TABLETS, AND CONNECTED TVS GameStop purchased Spawn Labs in 2011, acquiring technology to stream video games. Unlike competitors like OnLive, which only virtualize and stream Windows PC games, the Spawn Labs idea works with any video source, allowing for console game streaming. The technology, however, requires that a separate console each with its own disc be set up for each player, which has presented challenges in scaling the service. Bartel's statement can imply two different possibilities. First, that GameStop would move away from streaming console games at all, modifying the Spawn formula to stream Windows PC games and thereby directly compete with OnLive. The other possibility is that, by focusing on "PCs, tablets, and connected TVs," GameStop may still stream console games, but it won't stream them to actual game consoles. The press release annoucing the Spawn Labs acquisition said that GamesStop wanted to bring "access to a wide selection of high-definition video games on demand on any Internet-enabled device." Today's announcement appears to be more limited in scope. We reached out to GameStop for clarification, and a representative reiterated Bartel's statement above from earlier today rather than offering additional detail. The announcement may also signal a shift from the company's traditional focus on selling new and used console games to a more PC-focused business model, which would include both games and services like Spawn. Earlier today, GameStop announced that, despite an 11.1 percent drop in global sales, its digital revenue increased 27 percent. VIAGAMASUTRA SOURCEGAMESTOPSEEKING ALPHA RELATED ITEMSSTREAMINGGAMESTOPSPAWNSTREAMING GAMESONLIVESPAWN LABSGAME STREAMINGTONY BARTEL THERE ARE 8 COMMENTS. LOAD EM UP!</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1345310557000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:22:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345310563000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon Kindle Fire 2 rumors and expectations</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1345177879000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 00:31:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- In excerpts. Amazon’s Kindle Fire WAS one of the best things to have happened to the Struggling Android tablet computer market. But then came Jeff Bezos who reinvented the wheel and showed people how to really make an iPad-killer. Well, of course, the Fire didn't kill the iPad, nor did it threaten its dominance, it did in fact pave the way for Google’s amazing new Nexus 7 tablet. Kindle Fire’s stint at tablet dominance was Short Lived, as Apple and Google quickly got hold of the market. Consequently, the onus is on Amazon to deliver something special again. Kindle Fire 2, the rumored successor to Kindle Fire is all set to be released this year. No release date has been confirmed yet but rumors suggest that it might show up as early as August 31st. So, what will Fire 2 bring along? And what to expect from it? Let’s find out. Bigger Screen: A 9-inch one? A 10-inch one maybe? We don’t know. Price: Rumors suggest, Fire 2 will be priced at $199. Kindle Fire’s price was one of its biggest killer features that made it so popular. Better Display: Kindle Fire 2 will have a better display as compared to its predecessor. We really hope that it’s much better than what Nexus 7 offers. Better Performance: We have no ideas as to which processors or how much memory Fire 2 will come with. Operating System: Amazon’s customized version of Android will make its appearance again. Though not everyone’s impressed by it. Also, Amazon’s app store might get revamped or more apps might be added to it. Using Amazon’s app store is a pretty bad idea. Google Play store already houses millions of apps, most of which Kindle Fire users can’t install. This is a huge bottleneck when compared to what Nexus 7 offers. Camera, GPS might show up: Unlike its predecessor, Fire 2 might include cameras and/or GPS. We might also get to see microphone and other interesting features. Overall, we hope that the Kindle Fire 2... should bring something really unique and surprising to the table. Otherwise, Google Nexus 7 will simply crush Fire 2 even before it takes flight." "Crushed even before it takes flight." The Kindle Fire 2 sounds like a scratch, boys. -</Msg><Username>itsascratch</Username><Timestamp>1345310563000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:22:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345311404000-19</Id><Title>Sony ceontalks importance of cloud gaming</Title><Msg>The PlayStation 4 is still just a rumor, but Sony CEO Kaz Hirai's increasing emphasis on cloud gaming hints at what the console will be. There will be a PlayStation 4. It might be called Orbis. It may or may not play used games, but it will very likely play Blu-ray discs as well as video games downloaded from the PlayStation Network. It’ll do everything the PlayStation 3 does today, and the games will be prettier with more advanced physics. That’s what a new console is supposed to do. It’s what they’ve always done. PlayStation 4 will do more though. It will almost certainly be the first video game console from an established industry leader to make cloud-based streaming gaming a central part of its business. “We need to make sure that we continue our success in the entertainment space—in the music space, in the video game space, and in motion pictures. That’s an area where we are profitable, and it needs to continue to grow,” Sony CEO Kaz Hirai told Business Week. Until 2012, Hirai was president of Sony Computer Entertainment and was largely responsible for rehabilitating Sony’s console business after the PlayStation 3’s disappointing 2006 debut. Now he hopes to rehabilitate all of Sony’s businesses, by unifying them through all its hardware and cloud services. “People are moving more and more to the mobile space, the two keywords, and you’ll probably hear this from everybody: smartphones and tablets. Related to that is moving a lot of things to the cloud,” said Hirai, “In regards to the cloud, one of the things that you probably saw is our acquisition of a company called Gaikai. That is a company that’s going to propel the movement of the video game business into the cloud space very quickly.” Gaikai isn’t the only purchase Sony’s made this summer in building its nascent cloud-based entertainment business. Earlier this week, Sony announced its intent to gain full ownership of Japanese broadband company So-Net so it can “advance the pursuit of cloud services and interactive entertainment experiences in Japan and Asia.” Sony built its global empire on selling hardware and controlling the physical medium that people consumed entertainment on, a company of materials first and foremost. Its business was Walkmans, televisions, CDs, and DVDs. It’s desperately clung to that past in the last decade, hoping Blu-ray and devices like PlayStation Vita would somehow, someway keep earning the cash that Sony’s goods did in the past. It’s over though. Digital won. Now Hirai’s working overtime to make sure Sony is ready for a future when even digital goods aren’t stored on your hardware. Read between his comments, and the PlayStation 4 takes on a very clear shape as a streaming device.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1345311404000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:36:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345312602000-20</Id><Topic><Title>BULLISH</Title><Username>tamara_jackson65</Username><Timestamp>1345306874000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:21:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't Believe This WOW</Msg><Username>sophia_isaiah45</Username><Timestamp>1345312602000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:56:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345312721000-21</Id><Topic><Title>poll!! Is it okay to alledge manipulation?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1345223182000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 13:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Look at the bright side, boys. Having a perfectly straight line stock price. For four hours. Is better than it's usual late afternoon plunge. Right boys? -</Msg><Username>best_was_here</Username><Timestamp>1345312721000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:58:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>44</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345313282000-22</Id><Title>Intel's Xeon Phi</Title><Msg>Intel's "MIC" Xeon Phi die has 62 cores, and was aimed for clocks much higher than 1GHz to fight Nvidia GK110 http://vr-zone.com/articles/intel-s-mic-xeon-phi-die-has-62-cores-and-was-aimed-for-clocks-much-higher-than-1ghz-to-fight-nvidia-gk110/17019.html</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345313282000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:08:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>79</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345314299000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Xeon Phi</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345313282000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:08:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- In excerpts. "The B0 sample list is topped by 1+ GHz 61 core part, enough to reach roughly 1 TFLOPs DP performance peak, akin to AMD's top level, just released, FirePro W9000 card - except that the Intel offering has More RAM, 8 GB on a 512-bit bus, vs 6 GB on a 384-bit bus on AMD. Xeon Phi is a sort of mutated X86 with less of some post-Pentium stuff but plenty of SIMD resources superior even to AVX, a 512-bit wide unit on each core with FMA, compared to 256-bit wide without FMA on the current Ivy Bridge (Haswell will add FMA, though - but only in 2014 for workstations and servers). The real competitor that Intel aims Xeon Phi at is, of course the infamous Nvidia. While its first generation of Kepler chips had near non-existent double precision FP performance, and not exactly great single precision FP either, the upcoming (yearend?) GK110 chip, supposed to show up in expensive Tesla K20 cards, then the workstation Quadros, before (if) any are left for the GeForce gaming, should solve that problem - it's claimed to have near 1.5 TFLOPs DP peak speed limit. Now, Nvidia is rushing to show off at least some of these in time for the SC supercomputer conference in Salt Lake City this November, but maybe at the cost of reduced performance on those initial samples. Either way, Intel's real target was to have a full 62-core (yes, that many are on the die itself) Xeon Phi run at about 1.3 GHz, or even more for selected speed bins, to match the claimed speed of GK110 before the latter even appears! What seems to stand in the way are the yields, both in terms of core count and for the frequency delivered. What I heard this weekend is that Intel is feverishly working on fixing these two too, so that they can Spoil Nvidia's chances at SC show too - remember, this Larrabee follow-on is, after all, &gt; made in 22 nm process &lt; giving them a half-node edge over Nvidia and AMD. Another aspect is, of course, that the simple recompile usually sufficient to make the codes work on Phi beats CUDA porting time by a factor of ten. This is a big advantage." http://vr-zone.com/articles/intel-s-mic-xeon-phi-die-has-62-cores-and-was-aimed-for-clocks-much-higher-than-1ghz-to-fight-nvidia-gk110/17019.html#ixzz23vGv7v6v Intel's Xeon Phi -- The nvidia Kepler Killer. It's good to see Intel making use of all those patents Jen gave them unlimited rights to use. Right boys? -</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1345314299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:24:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>88</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345314519000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Xeon Phi</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345313282000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:08:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- "Intel's real target was to have a full 62-core (yes, that many are on the die itself) Xeon Phi run at about 1.3 GHz, or even more for selected speed bins, to match the claimed speed of [nvidia's] GK110 Before the Latter Even Appears!" Oh my! My my my. The nvidia GK110 Kepler could be a scratch, boys. -</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1345314519000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:28:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>89</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345314955000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Xeon Phi</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345313282000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:08:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- So Best? This late-breaking news of Intel's Xeon Phi ABSOLUTELY CRUSHING the nvidia GK110 Kepler before it even appears, -- it's not yet priced into the nvda stock price, is it? Could be Southbound on Monday, boys. -</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1345314955000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:35:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>88</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345315267000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Xeon Phi</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345313282000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:08:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- And Best? How is Jen ever going to pay for all that R&amp;D if Intel is making his not-yet-launched Kepler GK110 Obsolete? DOA Kepler chips do not make for a good ROA. -</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1345315267000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:41:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>88</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345316753000-27</Id><Title>ask_pest, it sure feels good to give yourself five-star ratings..does</Title><Msg>doesn't it? Not just one, but dozens of them. It is all free from Yahoo... LMAO!</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1345316753000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:05:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345316965000-28</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT to build more than 3m Surface tablets: IDC</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1345303822000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:30:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that 3m is windoz8 and winRT. If split 50/50, that's 1.5M tegra 3 for the rest of the year for msft = $30M for the rest of the year. Just pocket change. A lot of parts are moving, getting pushed around by the success of Nexus. First casualty being Kindle Fire 2. And Jen probably counted all his eggs before they are hatched for Q3. He ain't going to make his raised forecasts. Unless msft sells the SurfaceRT at $200, Jen ain't going to come even close to his numbers for the rest of the year. Somebody had better bring out a 10" for $300 - amzn, goog, somebody big.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1345316965000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345316986000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Xeon Phi</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345313282000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:08:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont you mean unlimited rights for five years? Its always interesting what your posts choose not to mention. After 5 years of Intel playing around with those valuable patents, creating chips and platforms using proprietary technology developed by nvidia, those platforms may become revenue streams for nvidia via licensing There's a bit of Intel in every computer in the world.</Msg><Username>pennyforabuck</Username><Timestamp>1345316986000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:09:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>20</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345317338000-30</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT to build more than 3m Surface tablets: IDC</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1345303822000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:30:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>to go with missing sales, Jen is going to get stuck with a huge Tegra 3 inventory problem by the end of the Q.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1345317338000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:15:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345318089000-31</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT to build more than 3m Surface tablets: IDC</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1345303822000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:30:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and some other tacky stuff still foaming from the corners of your mouth....</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1345318089000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:28:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345319845000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Xeon Phi</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345313282000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:08:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- You boys have clearly never actually read the terms of the PATENT CROSS LICENSE AGREEMENT BETWEEN NVIDIA CORPORATION AND INTEL CORPORATION, dated January 10, 2011. Here. Allow Best to educate you boys. Again. http://download.intel.com/pressroom/legal/Intel_Nvidia_2011_Redacted.pdf "4.1. Term. This Agreement and the rights and licenses granted hereunder shall become effective on the Effective Date, and shall continue in effect until the expiration of the last patent licensed hereunder to expire unless such rights and licenses are sooner terminated by a Party pursuant to Section 4.2. Except as expressly set forth in Sections 4.2(a) or 4.2(b), neither this Agreement nor any of the rights or licenses granted herein may be terminated for any reason." “Capture Period” shall mean any time on or prior to March 31, 2017. So Jen has given Intel the right to make rapious use of, -- and "continue in effect until the expiration of the last patent licensed hereunder" -- ALL (100%) of nvidia's patents through the "Capture Period" of March 31, 2017. Capture 'em for a six (6) year period. And Intel can use those patents until they expire. No additional future licensing by Intel required, boys. None. Looks like Intel's King Otellini got the Deal of the Century, boys. THE Deal of the Century. Oh, and pennyforabuck? Please UNDERSTAND what you are talking about. Before wasting our pixels with your nonsense FUD messages. -</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1345319845000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>88</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345320109000-33</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT to build more than 3m Surface tablets: IDC</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1345303822000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:30:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what a mess you have a ceo who is drinking his own Koolaid, believes in how own b s just because nexus moved, he is into 'really takes this long to develop OS, eco system... from now on there will be a steady market for Android tablet and all the potential orders will all be booked....' he ain't going to come even close to his Q3 forecast.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1345320109000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 16:01:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345323457000-34</Id><Topic><Title>My my my. So Many options expiring Friday.</Title><Username>ct.bestula</Username><Timestamp>1345170742000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 22:32:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- It appears that those who control the price of nvda stock made a clear, deliberate and very bold statement on Fryday. Pinning the stock price to $14.65 for four (4) hours. That's the price they apparently needed to maximize the profit on their book of nvda options written. And that's what they did. Pinned it -- to the price they needed. Only a fool would ignore their Awesome Power. To effectively play "Name That Price". Of your precious nvda. -</Msg><Username>best.etal</Username><Timestamp>1345323457000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 16:57:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345325326000-35</Id><Topic><Title>poll!! Is it okay to alledge manipulation?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1345223182000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 13:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- So Best? Maybe the S&amp;P 500 folks should re-examine if nvda belongs in their S&amp;P 500 Index? Having a liquid, functioning Market for the stock is important, right? That's what the S&amp;P 500 folks say. Take a look. http://www.nvidia.com/object/IO_20011129_5344.html "The S&amp;P 500 Index consists of 500 stocks chosen for market size, LIQUIDITY, and industry group representation." So if little nvda now gets rag-dolled on a regular basis on every options expiry Fryday -- like some swarthy Canadian pink sheeter -- and their industry reputation ain't the best, maybe they no longer belong among the S&amp;P 500 Index of decent, liquid, stocks. -</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1345325326000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 17:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>42</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345325590000-36</Id><Topic><Title>poll!! Is it okay to alledge manipulation?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1345223182000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 13:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Good point, Best. Getting your stock price pinned to $4.65 for four (4) hours isn't exactly the kind of liquid, freely-trading stock that the S&amp;P 500 Index folks are looking for. I think they should delete nvda from their Index. For trading so badly. -</Msg><Username>good_point_best</Username><Timestamp>1345325590000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 17:33:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>43</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345327577000-37</Id><Topic><Title>poll!! Is it okay to alledge manipulation?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1345223182000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 13:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- So Master? Broadcom or Freescale would make nice replacements for nvidia. In the S&amp;P 500 Index. But they're already Members too. Could the S&amp;P 500 folks delete nvidia for trading badly, and count one of those others Twice? Until a better semiconductor stock comes along. Say, come to think of it, if Apple's semiconductor subsidiary ever gets spun-off and goes public, that would be the iPerfect substitute for nvda. It's twice as large as all of nvidia. And just captured another 11.5% market share for ALL tablets sold on the planet. So Apple's semiconductor subsidiary now has something like Seventy Percent (70%) market share for tablet processors. Would make a nice substitution for nvda in the S&amp;P 500 Index. Right boys? -</Msg><Username>best.clone185</Username><Timestamp>1345327577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:06:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>44</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345328254000-38</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT to build more than 3m Surface tablets: IDC</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1345303822000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:30:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WTF do you care what NVDA does in tegra sales.. let alone what others think ... STFU....</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1345328254000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345328650000-39</Id><Title>BEST truly a loser..</Title><Msg>Doesn't work for a firm yet dedicates his life towards anonymous message board harassment.... full time harassing.. for nothing.. but a massive chip on his shoulder from life savings loses in RMBS. To think of all the other stocks you could have thrown your life towards.. I mean literally any other stock... And to think you have the nerve to comment on investing in tech stocks... HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA H.A Can you say Greek tragedy/comedy...</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1345328650000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:24:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345329737000-40</Id><Topic><Title>BEST truly a loser..</Title><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1345328650000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Ever notice what really tips 'em over? The paid pumper boys that is. Analysis and discussion of their precious nvda getting deleted from the S&amp;P 500 Index. For trading badly. Witness the scandalous and rapacious trading in nvda on Fryday, where some hedgie pinned the price of their precious nvda to $14.65 for four (4) hours. Tips 'em over Every time. And then they start their lame personal attacks on Best. A sad sad way to earn a meager paycheck, right boys? -</Msg><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1345329737000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:42:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345330408000-41</Id><Topic><Title>BEST truly a loser..</Title><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1345328650000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just want to know why you waste so much time doing what you do.. what's the motivation/reward...? You are like some obscure psychological experiment ... describe yourself as to why you do this ... because the only that pops in my head is LOSER......</Msg><Username>mikeywalson</Username><Timestamp>1345330408000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:53:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345330716000-42</Id><Title>Lenovo not worried about MS's Surface RT, expects to beat it</Title><Msg>Lenovo is most certainly NOT QUITTING.. Like whoBroad had predicted.....more eggs on her face! http://www.pcadvisor.co.uk/news/software/3376494/lenovo-not-worried-about-microsofts-surface-tablet-expects-beat-it/</Msg><Username>lordgaga81</Username><Timestamp>1345330716000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:58:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345334778000-43</Id><Title>Time for the run up to $22.42</Title><Msg>August options are wiped out so it's time to let 'er rip for all the product launches with Tegra for Q3. Google, Apple, Amazon, Microsoft, Lenovo, etc. Earnings will be up 20% just on current estimates alone. http://finance.yahoo.com/q/ae?s=NVDA+Analyst+Estimates $1.08 from $.90 Revenue will explode by at least another 800M to go to $5.19B from $4.39 this year, imho. That's an 8.5% increase from $4.78B revenue estimates which I anticipate will be $1.18 in earnings for next year vs. $1.08 estimates. That's a 19 p/e @ $22.42 per share and is very realistic with this exciting product cycle ramping up with quad-core tablets and quad-core smart phones. http://finance.yahoo.com/q/ta?s=NVDA+Basic+Tech.+Analysis&amp;t=2y</Msg><Username>tech_six_sense</Username><Timestamp>1345334778000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 20:06:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345340243000-44</Id><Topic><Title>Helpful Analysis</Title><Username>ebentxw773</Username><Timestamp>1345295445000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great return</Msg><Username>catiespz553</Username><Timestamp>1345340243000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 21:37:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345342620000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Amazing !!!</Title><Username>rhodyssj460</Username><Timestamp>1345302961000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:16:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I AM UP TODAY!</Msg><Username>biddieidu926</Username><Timestamp>1345342620000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 22:17:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345346457000-46</Id><Title>Nvidia heading to $11 logic</Title><Msg>1. Earnings gonna dissappoint = heading to $11 2. Not doing business with Apple ie no macpro wins= heading to $11 3. No major tablet wins, ie not in kindle fire = heading to $11 4. No notebook wins, no ones using kepker = heading to $11 But with Earnings beating, Macpro winning, Tablet nexus wininng, kepler winning; bashers still trumpeting Nvidia heading to $11. I guess to the extreme that Nvidia going into iphone processer, Nvidia still heading to $11 !!!???? Bashers logic???!!! Lol</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1345346457000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 23:20:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345347315000-47</Id><Topic><Title>Time for the run up to $22.42</Title><Username>tech_six_sense</Username><Timestamp>1345334778000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 20:06:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- "It's time to let 'er rip for all the product launches with Tegra for Q3... Apple, etc." Let's all say a big HELLO to Jen's newest Summer Intern -- tech_six_sense -- on his first day on the pumper job. Ya got a LOT to learn, son. Starting with why Apple has no use for the nvidia Tegra 3. None. -</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1345347315000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 23:35:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345348609000-48</Id><Topic><Title>poll!! Is it okay to alledge manipulation?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1345223182000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 13:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- That hedge fund that so blatantly rag-dolled nvda on Friday. What if the guy is on vacation next week? And didn't turn off his PC. And left his Black Box Market Management System running. Will we see $14.65 all week? Monday. Open $14.65 High $14.65 Low $14.65 Close $14.65 AH $14.65 Tuesday. Open $14.65 High $14.65 Low $14.65 Close $14.65 AH $14.65 Wednesday. Open $14.65 High $14.65 Low $14.65 Close $14.65 AH $14.65 Thursday. Open $14.65 High $14.65 Low $14.65 Close $14.65 AH $14.65 Friday. Open $14.65 High $14.65 Low $14.65 Close $14.65 AH $14.65 "Rise and shine campers. It's gonna be $14.65 today." -</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1345348609000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 23:56:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>43</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>