<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-29"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354168543449-1</Id><Title>Windows on ARM is dead with Surface RT flop.</Title><Msg>Long live the X86.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354168543449</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 00:55:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354168588351-2</Id><Topic><Title>Windows on ARM is dead with Surface RT flop.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354168543449</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 00:55:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just testing this message</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354168588351</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 00:56:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354169074810-3</Id><Topic><Title>Why did NVDA announce a dividend when a "special one time cash dividend would have been better for shareholders?</Title><Username>opseaime</Username><Timestamp>1354130082142</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 14:14:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so fmr best- how many logons u got anyway???? Based on your post you are long shares you wrote 'we shareholders' ??? Hmmm how many shares do you hold long? Looks like someone just got caught outing themselves eh??? lol</Msg><Username>best_the_turkey</Username><Timestamp>1354169074810</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 01:04:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354174084491-4</Id><Topic><Title>Sell AMD, NVDA and buy QCOM. QCOM 'new' chip is better... fact/ article.</Title><Username>femasux</Username><Timestamp>1354121441621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 11:50:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra 3 was designed for tablets and they have the lions share in android non-samsung market. S4 was released a few months after Tegra 3 and is obviously better performing on CPU + GPU because of A15, 28nm etc. You can bet your bottom dollar that Nvidia will trump S4 next year with Tegra 4. When it comes to packing silicon on a dye, Nvidia cannot be matched. Just see GK110 with 7.4 Billion transistor count. The problem for Nvidia is addressable BOM in a smartphone. S4 provides the following integrated in a single chip: - dual-core cpu - gpu - lte - wifi - GPS - BT - Power Management as opposed to Tegra 3 - quad-core cpu - gpu most volume smartphone will use an integrated SOC like S4 Pro and Qualcomm will be able to charge at least double the price ($40 vs $20) and still provide savings of $5-$10 on each phone for OEM. Integrated Power Management will allow QCOM to provide much better battery performance. Tegra 4 (Grey) integrates Icera 500 but it will not be able to address wifi, gps, bt and will continue providing a more complex, expensive and power in-efficient solution as opposed to QCOM.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354174084491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 02:28:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354178182524-5</Id><Topic><Title>Sell AMD, NVDA and buy QCOM. QCOM 'new' chip is better... fact/ article.</Title><Username>femasux</Username><Timestamp>1354121441621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 11:50:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nvidia will trump S4 next year with Tegra 4" Kepler GPU "When it comes to packing silicon on a dye, Nvidia cannot be matched." INtel... INtel also has advanced packaging technology... "Just see GK110 with 7.4 Billion transistor count." Yeah... "Tegra 4 (Grey) integrates Icera 500 but it will not be able to address wifi, gps, bt and will continue providing a more complex, expensive and power in-efficient solution as opposed to QCOM." Hmmm.... is a phone just a checklist... or might Tegra 4 have other features...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1354178182524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 03:36:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354179237844-6</Id><Topic><Title>Sell AMD, NVDA and buy QCOM. QCOM 'new' chip is better... fact/ article.</Title><Username>femasux</Username><Timestamp>1354121441621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 11:50:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is more than capable but they have a big company problem and are not as nimble or, driven from top as Nvidia. In any case, I see INTC as secondary threat for NVDA. QCOM is the big dog in the house when it comes to mobility. Tegra 4 may have other features - I think they already tried to integrate a multi-touch controller but I have not seen any design wins. Nvidia's key advantage has to be graphics but that is more relevant on tablets and not so much on smartphones. Icera will be poor second to QCOM when it comes to wireless performance.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354179237844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 03:53:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354194322726-7</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia, H-P shares gain as software stocks fall</Title><Username>noemireeder068</Username><Timestamp>1313163179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2011-08-12 11:32:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are increasing fixed expenses.</Msg><Username>kayleejohn672</Username><Timestamp>1354194322726</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 08:05:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354195301477-8</Id><Topic><Title>ATEN's DVI KVM products receive NVIDIA 3D Vision Ready certification</Title><Username>lynnette.spraggsvlaa</Username><Timestamp>1313597431000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2011-08-17 12:10:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very good chart analysis.</Msg><Username>kayleejohn672</Username><Timestamp>1354195301477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 08:21:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354196507222-9</Id><Topic><Title>Buy Calls</Title><Username>omar_richardson1550</Username><Timestamp>1328288674000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-02-03 12:04:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the site</Msg><Username>kayleejohn672</Username><Timestamp>1354196507222</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 08:41:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354197570452-10</Id><Title>Apple new Macs with NVDA chip: When is the announcement? tomorrow?</Title><Msg>Apple’s Super-Skinny iMac Coming Nov. 30 Email2Smaller FontTextLarger Text|Print Image credit: Apple Sure, all the kids are asking for iPads. But the adults? They might just be eyeing Apple’s super-thin new 21.5-inch iMac for the holidays. Apple announced today that the all-in-one desktop computer will hit stores on Friday, Nov. 30, for a starting price of $1,299. Apple typically refreshes its big-screened desktop every year, but this year the models didn’t just get an internal performance bump. The machine measures just 5 mm at the top edge and the IPS display has been recrafted with a new glass that has less reflection and glare. All that is matched with high-end organs — there are a range of quad-core processor options, up to 16GB of RAM, Nvidia GeForce graphics, and 1TB hard drives. Apple has actually done a bit of work on those hard drives, or what it’s calling Fusion Drives. The Fusion Drives combine fast flash or solid-state drives with older, spinning hard drives. Simply put: the Mountain Lion operating system and apps will be very snappy, but you still get a ton of storage space. The $1,299 base level 21.5-inch iMac will be available with a 2.7 GHz quad-core Intel Core i5 processor and Nvidia’s GeForce GT 640M graphics. The larger 27-inch iMac will ship in December. Apple is also expected to release the new version of iTunes before the end of this month. The company pushed the release off a month in October.</Msg><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1354197570452</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 08:59:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354198419765-11</Id><Title>NVDA down trend is still intact. See a 5 month chart.</Title><Msg>At least you can still trade it. This sector is in dire times and that's the truth and that's the truth straight way.</Msg><Username>femasux</Username><Timestamp>1354198419765</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 09:13:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354199994362-12</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA down trend is still intact. See a 5 month chart.</Title><Username>femasux</Username><Timestamp>1354198419765</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 09:13:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This board is in dire times with imbeciles like you posting blather all the time. You sound like you're from Canada?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1354199994362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 09:39:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354200206977-13</Id><Topic><Title>Why did NVDA announce a dividend when a "special one time cash dividend would have been better for shareholders?</Title><Username>opseaime</Username><Timestamp>1354130082142</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 14:14:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you been holding/trading the stock for 19 years? If so, you have most likely made huge profits from time to time as this stock has gone up and down, like most of us that have followed this company for long. It was a growth company, they don't tend to pay dividends. As they are large now, and future growth will never be as spectacular as NV was in the late 1990s early 200x, and the run up in 2008; so now they are shifting to be more of a large stable (we hope) company that does things like pay a dividend. You want a $4 dividend from your $12 stock. Yea that be great, remove most of the cash from the company so they can head the way of AMD. You are a short sighted fool. If only all American businesses were run by fools like you, there would be no surviving America Companies in a few years. Wow, the childish drivel that gets posted on this board is just astounding. No wonder I can rarely stomach reading this mess.</Msg><Username>really_chris</Username><Timestamp>1354200206977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 09:43:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354201688701-14</Id><Title>an easy pullback for options expiry, expected</Title><Msg>a controlled stock price, just have to expect it...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1354201688701</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 10:08:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354202527289-15</Id><Topic><Title>Why did NVDA announce a dividend when a "special one time cash dividend would have been better for shareholders?</Title><Username>opseaime</Username><Timestamp>1354130082142</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 14:14:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would rather see a massive buyback. Instead, we got tiny dividend and continuous dilution through options for insiders.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1354202527289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 10:22:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354205862545-16</Id><Title>CAN SOMEONE PLEASE TAKE OFF THE BRAKES</Title><Msg>this thing can't get any ground... like watching paint dry.</Msg><Username>turnqj</Username><Timestamp>1354205862545</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 11:17:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354206924918-17</Id><Title>pullback for options per nasdaq bylaws?</Title><Msg>nasdaq should publish these patterns..</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1354206924918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 11:35:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354209774888-18</Id><Topic><Title>How frustrating is this?</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354130684072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 14:24:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>same story as every day - NVDA solid under-performer</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354209774888</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 12:22:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354210027285-19</Id><Topic><Title>How frustrating is this?</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354130684072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 14:24:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL this chump tells us AFTER THE FACT how he timed all his trades jsut right. Come on junior that is like school yard #$%$ and simply points out to us all what a amtr. you are!</Msg><Username>best_the_turkey</Username><Timestamp>1354210027285</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 12:27:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354212150967-20</Id><Topic><Title>CAN SOMEONE PLEASE TAKE OFF THE BRAKES</Title><Username>turnqj</Username><Timestamp>1354205862545</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 11:17:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brakes OFF, they got it in REVERSE now! WAHTAPOS.</Msg><Username>isrhsopt</Username><Timestamp>1354212150967</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 13:02:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354219623882-21</Id><Title>Windows on ARM is dead. Next Android on ARM tablets</Title><Msg>will be dead. ARM is too slow folks. good enough for smartphones, but BAD for tablets or real computing. tegra3 is a DEAD too.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354219623882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 15:07:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354223097173-22</Id><Topic><Title>How frustrating is this?</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354130684072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 14:24:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what are the excuses for today? NVDA: Down -1.88% (YTD: Down -13.13%) QCOM: UP +1.12% (YTD: UP +15.81%) BRCM: UP +0.87% (YTD: UP +10.49%) AAPL: UP +1.09% (YTD: UP +45.52%) Lets face it - NVDA is a loser short term and long term.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354223097173</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 16:04:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354223196678-23</Id><Topic><Title>CAN SOMEONE PLEASE TAKE OFF THE BRAKES</Title><Username>turnqj</Username><Timestamp>1354205862545</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 11:17:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Been watching the tape blow by blow for the last few trading sessions and I've noticed there's a helluva lot more sellers than buyers even on up days. Also noticed some pretty big trades come thru on the sell side like in the last minute today an order came thru for 80K shares. That isn't your ordinary trader or investor. Mucho negative bias right now and I don't know how much longer it's going to take to shake it off and cease all this damn selling.</Msg><Username>cantdance123</Username><Timestamp>1354223196678</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 16:06:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354223416582-24</Id><Topic><Title>CAN SOMEONE PLEASE TAKE OFF THE BRAKES</Title><Username>turnqj</Username><Timestamp>1354205862545</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 11:17:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NVDA has been moving lower on above average volume and all this while beaten semi's have recovered 15-20%. Feels like major fund liquidation activity.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354223416582</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 16:10:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354224815694-25</Id><Topic><Title>Windows on ARM is dead. Next Android on ARM tablets</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354219623882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 15:07:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fuggedaboutit - x86 is and will always remain a power hog. Go back to school to learn about differences between CISC and RISC instruction sets. If Intel embraces ARM and fabs it on its line, the whole world will benefit. But that is too much to ask - its like asking Microsoft to embrace open-source.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1354224815694</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 16:33:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354229328778-26</Id><Topic><Title>Windows on ARM is dead. Next Android on ARM tablets</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354219623882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 15:07:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not for long! Intel is planning for a 5nm chip by 2015. They have already laid down their roadmap. Given that Bay Trail-T (x86) has already significantly reduced power consumption with a quad-core 22nm, imagine what a "5nm" could do. “According to Xbit Labs, which got its hands on some telltale slides, Paul Otellini et al. have the roadmap for 10nm, 7nm and 5nm processes locked down, and the company is preparing fabs in the states and Ireland to make chips using the 14nm fabrication method. Given that timeframe, Intel says 10nm chips will ship in 2015, with work on 5nm technology beginning that same year” -engadget</Msg><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1354229328778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 17:48:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354240803567-27</Id><Topic><Title>When are we gonna see the 1st Snapdragon S4 powered Win 8 tablet?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354238342982</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:19:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What I have noticed is Nvidia hooked up with the only major PC manufacturers that are growing...i.e. ASUS and Lenova and both have introduced Windows 8 RT tablets. Sure the Microsoft Surface with Windows 8 RT will only sell a couple of million this year. But perhaps ASUS and Lenvoa can kick in another 1M. Now who do you think Mr. Softy will remember for that next big order? Qualcomm --- Don't think so! First have to be certified Texas Instruments - They gave up and have no partners to produce Win 8 RT tablets. Nvidia - "We're here. We're on time and were willing" Different topic - Sure the next generation Kindle Fire and Barnes and Noble Nook may use the rumored but unreleased TI OMAP 5 although TI just said they are out of here. But you know TI has a long history of raising prices for Legacy Products. Mr. Brazos might not get his typical 25% cut in pricing for a product that TI has announced they don't want to sell into the consumer market anymore. LOL Freescale - They also said forget about it and dropped out. That leaves, let me think, it's on the tip of my tongue...Oh what is that company's name?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354240803567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 21:00:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354242208986-28</Id><Topic><Title>When are we gonna see the 1st Snapdragon S4 powered Win 8 tablet?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354238342982</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:19:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft may kill of Windows RT. No one is buying that crap, and its confusing everyone.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354242208986</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 21:23:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354243305337-29</Id><Topic><Title>When are we gonna see the 1st Snapdragon S4 powered Win 8 tablet?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354238342982</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:19:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL - Your alias says it all! Got any AMD real estate to sell? But seriously a couple of million Tegras per quarter - Microsoft Surface, a Million or so Lenova and Asus tablets, 2 to 3 million Google nexus 7 tablets, a couple of million HTC One X+ phones, 500K Fujitsu phones in Japan, 4 phones in China, and voila your talking about the same or better as last quarter for Tegra..... And then along came Wayne with a Nvidia Lte modem at CES 2013. Of course I defer to Getanid but Project Denver is nearing completion!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354243305337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 21:41:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354244068838-30</Id><Topic><Title>When are we gonna see the 1st Snapdragon S4 powered Win 8 tablet?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354238342982</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:19:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TI OMAP 5 still exists. They are going to sell it into the industrial and car market and Mr Brazos at Amazon can certainly buy it for a hugely profitable price for TI. Trouble is he will choke on the price and go with Nvidia. Yes I know - They are targeting the car market market where Nvidia pioneered it 3 years ago. Duh! In Bleeding Edge Tech...the profits go to the last man standing.......Nvidia is in a select group now. Qualcomm, Nvidia, and Intel knocking on the door in 2014. I really wonder who will buy Nvidia to stop this incessant reaching for the stars.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354244068838</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 21:54:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354244780789-31</Id><Topic><Title>When are we gonna see the 1st Snapdragon S4 powered Win 8 tablet?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354238342982</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:19:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. you dumbo stupid longs take note: don't even think for a minute that nvda will benefit from txn getting out of app processors. ibex already told you - nvda's not going to get that socket, somebody else would. You can take that to the bank. 2. ibex, you are so neutral, always reporting all sides of nvda, per you anyway, where are the articles that msft's cutting production for winRT?? 3. as I said, not only is winRT DOA, but the only guys coming out of this thing smelling like a rose are the guys who 'procrastinated' - HP, DELL etc. Asus was smart, they dropped prices first to get rid of inventory before everybody tries to get out the burning barn all at the same time. $100M Q4 Tegra loss coming right up! no new product in the pipe, by the end of 2013, loses should top $200M/Q. And you want the stock to do what again??</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1354244780789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 22:06:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354245777367-32</Id><Topic><Title>When are we gonna see the 1st Snapdragon S4 powered Win 8 tablet?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1354238342982</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:19:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whosunw, You have a remarkable ability to spin words to your position without posting any facts. Congrats First is HPQ and Dell growing PC market share are losing profit? Yes or No? Second are HPQ and Dell's profits growing or shrinking? Yes or No? Third are Lenova's and ASUS's PC market share and profits growing? Yes or No? Fourth - Microsoft Surface BOM costs show a larger profit than Apple gets on their flagship IPad. Yes or No? Fifth - If you were a PC mfg use to tiny margins would you not drop prices on your Windows 8 tablet. I mean after all the profit margin is 4 times larger than on a typical ultrabook. Yes or no? Note: they didn't drop prices they just under priced Microsoft at the outset. P.S. - Good Luck with your short!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1354245777367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 22:22:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354249942537-33</Id><Title>Is $12 the NEW pretend its still $16?</Title><Msg>Same cut-n-paste boys going at it. Pump that Nvidia junk. lol</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1354249942537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 23:32:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354250129233-34</Id><Title>Dow Jones Industrials closed above 13,000 today. Non-industrious nvda tanks. Tanks badly.</Title><Msg>A nice day for the Market today, boys. The Dow Jones Industrials closed above the 13,000 mark. While non-industrious, non-fab plant owning, non-chip manufacturing nvda tanked today. And Tanked badly. Let's take a look, shall we? + 4.08% __ Advancing Micro Devices, Inc. + 3.96% __ Research In Motion Limited + 2.43% __ Micron Technology, Inc. + 1.26% __ Hewlett-Packard Company + 1.12% __ Qualcomm Incorporated + 1.10% __ Apple Inc. + 0.98% __ Freescale Semiconductor, Ltd. + 0.87% __ Broadcom Corp. + 0.68% __ The Entire NASDAQ Composite Index + 0.51% __ The Average Gain on the 3,000 Stocks in the Russell 3,000 Index + 0.43% __ The Average Gain on the 500 Fine Stocks in the S &amp; P 500 Index + 0.28% __ The Dow Jones Industrious Stocks Index -- which rose above 13,000 today (- 1.79%) __ nvidia No coat-tailing the Market today, boys. For non-industrious nvda. Looks like Jim Cramer called it exactly right on 11/26/2012. "The stock has been doing ABSOLUTELY NOTHING, which is a Problem." "It's a VERY EXPENSIVE STOCK that isn't performing."</Msg><Username>lets_take_a_look_shall_we</Username><Timestamp>1354250129233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 23:35:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354251125263-35</Id><Topic><Title>Dow Jones Industrials closed above 13,000 today. Non-industrious nvda tanks. Tanks badly.</Title><Username>lets_take_a_look_shall_we</Username><Timestamp>1354250129233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 23:35:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's an educated look from a committed basher, informative, biased, but not very objective, of course designed to undermine any confidence that longs might hold for their stock. And, of course designed to accelerate your short sale profits!! Entertaining, free speech, not objective.</Msg><Username>jrdelane</Username><Timestamp>1354251125263</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 23:52:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>