<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353303604606-1</Id><Topic><Title>So Best? If Jen chopped guidance by (-15%), shouldn't the stock fall by (-15%) too?</Title><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1352775526737</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:58:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The nvda stock price has now declined ( - 9.75%) from the closing price on Thursday November 8th -- right before Jen gave his confessional about chopping guidance by (-15%) Clearly the Market, she still has a looong ways to go yet in walking this one down to it's logical price of $10.72 But she'll get there -- with the fullness of time." So Best? Maybe $10.72 by Christmas Eve? Although, the stock price does seem to be declining at a faster and faster rate here. So maybe before then?</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1353303604606</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 00:40:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353326844267-2</Id><Topic><Title>whosunw</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353292298667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 21:31:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO Wayne in Jan/CES. read ibex's post carefully: a. talks up the 'power' of Wayne. b. Grey tapes out 'this Q', and Wayne will be announced at roughly the same time frame. Ibex, when will Wayne come to market?</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1353326844267</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 07:07:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353333454795-3</Id><Topic><Title>whosunw</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353292298667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 21:31:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So the question from the nice lady is, "When will Wayne come to market?" But the answer, like everything around nvidia, well, it's difficult. Are we talking, 1. When Jen waives the first prototype Wayne in the air at a gathering of analysts? 2. When the Wayne development kit becomes available for order? 3. When Asus receives their first 100k of Wayne "engineering samples"? 4. When the first Wayne "out-of-stock-tracker" goes live? "When will Wayne come to market?" It's a difficult question for nvidia to answer.</Msg><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1353333454795</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 08:57:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353334423679-4</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA - over promise under deliver</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353102105382</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 16:41:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's illuminating to see just exactly what Jen promised for running up the R&amp;D on Tegra and getting those huge Tegra loses each Q, ref. nvda's 10Q. Instead of one R&amp;D team and working on the chips consecutively, Jen staffed up 3 R&amp;D teams. One for Denver, and two for Tegras. So instead of working on the TEgra chips consecutively, he has two Tegra chips going at the same time. Intention is to come out with chips at an annual clip to leap-frog the competition. So what has Jen delivered - while both Samsung and Qcom and aapl are getting revenue from their A15 cores, nvda's Wayne is total AWOL. If you count almost one year chip introduction to revenue, you can see how far behind the Tegra program is compared to the competitions'. nvda will receive zero revenue from Wayne all of 2013. And god knows how far into 2014 it will be before tegra sales grows again. And between now and then, Tegra sales will continue to decline. And Jen, from the last cc, is still ramping up tegra R&amp;D while Tegra 3 sales will fall off a cliff after X'mas.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1353334423679</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:13:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353334549876-5</Id><Topic><Title>whosunw</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353292298667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 21:31:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whaaaaat? NO Wayne at the January Consumer Electronics Show in January? But, but, but -- Jen already ordered his CES Best in Show trophy.</Msg><Username>good_one_best</Username><Timestamp>1353334549876</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:15:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353335988074-6</Id><Topic><Title>Some numbers from SC12 - either announced or known/confirmed</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1353212208211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 23:16:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? Will the highly energy efficient Genuine Intel Xeon Phi accelerator chips kill-off the nvidia Tesla? Which sucks juice like an Elephant. And when it happens, can Jen try to sue Intel for another handout ? For kiling yet Another nvidia business line.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1353335988074</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:39:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353336582494-7</Id><Topic><Title>whosunw</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353292298667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 21:31:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"NO Wayne in Jan/CES. read ibex's post carefully: a. talks up the 'power' of Wayne. b. Grey tapes out 'this Q', and Wayne will be announced at roughly the same time frame. Ibex, when will Wayne come to market?" ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------- OK, it's a start... Not talking about hitting the shelves, but just actual being able to demo silicon... Are you claiming there will still be NO Wayne to demo at CES ?? If still NO to CES, how about being able to demo Wayne at MWC in February ?? If I was able to read ON the lines from your previous posts, is it correct, from your view, that first demos of Wayne will be in Q3 2013 ???</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353336582494</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:49:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353337063909-8</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news: Intel CEO to retire in May</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1353336568366</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:49:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was one of the best CEOs the industry has ever seen !!! I tip my hat to him...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353337063909</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:57:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353337880530-9</Id><Title>I know Nvidia doesn't want to be acquired, but...</Title><Msg>You'd think they'd be a very attractive takeover candidate for someone -- more so with each day given their mobile positioning with Tegra. Don't you think people are trying to woo Jen on a regular basis? Is there any deal he'd actually consider taking? There's a lot of cash out there in the tech world just looking for a place to go...</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1353337880530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:11:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353338370089-10</Id><Topic><Title>whosunw</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353292298667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 21:31:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>definitely no Wayne at CES in Jan. "Wayne release roughly same time frame as Grey, which is taping out this Q" and will be nvda's first try at integrating a radio, which is not trivial. So when will Wayne be seen? anybody's guess. Like I said when ibex showed link on the 'roughly same time' bit.... nvda just pushed out Wayne to infinity. you are, were?, a mindless pumper. ibex is way more than that. No real long with his money on the line will continue to pump when such an important chip has been delayed time and time again. That is not mindless pumping. What ibex does is simple brown nosing. Q3 tegra sales $240M Q1 tegra sales $160M, and that is with the full month of Nov to ship against some X'mas sales Q2 tegra sales</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1353338370089</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:19:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353338464985-11</Id><Topic><Title>I know Nvidia doesn't want to be acquired, but...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1353337880530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:11:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" people are trying to woo Jen on a regular basis" Maybe, but folks like Jensen would make the price so high that it won't happen... "Is there any deal he'd actually consider taking?" Yes... but his one sticking point has been he has to be the CEO...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353338464985</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:21:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353339076315-12</Id><Topic><Title>whosunw</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353292298667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 21:31:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, I got your view that I can understand... btw, Ibexx has got under your skin...when I ask your views, you answer with Ibexx, Ibexx, IBEXX "you are, were?, a mindless pumper. " I might just take up your habit so I can expand my mind...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353339076315</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:31:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353339618568-13</Id><Topic><Title>I know Nvidia doesn't want to be acquired, but...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1353337880530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:11:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not long NVDA in hopes of a takeover bid being announced soon for may of the reasons you state. Having said that is it outside the bounds of reality that Jen woudl HAVE to take a price that was so lucrative to current stakeholders he and Board woudl be honor bound to accept it? Yes. Also, while I agree he needs to tbe the head of something and may be given it by suitor to get the company, sometimes these hard driven genius types dont mind trying to head the next big thing. I have little doubt in my mind Jen has been approcahed to do a deal but he may be right that the greatest return of all would come to buy and holders that stick with him for the next few years. Look, cash cushion plus lucrative new dividend is going to equal a lot of institutional participation as this cycle occurs: rotating out of INTC and slowly into NVDA and some others. sS chips in general get hot again large moves up in NVDA. Watch for it!</Msg><Username>nvda_4_ever</Username><Timestamp>1353339618568</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:40:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353339901085-14</Id><Topic><Title>If Jen doesn't get the 10-Q out next week, I'm callin' the Authorities.</Title><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1353253979585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 10:52:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? How much money did the tegra/cpb division Lose last quarter? Nobody knows, right? 'Cause the company is still dawdling-around getting their 10-Q out. In the meantime, shares and options are trading, well, blindly. Without the crucial Facts.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1353339901085</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:45:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353340309878-15</Id><Topic><Title>I know Nvidia doesn't want to be acquired, but...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1353337880530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:11:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Jen woudl HAVE to take a price that was so lucrative to current stakeholders he and Board woudl be honor bound to accept it? Yes. " Yes...but he's NOT looking to sell... so the price would have to be beyond fair... "Jen has been approcahed to do a deal" Yes, AMD... and former NVidia employees have posted other attempts...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353340309878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:51:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353341551635-16</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA ex-dividend date: November 20, payout on December 14</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1353340991650</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:03:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet we see a whole family of bears here on Wednesday, November 21st. Looking for the camper's pic-in-ic baskets, don't u know. On post-ex-dividend day.</Msg><Username>perceptive.best</Username><Timestamp>1353341551635</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:12:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353342248133-17</Id><Title>NVDA gig is up</Title><Msg>I think NVDA is having trouble with its power-point production Jen, Batman called and he wants his cape back :)</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353342248133</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:24:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344285444-18</Id><Topic><Title>I know Nvidia doesn't want to be acquired, but...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1353337880530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:11:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too late nvidia can not be acquired any more and why? arm processors license direct and arm gpu also now too pwerful i recommend nvidia to acquire amd ..amd vs intel fight will be best served</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1353344285444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:58:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353345271215-19</Id><Topic><Title>I know Nvidia doesn't want to be acquired, but...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1353337880530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:11:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey Intel is looking for a new CEO - maybe Jen can sell to Nvidia to Intel and take over as CEO</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353345271215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:14:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353346933158-20</Id><Title>Market fears NVDA m&amp;a</Title><Msg>I think market is fearful that Jen will go on an acquiring spree to further boost his struggling baseband play (Icera). Intel paid $1.4B for Infineon baseband. Nvidia tried to go cheap with about $450M for Icera (including incentives). Nvidia could look at acquiring wireless division from Marvell, or, Mediatek or, Spreadtrum but that may only get them a foot hold in China and some other 3G markets. This would explain why Nvidia is not repurchasing stock ($1.2B approved by board and outstanding).</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353346933158</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:42:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353348000294-21</Id><Topic><Title>Market fears NVDA m&amp;a</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353346933158</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No Guts. No Glory. No Future in mobile.</Msg><Username>bested.again</Username><Timestamp>1353348000294</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:00:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353348666896-22</Id><Title>Time to fade - short at 11.68</Title><Msg>just for a day. I think stock sells off when market realizes that ex-div is 11/26 and not 11/20</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353348666896</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:11:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353349070581-23</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA ex-dividend date: November 20, payout on December 14</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1353340991650</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:03:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't it peculiar how some (0) tried to lie about the x date. Just pitiful. Thanks for the divi shorts. HAHAHAHAHAHA</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1353349070581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:17:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353349568437-24</Id><Topic><Title>whosunw</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353292298667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 21:31:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the reason why I always harp on ibex.... he may be pumping beyond what a long might, but if you read the articles that he posts very carefully, you can construct some kind of hints of what is going on inside nvda. those xbit articles, for example. read his articles and read between the lines, just don't just jump onto his hypewagon.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1353349568437</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:26:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353350918956-25</Id><Topic><Title>Time to fade - short at 11.68</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353348666896</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:11:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too easy - like clockwork, will cover by close of day today. NVDA tends to close near day low</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353350918956</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:48:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353352506091-26</Id><Topic><Title>Some numbers from SC12 - either announced or known/confirmed</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1353212208211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 23:16:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't fairly compare the power efficiency of the top supercomputer with one much less powerful. And it's certainly not a apples-to-apples comparison if you are trying to compare the power efficiency of the K20X with the Phi, when much of the power draw of the system is in the host CPUs and the network. My reading of the performance and power numbers is that Titan would draw slightly more power and have between 20% to 40% lower performance with Phi. Phi's performance numbers will undoubtedly improve as people learn how to use them, but right now they are much less than Intel hinted at.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1353352506091</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:15:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353353133623-27</Id><Title>intc/nvda/arm holding, new ceo!!!!</Title><Msg>why not, they all need each other badly....</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1353353133623</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:25:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353353742535-28</Id><Topic><Title>Market fears NVDA m&amp;a</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353346933158</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not a fair comparison. The modem business was a bit of a paradox. It's essential in mobile. The capabilities and power draw make or break the end product. But the companies in the business didn't have pricing power and couldn't make money. Intel got much more than a single modem with their Infineon purchase, but what they didn't get was a ready-to-go LTE modem. If the Blue Wonder purchase is any indication, there still is quite a bit of development to do. It seems that part of Intel is still hoping that WiMax will be the future. Nvidia perhaps overpaid for modem-only Icera, but got a development team and design approach that has the potential to be a market leader. They hardly "went cheap", but may have bought a better time-to-market deal. We'll know in a few months. Qualcomm is the one selling chips and phones, and will probably be cashing checks even if they lose their present advantage.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1353353742535</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:35:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353354287278-29</Id><Topic><Title>Market fears NVDA m&amp;a</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353346933158</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well, the reason I say that Icera was cheap is that Icera had raised close to $300M in VC rounds and was supposedly eyeing a $1 - $1.5B IPO. The proof will be in the pudding - didn't Icera have ~$100M revenue stream from USB dongles, laptop's etc? I think they focused on data side only. That revenue seems to have magically disappeared after acquisition? At the time of acquisition, Icera was supposed to have been accretive in 2H 2012, I doubt that has been the case. funny line about Intel still hoping for a WiMax comeback - how much money did they sink in WiMax!</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353354287278</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:44:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353354775994-30</Id><Topic><Title>On second thought - probably a dumb idea to short NVDA here</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353285006240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 19:30:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'the only thing nvda has proven by being so late with Wayne is that they have no idea what they are doing designing processors.' The A15 is already designed but I get what you mean. At the time I did point out Nvidia had licensed the A15 design about 6 months after every one else but everyone dismissed this as irrelevant but it obviously is not as it takes about 2 years to produce a licensed cpu, 4 years if you design one youself. I also did point out at the time that the roadmap was ridiculously optimistic and so it has proven, remember the one year from tapeout to production rule of thumb that you dismissed ? Having made these general points there is some other general matters that need to be taken into consideration, the A15 (at 32nm) is power hungry even in just dual-core form so trying to build a 5-core version even at 28nm that fits into a tablet will be no easy feat especially as I presume Nvidia will have to master brand new TMSC HPM and HPL 28nm processes which maybe late in themselves. What is also clear is that there is no dual-core A15 version to put into phones so I presume they will shrink Tegra 3 on 28nm to carry that going on phones. Eventually Wayne at say 20nm or 16nm will have the power consumption to fit into phones but that is a long wait and is an executive design decision which may leave Nvidia exposed in the marketplace relying on quad-core A9s for too long.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353354775994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:52:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353355215364-31</Id><Topic><Title>On second thought - probably a dumb idea to short NVDA here</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353285006240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 19:30:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>afaik - Wayne tapeout was completed last quarter, I think there is a good chance you will see tablets using Wayne early next year starting CES. its Grey that has been giving people heartburn because without that Nvidia will not be able to move the needle on smartphone SOC which has 10x tablet SAM.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353355215364</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 15:00:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353357272016-32</Id><Title>The short basher here lost $5M over last 6 mo's</Title><Msg>that's what I am hearing....</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1353357272016</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 15:34:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353360084604-33</Id><Topic><Title>The short basher here lost $5M over last 6 mo's</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1353357272016</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 15:34:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a short's nightmare, right boys? Those new 52-week lows for nvda. HA HA HA HA HA!</Msg><Username>best.wins</Username><Timestamp>1353360084604</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:21:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353364934728-34</Id><Title>10Q posted - CPB segment improvement clues</Title><Msg>Sequentially, CPB segment qtrly revenue went up from $179M to $243M an increase of $64M, +36% Operating Loss went from -$89M to -$41M, that is a decrease of $48M. That is a clear sign that Project Wayne tape out expense was largely recognized in July 2012 Qtr. Again, in Jan 2013 Qtr Nvidia will incur an increase of $30M in operating expense. That really points to a Project Grey tape out.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353364934728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:42:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353366984510-35</Id><Topic><Title>10Q posted - CPB segment improvement clues</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353364934728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:42:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They will likely announce Grey in 1Q next year but it will take longer for products/smartphones to be available in my opinion. But I would not mind to be happily surprised.</Msg><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1353366984510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 18:16:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353367344058-36</Id><Topic><Title>On second thought - probably a dumb idea to short NVDA here</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353285006240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 19:30:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" they have no idea what they are doing designing processors." How long did INtel take to get Larabee out the door... ?? Where is INtel's high-end GPUs that was guaranteed to make NVidia RIP ??</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353367344058</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 18:22:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353372342034-37</Id><Topic><Title>10Q posted - CPB segment improvement clues</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353364934728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:42:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>assuming 50% margins, you can now calculate what is the breakeven of CPB, even without the r&amp;d ramp this Q. I've got a breakeven of $324M/Q or $1.3B/yr. That's up from just a forecast breakeven of $1B just 18 months ago. Q1, with nov to ship T3 for X'mas, will be $160M. you can calculate the loss from that. No Wayne $s till way into 2014..... CPS sales will continue to fall...., you do the math on the losses for the next 6 Qs. Yes, Hans, when you are that late in delivering new products, there ARE consequences. getanid, you looked yet over the links that ibex supplied here the last 2 weeks? What did the links say about Wayne's schedule?</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1353372342034</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:45:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353373466996-38</Id><Title>Nomura Gives Buy Rating to NVIDIA (NVDA)</Title><Msg>Nomura Gives Buy Rating to NVIDIA (NVDA) November 19th, 2012 - 0 comments - Filed Under - by Patrick Bannon Filed Under: Analyst Articles - US - Stock Market NVIDIA (NASDAQ: NVDA)‘s stock had its “buy” rating reiterated by investment analysts at Nomura in a note issued to investors on Monday. They currently have a $16.00 target price on the stock. Shares of NVIDIA traded up 1.67% during mid-day trading on Monday, hitting $11.57. NVIDIA has a 52 week low of $11.15 and a 52 week high of $16.90. The company has a market cap of $7.201 billion and a P/E ratio of 14.21.</Msg><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1353373466996</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:04:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353375883620-39</Id><Title>Tegra/CPB Loses more than Twice (2x) what it Lost last year!</Title><Msg>Jen's Tegra/CPB folly isn't getting better. Oh no no no. It's getting worse. Much Much Much Worse. Take a look at the newest Tegra Losses, boys. From the brand-new nvidia 3Q 10-Q, page 27. Tegra/Consumer Products Business (CPB) ( -$116,486,000.00) __ Operating Loss, 9 months 2011 ( -$233,545,000.00) __ Operating Loss, 9 months 2012 _______________ ( -$117,059,000.00) __ Horrendously Worsening Tegra Loses, year-over-year Wasn't the Tegra supposed to start making money when it "ramped-up"? Well, it's been "ramping-up" for four (4) years now, and all that's ramping-up are the Gigantic Losses. ( -$233,545,000.00) MORE THAN A QUARTER OF A BILLION DOLLARS LOST. Just in the Nine Months so far of 2012. Which is more than Two Times (2x) Worse than last year. ( -$117,059,000.00) worse than last year, actually. Now, the Tegra #2 has completed it's life cycle and is done. The Tegra #3 is now old and stale and is pretty much done, competitively speaking. And the Tegra #4 is missing in non-action. So when does Jen's Tegra folly finally break even on the Billions invested? Hummm? Never is the likely answer. It's high time for the Institutional Investors to step in here and have a "Come to Jesus" discussion with the Nvidia Board of Directors about Jen's ridiculous, enormous loss-making Tegra folly.</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1353375883620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:44:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>61</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353377965649-40</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra/CPB Loses more than Twice (2x) what it Lost last year!</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1353375883620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:44:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's high time for the Institutional Investors to step in here and have a "Come to Jesus" discussion with the Nvidia Board of Directors about Jen's ridiculous, enormous loss-making Tegra folly." So Best? Could they do that? The Institutional Investors. Could a major Institutional Investor -- like for example, Fidelity -- say to the Board, "Look Board." "We've watched enough shareholder's cash get pizzed-away on Jen's Tegra folly. ( -$233,545,000.00) MORE THAN A QUARTER OF A BILLION DOLLARS LOST. Just in the Nine Months so far of 2012. And either you boys Pull The Plug on Jen's Tegra chip folly, or we're going to start liquidating our 68,685,556 nvidia shares." Could they do that, Best?</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1353377965649</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:19:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>38</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353378656676-41</Id><Title>the short basher here is wrong about his conclusions</Title><Msg>thank goodness he's not paid...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1353378656676</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:30:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353379789811-42</Id><Topic><Title>10Q posted - CPB segment improvement clues</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353364934728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:42:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"getanid, you looked yet over the links that ibex supplied here the last 2 weeks? " not really...but I just did look at the xbitlabs for you....So, from xbitlabs on 11/14 "“That [Tegra ‘Grey’] is really the product that in about a year's time frame will really matter to get us into a larger part of the smartphone market,” added Mr. Huang." Is that what you wanted me to read ?? But from my own hunch... NVidia's ICera LTE is behind... and that's what's holding up Grey... If they did tapeout Grey, then the Icera discrete must be stable in bring up... Internet expectations is Tegra 4 first look at CES... However, NVidia is truly mum on this... Tegra 4 should be trivial compared to Kepler... My guess is Icera discrete is late...and that they wanted to launch Tegra 4 together... You, me, everyone will have their eyes on CES...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353379789811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:49:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353380113808-43</Id><Topic><Title>10Q posted - CPB segment improvement clues</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353364934728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:42:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If they did tapeout Grey, then the Icera discrete must be stable in bring up..." clarifying...Grey is integrated with LTE, but they had to bring up the discrete LTE first...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353380113808</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:55:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353381154601-44</Id><Topic><Title>10Q posted - CPB segment improvement clues</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353364934728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:42:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there is a rumored Icera 500 in customer's hands. But I suspect you are right - its not ready for prime time and hence it has not made it in any product yet. It was very disappointing to see 2 great opportunities missed with this socket in recent product announcements: - HTC One X+, uses Qualcomm LTE baseband - Nexus 7 with mobile data, uses Infineon/Intel HSPA+ baseband The problem with LTE is that its a power-hog, Tim Cook has been critical of LTE designs in the past. Qualcomm has done a great job "marketing" all in one S4 Pro with integrated power management for various parts etc. So to be competitive in near term, Nvidia has no choice but either realize their "Grey" vision or, cut bait (like TI) and slim down.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353381154601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 22:12:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353383292211-45</Id><Topic><Title>10Q posted - CPB segment improvement clues</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353364934728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:42:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dude you need to chill out, you are dismissing Qualcomm as if they are a little baby invited to big boy party... no they are the big bad 800 lb gorilla or, even godzilla that can only be contained - forget about beating them. Qualcomm has S4 Prime MSM8974, a Quad-core 2-2.5GHZ part with everything integrated. Yes, it will show in a RIMM early next year. Nvidia/Icera will pay a license fee to Qualcomm for every modem they ship. Don't be so naive that Nvidia can dethrone the king so easily. Nvidia has 1 possible edge in next-gen, GPU Qualcomm has countless - LTE, Wifi, BT, GPS. I think you can count Krait vs. stock A15 core license as an edge for Qualcomm.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353383292211</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 22:48:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353384536056-46</Id><Topic><Title>Correction of typo: QC had to license ImaginationVR in a hurry at the suggestion of Ballmer</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1353383030961</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 22:43:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fair enough - I guess one will have to wait for CES product announcements. I hope you are not counting on Surface RT revival? that beast is pretty much dead - Microsoft will have to make some radical price cuts and improvements to Metro interface to move the needle.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353384536056</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 23:08:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353385810067-47</Id><Topic><Title>10Q posted - CPB segment improvement clues</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1353364934728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:42:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It was very disappointing to see 2 great opportunities missed" Always... but it's a what have you done for me lately industry... so no time to rest... "I think you can count Krait vs. stock A15 core license as an edge for Qualcomm." Probably...But NVidia will have their ARM64 Project Denver... Assuming NVidia pulls it off...they will have more than an edge...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353385810067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 23:30:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353386846312-48</Id><Topic><Title>The Tegra, it is like elephant</Title><Username>naziba.adongo</Username><Timestamp>1349843708263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Tegra, it is like elephant When small, it come and go from hut No one care It is cute Then Elephant grow bigger And bigger It smash hut of owner To eat roof Then neighbor's hut too Munch munch munch No roof Then smash half of village Eating roof after roof Munch munch munch munch munch munch Villagers get angry Oh so angry No like feeding roof to Elephant Paint faces and shout "Kill the Tegra" "Kill the Tegra" Wise council bosses order chief of village to kill Elephant Prosperity returns to village Lesson: Kill the Tegra before it smash and eat village For the Nine Months ending October 28, 2012 the CPB (Tegra) Division wiped-out 32.5% of nvidia's Operating Income, as follows: $434,818,000 __ Operating Income, GPU Business $283,520,000 __ Operating Income, Professional Solutions Business ___________ $718,338,000 __ Operating Income without Tegra/CPB Business ($233,545,000) __ Operating Loss, Tegra/Consumer Products Business ($233,545,000) / $718,338,000 = 32.51% Munch munch munch munch munch munch Villagers get angry Oh so angry No like feeding operating income to Tegra</Msg><Username>naziba.adongo</Username><Timestamp>1353386846312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 23:47:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>19</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353387022604-49</Id><Topic><Title>The Tegra, it is like elephant</Title><Username>naziba.adongo</Username><Timestamp>1349843708263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nonsense chasing nonsense !!!!!!! on IGNORE you go</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353387022604</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 23:50:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353387209087-50</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA is bad. This is the reason why.</Title><Username>garypogue21</Username><Timestamp>1351094112628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$</Msg><Username>t84b49</Username><Timestamp>1353387209087</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 23:53:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>