<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366435613132-1</Id><Title>Xiaomi to launch Xiaomi Mi3 with Tegra4, LTE, 4.5" screen in mid 2013</Title><Msg>SOURCE: maxdioDOTcom/xiaomi-to-launch-xiaomi-mi-3-with-tegra-4-lte-4-5-screen-in-mid-2013/ Xiaomi to launch Xiaomi MI-3 , After the Xiaomi M2 successor which was only recently announced, the Beijing based phone maker are already working on the details of its successor the Xiaomi M3. According to the latest rumors, he Xiaomi M3 will come equipped with Nvidia’s latest quad-core chip, the 4 CPU will offer a quad-core Cortex-A15 CPU with clock speeds between 1.8 GHz and 2 GHz with around 2.5 GB worth of RAM., it is also rumored the new M3 will get a larger 4.5-inch display from JDI (Japan Display Corporation) which will likely have a stunning DPI. Finally, the camera have a 12 megapixel sensor. All of this sounds really exciting and knowing the kind of competitive pricing Xiaomi normally does, we just hope the company brings the smartphone (if it’s real of course) outside of its home market. _____ PS: --The updated launch date is 1-2 quarters earlier sooner than previously reported. Good news if true. --Xiao is a premium smart phone manufacturer in China. Previous versions of Xiao M1, M2 were sold out in days after release. About 7 millions of Xiaomi Mi2 were sold in 2012.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366435613132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 01:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366452373975-2</Id><Title>Once again, a lack of follow through</Title><Msg>Last week rallied above $13, looked promising. This week smacked down. Watching this stock is like watching paint dry. Lots of nothing. Why? Its needs growth. But its not happening. Plus its tegra 4 have pathetic wins. Hence they announced $1b giveaway back to shareholders. Or else its share price will tank. Jen is smart . Buying some time til they figure out something significant. Eg. Perhaps a successful project Denver. But this is just an assumption of a successful project. Cos the pass few years, Nvidia is nothing but hope and hype, with no substance. Meanwhile, investing in it is likely still watching paint dry, or ....watching grass grow.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366452373975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 06:06:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366456377810-3</Id><Topic><Title>Once again, a lack of follow through</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366452373975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 06:06:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your posts are nothing but drive-by blather!</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1366456377810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 07:12:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366456877437-4</Id><Topic><Title>Once again, a lack of follow through</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366452373975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 06:06:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My posts are facts: What did Nvidia shares price do past 6 mths, nothing! A nexus win was shouted as huge , but share price tanked after initial hype. Now suddenly, a nexus loss is nothing??? Before tegra 4 is announced, all said its a big deal. Now its out, what's the big deal? Jen even talked about 4a, and tegra 5, ! No! When u bring in a new product, u focus on delivering it well, not making noise on future generations unless of course the present one is not optimistic. Common sense. Argue with me based on facts, not your mood. Grow up.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366456877437</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 07:21:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366457384824-5</Id><Title>Why share price labouring even when $1b is giveaway?</Title><Msg>I suspect market knows Nvidia losing on nexus7 to qcom. When its really unveiled, Nvidia will tank $1. Hopefully when it tanks, its around $13.5, then $1 will be $12.5, Still within its 6 mths range. Else a convincing drop below $11.5 will bring it to single digits. Not going to be pretty.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366457384824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 07:29:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366465463805-6</Id><Title>Motorola X</Title><Msg>There’s been a rumour for the past couple months that Motorola will release a new flagship smartphone this year, potentially called the “X Phone.” The specs of this powerhouse Android are impressive: a 4.7-inch full HD screen, NVIDIA Tegra 4i processor, 16MP camera and a 5MP front-facing camera and be only 7.9mm thin.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1366465463805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:44:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366466182132-7</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola X</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1366465463805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:44:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>market says, "Show me the $!" Jen says, "OK, here are the $100M/Q loses, enuf $ for yar?"</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1366466182132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:56:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366466928887-8</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola X</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1366465463805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:44:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No soup for you!</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1366466928887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:08:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366468461909-9</Id><Topic><Title>Once again, a lack of follow through</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366452373975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 06:06:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, here are some points for you to argue if you are really interested in any discussion on the truth, and not distorted propaganda blathered by the drive-by trailer park trash that regularly post here. Nobody said that except for you. It's not out. It's been stated by Nvidia that it would be late by a quarter due to a decision to dedicate resources to the T4i so it could be pushed-up by 2 months. Perhaps the delay was due in part to the latest rumor posted by ibexx today in regards to the Xiaomi M3 that will come equipped with Nvidia’s T4i chip? If true, the Chinese market has tremendous sales ramifications. Customers don't allow their products to be announced by suppliers until they are given permission to do so. This is especially true in a very competitive market that the ultra portable sector is. Most everybody knows this, why don't you? I'm not sure why you and others proclaim T4's demise when it's only the first month of the second quarter of the year when many new product releases/announcements are still months away? Perhaps in future posts you might consider becoming more acclimated with known information first?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1366468461909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:34:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366468482418-10</Id><Title>Solar comeback is going to be like Smartphone bet like APPL 2 years ago</Title><Msg>Search for "Japan to Become Largest Solar Market After China" and "Toshiba SunEdison (WFR) to build solar" Do your DD. Cheers!</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1366468482418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:34:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366476548941-11</Id><Topic><Title>Once again, a lack of follow through</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366452373975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 06:06:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, your Xiaomi is a speculation. Nvidia has been touting China wins for 12 months. The end results are just average. Losing tremendously to mediatek. Hence, even with xiaomi, the result could be still a not moving stock. I wish Nvidia success , but with their surprising $1b spending, it really points towards buying time for a really successful product. So far all fanciful, but average endings. Hence, its boring share price. And that's my point, til there is better follow through, ie, a constant stay above its 50 dma and 200 dma, watching it will be like watching grass grow. Oh project shield fyi, is yet another hype. A decoy, a distraction to zero consoles win. Recall project denver, why no update? And why the sacking of its tegra chief last year? Look at Microsoft, after sacking their windows rt chief shortly after launch, rt is proven to be lackluster. So tegra chief sack likely = lackluster tegra too.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366476548941</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:49:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366479786500-12</Id><Topic><Title>Once again, a lack of follow through</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366452373975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 06:06:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you will need to wait until E3 on June 11-13 to see if it's all hype or not? It appears that you have a limited understanding of many elements surrounding Nvidia. Perhaps you should go to Nvidia's site and view the recent annalist meeting, or you should just move on to another stock that has more exciting price action that you seem to be looking for?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1366479786500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:43:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366484929257-13</Id><Topic><Title>Once again, a lack of follow through</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366452373975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 06:06:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to speak to yourself about growing up with the comment you just made. You are presenting only the 'facts' you want to present to bash away. We know it's going to be in a tight range into the second half of the year and no one that does their research is surprised at the current price range at all. What has been well presented is a well planned and well thought out strategy based on 'facts'. So sure, it's not a great stock for the short term investor who wants to short the stock and make a quick buck on one of the swings this stock has had such a reputation for in the past. Now, it's not a short-term play, but a long-term investment. Hence, the growing up starts with you looking in the mirror and facing the facts that you can't play the game you usually play with this stock. Go to AMD or somewhere else and by a sub-$5 dollar stock to make your short-term play there.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366484929257</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 15:08:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366494918794-14</Id><Topic><Title>"Nvidia scores sole Tegra 4 design win, courtesy of ZTE"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366410986010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:36:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only One design win, Not One Product on the market, One Sorry Showing. Why bother, if the current Tegra 3 customers don't want Tegra 4 the writing is on the wall. Tegra 4 is DOA. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366494918794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:55:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366495410875-15</Id><Topic><Title>"Google's next Nexus 7 tablet will shun Nvidia in favour of Qualcomm"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1365008441897</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 13:00:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"HARDWARE DESIGNER Google is working on a sequel to its Google Nexus 7 tablet, which won't have an Nvidia Tegra 3 chip but rather a Qualcomm processor." If current Tegra customers are shunning Tegra 4 then forget it. Who would know more about Tegra than current paying customers? Do you think an Nvidia message board pumping crew know more about Tegra than Google, who accounted for 60% of Tegra 3 sales? And what did Google do to Tegra 4? One word Nvidia fans, "SHUN". Now say ot ain't so. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366495410875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:03:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366511332031-16</Id><Topic><Title>Once again, a lack of follow through</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366452373975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 06:06:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Grow up dude. Stop putting your head in the sand. Looks like u agreed with me. U said that it is not a short term stock, its a long term stock. Dude a long term stock is one that rallies for years, eg Apple previously. Also u said it will be in a tight range. Hey, isn't that what I meant, watching grass grow ??!!! Lol I ain't bashing nvda saying it will crash. I just said its doing nothing. A waste . Tho there'sa possibility, with $1b great news still dun rally well, a bad news eg nexus loss could force it down its range. As we all know, the longer the range, the break of it is worse.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366511332031</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366511871507-17</Id><Topic><Title>Once again, a lack of follow through</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366452373975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 06:06:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong, I have followed them a while. Analyst meeting? Hey, the facts are they have been hyping for years and always, its the results that matter . They must start delivering. They have been saying about great future products etc etc. No. Start delivering now with huge earnings results too. Else no one will trust them. I wish Nvidia success. Til there is a rally and follow through, then start investing and saying its a good company. Dun say that its a good company when share price plunged 26 to 12, and spent so many months doing nothing. A good company is ARMH, not nvda. Nvidia is a POS till proven otherwise.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366511871507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366512499822-18</Id><Title>Yes Ladies and Gentlemen, It's Up To Project Shield</Title><Msg>Think about it. We are 4+ months after the Tegra 4 announcement and we have zero, yes zip, Tegra 4 products shipping. But we have Project Shield due in a month or so. But alas Nvidia's CEO said and I quote, "I have no expectations about Project Shield and neither should you!" Stock buyback in process. $100M last quarter, $100M in Q1. and $600M over 2Q, 3Q, and 4Q.So what's the complaint. Perhaps, Nvidia should announce how many new shares will be issued to employees. Based on past performance at least half of the buyback will be negated by employee options and management RSU! It's very hard to keep 35 Senior Vice Presidents satisfied. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1366512499822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:48:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366512549020-19</Id><Title>Stop listenimg to the lies that tegra is great.</Title><Msg>When tegra 3 won a spot in nexus 7, all said its great. And that tegra 4 will mean even more design wins. But Google gonna kick tegra to the curb. If tegra is great, Google will continue with Nvidia. This is a fact. Nvidia is nervous with design losses. Hence announced white design plan idea Phoenix. But as usual, its a hype with little results to show for. Until they start delivering successfully, still a waste of time stock.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366512549020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366512708721-20</Id><Topic><Title>Once again, a lack of follow through</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366452373975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 06:06:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well dude, 'as we all know' the break is neither worse nor better the longer the range, that's pure speculation on your part, not factual at all. You mix a few 'facts' with your bs and sure, you make SO much sense . . Please, you don't have a clue. The lack of maturity shows in how you respond and talk on the surface of things, not to mention writing like a teenager, but that's your choice. And since when is a tight range with both a dividend and a buyback, a waste, based on your VERY shallow review of the company? Nvidia is in a great position to do as you say Apple has done, but I doubt you will be around to find that out. Do yourself a favor and spend time on a more speculative stock like AMD where there is virtually no chance of long-term growth, but plenty of chances to speculate and make money shorting . . it's crowded company there. Maybe that's why you are over here . .</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366512708721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:51:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366512821652-21</Id><Topic><Title>Yes Ladies and Gentlemen, It's Up To Project Shield</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1366512499822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:48:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree. They are just buying time for a really successful product. They are throwing everything on the wall hoping it sticks, but none so far. Hence lousy share price. Well, I do hope one product finally sticks and share price rally above $20. But, til now, it is still a POS til proven otherwise.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366512821652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:53:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366513263840-22</Id><Topic><Title>Stop listenimg to the lies that tegra is great.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366512549020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But Google gonna kick tegra to the curb. If tegra is great, Google will continue with Nvidia. This is a fact." Well, that's not a fact, you just made that up. Google repeatedly changes vendors on their products and will continue to do so. It's part of their strategy not to empower one vendor more than another at this point and has been since they started developing/making their own tablets, phones and notebooks, ie Chromebooks. Also, Jen has repeatedly said their design wins have already been confirmed but they 'never' announce product wins for the companies that use their chips, never. And it's been made clear we'd see most of these wins in the second half with the earliest announcements towards the end of the 2nd quarter going into the 3rd quarter. These are the 'facts' clearly stated and easily found by investors who really are serious about understanding the plans of their investment. The more you write, the more foolish and amateur you come across. I've already wasted too much of my weekend posting in response to you, so see ya. Good luck with your investments . . if you have any.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366513263840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366514616666-23</Id><Topic><Title>Stop listenimg to the lies that tegra is great.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366512549020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Returds respond to trolls, ciao</Msg><Username>yisuakraq</Username><Timestamp>1366514616666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:23:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366515475836-24</Id><Topic><Title>Stop listenimg to the lies that tegra is great.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366512549020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't matter dude, fact is tegra still ain't producing in big numbers to rally its share price . This is the indisputable fact now. After 4 versions of it.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366515475836</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:37:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366515789899-25</Id><Title>Breaking news! Project Shield, Project Denver, Project Boulder, &amp; Project Phoenix from Jen!</Title><Msg>From Jen: Haven't I already made known, its a project. Heard of high school project? Ever expect anything of it? Its just a project! Lol Its Sunday, time for a bit of joke. JMHJ</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366515789899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:43:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366516737161-26</Id><Topic><Title>Once again, a lack of follow through</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366452373975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 06:06:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fool u. Huh, why did u bring up amd. Amd is a worse stock then Nvidia. A good stock is ARMH, u buy and it rallies and u stay safe and happy. No need to be hopeful, cos its share price rally, ie it delivers. Even sndk is better. Yes it crashed months ago, but it rallied back up to its highs quickly. Nvidia crashed and labour 6 mths. U, u dun kid yourself putting head in sand. U happy with dividend? If u want dividends, u go for MacDonald. U bought Nvidia cos u r greedy, hoping for 100% or more gains. Nvidia used to deliver. Not anymore. Until that changes, when it change, I will rejoice and say its a great stock. Not now, as it disappoints. Remember the hopefulls of amd at $5? Nvidia board laughed at them. With Nvidia not performing, u r only bit better</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366516737161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:58:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>