<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-17"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358399142781-1</Id><Topic><Title>What is Icera i500 “soft” modem or in long form, a Software Defined Radio (SDR)?</Title><Username>autoblast123</Username><Timestamp>1358376206950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 17:43:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doing a side by side comparison is hard to do because the underlying architectures are fundamentally different with little or no commonalities. There are efficiencies to be had or must in either solutions that can impact the comparison either way. From a pure theoretical standpoint anytime you add layers of abstraction (SDR) you are potentially adding inefficiencies. However, a good software design can outperform a poor ASIC's design. Now that being said I think the real question is not which one is better by comparing raw numbers but how negligible can you make the perceptions of those inefficiencies from one solution to another. Thus there is no reason good engineers can't overcome these problems and provide a solution that is perceived to be as good as a good hardware solution or even better than a less efficient HW solution.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358399142781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 00:05:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358399298682-2</Id><Topic><Title>What is Icera i500 “soft” modem or in long form, a Software Defined Radio (SDR)?</Title><Username>autoblast123</Username><Timestamp>1358376206950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 17:43:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are so annoying ...</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1358399298682</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 00:08:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358400542307-3</Id><Topic><Title>What is Icera i500 “soft” modem or in long form, a Software Defined Radio (SDR)?</Title><Username>autoblast123</Username><Timestamp>1358376206950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 17:43:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The main advantage of a soft modem is the ability to change it fast as specs evolve. It also saves on power and cost.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358400542307</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 00:29:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358401571800-4</Id><Topic><Title>What is Icera i500 “soft” modem or in long form, a Software Defined Radio (SDR)?</Title><Username>autoblast123</Username><Timestamp>1358376206950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 17:43:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cost and flexibility are both advantages but that wasn't the question posed. The question was how do the compare bit for bit. Also, power isn't an innate advantage - not to say that it can't be by it's not by definition. I am willing to bet I can create a very inefficient software stack that yields a higher power profile despite there being less silicon.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358401571800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 00:46:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358403806186-5</Id><Title>Jen-Hsun Huang : "We respect the intellectual property of others."</Title><Msg>From Nvidia's "Our Code". In excerpts. Our Code : Creating a Principled Workplace "The bedrock of our culture is impeccable integrity." This is the expectation that each of us operates at the highest ethical standard. It’s important for you to familiarize yourself with Our Code, which sets out the standards guiding our professional relationships. It describes the principles that apply to how we act toward customers, COMPETITORS, partners, vendors, government regulators, stockholders, fellow employees, as well as the community at large. These standards... will help determine our future. In everything we do, we must act honestly, ethically, fairly, legally, and in a manner in which all of NVIDIA can take pride. We don’t do this simply because we’d get in trouble if we didn’t. We do it because honest and ethical dealings have been, and will remain, fundamental to our long-term success. Our Code forms the basis of our culture and what it means to be part of NVIDIA. It’s a great privilege for me to build this amazing company with you. Jen-Hsun Huang Co-Founder and CEO "Respecting Intellectual Property." As a technology company, our lifeblood is intellectual property: patents, copyrights, trade secrets, and trademarks. If we want others to respect our intellectual property, we must do the same in return. We respect the intellectual property of others. When we use patents and copyrighted material belonging to others, we obtain the proper licenses and permissions. When we cite the trademarks of others, we use them in accordance with the guidelines provided by the owners. We do not use NVIDIA networks, computers, or other resources to acquire, share, or store copyrighted material that is not properly licensed." A nice looking little brochure, right boys? It sure is nice looking. And ya gotta just Love that part about, "In everything we do, we must act honestly, ethically, fairly, legally, and in a manner in which all of NVIDIA can take pride." "We respect the intellectual property of others."</Msg><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1358403806186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 01:23:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358404081956-6</Id><Topic><Title>Jen-Hsun Huang : "We respect the intellectual property of others."</Title><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1358403806186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 01:23:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We respect the intellectual property of others." The key adjective here seems to be 'intellectual'...so is that reason nobody 'respects' you?</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358404081956</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 01:28:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358404379198-7</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD accuses former staff of giving 100,000 secret documents to NVIDIA"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358384945597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 20:09:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder what nvidia's Code of Ethics -- "Our Code" -- says about this? Hummm? Ah, here it is. "Respecting Intellectual Property." "As a technology company, our lifeblood is intellectual property: patents, copyrights, trade secrets, and trademarks. If we want others to respect our intellectual property, we must do the same in return. We respect the intellectual property of others. When we use patents and copyrighted material belonging to others, we obtain the proper licenses and permissions. When we cite the trademarks of others, we use them in accordance with the guidelines provided by the owners. We do not use NVIDIA networks, computers, or other resources to acquire, share, or store copyrighted material that is not properly licensed." "If we want others to respect our intellectual property, we must do the same in return. We respect the intellectual property of others."</Msg><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1358404379198</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 01:32:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358404770453-8</Id><Topic><Title>What is Icera i500 “soft” modem or in long form, a Software Defined Radio (SDR)?</Title><Username>autoblast123</Username><Timestamp>1358376206950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 17:43:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A SDR has to be better designed to save on power. It very likely reduces the die area (which is reduces the cost of production) and enables field fixes and upgrades. From a power standpoint, it's best to have an optimized, hard-wired implementation of each radio and modem and power gate (turn off) all but the one in use at the time. But this design strategy can't be used in the real world because of bugs, evolving standards and improved understanding of operating conditions. If you add enough hooks and programmability in a hard-wired design to allow fixes, it's likely to end up less efficient than a SDR. If Icera has enough right that the i500 works, it's a big step forward for the industry. Every new design will be a SDR.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1358404770453</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 01:39:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358407054516-9</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD accuses former staff of giving 100,000 secret documents to NVIDIA"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358384945597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 20:09:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Attention. Attention. Will the owner of the One Hundred Thousand lost confidential documents please report to the Nvidia Visitor's Center Lost and Found. Thank you.</Msg><Username>good_one_best</Username><Timestamp>1358407054516</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 02:17:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358415552140-10</Id><Title>S4 Pro Die Area</Title><Msg>Anybody has a link to this or know what it is - the die area of the S4 Pro. You would think that Anand would volunteer this info when he supposedly tore it apart and did "extensive" analysis on how great this chip is. Thanks</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1358415552140</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 04:39:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358416137208-11</Id><Topic><Title>what Nvidia can achieve in next few days?</Title><Username>jeffrey.howerton</Username><Timestamp>1358356626224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:17:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very nice report</Msg><Username>brandontanaka</Username><Timestamp>1358416137208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 04:48:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358417709038-12</Id><Topic><Title>what Nvidia can achieve in next few days?</Title><Username>jeffrey.howerton</Username><Timestamp>1358356626224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:17:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thank you!</Msg><Username>jimmydavis378</Username><Timestamp>1358417709038</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 05:15:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358418618105-13</Id><Topic><Title>what Nvidia can achieve in next few days?</Title><Username>jeffrey.howerton</Username><Timestamp>1358356626224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:17:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very helpful, thanks</Msg><Username>jlarry267</Username><Timestamp>1358418618105</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 05:30:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358419485884-14</Id><Topic><Title>what Nvidia can achieve in next few days?</Title><Username>jeffrey.howerton</Username><Timestamp>1358356626224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:17:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thank you, that was very helpful</Msg><Username>brianmay216</Username><Timestamp>1358419485884</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 05:44:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358421583759-15</Id><Title>Asus / Google Nexus 7 out sell Apple iPad in Japan, last month</Title><Msg>2013.01.17 02:45 pm BCN last month sales figure：Nexus 7 44.4% market share Apple iPad 40.1% Nexus 7 uses NVIDIA® Tegra® 3 quad-core processor</Msg><Username>leezenwang</Username><Timestamp>1358421583759</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 06:19:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358423370363-16</Id><Topic><Title>Good News Ahead... technical analysis stock trends,</Title><Username>avispoleniqkd9604</Username><Timestamp>1307204969000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2011-06-04 12:29:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Promised Profit</Msg><Username>macjennifer803</Username><Timestamp>1358423370363</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 06:49:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358425801504-17</Id><Topic><Title>Asus / Google Nexus 7 out sell Apple iPad in Japan, last month</Title><Username>leezenwang</Username><Timestamp>1358421583759</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 06:19:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And TMSC reports net profit soared by 31.6% today, we know it wasnt all QCOM driven - NVDA should report a strong Q4</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1358425801504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 07:30:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358427106986-18</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA may perhaps wind up the company to see this month.</Title><Username>william_stabile</Username><Timestamp>1357301964184</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 07:19:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DANGEROUS SCAM VIRUS REPORTED !</Msg><Username>alphonite</Username><Timestamp>1358427106986</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 07:51:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358430750443-19</Id><Title>Tegra 4 to be in LG produced Nexus 5 Phone and LG produced Nexus 7.7 Tablet</Title><Msg>It looks like after what appears to be a successful Nexus 4 partnership, hardware-maker LG will once again partner up with the Android OS-maker to deliver two new Nexus products, the Nexus 5 smartphone and a Nexus 7.7 tablet. Nexus 5.5 Smartphone The LG-made Nexus 5 is rumored to debut with a 5-inch display, and not the 5.5-inch full HD panel that LG’s been rumored to sport on its new Optimus G2 phone arriving sometime this year. The Nexus 5, like the HTC Droid DNA, would have a full 1080p HD panel on its 5-inch display. The phone would use NVIDIA’s Tegra 4 processor and have 2 GB of RAM and a 13-megapixel camera. It’s unclear if this camera module is the same 13-megapixel sensor that’s found on the international and Sprint version of the current Optimus G, or if it’s a newer Sony Exmor sensor that will debut on the Sony Xperia Z smartphone. Like today’s Nexus 4, the Nexus 5′s 8 GB model is said to debut at $299, making it an affordable option given that it requires no contract or carrier subsidies. Nexus 7.7 Tablet Additionally, it looks like LG may have won the tablet bid with the next generation of Nexus tablets, replacing Asus on the current Nexus 7 with a Nexus 7.7 model. The Nexus 7.7 will have a high resolution 1920 X 1200-pixel display with a 294 ppi, according to Phone Arena. With a 7.7-inch panel the Nexus tablet will be inching closer to Apple’s heavily marketed iPad mini with a 7.9-inch display. The Nexus 7.7 will use the Tegra 4 CPU from NVIDIA and will start with 8 GB of storage. The slate will also have front-facing and rear-facing cameras, though the exact specs are unknown. If in fact early development of Key Lime Pie was centered around the NVIDIA Tegra 4 chipset, as the new Nexus 5 and Nexus 7.7 suggest, it would be a huge win for NVIDIA as the last time its chipset was the center of Google’s Android development was on the Motorola Xoom, which used the Tegra 2 dual-core CPU. LG LG has announced its aggressive turnaround plan to be more competitive in the phone market with plans to ship 75 million phones, of which 45 million will be smartphones. Its partnership with Google for the Nexus 4 had helped to increase the visibility of LG as a phone-maker and the continued partnership will likely help to benefit LG.</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1358430750443</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 08:52:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358431210873-20</Id><Title>Nexus 7 -32GB with T-Mobile Data</Title><Msg>added to GooglePlay last night. Another large distribution point. Anyone else notice that Google likes to stay away from WCDMA. Maybe it's to keep the cost down and not have to pay Qualcomm royalties on the modem chip.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358431210873</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:00:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358431310567-21</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 -32GB with T-Mobile Data</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358431210873</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:00:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>has this thing got a radio? whose radio?</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358431310567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:01:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358432042670-22</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 -32GB with T-Mobile Data</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358431210873</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:00:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>data modem - T-mobile Sim card - Huawei</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358432042670</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:14:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358432429526-23</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD accuses former staff of giving 100,000 secret documents to NVIDIA"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358384945597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 20:09:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Master? Will this whole secret documents caper become a movie? You know, like that documentary/thriller movie about the Watergate break in. "All the President's Men" The plot is far better than anything Hollywood writers could make up. They could call it "Desperado II" Or maybe, "Outward Bound -- The Final Days" It would be a gud movie for sure, Master.</Msg><Username>best.clone185</Username><Timestamp>1358432429526</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:20:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358433002840-24</Id><Topic><Title>Jen-Hsun Huang : "We respect the intellectual property of others."</Title><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1358403806186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 01:23:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a very nice brochure and all -- "Our Code." But maybe Jen should have made it into like a video game. And many more nvidia employees might have actually looked at it. Just a helpful suggestion.</Msg><Username>bests.idea</Username><Timestamp>1358433002840</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:30:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358433404544-25</Id><Topic><Title>Jen-Hsun Huang : "We respect the intellectual property of others."</Title><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1358403806186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 01:23:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of helpful suggestions, maybe you and your 50 plus aliases should get a job and quit being the professional pest that you are. Just think if you save your money you might be able to move your mobile home from the river back to a trailer park around people? Just remember that you will be kicked out again if you start molesting the pets like you did at the last place.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1358433404544</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:36:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358434553130-26</Id><Title>This is encouraging</Title><Msg>1. NVDA busted through MA-50 quite easily 2. Tegra 4 is winning against QCOM 300/600/800 branding thinkdigitDOTcom/Mobiles-PDAs/Tegra-4-trumps-Snapdragon-800-series-in_13098.html</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358434553130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:55:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358434875012-27</Id><Topic><Title>This is encouraging</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358434553130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3. Jen is probably buying back stock -- you know, to mop-up the extra sell orders today. The fundamentals are unchanged, well, except nvidia's Cash goes down.</Msg><Username>elf.best</Username><Timestamp>1358434875012</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 10:01:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358435175258-28</Id><Topic><Title>This is encouraging</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358434553130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel earnings speculation? Not sure if I should add...</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358435175258</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 10:06:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358435632655-29</Id><Topic><Title>This is encouraging</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358434553130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I cant imagine Intel beating by too much or, being too rosy about the future. But then again what does Paul O care at this point - he may want to leave on a high note and paint a rosy future and let the next guy mop things up. I can personally attest that I am none too pleased with IGP solution from Intel. I just got a new Dell Latitude refresh, I didn't realize that IGP solutions use System RAM for GPU purposes. #$%$? If one wants better GPU performance, sacrifice more RAM to GPU. This is not good - Intel could easily have added some dedicated memory to their chip.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358435632655</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 10:13:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358436107643-30</Id><Topic><Title>This is encouraging</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358434553130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't have a discrete GPU in my work laptop and the CPU gets throttled when doing anything visual demanding. Seems to be a lot buyers by looking at the B/A. I am just a bit nervous to add ahead of Intel.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358436107643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 10:21:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358436544488-31</Id><Topic><Title>This is encouraging</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358434553130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have been watching the volume and blocks and on the face of it there still seems to be institutional selling at NVDA. INTC charts look beautiful but overbought at this time. I would not add NVDA ahead of INTC earnings. NVDA will only move significantly on NVDA news. There is too much confusion on NVDA strategy - they need to clarify and provide 2014 FY guidance.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358436544488</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 10:29:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358436914843-32</Id><Topic><Title>This is encouraging</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358434553130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you see that is cluing you into institutions selling? I am not reading it that way or not looking at the same data so I am curious.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358436914843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 10:35:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358439928368-33</Id><Title>stock return/board noise ratio flat.....</Title><Msg>I'm starting an index on this</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1358439928368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 11:25:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358441466397-34</Id><Title>CES 2013 interview: Jen-Hsun Huang, CEO Nvidia</Title><Msg>Long Interview at CES, but the question and answer part-back half is quite interesting. One or two hints are dropped. youtube.DOT/watch?v=LvlyW1Rx3zE I do like the change that has come over Nvidia in the last 6 months. Under promise and over deliver. I know it affects the option players but so be it. Slow and steady. Love the dividend...Don't you?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358441466397</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 11:51:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358446577949-35</Id><Title>12:54 PM LG and Google (GOOG) are reportedly working on a new Nexus phone.The device is said to feature Nvidia's (NVDA) new Tegra 4 processor</Title><Msg>12:54 PM LG and Google (GOOG) are reportedly working on a new Nexus phone, one that could be a decent high-end entry. The device is said to feature Nvidia's (NVDA) new Tegra 4 processor, a 5" 1080p display (standard for the latest high-end Android models), and a 13MP camera. Also reportedly in the pipeline is a Nexus 7.7 tablet with a Tegra 4 and 1920x1200 display. Google's Nexus 7 tablet has sold pretty well, but sales of the Nexus 4 phone (also a Google/L2G collaboration) has been hurt by limited availability and a lack of 4G support.</Msg><Username>robot5investor</Username><Timestamp>1358446577949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 13:16:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358449311597-36</Id><Topic><Title>This is encouraging</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358434553130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>o.investor Weren't you just saying, just the other day, that the iGPU was more than good enough and that discrete GPU is dead?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358449311597</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 14:01:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358453936524-37</Id><Topic><Title>Google Nexus 7 beats Ipad in Japan for the first time</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358440991898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 11:43:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wait till they, OEM's, start incorpatin T4</Msg><Username>dont_a_pik</Username><Timestamp>1358453936524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 15:18:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358454527822-38</Id><Title>Grey T4, Fools take</Title><Msg>FOOLS: hope you enjoy this excerpt, which examines at five key catalysts facing the company. Integrated graphics performance: There will always be a market for discrete GPUs among serious gamers and enthusiasts. However, integrated graphics remains a threat. For example, Intel's (NASDAQ: INTC ) latest Ivy Bridge chips have seen graphics performance up to 41% better than the previous generation Sandy Bridge processors. AMD's (NYSE: AMD ) Llano processors outperform Ivy Bridge by 33%. The threat that these CPUs pose is commensurate with their improvements in integrated graphics performance. Tegra "Grey" release: The launch of a Tegra chip with integrated LTE will be a momentous occasion for NVIDIA, one that will give the company a new level of legitimacy in challenging Qualcomm's (NASDAQ: QCOM ) dominant lead in the market. In some cases, NVIDIA has been forced to split design wins (like the HTC One X) with Qualcomm when OEMs want integrated LTE variants for certain markets. With "Grey," NVIDIA could potentially score those spots exclusively. Competition with Intel: NVIDIA and Intel historically sold complementary products, but rivalry between the two will only increase in the future. In January 2011, NVIDIA scored a six-year cross-licensing agreement with Intel, earning it $1.5 billion in licensing fees payable in five annual installments. However, the two companies will see competition intensify in supercomputers, mobile applications processors, and baseband modems. PC market: As NVIDIA's largest segment, GPU sales into the PC market remain incredibly important to the company's overall results. If growing Tegra sales merely offset GPU declines, the net result may be little to no sales growth. NVIDIA is intent on diversifying away from the PC market and into mobile devices, but this transition is still a work in progress. Tegra tablet wins: The tablet market is ripe with growth, and NVIDIA is set to capitalize on the non-iPad segment. Important wins like the Nexus 7 and Surface RT are just the beginning. There will be an entire wave of Tegra-powered Windows RT devices and new Android tablets in the near future.</Msg><Username>dont_a_pik</Username><Timestamp>1358454527822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 15:28:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358455646355-39</Id><Title>Think Intel, think PCs, think Nvidia....I am out!</Title><Msg>000000000000001</Msg><Username>bucue976</Username><Timestamp>1358455646355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 15:47:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358458044111-40</Id><Topic><Title>Think Intel, think PCs, think Nvidia....I am out!</Title><Username>bucue976</Username><Timestamp>1358455646355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 15:47:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good luck with your short...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358458044111</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 16:27:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358458967059-41</Id><Topic><Title>Think Intel, think PCs, think Nvidia....I am out!</Title><Username>bucue976</Username><Timestamp>1358455646355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 15:47:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why not think Qualcom, Tablets/Phones, Nvidia? However, I have to agree I don't think we are in store for a rough ride until MWC.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358458967059</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 16:42:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358459700282-42</Id><Title>Think Qualcomm Snapdragon, think Nvidia Tegra.....I am out more!</Title><Msg>000000000000</Msg><Username>bucue976</Username><Timestamp>1358459700282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 16:55:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358459903150-43</Id><Topic><Title>Think Qualcomm Snapdragon, think Nvidia Tegra.....I am out more!</Title><Username>bucue976</Username><Timestamp>1358459700282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 16:55:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok fine...but do you have to keep posting your IQ in the body of these messages? Sheesh!</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358459903150</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 16:58:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358460241498-44</Id><Topic><Title>Think Qualcomm Snapdragon, think Nvidia Tegra.....I am out more!</Title><Username>bucue976</Username><Timestamp>1358459700282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 16:55:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much did you short...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358460241498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 17:04:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358460576594-45</Id><Topic><Title>Think Qualcomm Snapdragon, think Nvidia Tegra.....I am out more!</Title><Username>bucue976</Username><Timestamp>1358459700282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 16:55:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you live in the same trailer park that best the pest lives in?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1358460576594</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 17:09:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358461913429-46</Id><Title>Intel after hour quote</Title><Msg>http://data.cnbc.com/quotes/intc</Msg><Username>bucue976</Username><Timestamp>1358461913429</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 17:31:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358462978302-47</Id><Topic><Title>INTC off4%. Q4 revenue in-line, EPS beats; Q1 and yearly view light</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358462397842</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 17:39:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They don't expect integrated lte until 2014. Way behind.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1358462978302</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 17:49:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358463831559-48</Id><Title>nvda getting so broadly diversified</Title><Msg>pc, tablet, notebook, camera, phone, auto, tv, gaming console &amp; anything /everything requiring superior graphics &amp; photos..... Bearish bets based upon slowing pc sales are ridiculous. furthermore, Nvda's chips are specialized within the pc mkt...much slower degradation vs the overall mkt. What a screaming buy here! look for Nvda to be huge share repurchaser's of stock as well. Analysts forgetting about the annual patent settlement payments rolling in...</Msg><Username>netttrunner</Username><Timestamp>1358463831559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:03:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358464414733-49</Id><Topic><Title>nvda getting so broadly diversified</Title><Username>netttrunner</Username><Timestamp>1358463831559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:03:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fall off that Intc reported from PC where never in the Nvidia market, as you say. It's the high end high margin where Nvidia makes it's money on the PC side of things. Nobody seems to realize that a portion of that the PC segment that keeps dropping off is adding not subtracting to Nvidia's base. Web surfers and youtube watchers don't buy PC's with high graphics cards but they do buy tablets with Tegra...enough said.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358464414733</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:13:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358464486394-50</Id><Title>Read this Intel news. Read the first paragraph!</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-4q-profit-down-beats-212847625.html</Msg><Username>plungy</Username><Timestamp>1358464486394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:14:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358464778514-51</Id><Topic><Title>Read this Intel news. Read the first paragraph!</Title><Username>plungy</Username><Timestamp>1358464486394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:14:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean the cheap PC business that Nvidia left 2 years ago and switched to selling tablet processors to tablet manufacturers that caused the downturn for Intel. P.S. - Intel's PC client division was down only 1.7%. Yes that's a ton of cheap O PC's but doesn't affect Nvidia. Now AMD it will probably Kill off.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358464778514</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:19:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358465686379-52</Id><Title>And You Thought Jensen Was A Spendthrift--Check Out Intel</Title><Msg>Intel raised their Capex for 2013 to 13B while taking excess capacity charges in Q4 2012 with existing fabs running at 50% of capacity. Yes I get Intel spending to shrink the die constantly but good grief perhaps this time they have gone too far? What do you think?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358465686379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:34:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358465931006-53</Id><Topic><Title>And You Thought Jensen Was A Spendthrift--Check Out Intel</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358465686379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:34:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...a monopoly has its advantages...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358465931006</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:38:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358466369678-54</Id><Topic><Title>Read this Intel news. Read the first paragraph!</Title><Username>plungy</Username><Timestamp>1358464486394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:14:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many aliases you got ??? why hide behind so many aliases ?? good luck with your short</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358466369678</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:46:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358466611414-55</Id><Topic><Title>And You Thought Jensen Was A Spendthrift--Check Out Intel</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358465686379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:34:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think desperation. They overslept and were late to the bus stop. so they've decided to hail a cab and pay the high fare and they are hoping they get to school in time before lunch and all the food is gone. :-)</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358466611414</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:50:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358467416186-56</Id><Title>tegra4 is a bust. Can't make a profit selling $20 chips.</Title><Msg>tegra 3 was a loss leader. Tegra 4 will bring even more losses.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358467416186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:03:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358467690664-57</Id><Topic><Title>tegra4 is a bust. Can't make a profit selling $20 chips.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358467416186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:03:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hasn't stopped Qualcomm has it? For that matter I hear you're mom does quite well selling her chips for $20 a pop too. :-p</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358467690664</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:08:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358467757937-58</Id><Topic><Title>tegra4 is a bust. Can't make a profit selling $20 chips.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358467416186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:03:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and before anyone comments...YES it has digressed to that.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358467757937</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:09:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358467849172-59</Id><Topic><Title>Read this Intel news. Read the first paragraph!</Title><Username>plungy</Username><Timestamp>1358464486394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:14:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude, how did you post the link ?? Yahoo boards suck these days...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358467849172</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:10:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358467948596-60</Id><Topic><Title>Read this Intel news. Read the first paragraph!</Title><Username>plungy</Username><Timestamp>1358464486394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:14:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's wrong with the link???</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358467948596</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:12:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358468257129-61</Id><Topic><Title>Read this Intel news. Read the first paragraph!</Title><Username>plungy</Username><Timestamp>1358464486394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:14:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The new yahoo boards won't let me post links...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358468257129</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:17:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358468280936-62</Id><Topic><Title>tegra4 is a bust. Can't make a profit selling $20 chips.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358467416186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:03:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Qualcomm sells $40 chips with integrated 4G/LTE.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358468280936</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:18:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358468659286-63</Id><Topic><Title>And You Thought Jensen Was A Spendthrift--Check Out Intel</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358465686379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:34:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just saw Stacy Smith the CFO say that they have to spend even more to keep shrinking the die to really get their X86 architecture into mobile and he said they would spend every dime they have to get there. After all for the last 40 years it has worked and that's the only thing they know. Can't wait for those $100 mobile processor chips selling in $200 to $300 smartphones. Same problem Apple is facing....Who wants to pay $800 for an Iphone when the carriers stop subsidies. Get this You can buy a Nexus 4 on Googleplay unlocked for $299 or go to T-Mobile and buy a Nexus 4 for $199 with a 2 year contract or buy from them without a contract and pay $499. Yes I know the math doesn't work there but it does explain where LG is sending their phones. P.S. AT&amp;T just booked a $10B charge because of smartphone subsidy charges.... Methinks it's all going to end badly for Apple.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358468659286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:24:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358468939724-64</Id><Topic><Title>Read this Intel news. Read the first paragraph!</Title><Username>plungy</Username><Timestamp>1358464486394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:14:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>curious if yahoo lets you post yahoo links ??</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358468939724</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:28:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358469384264-65</Id><Topic><Title>And You Thought Jensen Was A Spendthrift--Check Out Intel</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358465686379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:34:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah - I am willing to bet there is a bit of Samsung in that mix as well. Personally I think Intel is missing the boat by focusing on stuffing a few more transistors on to a smaller and smaller die. In the the end I think the ROI is going to be small, unless like you said they sell their chips for huge premiums but other than being small and maybe outperforming some ARM chips on worthless benchmarks most people don't care about I am not sure what value it will deliver to the OEM, and customer a like.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358469384264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:36:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358469459687-66</Id><Topic><Title>Read this Intel news. Read the first paragraph!</Title><Username>plungy</Username><Timestamp>1358464486394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:14:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The new yahoo boards won't let me post links... getanid I will give you a hint...Yahoo won't let you post a link to some other website rather than one of their own so people won't post links on yahoo to generate clicks for websites that depend on Google Ad sense revenue. I suppose it's hurts some websites rather hard....No names mentioned of course...LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358469459687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:37:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358469699589-67</Id><Topic><Title>tegra4 is a bust. Can't make a profit selling $20 chips.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358467416186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:03:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh well...I guess that leaves just you're mom then.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358469699589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:41:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358469879331-68</Id><Title>Check out cray</Title><Msg>yet another deal selling nvidias chips. Talk about your growth areas</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1358469879331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:44:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358470159901-69</Id><Topic><Title>Check out cray</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1358469879331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:44:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correct me if I am wrong but isn't this old news?</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358470159901</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:49:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358475679962-70</Id><Topic><Title>And You Thought Jensen Was A Spendthrift--Check Out Intel</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358465686379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:34:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One more reason I'm big into Nokia now.....I think they're powering ahead of the pack.</Msg><Username>barjonicat</Username><Timestamp>1358475679962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 21:21:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358482780632-71</Id><Title>What's this? Intel PLUMMETS (-5.25%) after hours due to WEAK PC DEMAND?</Title><Msg>What's this? Intel PLUMMETS (-5.25%) after hours due to WEAK PC DEMAND? And didn't current CEO Jen say that Two Thirds of nvidia parts ATTACH to those out-of-fashion, weakly-demanded PC's? He sure did. My my my. As Best taught us to say, "The first ones out get the best and highest prices."</Msg><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1358482780632</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 23:19:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358483154594-72</Id><Topic><Title>What's this? Intel PLUMMETS (-5.25%) after hours due to WEAK PC DEMAND?</Title><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1358482780632</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 23:19:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Next." That's a very scary word, right? "Next." If you're the #3 cow in line. At the slaughterhouse. And you just witnessed the two cows ahead of you become Oscar Meyer products. Right before your eyes. "Next."</Msg><Username>i_know_best</Username><Timestamp>1358483154594</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 23:25:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358483957935-73</Id><Topic><Title>What's this? Intel PLUMMETS (-5.25%) after hours due to WEAK PC DEMAND?</Title><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1358482780632</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 23:19:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"My bologna Had a first name, it's B-e-s-s-y No. 3...." Ha ha ha ha! See ya all tomorrow, boys. On the LOWER LEVEL, right?</Msg><Username>sing_along_with_best</Username><Timestamp>1358483957935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 23:39:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358485071478-74</Id><Topic><Title>What's this? Intel PLUMMETS (-5.25%) after hours due to WEAK PC DEMAND?</Title><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1358482780632</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 23:19:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? Will Mister ashraf.eassa be asking again on Friday? You know. "What the Heck Happened?" And, "Who is Prophet Best?" And maybe that always popular bagholder lament -- "It's so Unfairly oversold." Ha ha ha ha! That last one has always been my favorite too.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1358485071478</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 23:57:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>