<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364273756891-1</Id><Topic><Title>If you build it, they will come</Title><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1361855539639</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 00:12:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo's information architecture is very messy, so I will just respond to the header in this thread. Someone asked what might be Tegra's FY 2014 'revenue (year ending January 2014, almost equivalent to CY 2013 revenue with a different ending month), the research note by Hans Mosesmann provided an approximate answer: $764 million, vs $540 in the prior year (from my memory, but in the right ballpark). It is not clear whether NVIDIA management gave Hans this information, he arrived at it based on Raymond James's models. Not bad at all considering that it could be the low end of a wide range. In the same article Mosesmann suggested that the breakeven point for Nvidia Tegra would be below $1 billion. We should know how soon NV could reach that level by the end of the year, or before. One of the focal point of concern right now is the lack of visibility re. NV's new offerings. As Mosesmann cleared stated, all greenfield products are backend loaded - the uptake path is never a straight line. Folks who want both the stability and growth prospects at every time point should remember that nVIDIA doesn't sell laundry detergents: you can't have both within a short time span; however, over a longer period of time, the leaps and stalls may be smoothed out and, yes, you could have both by viewing it longitudinally.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364273756891</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 00:55:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364276085266-2</Id><Title>Snapdragon S800 Antutu benchmarks leaked: 32146 (vs Tegra 4: 36000+)</Title><Msg>At the moment, only the ZTE Grand Memo was announced as the first device that powered by the Snapdragon 800 quad-core processor. How fast is this Snapdragon 800 Series processor? Qualcomm said that it has 75% improvement from the Snapdragon S4 Pro. So you can imagine the performance even it is just a quad-core processor. A device with the model number of MSM8974 that clocked up to 2.3GHz was spotted at AnTuTu Benchmark result. Basically the MSM8974 is a processor of Snapdragon 800 Series. The 2.3GHz Snapdragon 800 MSM8974 scores 32,146 points at the AnTuTu Benchmark result. Please remind that the 32,146 points were belonging to the a prototype device that is yet to finalize the software development. So the points could be higher if the Snapdragon 800 processor is in a developed device. For the AnTuTu Benchmark results of other processors, Snapdragon 600 scores about 23,000 points, Samsung Exynos 5 Octa scores about 26,000 points, the NVIDIA Tegra 4 scores about 36,000 points and Intel Clover Trail+processor scores about 27,000 points. The HTC One and LG Optimus G Pro are the devices with Snapdragon 600, Samsung Galaxy S4 with Exynos 5 Octa and Lenovo Ideaphone K900 with Intel Clover Trail+ processor. SOURCE: gsminsiderDOTcom/2013/03/24/snapdragon-800-msm8974-antutu-benchmark-result-leaks-scores-more-than-32000-points/</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364276085266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 01:34:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364296222695-3</Id><Topic><Title>Snapdragon S800 Antutu benchmarks leaked: 32146 (vs Tegra 4: 36000+)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364276085266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 01:34:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nvda put up huge Q loses in the name of having two development teams so they can beat out competition with faster product releases and get the design wins. Looks like it's qcom is the one with the fast product introduction cycles and the socket wins: S4, S4 Pro, S600, S800.... nvda, nvda's holding the bag of huge loses and products that are not manufacturable like the early T2, T3 days that making OEMs staying away in droves. This is a management failure.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1364296222695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 07:10:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364304534625-4</Id><Topic><Title>Snapdragon S800 Antutu benchmarks leaked: 32146 (vs Tegra 4: 36000+)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364276085266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 01:34:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you fit T4 into a phone?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1364304534625</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 09:28:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364305965855-5</Id><Topic><Title>"Nvidia may lose almost eight million processor shipments in 2013"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363734273144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1) 10m tegra 4 for tablet = profit $30x 10m 2) 10m tegra 4 for shield = profit $150 x 10m If you were Jen , ...... Pls select the most profitable strategy</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1364305965855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 09:52:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364307382503-6</Id><Title>The PPS share keeps narrowing...</Title><Msg>And volume continues to dry up... I wonder how long this can last? Just seems like something has to give???</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1364307382503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 10:16:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364308378824-7</Id><Topic><Title>"Nvidia may lose almost eight million processor shipments in 2013"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363734273144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"1) 10m tegra 4 for tablet = profit $30x 10m 2) 10m tegra 4 for shield = profit $150 x 10m" If you are going to make up numbers for units sold and profit per unit and then post BS why stop at 10m and $150? Anyone can post BS. Is this more BS? whay not? 50m tegra 4 for shield = profit $300 x 50m or why not? 100m tegra 4 for shield = profit $500 x100m It is BS right? Because Jen didn't share profit margins with you or any one else for products NOT SHIPPING or profit margin on tablets and neither you or Jen have a clue about how many SHIELD toys will sell. So the answer is both options 1) and 2) are made up BS . Now say it ain't so. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364308378824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 10:32:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364310439029-8</Id><Topic><Title>Snapdragon S800 Antutu benchmarks leaked: 32146 (vs Tegra 4: 36000+)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364276085266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 01:34:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf: Tegra 4 is "architecturally" efficient in comparison with competitors, meaning that: --performance per ^mm --performance per watt are both superior to competition. "Architectural efficiency" is a new concept introduced by NVIDIEA; previously only energy efficiency was emphasized. (Detail numbers can be found in NVIDIA Analysts Call, March 19, slides presentation) Geez.... your question surprised me coming from a regular NVIIDA blogger....on the other hand I shouldn't be surprised knowing you are a SA blogger. There is another example testifying to that effect.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364310439029</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 11:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364310596407-9</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra, Tegra, Tegra, Tegra</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364243089755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:24:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even pumping cheer leaders have doubts when the team takes the field with pictures of their cups instead of wearing them? Jen is still talking about tegra 4 with pictures at any show and tell he can find right? Tegra 4 has yet to suit up and take the field. You seem so happy making up numbers why not make up some tegra design wins to go along with the other BS you post and be happy with that? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364310596407</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 11:09:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364310956575-10</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese Allwinner selling its quad core chips for $10. Tegra is done.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1364259701128</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 21:01:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Used car shop on the corner selling '98 Fords and Chevy for $2,000. New car companies are done. Same logic. If you want old tech, you get what you pay for. If that is all you need, then the good deal is yours.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1364310956575</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 11:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364311190718-11</Id><Topic><Title>Snapdragon S800 Antutu benchmarks leaked: 32146 (vs Tegra 4: 36000+)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364276085266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 01:34:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra 4 is not available for benchmarking because Nvidia hasn't sold ONE yet. Any benchmark numbers for PRODUCTS NOT FOR SALE is pure BS and you should know better. ONLY when reputable sights can get their hands on actual products for sale on the open market can there be REAL BEABNCHMARKS. Cherry picking parts from a trial run for benchmarks is BS. Selected releases of Nvidia In house benchmarks results is BS. If Intel or QCOM did that nonsense it would be BS so why the free pass for Nvdia? Where is the REAL Tegra 4 PRODUCT that was used in the benchmarks? You knew it had to be BS and you posted it anyway. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364311190718</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 11:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364311492669-12</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra, Tegra, Tegra, Tegra</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364243089755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:24:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Saying that there are going to be no tegra design wins is like saying the PS4 will have no games for it because it hasn't announced any yet. Operating under the assumption that the T4 already has more tablet design wins than the T3 is reasonable, given that management has announced it. They may have lost the Nexus 7, most likely due to the production shift, but this is completely reasonable considering that it helped bring the T4i 6 months ahead of schedule, considering how Nvidia was virtually non-existant in the mobile market. Trading one high profile device for a guaranteed more diverse mobile portfolio was the right choice.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1364311492669</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 11:24:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364311736279-13</Id><Title>Samsung held more bizzare events for Galaxy 4 #$%$ Sammie?)</Title><Msg>youtubeDOTcom/watch?v=mhMKRZ8d1Us&amp;list=UUZHOnKmxXrHDWVL6Sgk2ETw</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364311736279</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 11:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364312344727-14</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the 64 bit 8 CORE CPU+GPU to power the new PS4 Nvidia had to offer Sony?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363367895356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:18:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Where is the 64 bit 8 CORE CPU+GPU that Sony wanted and Nvidia had but decided not to sell? " PC and PlayStation game developers are now saying they like the AMD Sony deal. New reports are out that game developers wanted a 64 bit x86 platform for Consoles to match the PC with a REAL GPU on board. Not having to port x86 PC game code to a console one off CPU architecture saves money and time. Saving money and time is a good thing right? Where is the good thing Nvidia had to offer Sony and game developers? Where is Nvidia's competing 64 bit product that they passed on selling Sony? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364312344727</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 11:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364312439523-15</Id><Topic><Title>The PPS share keeps narrowing...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1364307382503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 10:16:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nuts. I've never seen the stock trade like this in the decade or so I've been following it. No one can make money if the shares never budge...</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1364312439523</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 11:40:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364312765488-16</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra, Tegra, Tegra, Tegra</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364243089755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:24:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Saying that there are going to be no tegra design wins" CAN YOU READ? Where did you see "there are going to be no tegra design wins" in that post? Who said that? Did you see the word "yet"? Starting your post with a lie for your first sentence is not how to go about pumping Nvidia. How many Tegra 4 products are on sale TODAY? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364312765488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 11:46:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364312957967-17</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra, Tegra, Tegra, Tegra</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364243089755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:24:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many S800 products are on sale today?</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1364312957967</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 11:49:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364313029607-18</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra, Tegra, Tegra, Tegra</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364243089755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:24:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also it was very tough to interpret you're broken English post, so that is why I got confused.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1364313029607</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 11:50:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364313775151-19</Id><Title>You can't post REAL Benchmarks for a Product that NO ONE CAN BUY without posting BS</Title><Msg>Tegra 4 is not available for benchmarking because Nvidia hasn't sold ONE yet. What site has a production Tegra 4 product today to Benchmark and can release benchmarks numbers ignoring any NDA with the Vendor and Nvidia? Any benchmark numbers for PRODUCTS NOT FOR SALE is pure BS. Any anyone posting Benchmarks HERE for Tegra 4 that Nvidia has yet to release is posting BS, EVEN if Nvidia did it. If Intel or QCOM were to claim that their in house bencharks for unreleased parts beats Tegra 4 isn't that BS? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364313775151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:02:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364313871048-20</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra, Tegra, Tegra, Tegra</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364243089755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:24:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First thing to know is they have to get in line. The first 2 million 4's are ours. They will be in the shield. After that it will be friends first.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1364313871048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:04:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364313995488-21</Id><Topic><Title>You can't post REAL Benchmarks for a Product that NO ONE CAN BUY without posting BS</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364313775151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:02:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you can, especially when you compare them to the benchmarks of a competing product that no one can buy yet as well.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1364313995488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:06:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364314247094-22</Id><Topic><Title>Snapdragon S800 Antutu benchmarks leaked: 32146 (vs Tegra 4: 36000+)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364276085266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 01:34:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf asked: "Can you fit T4 into a phone?" To make learning easier for you: T4 is about the same size of T3, perhaps just a shade bigger. Now go and figure out whether T4 can fit into a phone or not. lol</Msg><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1364314247094</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:10:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364314285227-23</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra, Tegra, Tegra, Tegra</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364243089755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:24:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Also it was very tough to interpret you're broken English post, so that is why I got confused." Shove the insults. We all know the analogy to sports went over your head. I won't argue with you about one thing though: "that is why I got confused", you do seem confused. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364314285227</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364314712595-24</Id><Topic><Title>You can't post REAL Benchmarks for a Product that NO ONE CAN BUY without posting BS</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364313775151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:02:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I think you can, especially when you compare them to the benchmarks of a competing product that no one can buy yet as well." Says it all. Made up benchmarks compared to made up benchmarks for products that NO ONE CAN BUY makes sense to you? Then enjoy your Nvidia made up benchmarks compared to anything you want. One word decribes that logic, CLUELESS. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364314712595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364315057235-25</Id><Topic><Title>The PPS share keeps narrowing...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1364307382503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 10:16:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>man! 3 hours went off today and the stock has going nowhere not even a penny up</Msg><Username>misterx.herrx</Username><Timestamp>1364315057235</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:24:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364315878158-26</Id><Topic><Title>"Nvidia may lose almost eight million processor shipments in 2013"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363734273144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2012 10m tegra 3 profit ($30-$15) $15 x 10m 2013 2m shield profit ($299-$150) $149 x 2m</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1364315878158</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364316088814-27</Id><Topic><Title>The PPS share keeps narrowing...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1364307382503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 10:16:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"And volume continues to dry up... I wonder how long this can last? Just seems like something has to give???" It can go on for months.....Just no interest in the stock right now. If the CEO can say "I am not being Coy, I truly just don't" how can anyone else. Write some calls. It will give you something to do.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364316088814</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:41:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364316548991-28</Id><Topic><Title>BrreakingNews: EU ministers agree to a bailout package for Cyprus</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364180709731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 23:05:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Barring unforeseen factors, market should respond to the news positively." Claiming to know what markets will do on an Nvidia message board shows everyone that someone want to be a KNOW IT ALL even if often wrong? So were you right buying thousands of shares of Nvidia at $16.01 weeks before Nvidia would see $8s? Were you right about what markets would do? And why do you need to claim to know what markets will do on an Nvidia message board? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364316548991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:49:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364316678311-29</Id><Topic><Title>You can't post REAL Benchmarks for a Product that NO ONE CAN BUY without posting BS</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364313775151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:02:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really shouldn't say made up to describe these benchmarks, they are actually tested chips, they just aren't the production models. I mean the T4 was benchmarked in front of people.. I will assume that both the S800 benchmarks and T4 benchmarks are based on prototypes that are spec'ed to do as well as possible for them. So yes, it is possible to compare them. If the T4's best is better than the S800's best, regardless of either of them not being in production, it is logical to assume the T4 production model will beat the S800 production model.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1364316678311</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:51:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364317012899-30</Id><Title>google selling nexus 7 in India</Title><Msg>Lest we forget. We are Nexus 7!!! and tegra 3 will bew around for 10 yrs.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1364317012899</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:56:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364318097315-31</Id><Topic><Title>You can't post REAL Benchmarks for a Product that NO ONE CAN BUY without posting BS</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364313775151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:02:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you Nvidia fans losing it? Tegra 4 is not a product that ANYONE will ever buy at retail. You need a REAL product using a Tegra 4 chip to release Tegra 4 benchmarks unless you think consumers will be out shopping for bare Tegra 4 chips to benchmark. Where is the REAL product used to benchmark a Tegra 4 chip? Tegra 4 is NOT FOR SALE and therefore there are NO Tegra 4 PRODUCTS for sale today. No Part for sale and No Product for sale based on the fact that there are No Parts for sale means the benchmarks are all made up BS. Try to keep up. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364318097315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 13:14:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364318347254-32</Id><Title>Low volume</Title><Msg>very low volume. Also what will take NVDA to move up?? Can't believe</Msg><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1364318347254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 13:19:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364318940770-33</Id><Topic><Title>google selling nexus 7 in India</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1364317012899</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:56:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" tegra 3 will bew around for 10 yrs" We can only hope Nvidia is still selling tegra 3 parts 10 years from now. And I hope you will be spending your wages on a tegra 3 product 10 years from now. You and tegra 3 hand in hand 10 years from now puts a simile on my face just like those old cell phones the size of a brick some years ago. Enjoy your Nvidia purchase imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364318940770</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 13:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364319352908-34</Id><Topic><Title>PlayStation money GONE, Nexus money GONE, $26 per Share LONG GONE</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363897547973</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:25:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"PlayStation money GONE, Nexus money GONE, $26 per Share LONG GONE" The more things change the more they remain the same. STILL hugging $12.42 or what? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364319352908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 13:35:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364319558823-35</Id><Topic><Title>You can't post REAL Benchmarks for a Product that NO ONE CAN BUY without posting BS</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364313775151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:02:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See my post below.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1364319558823</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 13:39:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364319611745-36</Id><Topic><Title>"Qualcomm to Replace NVIDIA for Google's Next-Gen Nexus 7"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363724734020</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:25:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Qualcomm to Replace NVIDIA for Google's Next-Gen Nexus 7" Did everyone see this? Had it been the other way around The resident pumping Mr Cut-N-Paste would tag the aritcle as "Breaking News" or "Just In" or "Must Read" but not "Oh Oh" right? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364319611745</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 13:40:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364319723977-37</Id><Topic><Title>The PPS share keeps narrowing...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1364307382503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 10:16:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>msian, the 50 dma and 200 dma of NVDA are on their way to converge.....when that happens, it is called a golden cross. Currently, NVDA sits on top of the 50 dma and just below the 200 dma line. Get ready for a trend change. (TA doesn't tell you the direction exactly, but I know what my guess is)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364319723977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 13:42:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364320063329-38</Id><Topic><Title>google selling nexus 7 in India</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1364317012899</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:56:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm new to this planet. Are there many potential buyers there?</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1364320063329</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 13:47:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364320146961-39</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese Allwinner selling its quad core chips for $10. Tegra is done.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1364259701128</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 21:01:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of the press stories are going out with a "under $20" price on the Allwinner quad core. Presumably that pricing is capped by the Tegra 3, which may still have a performance edge. Allwinner may have cost issues dropping it to $10. ARMH has been telling investors that the A7 carries a much higher royalty payment due to the sophisticated design, the GPU is license isn't cheap, and the dual channel memory controller has a higher area and package cost than a single channel design. Part of the die area cost is offset by using a smaller L2 cache. Despite being a lean design firm, Allwinner can't sell these things at cost/COGS. They must have at least 50% gross margin to cover design risk and production risk. Plus if they intend to become a market leader, they'll have to start investing in device drivers. I do find it interesting that they chose a Tegra-like 4+1 energy-saver core design, instead of big.LITTLE. That lets Allwinner use the mature Tegra 2/3, rather than spending money developing the still-experimental big.LITTLE OS support.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1364320146961</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 13:49:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364320889339-40</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese Allwinner selling its quad core chips for $10. Tegra is done.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1364259701128</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 21:01:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I do find it interesting that they chose a Tegra-like 4+1 energy-saver core design, instead of big.LITTLE." Actually the energy-saver core is a modern view to bigLITTLE... The energy-saver core is still an A15, but designed to operate at slower speeds... NVidia found it more optimal to design a cache, memory, and interfaces to one type of CPU than to optimize to two different CPUs...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1364320889339</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 14:01:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364321005490-41</Id><Title>On Ignore: Is that for Posters, Bad Tegra 4 Press or the Lousy Way the Market treats Nvidia?</Title><Msg>Seems there are more posters on this board are asserting the "On Ignore" clause to put anything or anyone "On Ignore", is the Nvdia way? Nvidia was $26 and is now $12s, "On Ignore" . Nvidia was the Play Station supplier but no more, you guessed it, "On Ignore". Nvidia once was the sole processor supllier for Nexus 7 tablet but soon to be replaced by QCOM, "On Ignore" Don't like the fact that you mentioned any the abovet so, "On Ignore" Is "On Ignore" in the Nvidia shareholders manual? That question is rhetorical so you need not reply and besidses I have you "On Ignore". lmao imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364321005490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 14:03:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364321233323-42</Id><Topic><Title>google selling nexus 7 in India</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1364317012899</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:56:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO, Not for OLD Technology when competitors have a better part for sale. What planet are you from? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364321233323</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 14:07:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364322092644-43</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese Allwinner selling its quad core chips for $10. Tegra is done.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1364259701128</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 21:01:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More importantly, according to NV, the fifth core in Tegra 4 is INVISIBLE to OS - it's altogether a different energy-saving architecture from big.LITTLE. gizmagDOTcom/nvidia-tegra-4/25665/</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364322092644</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 14:21:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364322639415-44</Id><Topic><Title>Come on Nvidia PASS on the Xbox WORK too and make it a all 3. Tell WS you are too busy to WORK.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363719630893</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia fans are you waiting for that Nvidia talking head to issue a PR statement claiming to have PASSED on Xbox next? Do you think the same Nvidia talking head can issue a PR release back dated claiming to have PASSED on Nintendo WII. Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364322639415</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 14:30:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364323938334-45</Id><Title>Lets face it folks, tegra4 is a DUD. All those performance this, benchmarks that</Title><Msg>mean very little if it is a power hog.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1364323938334</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 14:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364324819299-46</Id><Topic><Title>Snapdragon S800 Antutu benchmarks leaked: 32146 (vs Tegra 4: 36000+)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364276085266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 01:34:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ibexx, Let me rephrase: at the quoted performance numbers, with acceptable battery life, can Tegra 4 @ 1.9GHz fit the power envelope required for a modern smartphone? At 5W, my guess is "no". I am much more interested in seeing how the Tegra 4i does against the Qualcomm offerings. BTW, no need to be rude about my work on SA. A full on quad core A15 does not seem like it can fit into a phone's power envelope.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1364324819299</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:06:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364325670138-47</Id><Topic><Title>The PPS share keeps narrowing...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1364307382503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 10:16:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First time I've seen consistent 100k for sale at each penny level.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1364325670138</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364325679052-48</Id><Title>Tegra 4 profit</Title><Msg>1) 10m tegra 3 profit ($30-$15) $15 x 10m Revenue $30 x 10m 2) 2m shield profit ($299-$150) $149 x 2m Revenue $299 x 2m If you were Jen, please select 1) or 2) Of course 2) double revenue / profit</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1364325679052</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364325905306-49</Id><Title>Nice end of day pop!</Title><Msg>Couple days in a row at end of day. Once whomever is trying to hold the stock down leaves, we will finally break out. GLTA!</Msg><Username>apdamic</Username><Timestamp>1364325905306</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:25:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364326934641-50</Id><Title>Intel to form own internet tv streaming service</Title><Msg>What are they going to use? Grid?</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1364326934641</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364326990282-51</Id><Topic><Title>Snapdragon S800 Antutu benchmarks leaked: 32146 (vs Tegra 4: 36000+)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364276085266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 01:34:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf, I think you might be misinterpreting how the power is used on T4 because there have been reference tablets and phones with the T4 chip inside going back to MWC. T3 was workable for smart phones and as I understand it the T4 was not intended exclusively for tablets, chromebooks and/or 'consoles'. The way the A15 cores are used is critical to the power consumption and I think some of us are falling into an assumption that the 4+1 still works the same way it did with T3. I don't think simply seeing it as 5W adequately describes how the power envelope is managed. In any case, we'll know soon enough.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1364326990282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364327175996-52</Id><Topic><Title>Snapdragon S800 Antutu benchmarks leaked: 32146 (vs Tegra 4: 36000+)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364276085266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 01:34:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My take is that the quoted performance numbers are just peak performance. As Nvidia has stated in many cases it is about getting the job done as fast as possible and then ASAP go to sleep. Performing the task fast(er) and hence going to sleep state faster can be better for battery life and end user experience. But, with those numbers Nvidia could choose to adjust the frequency if better for smartphones and still be competitive. /Take care Frank. P.S. I appreciate your articles from SA and your more balanced view of things but often your advice/conclusions seems very attached to near term events rather than the bigger story unfolding. What audience do you intend for your SA articles?</Msg><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1364327175996</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:46:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364327364188-53</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 4 profit</Title><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1364325679052</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>50m gamers in the world 1/10 buy shield If 5m shield profit $149 x 5m 500% profit of 2012 tegra 3 profit</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1364327364188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:49:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364327531528-54</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 4 profit</Title><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1364325679052</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Tegra 4 profit" You can't have a profit for a chip before it goes on sale but you can MAKE UP NONENSE NUMBERS based on nothing. Neither Jen or Nvidia share any pricing, margin or sales data with you n Tegra 4 before Tegra 4 goes on sale. You don't have a clue about Nvidia profits on unreleased chips. Why are you wasting this boards time posting your MADE UP BS? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364327531528</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:52:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364327731506-55</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 4 profit</Title><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1364325679052</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you make any profit from short sell nvda shares? It is going up soon Better cover ASAP</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1364327731506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:55:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364327858531-56</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 4 profit</Title><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1364325679052</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"50m gamers in the world 1/10 buy shield" Is SHIELD or Tegra 4 on sale today? And you know 1/10 of gamers will buy a SHIELD toy because of what? Did you just make that up? Is that based on how well SHIELD is selling now or how well Tegra 4 is selling now or made up BS? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364327858531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:57:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364328297956-57</Id><Topic><Title>Lets face it folks, tegra4 is a DUD. All those performance this, benchmarks that</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1364323938334</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 14:52:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Lets face it folks, tegra4 is a DUD" Nvidia fans put that bit On Ignore a long time ago. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364328297956</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 16:04:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364328615964-58</Id><Topic><Title>You can't post REAL Benchmarks for a Product that NO ONE CAN BUY without posting BS</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364313775151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:02:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone else want to post BS benchmarks for a product that is not for sale with a chip that is not for sale and compare to other products not for sale with chips not for sale and then claim Nvidia is winning? lol If REAL Benchmarks for REAL Products aren't available then you always try to BS your way through right Nvidia fans? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364328615964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 16:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364329039030-59</Id><Topic><Title>PlayStation money GONE, Nexus money GONE, $26 per Share LONG GONE</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363897547973</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:25:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"PlayStation money GONE, Nexus money GONE, $26 per Share LONG GONE" Did I make any of that up? Is Nvidia still expected to supply Sony for the NEW PS4 or Google for the NEW Nexus tablet? Is the stock still $26? What is the deal with Nvidia fans posting MADE UP BS on this board? Can't you Nvidia fans find enough REAL good things about Nvidia to say without making it up? Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364329039030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 16:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364330846217-60</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 4 profit</Title><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1364325679052</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3rd May earning report + next quarter estimate (include shield launch date and sales estimate) If you want to know exact number come back 3rd May Please don't BS everyday BS and BS</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1364330846217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 16:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364330850546-61</Id><Topic><Title>You can't post REAL Benchmarks for a Product that NO ONE CAN BUY without posting BS</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364313775151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:02:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See post below? It's a pretty logical train of thought.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1364330850546</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 16:47:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364331452520-62</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360282938040</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:22:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!" Who else wants to post LIES and nonsense that is completely MADE UP? Has this board become accepting of LIES and MADE UP BS in place of news or facts about Nvidia? Why bother to post and read a board if everyone seems to think its acceptable to MAKE IT UP? REAL Nvidia news isn't the problem but the MADE UP NONSENSE is. Over a month later he post another NEW LIE to cover up his first LIE? "Substitute "Per Share" with Market Capitalization and the statement is true." More NONSENSE from someone who doesn't care about the truth. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364331452520</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 16:57:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364332664934-63</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 4 profit</Title><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1364325679052</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"3rd May earning report + next quarter estimate (include shield launch date and sales estimate)" Really? And you know in advance what will be included in an Nvidia May earnings report because of what? Is this March or May? So the numbers you posted today is JUNK YOU MADE UP and are based on NONSENSE right? Stop embarassing yourself. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364332664934</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 17:17:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364333042298-64</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 4 profit</Title><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1364325679052</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 15:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3rd May earning will tell you everything Remember to cover all your short shares and cover short calls ASAP</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1364333042298</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 17:24:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364333267234-65</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese Allwinner selling its quad core chips for $10. Tegra is done.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1364259701128</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 21:01:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, I'm sure Intel and Qualcom will go out of business too....especially since the Chinese are known for high quality and developing their own IP. Tool</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1364333267234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 17:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364334211354-66</Id><Title>Intel Pay Internet TV</Title><Msg>Bloomberg news reported yesterday that Intel will be launching a pay internet Tv service this year and that they are in advanced talks with Media Content providers. bloombergDOTcom/news/2013-03-26/intel-said-nearing-media-company-deals-for-pay-tv-service.html _______________________________________________________________________ When I saw this I thought....What staid old Intel will beat Apple to the punch. This is a joke right. But the stock popped 3%. Evercore Partners reported yesterday: "Evercore Partners tech analyst Patrick Wang today offers up clients some notes from his trip through Silicon Valley last week, ranging across a number of semiconductor names." "Wang thinks server chip trends are shaping up a little better for Intel (INTC) at the moment than some might think: Our checks indicate stable and more robust Romley trends through March, perhaps driving upside to generally low investor expectations. This server strength appears somewhat broad-based, covering Cloud / direct as well as more traditional Enterprise customers. While a positive for VLTR (VLTR) 1Q trends, our LT concerns remain. We also heard about recent price cuts to AMD (AMD) Opteron in order to keep up with INTC. As we previously wrote (note), AMD’s x86 Opteron roadmap may be nearing its end." blogsDOTbarronsDOTcom/techtraderdaily/page/2/ ____________________________________________________________________________ Romley upside is good for Nvidia (Quadro) as well as Intel. Evercore partners - AKA Hedge Fund types have a neutral rating on Intel PT $22 and A sell rating on Nvidia PT $11. No mention of Nvidia in the Barrons Tech Trader article. Full disclosure I bought some Intel Shares yesterday. Still hold Nvidia shares after selling some yesterday morning, but most covered by selling near term covered calls. Like Nvidia Long term just tired of watching the flat line. I wish all posts required specific disclosures....perhaps I will start a new trend.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364334211354</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 17:43:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364334283780-67</Id><Title>Xc3155 GTX Titan sold out in few days</Title><Msg>What do u think of 3rd May earning report, Good Luck to you</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1364334283780</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 17:44:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364335408851-68</Id><Title>Look who is pumping Intel on the Nvidia board after dumping Nvidia?</Title><Msg>Another Nvidia pump and dump before being bitten in the rump holding junk. lmao And but of course AFTER an Intel up day he claims to have bought Intel yesterday. "Intel Pay Internet TV" what? What was that about TV again? Is everyone tuned into his Channel NONSENSE? lol His new pump is Intel is sexier than Apple and Nvidia is a " flat line" coma patient. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364335408851</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 18:03:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364336999028-69</Id><Title>"AMD builds a game console monopoly"</Title><Msg>"AMD has quietly gained control of the game consoles currently shipping (with the exception of the PS3), and the company recently confirmed it will be providing the core technology for Sony's upcoming PS4." ... "Wrapping Up: AMD’s Not So Secret Advantage However, the not so secret advantage in doing this is that graphically, AMD will basically own the high performance gaming market because developers will feel more comfortable writing to AMD’s unique graphics capabilities once they exist across all the game systems and in PCs. Now because games are increasingly portable between PCs and consoles, this should give them a competitive advantage in the PC gaming market as well that they’ll surely exploit. You see, it isn’t always the fastest or most powerful product that wins, but it may be the one that is most efficiently utilized. Simply put, this can result in more performance for the buck and buyers, either those building consoles or PCs, are interested in products with the best value because those are the ones consumers often chase. AMD quietly has moved into a position where it could dominate all but portable gaming. And, should they eventually target that, they’ll come in with the advantage of dominating another market first. I guess AMD has decided it doesn't want to be an underdog anymore." Source: TGDaily</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364336999028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 18:29:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364337290878-70</Id><Topic><Title>Look who is pumping Intel on the Nvidia board after dumping Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364335408851</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 18:03:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Xc, As I said "I am hoping to start a new trend of full financial disclosure of all posters... So let's see if you can be #2......What is your financial interest in Nvidia? Short? None? Own a competitor's stock? and if so which one? I suspect that you may be a core AMD holder , but I do not know? Be interesting to hear!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364337290878</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 18:34:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364337598570-71</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD builds a game console monopoly"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364336999028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 18:29:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Full article was interesting, but the fact of the matter is that AMD was in 2 out of the 3 major consoles for the past 6 years and Nvidia was still the superior high end PC graphics provider. Also how many PC ported games there are for the PS3 compared to the Xbox 360.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1364337598570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 18:39:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364337871782-72</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD builds a game console monopoly"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364336999028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 18:29:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are there*</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1364337871782</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 18:44:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364338473962-73</Id><Topic><Title>Look who is pumping Intel on the Nvidia board after dumping Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364335408851</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 18:03:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I suspect that you may be a core AMD holder , but I do not know? " You don't know because I don't pump stocks on a messge board. No going higher, No buying more, No what a bargain at these levels NONSENSE in my post. And despite what you think, No going lower, No avoid buying when talking about Nvidia. Stating Nvidia was $26 and is $12s now is NOT bashing it is a fact. So you won't see any "Took My Profits" post after relentlessly pumping Nvidia to others as you did. BTW: I won't MAKE UP JUNK either like your "Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!" lie. Did that clear it up for you? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364338473962</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 18:54:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364339026120-74</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD builds a game console monopoly"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364336999028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 18:29:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Also how many PC ported games there are for the PS3 compared to the Xbox 360." So losing the PlayStation business is going to sting, hmm? No more bragging about having the high profile PlayStation business when it's ALL AMD inside hmm? lol Play Station MIND SHARE with developers is real according to you. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364339026120</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 19:03:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364339300438-75</Id><Topic><Title>Look who is pumping Intel on the Nvidia board after dumping Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364335408851</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 18:03:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Full disclosure I bought some Intel Shares yesterday. Still hold Nvidia shares after selling some yesterday morning, but most covered by selling near term covered calls. Like Nvidia Long term just tired of watching the flat line." That's what I posted.....XC.....so you have no financial holdings long or short in in Nvidia, nor any of it's competitors? You simply dedicate a large portion of your work week to intermittently post negative comments against Nvidia PPS and the Company? Is it because you have dedicated your life to protecting the Truth, Justice and the American Way? If not........ Are you receiving any financial remuneration from some 3rd party? These are fascinating questions and I hope you respond directly to both. I still believe you are a core AMD stock holder and if so I wish you would some information on said company. But I will not hold my breathe waiting.....Good luck.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364339300438</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 19:08:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364339491458-76</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD builds a game console monopoly"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364336999028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 18:29:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was thinking more along the lines that Sony games, tend to just stay on the console, while Microsoft exclusives eventually get ported to the PC, like Halo, Gears of War etc. Following this, two things are clear. 1. The more commonly ported games for Xbox, which had AMD graphics, did not make a differnece to the fact that Nvidia is the top provider of high end PC gaming graphics. 2. The less-none commonly ported games for the PS, shouldn't make a difference for high end graphics. IE, AMD isn't going to gain much ground in high end PC gaming graphics simply because they are in consoles.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1364339491458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 19:11:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364352150340-77</Id><Title>Project Shield's unannounced details...when would they be released?</Title><Msg>Somet chatters PAX EAST indicated that the pricing of Project Shield has been decided on internally at NVIDIA. We may hear about it along with other unannounced details at E3 in early June. Gaming journalists think the pricing will be competitive within the context of profitability. NVIDIA's marketing department should be well-conditioned to fine-gauge the price points after years of intense competition vs AMD in graphic cards. And June is also a crowed months for the release/demo/update of other gaming devices such as OUYA, Razer Edge Pro, GameStick, PS4, next-gen Xbox and "Steam Box" - not all of them are actual releases, of course, but you are gonna hear some thunderous noises.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364352150340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 22:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364353314665-78</Id><Topic><Title>Snapdragon S800 Antutu benchmarks leaked: 32146 (vs Tegra 4: 36000+)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364276085266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 01:34:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Frank, I understand that it is an unofficial convention (ref. Anandtech) that benchmarks comparisons were made at clock speeds allowing each chip/device's highest claimed HD resolution. The voltages may be different for each chip/devices being compared, but that is a fair way of treating it. I read about this in several of Anandtech articles. In my lead post for this thread, S800 was tested at 2.3GHz, I think the performance numbers for Tegra 4 was obtained at no higher than 2.3GHz.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364353314665</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 23:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364354313178-79</Id><Topic><Title>Project Shield's unannounced details...when would they be released?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364352150340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 22:42:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think NVIDIA marketing got a good feeling at Pax East re. how well Project Shield was received, and how much serious gamers are willing to pay....this may have sealed their decision on price points for Shield. I've speculated all along that the initial targeted adoptors for PS will likely be the serious and semi-serious gamers who also own a GTX 6xx graphic card, not for the J seven-pack crowd who comb the basement of Walmart for bargains.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364354313178</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 23:18:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>