<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367985883581-1</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi tegra 5!!!!?????</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367983733710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chrisssake, get your head up straight! Your master didn't screw it on the right way this morning. The news about Xiaomi Mi4 Powered by Tegran5 was disclosed by a Xiaomi affiliated website. NVIDIA didn't announce it. Now. go do your bashbot repairs....</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367985883581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 00:04:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367988915976-2</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi tegra 5!!!!?????</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367983733710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lol. Doesn't matter who announced it. Fact is, if bull here wanna bang table cheering this, then its a joke. Plus, u think marketing geniuses Nvidia need to announce everything themselves. They may just get others announced for them. Also benchmark tests and reviews, u think they don't pay those to market Nvidia products for them? Its all part of corporate strategy!</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367988915976</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 00:55:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367996450716-3</Id><Topic><Title>Are you ready for the fastest,</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367983678243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:27:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this a joke?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367996450716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 03:00:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367996599170-4</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi Mi4 to be shipped with Tegra 5 Logan SoC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367983037510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would be nice, but don't we need to get to Tegra 4 first? Also, I'd imagine to get to these clock speeds, we'd need to see a move to 20nm, which implies that this is well over a year out. I would much rather see some wins for Tegra 4i, especially as Jensen implied that there was significant interest in it. That's the part that will drive volume, and that's what could push Tegra to breakeven/profitbility during 2014.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367996599170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 03:03:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367997291865-5</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi Mi4 to be shipped with Tegra 5 Logan SoC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367983037510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf, the articles clearly stated that MI4 will be out after Q1 of 2014 whereas Tegra 4 gears are expected in H2 of 2013. Do you have a problem with the sequence of events? Do you not know that 2014 follows 2013 and not preceding it? Seeking Alpha should be able to hire someone more competent than Ashraf E.</Msg><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1367997291865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 03:14:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367998034603-6</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi Mi4 to be shipped with Tegra 5 Logan SoC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367983037510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm reluctant to chime in because I seem to make some people sick on this board :), but I think having Tegra 5 seem to be coming 'too soon' is a misunderstanding of the role 4i and 4 play in the roadmap. Tomasmann is right on the point (to me) about what is supposed to come this second half with Tegra 4 which is actually a shorter period then either 2 or 3 but is at least half a year before Tegra 5 'could' be coming out. Tegra 4i is aiming at the mid to lower priced smartphones, yes? And this phone model will be the top of the line in this company's products. At the same time, continuing to throw insults back and forth with the posters that are serious about the company and the industry doesn't really help anyone. Anyways, I like the news that there is more coming to push the envelope and cut into the edges of what has 'appeared' to be Qualcomm's domain. We still have a whole 6-8 months for Tegra 4 products to be released. (And continuing to complain that there isn't anything announced 'yet' doesn't really clarify or confirm anything.)</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1367998034603</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 03:27:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367998536431-7</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi Mi4 to be shipped with Tegra 5 Logan SoC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367983037510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tomasmann, Personal attacks are always unbecoming and usually reflect a lack of substance in the actual argument. As an Nvidia investor, I want to ascertain the truth - whether it suits my investment or not. Nvidia is scheduled to see first devices with Tegra 4 around Q3 2013, and those will be tablets, perhaps superphones. The problem I have with the alleged "1Q 2014" expectations are numerous: 1. TSMC does not expect 20nm to be significant part of their revenues (they hit the 2% mark) until 2Q 2014, so it is unlikely that we see volume shipments of a 20nm part in 1Q 2014. 2. If this is the case, then Tegra 5 is a 28nm part, in which case I believe that a superior GPU *and* a higher clocked CPU are unlikely in thermally constrained designs. There may be efficiency gains to be had on the GPU side from moving to Kepler, but the higher clock on the already rather power hungry A15's without a process shrink seems implausible. 3. I am not "hired" by SA - I submit articles, they are reviewed, and then they are published.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367998536431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 03:35:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367999077248-8</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi Mi4 to be shipped with Tegra 5 Logan SoC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367983037510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>roundhouse_c, I have no doubt that Nvidia is perfectly capable of designing strong SoCs, and I suspect the modem will be quite good. From an investment perspective, for the Nvidia story, I quite frankly don't care about the high end apps processor market and am infinitely more excited by the Tegra 4i/"Grey" story. Qualcomm's dominance is predicated primarily on modem/integration leadership. If Nvidia's products are as good as claimed, then there will indeed be some share shifts in Nvidia's favor, and this would immediately verify Nvidia's "bet the company on Tegra" move. Once there are signs of profitability here, and signs of ramping to significant scale, I see no reason why Nvidia couldn't be a significantly larger company (by market capitalization) than it is today. But really, I own this stock because Jensen Huang is a superb CEO and will find a way to make money with what he's got. When you have the world's best graphics technology, that alone is probably worth more than the market capitalization of Nvidia. Worst case, Intel buys them and calls it a day. Best case, Nvidia becomes a $30B+ company. Anyway, that's it for my visit to these boards for now. I'm sure ibexx and moorelawyer will come out and spew more nonsense about how I'm a day trader/paper trader/don't own Nvidia, so I'd like to let that storm pass before coming back.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367999077248</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 03:44:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368018932194-9</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi Mi4 to be shipped with Tegra 5 Logan SoC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367983037510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't think you have the brains the catch the drift - T5 is a clock-throttled T4 to cut down on power. now you get it/GET IT? as I had said, there is no top end merchant proc market. T4/T5/t6, all for naught!</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1368018932194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:15:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368019169425-10</Id><Topic><Title>Dow, Nasdaq and S&amp;P SIZZLE</Title><Username>roundhose_c</Username><Timestamp>1367981604557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 22:53:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fast stochastics rolled over 4 days ago. slow stochastics rolled over 2 days ago. sell at the open or be prepared to see low $13 today, sub-$13 tomorrow.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1368019169425</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:19:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368021277636-11</Id><Topic><Title>Prof Stephen Hawking 'boycotts' major conference</Title><Username>screwherbes</Username><Timestamp>1368020294828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you saying that this here Prof. Hawkins doesn't care for Juice? My take is he likes his prune Juice every morn for his constitutional. what does this have to do with Nvda not winning any sockets or its earnings tomorrow. Splain please in less than a couple of words, tia.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_cc</Username><Timestamp>1368021277636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:54:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368022154856-12</Id><Title>Anyone know......</Title><Msg>NVDA's estimate earnings and sales numbers? What about the WHISPER NO., any guesses? NVIDIA Stockholder Meeting Set for May 15; Individuals Can Participate OnlineMarketwired(Wed 9:00AM EDT). Anyone attending? Nvda one of 5 stock pushing electronics industry LOWER. As of noon trading, NVIDIA Corporation (NVDA) is down $0.26 (-1.9%) to $13.57 on average volume Thus far, 5.7 million shares of NVIDIA Corporation exchanged hands as compared to its average daily volume of 10.5 million shares. The stock has ranged in price between $13.52-$13.86 after having opened the day at $13.83 as compared to the previous trading day's close of $13.83. today Nvda at $13.75, watching paint dry.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_cc</Username><Timestamp>1368022154856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:09:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368023639581-13</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra benchmark tests!</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367983246899</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:20:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Benchmarks are a useful thing to watch. Benchmarks now general translate to sales in a few months. Only time will tell.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1368023639581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:33:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368029270061-14</Id><Title>AMD up over 5%, Nvda up 2% eh</Title><Msg>Need to stay positive going into earnings. Anyone have the expected earnings figure</Msg><Username>ruajrkmeoff</Username><Timestamp>1368029270061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:07:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368030847826-15</Id><Topic><Title>AMD up over 5%, Nvda up 2% eh</Title><Username>ruajrkmeoff</Username><Timestamp>1368029270061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:07:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah but from what level?? so your comment is useless!!</Msg><Username>aktienkonto</Username><Timestamp>1368030847826</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:34:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368031996827-16</Id><Topic><Title>AMD up over 5%, Nvda up 2% eh</Title><Username>ruajrkmeoff</Username><Timestamp>1368029270061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:07:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Yeah but from what level?? so your comment is useless!!" When YOU learn math let us know ok? If little Johnny deposits HIS LIFE SAVINGS in a bank and earns 5% is that better that 2% NO MATTER HOW MUCH MONEY Johnny had when he started saving? lmao When the silly Nvidia fans start arguing that gaining 2% is better than gaining 5% you know they've lost it. imho of course.</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368031996827</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368032128645-17</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra benchmark tests!</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367983246899</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:20:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Benchmarks FOR A PART NOT ON SALE IS BS SINCE NO ONE CAN VERIFY THEM. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368032128645</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368032197129-18</Id><Title>"AMD's Strategic Position In The Gaming Industry"</Title><Msg>... "For both of the next generation consoles to be based on an AMD APU is great for developers, and great for AMD" Sorce seeking alpha</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368032197129</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:56:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368033492139-19</Id><Title>AMD UP 40% over the last 8 Trading Days, on Avg 5% Per Day</Title><Msg>Now if putting UP 40% gains over the last 8 trading days ain't HOT then nothing is. youtubeDOTcom/watch?v=J91ti_MpdHA Enjoy Nvidia fans. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368033492139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:18:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368033879098-20</Id><Title>Nvidia cost you $13+ for 30 cents, AMD cost you $3+ for 25 cents. Which INVESTMENT is better?</Title><Msg>Would you rather be UP 7% or 2%? Take your time and show all work. lol Is it sinking in yet Nvidia fans? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368033879098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:24:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368034068175-21</Id><Title>XC: AMD Board Awaits You!</Title><Msg>You know that there is a whole board devoted to AMD, right? :) Shouldn't you be bashing INTC, anyway? Bigger threat to your job, right? Or did you come to AMD through the ATI acquisition, and old bashing habits die hard.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1368034068175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:27:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368034573701-22</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi Mi4 to be shipped with Tegra 5 Logan SoC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367983037510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing wrong or bad about Logan showing up earlier - it only means OEMs have a full range of processors to choose from. I wish the T3 could be sold at $10 or less and still do 50% GM - if they can - that would be the new low end CPU. The mid ends would be the T4/T4i and T5 the high end - sounds like that it was the plan all along - recall how they talked about mid end products - and it begs the question - what's the high end one?? Now we know. Architecturally - I am not sure if the T5 CPUs can perform better than the T4 CPUs at the same node and same clock - if they can Logan with 1 Kepler SMX may be feasible in 28nm and the die size will be less than 115mm2 (which is more or less the size of the QCOM quad cores). The Kepler SMXs will not run at the full clock in 28nm, but even at 1/2 the performance it'll reach ~ 200 GFLOPS! and comes with all the good stuff DirectX11, CUDA etc. The other option is to have 2 Logan CPUs + Kepler + LTE in 28nm - pretty much what QC does all the time. 20nM - If you saw the big fanfare on Apple starting 20nm work with TSMC and the not too subtle hints that it would be risk production ready by Q3/Q4 2013 - it's not too outlandish to think Logan in 20nm would be shipping by 1Q2014. Life is Good! That new INTC CEO will have a 6 months honeymoon with Silvermont and the nightmare begins soon after - talk about #$%$ comparing a 22nm product to a 28nm one and not to mention the cost and die size of the 22nm part.</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1368034573701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368034782884-23</Id><Topic><Title>XC: AMD Board Awaits You!</Title><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1368034068175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:27:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its more fun here wtatching Nvidia fans with their heads stuck in between Jen's rear trouser pockets. You Nvidia fans have been breathing BS so long you can't smell the roses anymore. Besides AMD fans already know what UP 40% in 8 days look like BUT NO ONE HERE DOES. lol IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368034782884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:39:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368034940834-24</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi Mi4 to be shipped with Tegra 5 Logan SoC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367983037510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"That would be nice, but don't we need to get to Tegra 4 first?" I can't add to that. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368034940834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368036509154-25</Id><Topic><Title>Jen was so happy that he was "THRILLED" to work on the PS3 and now what? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367941896163</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:51:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What this board needs is another Jen loves Sony press release? hmm? Perhaps another THRILLER? lol Just because Sony is dating AMD now there is no need for Jen to stop sending roses and trying right? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368036509154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:08:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368037035087-26</Id><Topic><Title>AMD UP 40% over the last 8 Trading Days, on Avg 5% Per Day</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368033492139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:18:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since HOT may not even describe what AMD is doing. Maybe the Alicia Keys Lyrics can nail it, "This Girl Is On Fire"? hmm? What you think Nvidi fans, iIs Fire hotter than just HOT? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368037035087</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:17:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368037306583-27</Id><Title>Nvdia is closer to $14 than AMD is to $4 but will Nvidia see $14 first?</Title><Msg>I have no idea if Nvidia will see $14 first BUT it puts a smile on my face that you Nvidia fans do. lol Come on chime in. Nvidia is only pennies from $14 right? A BIG head start on AMD and $4 right? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368037306583</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:21:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368037973462-28</Id><Title>Jensen will deliver</Title><Msg>gangbusters earnings... I am expecting a release date for SHIELD and maybe possibly another trick up his sleeve. Don't miss out..</Msg><Username>streamingsodapop</Username><Timestamp>1368037973462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368038018214-29</Id><Topic><Title>AMD UP 40% over the last 8 Trading Days, on Avg 5% Per Day</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368033492139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:18:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amd up 7.5% while NVDA is up 1.5% This is not even a contest. How can this be, AMD bleeding money like a sieve and NVDA loaded with a lot of cash, new products, great (will be) earnings and positive guidance?</Msg><Username>to2qur4usa</Username><Timestamp>1368038018214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:33:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368038467295-30</Id><Topic><Title>AMD UP 40% over the last 8 Trading Days, on Avg 5% Per Day</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368033492139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:18:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Amd up 7.5% while NVDA is up 1.5% This is not even a contest. How can this be, AMD bleeding money like a sieve and NVDA loaded with a lot of cash," That MAY be true, which simply means the MARKET sees more VALUE in AMD, to use that silly street term, "GOING FORWARD" than Nvidia. Just a thought. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368038467295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:41:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368039483361-31</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia cost you $13+ for 30 cents, AMD cost you $3+ for 25 cents. Which INVESTMENT is better?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368033879098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:24:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More like $13+ for 20 cents now and $3+ for 25 cents BUT whos counting right? Who notices these kind of silly things anyway right Nvidia fans? Only an investor would pay so much attention to something so silly like ROI anyway right?. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368039483361</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:58:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368040389418-32</Id><Title>Come clean AMD, Are you Pregnant? How'd you gain 40% in 8 days? lol</Title><Msg>Either AMD is pregnant or AMD sold its headquarters to move into a new rental located in the back of a Mickey Ds?. lmao Anyone here have a clue why AMD is getting FAT ? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368040389418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368041407612-33</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi Mi4 to be shipped with Tegra 5 Logan SoC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367983037510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>XIaomi MI4 will be equipped with 3D panoramic camera - state of the art in mobile photography. An additional comments about the marketing plans (as viewed by the public) of Tegra 4/5 chips and devices. --Tegra 4 tablets/smartphones and gaming devices - starting to ship end of Q2 of 2013, will continue into Q3 for the holiday seasons, serving the high-end market. --Tegra 4i phones will ship Q1 of 2014, serving the midrange and low-priced markets - the fastest growing and largest on the global basis. Sales into this segment will be a cash cow for NVIDIA for many months/years to come. --Tegra 5 based smartphones (ie. Xiaomi Mi4) will ship Q2 of 2014, serving a high-end, yet moderate-cost market. When Tegra 5 devices become available commercially, the Tegra 4 gears will be marketed in the mid-range mobile space. T4 and end products will co-exist (and overlap somewhat) with T5 and end products, just like Iphone 5,4,3 are on the market simultaneously, serving different customer bases. This is called smart product differentiation. A next-gen product does not replace or terminate the pre-gen product, as assumed by some half baked "analysts".</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368041407612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:30:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368041458105-34</Id><Topic><Title>Come clean AMD, Are you Pregnant? How'd you gain 40% in 8 days? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368040389418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:13:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you call $3 fat??!!! There must be a 'your mama' joke ...</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1368041458105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368041920939-35</Id><Topic><Title>Come clean AMD, Are you Pregnant? How'd you gain 40% in 8 days? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368040389418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:13:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If you call $3 fat??!!!" Can you read? Where did I say $3? And where did I say $3 is fat? Getting FAT is what I THINK I SAID? And yes putting on 40% in 8 days is GETTTNG FAT and for the math challenged it doesn't matter where you started from. Tell your doctor your head gained 40% in 8 days but then add it was only a peanut to start with I bet the doc would still be shocked?hmm lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368041920939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368042081454-36</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi Mi4 to be shipped with Tegra 5 Logan SoC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367983037510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah, Where is Tegra 4? Are we skipping the DOA parts now? lol Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368042081454</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:41:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368042556365-37</Id><Title>Even Nvidia fans must THINK Tegra 4 is DOA because they're pumping Tegra 5 NOW.</Title><Msg>No Tegra 4 products ANYWHERE and Nvidia fans are pumping Tegra 5 on a message board. Tegra 4 is DOA and THEY KNOW IT. Now say it ain't so. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368042556365</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:49:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368042952457-38</Id><Topic><Title>Even Stephen Hawking's Joining the Fight for Freedom</Title><Username>screwherbes</Username><Timestamp>1368020391815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:39:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All of your anti-semitic postings are emailed to yahoo!.</Msg><Username>transatlantic2013</Username><Timestamp>1368042952457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:55:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368043625710-39</Id><Title>Not even close, AMD ADDS 29 cents or 8.19% Today and a 45% RUN in 8 Days</Title><Msg>Nvidia cost you $13+ for 24 cents Today. While AMD cost you $3+ for 29 cents Today. Is it sinking in yet? AMD is on its way and Tegra 4 is DOA. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368043625710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:07:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368044321803-40</Id><Title>What INVESTMENT just PAID $450,000 on $1 Million in just 8 Trading Days?</Title><Msg>45% in 8 Trading Days or to put that in terms you might understand that would be $450,000 on a $1 Million investment in just 8 Trading Days. That is what the SMART Money just RAKED IN over the past 8 Trading Days. Over 50 Millions AMD shares traded today. And I know that it iis sinking in NOW Nvidia fans. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368044321803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368044855951-41</Id><Title>NVDA BLOWS BY $15.00</Title><Msg>Huge EPS beat and revenue on the TEGRA 4 &amp; 5!</Msg><Username>txsptsfan9870</Username><Timestamp>1368044855951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368045006334-42</Id><Topic><Title>XC all your post IGNORED</Title><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1368044749569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:25:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let this 50th PLUS TIME BE THE LAST TIME YOU PUT ME ON Ignore OK? You and your ignore post BS are a waste of time. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368045006334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:30:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368045425666-43</Id><Topic><Title>Not even close, AMD ADDS 29 cents or 8.19% Today and a 45% RUN in 8 Days</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368043625710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:07:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know, It stings betting the wrong dog and then being forced to watch the dog you called a useless "mutt" kick your dogs "tail" in the market place, doesn't it? Get use to it Nvidia fans Tegra 4 is DOA imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368045425666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:37:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368046352594-44</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD soars, analyst cites speculation on consoles"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367603481352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 13:51:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still think all that Nvidia WHINING about consoles made any sense Nvidia fans? If anything all that Nvidia WHINING about being too busy to WORK FOR IT when it comes to game consoles and then putting out PR about a condim sounding SHIELD Pocket Toy console highlighted CONSOLES. And who is WINNING GAME Consoles today? lol IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368046352594</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:52:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368046473171-45</Id><Topic><Title>" Nvidia is bitter about PlayStation 4, says AMD"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1364843643897</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 15:14:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Nvidia is bitter about PlayStation 4, says AMD" Nvidia MUST BE EVEN MORE BITTER NOW, if that is possible, watching AMD SOAR on GAME Console chatter. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368046473171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:54:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368046833986-46</Id><Topic><Title>XC: AMD Board Awaits You!</Title><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1368034068175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:27:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His ol' lady kicked him out of the house. You can't blame her for that either. He's been on my ignore list for ages. You should give it a try.</Msg><Username>daysofshred30000000000</Username><Timestamp>1368046833986</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:00:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368047158718-47</Id><Topic><Title>XC: AMD Board Awaits You!</Title><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1368034068175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:27:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you trying to add more zeros to the MANY IDs you had? HOW MANY TIMES WERE YOU DELETED FOR YOUR BS? Do you have a clue?</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368047158718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:05:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368047410652-48</Id><Title>After Nvidia reports on Thurs will you Nvidia fans be WHINING or CHEERING? lol</Title><Msg>The Nvidia reporting pattern has been CHEERING AHs on the day of and when the market opens the next day its been all WHINING. lol Lets see if the pattern holds Nvidia fans. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368047410652</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368047620435-49</Id><Topic><Title>Even Nvidia fans must THINK Tegra 4 is DOA because they're pumping Tegra 5 NOW.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368042556365</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:49:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep PUMPING Tegra 5, 6, 7 or Tegra 78 for that matter, it ONLY Proves that Terga 4 is DOA. EVERY post you put up about some outfit skipping Tegra 4 for the next part just PROVES Tegra 4 is DOA imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368047620435</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368048048513-50</Id><Title>any one selling before ER?</Title><Msg>eom</Msg><Username>danlin78</Username><Timestamp>1368048048513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368048177676-51</Id><Topic><Title>What INVESTMENT just PAID $450,000 on $1 Million in just 8 Trading Days?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368044321803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:18:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Put down those Nvidia POM POMs and get out an iPad and figure it out, Up 45% in 8 Trading Days is GOOD for any stock by any standards. While you were out cheering for your dog to get off the floor the smart money was seeing huge gains. And NO ONE can say it ain't so. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368048177676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:22:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368049988889-52</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi Mi4 to be shipped with Tegra 5 Logan SoC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367983037510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ibexx, The only "half baked analyst" here is you.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368049988889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:53:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368050044205-53</Id><Title>Nvidia May 9th earnings report overdue - where are the executives?</Title><Msg>Earnings report should have been out a long time ago and only music on the conference call that should have executives answering hard questions. Where is everybody at Nvidia...did the interim CFO already jump ship???</Msg><Username>techvest21</Username><Timestamp>1368050044205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:54:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368050443870-54</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi Mi4 to be shipped with Tegra 5 Logan SoC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367983037510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure, it's possible that we see Tegra 4 devices (phones) shipping in Q2 2014, but that would imply that it's either a 28nm part (since TSMC's 20nm won't be in any real volume then), or that the time-frame quoted is off. If it's a 28nm part, then I would expect that it is simply Tegra 4 with Kepler GPU instead of the current uArch, which would be a good improvement, but nothing too earth shattering. Anyway, I hope you're right about these time frames, but I will have to see it to believe it.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368050443870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 18:00:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368050720074-55</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia May 9th earnings report overdue - where are the executives?</Title><Username>techvest21</Username><Timestamp>1368050044205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:54:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really, you are that ignorant? It's tomorrow, but I'm doubting you really care about the real ER date.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1368050720074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 18:05:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368050963687-56</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi Mi4 to be shipped with Tegra 5 Logan SoC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367983037510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf, not sure where you are going with this, you aren't sounding like the original Ashraf that handles the comments in the SA articles with more respect, but I'm just noticing you are flipping between 4 and 5 in your comments. I think you meant Tegra 5 devices for Q2 2014.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1368050963687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 18:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368054957258-57</Id><Title>Latest Tegra roadmap, wow fastest Tegra 10....</Title><Msg>10 million! Suppose to power your car, tv, fridge, oven, washing machine, airplane, and even power the earth rotation! From the marketing materials of planet Pluto. But wait not a single tegra 4 is sold yet! Lol. Hahaha hahaha hahhaha . Nvidiots, did u see the real makers of qcom, mediatek, Samsung, always marketing many generations of chips ahead? I believe they always focus on doing a good job now. Nvidiafools !</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1368054957258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 19:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368059332623-58</Id><Title>Multiple models of Win 8 RT machines will run on faster Tegra 4</Title><Msg>SOURCE: Computerworld just in. May 8, 4pm PS: Y! wouldn't let me post the detailed source information.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368059332623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 20:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368059367872-59</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia May 9th earnings report overdue - where are the executives?</Title><Username>techvest21</Username><Timestamp>1368050044205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:54:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Numb-nuts probably paid his income tax on the 16th. Just one of many drive-by bashers who will inundate the board with moronic blather all day tomorrow.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1368059367872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 20:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368059498751-60</Id><Topic><Title>Multiple models of Win 8 RT machines will run on faster Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368059332623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 20:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Problem is, no one will buy em, because of backward compatibility.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1368059498751</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 20:31:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368060021405-61</Id><Topic><Title>Multiple models of Win 8 RT machines will run on faster Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368059332623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 20:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice find ibexx. Do you think that the x-box mobile might be coming soon? Do you think the 7" RT will be price competitive with the Nexxus? It almost has to be to effectively compete, and establish market share.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1368060021405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 20:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368061115292-62</Id><Topic><Title>Multiple models of Win 8 RT machines will run on faster Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368059332623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 20:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't have enough information to speculate on it yet. Remember Qualcomm had the hardest time to provide drivers for the original WIN RT hardware, and I am not sure how S6 and S8 would fare.... The news about multiple models in next gen win8 is truely heartening. Good thing about MS being a partner is that it's got deep pockets - xbox took years before it became a highly successful product. Street has turned very positive about MS as you may have noticed.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368061115292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 20:58:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368061429978-63</Id><Topic><Title>Multiple models of Win 8 RT machines will run on faster Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368059332623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 20:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IF there was a Tegra 4 part shippng and IF anyone was DUMB enough to use Tegra 4 in a tablet and IF Tegra 4 wasn'T DOA then MAYBE a DOA RT Might run on a DOA NON SHIPPING SoC, Maybe. lol IMHO of course</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368061429978</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:03:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368061634710-64</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia May 9th earnings report overdue - where are the executives?</Title><Username>techvest21</Username><Timestamp>1368050044205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:54:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thurs the 9th of May is tomorrow not today.</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368061634710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:07:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368061818615-65</Id><Topic><Title>Latest Tegra roadmap, wow fastest Tegra 10....</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1368054957258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 19:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra 4 is DOA, don't you see Nvidia fans PUMPING Tegra 4i, 5, 6, and ANY Tegra THAT IS NOT Tegra 4. Tegra 4 is DOA when Nvidia claimed THE MARKET DEMANDS A MODEM WITH ANY SoC. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368061818615</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:10:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368062093573-66</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia cost you $13+ for 30 cents, AMD cost you $3+ for 25 cents. Which INVESTMENT is better?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368033879098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:24:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too FUNNY, It ended up being AMD paying 29 cents and Nvidia paying 24 cents. So you Nvidia fans paid $13+ for 24 cents of gains BUT you could have had 29 cents of gains for ONLY $3+. But you know it all right? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368062093573</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:14:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368062522969-67</Id><Topic><Title>Even Nvidia fans must THINK Tegra 4 is DOA because they're pumping Tegra 5 NOW.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368042556365</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:49:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you Nvidia fans start PUMPING Tegra ANYTHING-BUT-4, You are acknowledging that Tegra 4 is DOA, no one can be that CLUELESS to not know that or can they? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368062522969</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:22:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368062625427-68</Id><Topic><Title>Multiple models of Win 8 RT machines will run on faster Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368059332623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 20:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try this: (same write up, different website) freenewsposDOTcom/news/article/b/243226/today/more-support-for-windows-rt-this-time-from-nvidia</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368062625427</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:23:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368062742770-69</Id><Title>Wishing everyone the best of luck, tomorrow night and Friday</Title><Msg>Since I will be in a meeting when the earnings are released, and won't hear the CC (until late) or see the after hours action, and then will be on the road all morning, Friday, to go say "goodbye" to my mother, I just wanted to wish everyone who owns NVDA stock the best of luck with what is said and what the reaction turns out to be. We're RIGHT on the cusp of ANOTHER HUGE break out...and I do believe that the CC will be the catalyst for the first of the 10+% days that I think are coming. The stock hasn't been this high since last August, and ANY kind of upside "surprise" in earnings, guidance, release date for PS (and the price) will propel the stock well past 14 and likely to the 15-16 level. IF there is an "attempt" by the Bears to make it a "sell the news" event, I truly don't see ANY way the stock goes back below 13, for more than a few seconds, if at all. I'll have an order in to buy more, a few pennies below 13, and another order to buy just below 13 1/2. Given the way a lot of tech stocks have performed after BAD news (other than QCOM), I think the likely move is significantly higher. There still hasn't been much covering in the 13 and 14 calls for May or June. The OI is virtually the same that it was a week ago, which only adds to my conviction that we might see a 2 strike move higher, i.e. through 14 AND 15 and approaching 16, by the end of NEXT week. The after hours volume "might" be a tell..if it's several million shares either way, but Friday's volume will certainly be significant unless it somehow stays below 10mm. I would expect to see 12-15mm at a minimum, and other than an exogenous "geopolitical or market event", we're going to see this stock grind higher and higher. As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. Max</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368062742770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:25:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368063419220-70</Id><Topic><Title>Multiple models of Win 8 RT machines will run on faster Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368059332623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 20:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What was the Wizard of OZ song? If I only had a Tegra 4 part or was it heart? But there is NO Tegra 4 ANYTHING to be HAD today so whay all the BS about RT runninmg on a part THAT IS NOW WHERE TO BE FOUND. Tegra 4 is DOA. No modem who cares about Tegra 4. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368063419220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:36:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368063839559-71</Id><Title>Where are those SOLD HALF and Took My Profits post before Nvidia opens it mouth? lol</Title><Msg>Every quarter a so called Nvidia long has DOUBTS and runs for the hills before earning? And then the other Nvidia fans call him a TRADER (and I don't mean stock trader) and votes him off the island for NOT LOSING MONEY like them. lmao TOO FUNNY, so you know its true. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368063839559</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:43:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368065338231-72</Id><Topic><Title>any one selling before ER?</Title><Username>danlin78</Username><Timestamp>1368048048513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:20:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They won't say, not anymore. The last guy to say Took My Profits here was called a TRADER and I don't mean stock trader. The others saw how he was treated and learned to shut up about selling and just pump. They won't let anyone know they are selling now while telling others to buy, not anymore. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368065338231</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:08:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368065528459-73</Id><Topic><Title>Wishing everyone the best of luck, tomorrow night and Friday</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368062742770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:25:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi Max, so,sorry to hear about your mother, best wishes to you and your family.</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1368065528459</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:12:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368066248235-74</Id><Topic><Title>any one selling before ER?</Title><Username>danlin78</Username><Timestamp>1368048048513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:20:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a small sell order at 14.75 so maybe?</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1368066248235</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:24:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368066350120-75</Id><Topic><Title>Wishing everyone the best of luck, tomorrow night and Friday</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368062742770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:25:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Likewise, best wishes to you and your family during this difficult time. I lurk on the boards, but I always enjoy your posts. They're informed, well written, and you're clearly a smart fellow. Be strong and travel safe. J</Msg><Username>jrdelaney1</Username><Timestamp>1368066350120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:25:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368067538236-76</Id><Topic><Title>Wishing everyone the best of luck, tomorrow night and Friday</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368062742770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:25:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>J- Thanks. I'm just hoping I'm not "as dumb as I look"...;) M</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368067538236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368071214555-77</Id><Title>Falling Ipad Mini demand to push Pegatron (the manufacturer) sales down, significantly</Title><Msg>SOURCE: Bloomberg ""Pegatron Corp. (4938), the Taipei-based maker of Apple Inc. (AAPL) devices, forecast its biggest drop in consumer-electronics revenue in six quarters as iPad Mini demand falls. Second-quarter revenue for the business, which also makes Microsoft Corp. (MSFT)s Surface tablet, will drop 25 percent to 30 percent from the previous three months, Pegatron said today. Thats the most since a 37 percent decline in the fourth quarter of 2011. Pegatron, spun off from Asustek Computer Inc. (2357) in 2010, joins Hon Hai Precision Industry Co. (2317) in facing a decline in orders from its largest customer. Apple last month reported its first profit drop in a decade amid shrinking margins and competition from Samsung Electronics Co., and said it will start rolling out new products later this year. A decline in revenue from the iPad Mini is more on demand, while price has been stable, Pegatron Chief Executive Officer Jason Cheng said.... bloombergDOTcom/news/2013-05-08/falling-ipad-mini-demand-to-push-pegatron-electronics-sales-down.html</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368071214555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 23:46:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>