<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361716956441-1</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation featured on MAD MONEY!</Title><Username>browndavid977</Username><Timestamp>1361452514381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:15:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>amazing report</Msg><Username>smithderek310</Username><Timestamp>1361716956441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 09:42:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361724912558-2</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation featured on MAD MONEY!</Title><Username>browndavid977</Username><Timestamp>1361452514381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:15:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████ SHUT DOWN ALL MY COOLING FANS !!!!!!! ████████ ████ $5000 GAMING SYSTEM WENT UP IN HUGE FIREBALL !! ████████ ████████ WHERE DO I SEND THE REPAIR BILL ?????? ████████</Msg><Username>zion_will_up_huge</Username><Timestamp>1361724912558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 11:55:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361726064353-3</Id><Topic><Title>No Tegra 4i in Samsungs new tablet?</Title><Username>real_estate_bobby</Username><Timestamp>1361674129624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 21:48:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exynos is samsung. Like the other top 2 in mobile, Samsung makes their own app processor, fab included. Samsung even has his own LTE. Don't look for samsung to buy anything from nvda anytime soon.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1361726064353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:14:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361727814997-4</Id><Title>Xiaomi phone "third generation" leaked, 5 inch, due out in mid-year (Tegra 4?)</Title><Msg>In terms of the hardware, rumours said the XiaoMi 3 will use the same display technology as Apple did for iPhone 5, the in-cell display technology provided by JDI. Speaking of the camera, XiaoMi will be equipped with a 13 mega pixel camera and it picture quality should reach the level of Full HD. According to the Chinese source, the Xiaomi 3 will make use of NVIDIA Tegra 4 processor is a 1.9GHz ULP GeForce GPU, its image processing is 6 times faster than the NVDIA Tegra 3, bringing us more outstanding gaming and multimedia performance. XiaoMi 3 is expected to roll out in mid-2013. If you are interested, stay tuned and we will report news about XiaoMi as soon as possible. SOURCE: myphonedailyDOTcom/2013/02/21/xiaomi-phone-3rd-generation-leaked-screen-to-be-at-least-5-inch/ _____ PS: FOr those who don't follow the Chinese handset market closely, Xiaomi is an extremely well known and popular brand. The xiaomi M2 (featuring Snapdragon S4 or S4 pro) was an instant sell-out. Xiaomi sold more than 10 million units of smartphones in 2012. Definitely not a minor player in that region.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361727814997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:43:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361732925251-5</Id><Title>TSMC 28nm Capaciy tight AGAIN!</Title><Msg>Digitimes - "TSMC chairman and CEO Morris Chang remarked at the company's most-recent investors conference that the foundry is close to achieving 100% foundry market share in 28nm technology." If it remains this tight - Nvidia will have to pass on some wins because they can't commit to the Volume required by the customer or they would have to sacrifice high margins GPU revenue for Tegra revenue. This is especially problematic at "Launch" where every custimer will want to have a certain volume in hand prior to launch. This could be an interesting problem. So dont expect them to drop GPU prices anytime soon - they can use the 28nm capacity for Tegra.</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361732925251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 14:08:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361733487199-6</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC 28nm Capaciy tight AGAIN!</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361732925251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 14:08:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's always been tight for 28nm... TSMC screwed up and under-estimated the 28nm demand and under-built capacity...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361733487199</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 14:18:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361734421342-7</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC 28nm Capaciy tight AGAIN!</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361732925251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 14:08:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>aapl is fully on board. Samsung must have a half MT Austin fab. Look for samsung to pick up the amzn acct and to finally get other oems to use their Exynos, those will be the only A15s NOT on allocation. "Real men have fabs." Jerry Sanders</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1361734421342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 14:33:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361735091164-8</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation featured on MAD MONEY!</Title><Username>browndavid977</Username><Timestamp>1361452514381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:15:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome!</Msg><Username>leevincent40</Username><Timestamp>1361735091164</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 14:44:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361740751293-9</Id><Title>HP just announced a 7 inch low-end tablet: dual-core A9 processor with very low resolution</Title><Msg>to compete with Nexus 7 in the very crowded low-priced market. Likely the first to come and to be followed by others... SOURCE: slashgearDOTcom/hp-goes-android-with-the-slate-7-tablet-for-169-24270830/ "Hopefully HP can complete in this market. They state this is the first step in offering their customers the Google experience, so we have a feeling that rumored top-tier Tegra 4 device could still be in the works. The new HP Slate 7 will be available in April for the low price of $169."</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361740751293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:19:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361741955792-10</Id><Title>Here's Tegra 4 Benchmarks - Mr. QCOM CMO AnandC Show Us Yours!</Title><Msg>"OK, so about those benchmarks: the Tegra 4 eradicated every current generation phone we've tested, and we test all the phones on the U.S. market. (Note to international readers: We don't generally test phones not sold in the U.S.) That's almost to be expected, as Tegra 4 is the next generation past the Tegra 3 and Qualcomm S4 chips we're seeing in phones today. How about the iPhone 5? Apple's A6 processor is speedy to be sure, but the Tegra 4 nuked it. When we benchmarked the iPhone 5 we got 1640 on Geekbench and 27 fps on GLBenchmark's Egypt HD offscreen benchmark, which tests graphics power. The Tegra 4 scores 4148 on Geekbench and 57 fps on the Egypt HD. Pow. AnTuTu - 36489 BrowserMark - 2777 GeekBench - 4148 GlBench OffScreen - 57 Taijl - 59.86 Source: pcmagDOTcom/article2/0,2817,2415809,00.asp Nvidia Chart</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361741955792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:39:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361742095231-11</Id><Title>At MWC: NVIDIA Tegra 4 supercharges smartphones (video hands on)</Title><Msg>SOURCE: CNET reviewsDOTcnetDOTcom/8301-13970_7-57570939-78/nvidia-tegra-4-supercharges-smartphones-hands-on-video/ BARCELONA, Spain--Nvidia's latest mobile processor, the Tegra 4, and its little brother, the Tegra 4i, will soon be turning up in all manner of smartphones and tablets. I went hands-on with some of Nvidia's reference devices at Mobile World Congress and found the new silicon to deliver some impressive results. Like the Tegra 3 chip before it, the Tegra 4 is a quad-core processor with a fifth power-saving core for less intense tasks. Based on ARM's latest Cortex A-15 platform, it boasts a faster clock speed and a whopping 72 GPU cores -- that's six times the graphics grunt offered by the Tegra 3 chips. There aren't currently any devices running the new chips, but Nvidia had some reference tablets to show it off. I booted up the Geekbench 2 benchmark test on one of the 1080p slates and was quickly given the superb score of 4,166. By comparison, Google's Nexus 7, running the Tegra 3 chip, achieved 1,536 -- and that's far from sluggish. I was shown the game Zombie Driver, too. It's been optimized for the Tegra 4 chip, making full use of dynamic, real-time shadows and high-definition graphics on the 1080p display. It seemed to run extremely smoothly with high frame rates that will no doubt keep casual gamers satisfied. That sort of power will typically have a huge drain on battery life, but Nvidia reckons it's able to be surprisingly sparing with the juice. Indeed, I saw a phone running a high-definition video clip on a 1080p display that was generating around 900 milliwatts of power -- around 25 percent less than the typical smartphone. We'll see how those figures really stack up when we get finished products in our hands. The Tegra 4i is the little brother to full-fat Tegra 4. It packs in fewer GPU cores, but still boasts the four-plus-one CPU, delivering up to 2.3GHz clock speeds. Unlike the super-elite Tegra 4, the 4i is aimed more toward the midrange market. I wasn't allowed to touch the Pheonix reference phone, but the glossy game Real Boxing certainly looked impressive. Perhaps not enough to challenge consoles, but certainly better than you'd expect from most current phones. The Tegra 4 chip is due to make its appearance in devices from the second quarter of this year -- so far, ZTE has announced it will use it -- with the Tegra 4i arriving toward the end of the year. As well as a whole slew of Android phones and tablets, Nvidia tentatively mentioned it will also appear in Windows RT slates. With its increased speed, it's likely the next wave of RT devices will have the power to challenge even today's low- to midrange laptops.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361742095231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:41:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361742121387-12</Id><Topic><Title>Here's Tegra 4 Benchmarks - Mr. QCOM CMO AnandC Show Us Yours!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361741955792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:39:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Of course, the competition isn't standing still. Qualcomm is countering the Tegra 4 with its Snapdragon 800, which the company claims is even faster than the Tegra 4. Samsung is readying the Exynos 5 Octa. Neither of those companies have let us run our usual benchmarks on their devices yet, but we can expect that they'll give the Tegra 4 a run for its money. The first hint we've seen of Qualcomm's new generation comes in some benchmarks done on the HTC One, which uses Qualcomm's new 1.7-GHz Snapdragon 600 chipset - not the 800, but the next notch down. The Tegra 4 still destroys it. Tegra 4 is first coming in Nvidia's Project Shield gaming handheld this spring, followed by phones and tablets later this year. Tegra 4i will come to mobile phones late in 2013."</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361742121387</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:42:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361743139355-13</Id><Topic><Title>Here's Tegra 4 Benchmarks - Mr. QCOM CMO AnandC Show Us Yours!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361741955792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:39:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bam!</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1361743139355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:58:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361743550989-14</Id><Topic><Title>Here's Tegra 4 Benchmarks - Mr. QCOM CMO AnandC Show Us Yours!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361741955792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:39:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very nice post on the benchmarks, thanks you J7! The comparison of Tegra 4 ref. device with HTC One (powered by Snapdragon 600) is most revealing of Tegra 4's performance superiority. Here are the numbers from the article: ...............................Antutu.............Browsermark Tegra 4..................................36489..............2777 HTC One...............................22678..............2262 Notes: --It was previously estimated by several websites that the Snapdragon 800 (available in late 2H), will be 20% faster than the S-600 variant. Still no match for Tegra 4! --Author of the article noted that neither Samsung nor Qualcomm would allow him to benchmark their reference devices. LOL! (Snapdragon 600)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361743550989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 17:05:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361743781506-15</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC 28nm Capaciy tight AGAIN!</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361732925251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 14:08:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whosunw, exynos 5 is dead - at least for now. Where have you been?</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361743781506</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 17:09:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361743872309-16</Id><Title>Why does the company consistently sells its stock each quarter( ~$433 Million in the last 3 years) ?</Title><Msg>It has a strong balance sheet of ~$668 Million in Cash &amp; ~42,462 M Short Term Investments and doesn't really need the additional proceeds.</Msg><Username>awangpro</Username><Timestamp>1361743872309</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 17:11:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361744445400-17</Id><Topic><Title>Here's Tegra 4 Benchmarks - Mr. QCOM CMO AnandC Show Us Yours!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361741955792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:39:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Flash back a month or so to CES — NVIDIA CEO Jen-Hsun Huang officially pulled back the curtain on the company’s new Tegra 4 chipset, and called it the “world’s fastest mobile processor.” It was a hell of a claim to make, but company did little to justify it at the time aside from pointing to its array of Cortex A15 CPU cores and its “72 GPU cores.” Fortunately, NVIDIA is much chattier here at MWC, and was eager to take show off rather impressive benchmarks for its latest and greatest mobile chipset. Well, maybe “eager” isn’t exactly the right word — NVIDIA really hates playing the mobile benchmark game. I don’t blame them. In many ways the sorts of numbers that these tests spit out just don’t accurately reflect the experience that users will actually have. During our early testing for instance, the Nexus 4 consistently put some strangely anemic Quadrant scores — which its cousin the Optimus G handily blew past — despite working like a dream. All that said, benchmarks are largely are for the most part inescapable, and the Tegra 4 SoC does a rather nice job on them anyway. Quadrant is one of our go-to mobile benchmarking tools, and the Tegra 4 did not disappoint — it scored in the mid-16,000s, topping out at 16,591. To put that in a little perspective, Samsung/Google’s Nexus 10 (which itself is powered by a relatively new dual-core 1.7 GHz Samsung Exynos chipset) usually scores in the mid-to-high 4,000s. Asus’ Transformer Pad Infinity TF700 (powered by a 1.6GHz quad-core NVIDIA Tegra 3) fared about the same, if not a hair higher. The results were much the same when we looked at AnTuTu scores — while tablets like the Nexus 10 and Asus’ TF700 will yield scores in the mid-8000s to low-9000s, the Tegra 4 demo tablet consistently hit scores above 36,000." "One of NVIDIA’s most prominent competitors these days is Qualcomm, and NVIDIA Product Marketing director Matt Wuebbling was eager to chat about the performance differential when I let slip the Q word. When asked about how much NVIDIA knows about Qualcomm’s updated Snapdragon chipsets, he replied simply enough: “we know a lot.” By his count, the Tegra 4 is about two to three times faster than Qualcomm’s Snapdragon 600 (used in devices like the new HTC One). He went on to say that the top-tier Snapdragon 800 is about 25 to 35 percent faster than the 600, with the implication that the Tegra 4 still comes out on top. Though his response has based on Qualcomm’s published Snapdragon claims, I’d still advise you to take that comparison with a grain of salt. That’s nothing against Wuebbling, but these sorts of simple comparisons don’t always paint the most accurate picture. I couldn’t reach Qualcomm for response at time of writing, but I’ll update if/when they respond to these claims. __________________________________________________________________ "When asked about how much NVIDIA knows about Qualcomm’s updated Snapdragon chipsets, he replied simply enough: “we know a lot.” AnandC of QCOM we and TechCrunch as well as others are waiting. What say You? You would think that this sort of horsepower would suck a battery dry in jiffy, but that doesn’t appear to the be the case. Another Tegra 4 demo had a video running at full resolution on a small 1080p display, an exercise that never drew more 1 watt of electricity at the most. Power consumption typically fell within the 900-950 milliwatt range — devices like the Droid DNA for instance tend to draw around 1.2 watts for similar tasks." _________________________________________________________________</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361744445400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 17:20:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361747249780-18</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC 28nm Capaciy tight AGAIN!</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361732925251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 14:08:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exyhosed is dead partly because Samsung 28nm is not ready or mature! When it's immature - you have massive uield issues and also very typically power issues due to poor control of the Poly gates - it only takes a couple of gates that are off spec on a SOC to turn it into a heater - it may still work but it runs hot. That puts Apple in a tough spot too and probably having t0 turn on TSMC a lot earlier eacerbating the the 28nm capacity issue. There is no way apple can turn on 28nm at Samsung if they are still learning on that process - Apple volumes and horrendous chip size would make volume production impractical. TSMC claimed ~ 100% 28nm is TSMC ie everybody else is trying.</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361747249780</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 18:07:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361747972813-19</Id><Topic><Title>Why does the company consistently sells its stock each quarter( ~$433 Million in the last 3 years) ?</Title><Username>awangpro</Username><Timestamp>1361743872309</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 17:11:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe it's part of the employee stock option pool. It's one of the reason Gaap is lower since the company has to account for it as an earnings hit. The hit is relatively unpredictable as it's upto each employee to decide when to sell - it probably would spike up when the stock price moves up quite a bit.</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361747972813</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 18:19:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361748028714-20</Id><Topic><Title>Here's Tegra 4 Benchmarks - Mr. QCOM CMO AnandC Show Us Yours!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361741955792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:39:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In all fairness, The HTC One/Snapdragon 600 does have something going for it which Tegra 4 lacks at this point of time: --The S-699 is reportedly integrated with LTE --Q1 availability Tegra 4 will be available in Q2 (per ZTE announcement while Tegra 4i will be a quarter later (per Engadget).</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361748028714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 18:20:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361748632612-21</Id><Title>T4 benchmaark results = short QCOM</Title><Msg>QCOM will be on a slippery slope forward - dang I love down hill skiing.</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361748632612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 18:30:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361748821494-22</Id><Topic><Title>Here's Tegra 4 Benchmarks - Mr. QCOM CMO AnandC Show Us Yours!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361741955792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:39:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ibexx, Snapdragon 600 does not have an integrated modem. Snapdragon 800 does per Qualcomm website specs on both. Source: qualcommDOTcom/snapdragon/processors/800-600-400-200/specs Qualcomm Marketing tends to muddy the waters I'm afraid. That's why I go to the source...i.e. Qualcomm website.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361748821494</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 18:33:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361749592983-23</Id><Topic><Title>Here's Tegra 4 Benchmarks - Mr. QCOM CMO AnandC Show Us Yours!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361741955792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:39:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>J7777, I quoted from xbitlabs as follows: The decision to use Qualcomm Snapdragon 600 system-on-chip may be logical, as it will be the most powerful mobile application processor available in Q1 2013. However, it is obvious that Snapdragon 800 will not only feature 20% higher performance thanks to increased clock-speed, but will also have integrated baseband capabilities, something that allows smartphone makers to reduce manufacturing costs, shrink size of printed circuit boards inside smartphones and therefore increase physical space for battery."" If they got it wrong, then I stand corrected. I will take your word for it if your information comes from the horse's mouth (QC site). The Q1 availability is still a big factor. Not happy about it, but it remains a fact.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361749592983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 18:46:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361750066588-24</Id><Topic><Title>Here's Tegra 4 Benchmarks - Mr. QCOM CMO AnandC Show Us Yours!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361741955792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:39:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You typed S699 which I read as S600 and acknowledged that the S800 has integrated baseband. But so doe Tegra 4i and both should be available roughly at the same time...perhaps S800 beats it by one or two months. Andit looks like Tegra 4i should beat S800 slightly at 1/2 the die size. But I'm sure Qualcomm marketing will post up benchmarks shortly on S800 or at least allow journalists to observe the test. When their chip is out of the Fab that is!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361750066588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 18:54:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361750633955-25</Id><Topic><Title>Here's Tegra 4 Benchmarks - Mr. QCOM CMO AnandC Show Us Yours!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361741955792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:39:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya...the typo. S-600 for sure. The availability date of Tegra 4i was revealed in a recent article by Engadget (just out this afternoon), and supposedly they got it on the spot from NVIDIA....saying 9 to 12 months out. Haven't seen anything about release date on Tegra 4i directly from NV though. The S800 will be fabricated by a more sophisticated 28nm process (LPM) at TSMC; it's expected that ramp-up will be slower than S600.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361750633955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 19:03:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361750954816-26</Id><Topic><Title>Here's Tegra 4 Benchmarks - Mr. QCOM CMO AnandC Show Us Yours!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361741955792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:39:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the Engadget article that refers to Tegra 4i release date: engadgetDOTcom/2013/02/24/nvidia-tegra-4i-phoenix-reference-phone-hands-on-video/?utm_source=engadget&amp;utm_medium=twitter</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361750954816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 19:09:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361751050526-27</Id><Title>The problem is not wether tegra4 outperforms Snapdragon, its the heat</Title><Msg>and power consumption thats important for smartphones and 7" tablets. Nvidia should just shutdown this tegra nonsense. Its just raising false hopes.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361751050526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 19:10:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361751267815-28</Id><Topic><Title>Here's Tegra 4 Benchmarks - Mr. QCOM CMO AnandC Show Us Yours!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361741955792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:39:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They'll come up with a new test as they did in the past. And they'll crank the clock to 2.31GHz and claim Clock superiority like AMD - they came from the same mold when they got the AMD GPU</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361751267815</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 19:14:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361751519018-29</Id><Title>Tegra 4 Power Draw of .90 Watt 25% lower Than Competition</Title><Msg>"That sort of power will typically have a huge drain on battery life, but Nvidia reckons it's able to be surprisingly sparing with the juice. Indeed, I saw a phone running a high-definition video clip on a 1080p display that was generating around 900 milliwatts of power -- around 25 percent less than the typical smartphone." Source: reviewsDOTcnetDOTcom/8301-13970_7-57570939-78/nvidia-tegra-4-supercharges-smartphones-hands-on-video/</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361751519018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 19:18:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361751827312-30</Id><Topic><Title>The problem is not wether tegra4 outperforms Snapdragon, its the heat</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361751050526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 19:10:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was under the impression that the 4i is intended to be marketed to smartphones, while the Tegra 4 is for "superphones". Also judging from the articles the Tegra 4 seemed to be performing fine power wise, which I have noticed has been a recent focus from Nvidia on most of their products, especially the 4i. Qualcomm also is trying to focus on power, but rather than making their chips perform well and be power efficient, they are simply making your device charge faster, which to me seems to sidestep the problem.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1361751827312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 19:23:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361755815128-31</Id><Topic><Title>The problem is not wether tegra4 outperforms Snapdragon, its the heat</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361751050526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 19:10:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a total waste of time and responding to your stupid higness, even more so - Anyway for amusment - YOU ARE RIGHT Cleaning Snapdragon's Clock is absolutely not a problem and with less power requirement than the current N7 there is absolutely no problem at all. The problem is in your #$%$ Have it check while they check your head.</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361755815128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 20:30:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361756768814-32</Id><Title>Why Get Your Specs From The Tech Press When You Can Go To The Source!</Title><Msg>Source: nvidiaDOTcom/2013/02/tegra-4-performance-grabs-headlines/ _____________________________________________________________________ P.S. AnandT you need to update your GFlops to 97 from 75 to account for the increased GPU clock speed of 672 for Tegra 4 vs. 520 for Tegra 3. GPU White paper. Also check out the one on the HDR camera function pretty cool.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361756768814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 20:46:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361756900042-33</Id><Topic><Title>The problem is not wether tegra4 outperforms Snapdragon, its the heat</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361751050526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 19:10:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUFFOON !!!! OK, how much power does tegra4 draw ?? Or you have NO CLUE... NONE !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361756900042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 20:48:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361757459724-34</Id><Title>Engadget did its own benchmarking on T4 - "it breaks all sorts of speed records" (Video and text)</Title><Msg>Must read. Below is a table showing a different set of benchmark tests: .........................Tegra 4 ref tablet...... Sony Xperia Tablet S (Tegra 3)......ASUS Transformer Pad Infinity (Tegra 3) Quadrant .......16,436........................ 4,349................................................... 4,685 (V2) AnTuTu...........36,305......................11,301..................................................12,027 SunSpider ......... 499........................1,606.....................................................2,012 (lower is better) CF-Bench......41,325......................12,625.................................................... 7,874 Battery life: long story short: Tegra 4 will give you 2 additional hours compared with Tegra 3. ""...Quadrant scores in the 16,000s? CF-Bench results in the 40,000 range? All unheard of. Just look at those benchmark scores. Particularly stunning was that SunSpider result, which should give you a strong idea of what you can expect in terms of web browsing performance. In short, the tablet chewed through all that code in just 499ms (keep in mind that lower numbers are better in this particular test). To give you some perspective, the iPad 4 scores an average of 865ms in the test. So if you enjoy the web browsing experience on your iPad, you're going to be pretty pleased what NVIDIA has to offer here. Put differently, when we ran SunSpider on a laptop, the desktop version of Chrome achieved a score of 188.8ms -- we're used to seeing a much bigger gap between desktop and mobile browsers."" MUST READ engadgetDOTcom/2013/02/24/nvidia-tegra-4-benchmarked/ PS: Apparently NV set up a reference tablet running Tegra 4 just for the tech journalists/analysts to benchmark to their hearts desire - that is unheard of in terms of confidence. (Repeat: QC and Samsung wouldn't let anyone touch their newly announced chipsets in reference devises.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361757459724</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 20:57:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361762545805-35</Id><Title>Anandtech: Tegra 4 architecture deep dive &amp; etc</Title><Msg>General a very favorable review. However, note that Anand was air-brushing the outstanding performance of Tegra 4 in benchmarks - no reference gadgets from QC or Samsung were provided - while he spent great length in speculating on energy consumption of T4. Just remember this guy or his outfit is reportedly on the payroll of Qualcomm, and has been for years. anandtechDOTcom/show/6787/nvidia-tegra-4-architecture-deep-dive-plus-tegra-4i-phoenix-hands-on/6</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361762545805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 22:22:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361763554323-36</Id><Topic><Title>Anandtech: Tegra 4 architecture deep dive &amp; etc</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361762545805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 22:22:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should readL Generally a very favorable....</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361763554323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 22:39:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361763623305-37</Id><Topic><Title>Anandtech: Tegra 4 architecture deep dive &amp; etc</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361762545805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 22:22:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM’s Cortex A15 and Power Consumption "Tegra 4’s CPU complex sees a significant improvement over Tegra 3. Despite being an ARM architecture licensee, NVIDIA once again licensed a complete processor from ARM rather than designing its own core. I do fundamentally believe that NVIDIA will go the full custom route eventually (see: Project Denver), but that’s a goal that will take time to come to fruition. In the case of Tegra 4, NVIDIA chose to license ARM’s Cortex A15 - the only vanilla ARM core presently offered that can deliver higher performance than a Cortex A9. Samsung recently disclosed details about its Cortex A15 implementation compared to the Cortex A7, a similarly performing but more power efficient alternative to the A9. In its ISSCC paper on the topic Samsung noted that the Cortex A15 offered up to 3x the performance of the Cortex A7, at 4x the area and 6x the power consumption. It’s a tremendous performance advantage for sure, but it comes at a great cost to area and power consumption. The area side isn’t as important as NVIDIA has to eat that cost, but power consumption is a valid concern." {{{Samsung noted that the Cortex A15 offered up to 3x the performance of the Cortex A7, at 4x the area and 6x the power consumption}}}</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1361763623305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 22:40:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361764592891-38</Id><Title>3 Important Events Tomorrow Monday 2/25</Title><Msg>All Times EST 10:00 AM - ZTE MWC Press Conference 7:45 PM = Nvidia Presents Morgan Stanley Tech, Media, &amp; Telecom Conference Note: Morgan Stanley increased holdings by 7.4M shares to 11.5M sharesin Q4 Last day to buy to earn the dividend. Nvidia goes ex-dividend Tuesday 2/26</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361764592891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 22:56:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361764690025-39</Id><Topic><Title>Why Get Your Specs From The Tech Press When You Can Go To The Source!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361756768814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 20:46:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It depends. For specs and release dates, surely the original vendor will be the best source. However, for performance evaluation and benchmarks, third-party assessments may provide an equally good perspective, if not better, and possibility higher degree of objectivity. Just common sense. (Third parties do not include competition).</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361764690025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 22:58:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361764814945-40</Id><Topic><Title>Anandtech: Tegra 4 architecture deep dive &amp; etc</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361762545805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 22:22:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anand airbrush - agreed - way too much of that #$%$ coming from them. Considering Exynos 5 is in very deep trouble - the only way that sucker is going to fly is crank down the max operating GHz and use an older slower less gates GPU. That leaves S800 which is totally vaporware at this time and for all we know could have serious power issues - 2.3GHz Quad Core + LTE and no power saver core. When it comes to QCOM - Anand treats them with kids gloves #$%$ footing around their issues instead of raising or pointing them out.</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361764814945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 23:00:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361764948377-41</Id><Title>T4 benchmarked by "The Verge" (video)</Title><Msg>thevergeDOTcom/2013/2/24/4024946/nvidia-tegra-4-benchmark-tests</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1361764948377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 23:02:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361765586802-42</Id><Topic><Title>Anandtech: Tegra 4 architecture deep dive &amp; etc</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361762545805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 22:22:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the tegra 4 has 4 cortex a15 cores like the samsung exynos 5</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1361765586802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 23:13:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>