<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-15"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366000444903-1</Id><Title>NVIDIA demonstrated Tegra 5 Logan SoC running Batterfield 3 (a DX11 game!) - calls iPAD graphics vintage 1999</Title><Msg>At the Investor Day conference, NVIDIA’s CEO Jen-Hsun Huang, demonstrated their upcoming Tegra 5 Logan SOC running a section of DICE’s Battlefield 3. NVIDIA showcased a live demonstration of Battlefield 3 running on their next generation mobile SOC, Tegra 5 Logan. The mobile SOC was unveiled by NVIDIA during their GTC 2013 conference where the company revealed their updated Tegra roadmap highlighting their current Tegra 4/ Tegra 4i, Tegra 5 Logan and Tegra 6 Parker SOCs. NVIDIA’s Tegra 5 Logan SOC would be a generation ahead of the competition boasting a new Kepler GPU architecture with CUDA and OpenGL 4.3 support, It is planned for launch sometime in 2014. In 2015, NVIDIA would reveal their Tegra 6 Parker SOC which would feature their Denver CPU and Maxwell GPU architecture which would once again push the boundaries on the mobile front. The live demonstration of Battlefield 3 which featured HDR lighting, Rich geometery, dynamic lightning and improved particle effects goes off to show the amazing power NVIDIA’s next gen chips hold and running a high-end game title on a mobile device would be a worth while experience in itself. The Tegra 6 Logan chip was also compared against the Apple iPad running its own graphical benchmark powered by its Dual Core A6X and Quad core graphics chip however it can be clearly seen that the demo holds nothing against Battlefield 4. NVIDIA also called the iPad graphics “Vintage 1999″. wccftechDOTcom/nvidia-demonstrates-gen-tegra-5-logan-soc-running-battlefield-3-calls-ipad-graphics-vintage-1999/#ixzz2QVFNAQ1q</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366000444903</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 00:34:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366000732509-2</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA demonstrated Tegra 5 Logan SoC running Batterfield 3 (a DX11 game!) - calls iPAD graphics vintage 1999</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366000444903</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 00:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank gawd they are dumping tegra4 and talking up tegra5. Anyone know how much power tegra5 will consume? Could be used in desktops maybe.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366000732509</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 00:38:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366009038019-3</Id><Topic><Title>Has Jensen seen the light and is killing off tegra? With competition like Rockchip</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1365978776625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 18:32:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You were claiming $10 quad core chips a week or so ago. The $10 SoCs are single or dual core, and quite basic with mediocre performance. They are good for undemanding apps, OK for some web surfing, but are noticeably slow with many web sites and tend to have bad video playback. The quad core parts are all around $20-ish (estimate w/ large quantity). Mediatek and Allwinner parts are slower than Tegra, with inferior device driver support, and go for a few dollars less. My personal line for minimum performance is being able to play Netflix, Amazon prime, etc with no skipped frames or artifacts, while having long battery life. With a good video decoding engine, that can be done with a modest CPU. But many parts either don't have the software support, or just don't have the hardware performance to do this.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1366009038019</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 02:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366030642532-4</Id><Title>The Updatus User</Title><Msg>The executives of this company have one heck of a lot of gall to create a partially hidden user account on our computers with a driver update, not getting our permission to do so, and then putting a little blurb on their website that it we don't like it, we can deactivate their product. It's hard to believe that any company could be so tone-deaf on an issue of customer security and privacy.</Msg><Username>beto_la</Username><Timestamp>1366030642532</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 08:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366031357211-5</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA demonstrated Tegra 5 Logan SoC running Batterfield 3 (a DX11 game!) - calls iPAD graphics vintage 1999</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366000444903</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 00:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>does not matter - there is no viable high end app proc market. They can compare an proc one year out with one already in production for a year and running full retina, but it all does not matter. There is no viable high end app proc market. PERIOD.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1366031357211</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 09:09:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366031988369-6</Id><Topic><Title>Who is killing the PC? Blame the cloud,,</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365828292436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:44:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I blame the demise of AMD on the hardware side, and win8 on the sw side. With AMD out of the way, Moore's law benefits are not seen anymore by the consumers. I looked at upgrading my laptop the last few months, for the same price, I get the same processing power and the same screen. Moore's law is just used to fatten the profits of the manufacturers. Zero incentive to upgrade. If nvda gets complacent with AMD out of the way, nvda will see the same exact slowdown as intel. And when I go kick tires at cpt stores, I am met with this ridiculous win8 metro. If I just want to consume content, I can buy a Nexus 7. If I want to create content on a computer, I want to do real work. Time spent on learning a new interface is time totally wasted, unproductive. Win8 just doesn't hack it. If I really must buy a computer today, the first thing I would do is to uninstall win8 and install win7. It has always taken msft two major iterations to get a windows refresh right. 98/98SE. winXP/winXP SP2. Vista/Win7. Win8 will be no exception. Just wait for win9.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1366031988369</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 09:19:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366034248636-7</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA demonstrated Tegra 5 Logan SoC running Batterfield 3 (a DX11 game!) - calls iPAD graphics vintage 1999</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366000444903</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 00:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is your problem.. you are the most worthless troll... go do something</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1366034248636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 09:57:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366036160849-8</Id><Title>The Bears are losing their grip.</Title><Msg>Even with the macroeconomic news, today, the Bears are losing their grip on this stock. Unless the market truly tanks by 200-300+ points, I don't see the stock staying under 13 for long, and any bounce overall will likely see the stock UP on the day. IF we go green, I expect to see another run at 13.25 and then much higher over the remainder of the week. Nothing really matters until The Final Hour, anyway. As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. Max</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366036160849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366037631423-9</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA demonstrated Tegra 5 Logan SoC running Batterfield 3 (a DX11 game!) - calls iPAD graphics vintage 1999</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366000444903</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 00:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There is no viable high end app proc market. PERIOD" The same thing was said about 3D graphics 20 years ago. What you fail to grasp is the evolving and dynamic market. What is high end today is mainstream in 2-3 years. It's called differentiation and the rest of the SoC suppliers are going to have a difficult time keeping up.</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1366037631423</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366039101253-10</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA demonstrated Tegra 5 Logan SoC running Batterfield 3 (a DX11 game!) - calls iPAD graphics vintage 1999</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366000444903</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 00:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whosunw, you were right about "does not matter" in one sense - you would be bashing NVDA anyway as you were paid to do.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366039101253</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 11:18:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366039404097-11</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA demonstrated Tegra 5 Logan SoC running Batterfield 3 (a DX11 game!) - calls iPAD graphics vintage 1999</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366000444903</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 00:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JH Huang said that NV sacrificed a quarter for Tegra 5 in order to get ahead of competition MULTIPLE YEARS. BRCM, along with Qualcom, will be left in a dust in 2015/2016. PS4 and xBox will look like vintage pieces, performing below than the mobile Parker powered devices on the go.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366039404097</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 11:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366042433406-12</Id><Topic><Title>loss of nexus overblown</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1365908733890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 23:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>High end is, IMO, something that is changing. I think that NVDA is wise to anticipate it. Companies that aim a 12-month product cycle roadmap at the products of today are just as risky as companies that aim a 12-month product cycle roadmap at products that don't yet exist. IMO.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1366042433406</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366044284535-13</Id><Topic><Title>loss of nexus overblown</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1365908733890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 23:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not luck that we need as investors of Nvidia, just patience . . and it's already beginning to payoff. It's apparent your m.o. hasn't changed at all since the last time I read one of your posts over a year ago. Pretty sad actually. Jen made it clear at the analyst's meeting that the company has more than enough to keep the projected sales of Tegra intact through the end of the year. A one quarter delay isn't a whole year.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366044284535</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:44:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366045319324-14</Id><Topic><Title>The Bears are losing their grip.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366036160849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After a 5% rally, last week, THIS is ALL the Bears have???? Pathetic...especially given the market near the lows and off 167. Sure looks to these old eyes like we'll be back over 13 and up on the day, later. As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. M</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366045319324</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:01:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366048613715-15</Id><Title>Does anyone else have problems with Yahoo message boards?</Title><Msg>Especially today, now...</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366048613715</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366048981410-16</Id><Topic><Title>Does anyone else have problems with Yahoo message boards?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366048613715</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:56:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm okay with it since it's better then the previous version to me. However, that isn't saying much. I think they are always tinkering with these boards.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366048981410</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 14:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366053773187-17</Id><Topic><Title>The Bears are losing their grip.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366036160849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not to mention the fact that MMs/Options bigs always drive down the stock on Monday and Tuesay of options expiry week. Wednesday is a toss-up depending on macro and stock-specific news, and by Friday the trading is usually quiet as the OP players will have unwind their positions already. Intel earnings on tap tomorrow. Hopefully all bad news are in; the uncertainly (a big one!) is the succession planning after Otellini's retirement. Three Intel execs are reported to be on the short list (ref. New York Times article today): --The guy who oversees operations (fabs, manufacturing etc) --The guy who oversees graphics --The guy who oversees Intel software development None of the three looks like the best person Intel board can find. But then, this process may be dictated by Intel culture that they HAVE to pick someone from within. Otellini's problems partially stem from the fact that he has no engineering background, thus failing to see the upcoming see changes caused by mobiles and cloud computing. Somewhat reminiscent of the Apple situation. I think Intel will continue to make big piles of $$$, but the sizes of the piles will also continue to diminish until a new Intel emerges that can keep abreast with the fast-changing tech scene. We should be grateful for JH being the visionary leader guiding NVIDIA through the treacherous waters.....I know I am.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366053773187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 15:22:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366064713279-18</Id><Topic><Title>Has Jensen seen the light and is killing off tegra? With competition like Rockchip</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1365978776625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 18:32:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are going to have a hard time selling a tablet chip that can't do Netflix or Amazon Prime properly. You do see those for sale for $100 in some places as off-brands, but you are going to have some very disappointed buyers. Name brands like Dell, Asus, etc aren't going to anger their customers like that.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1366064713279</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 18:25:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366064735237-19</Id><Topic><Title>Does anyone else have problems with Yahoo message boards?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366048613715</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:56:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo message board is probably the worst web application in the universe. Terrible ergonomics, slow, a lot of silly errors, difficult to search in, annoy users (writing "assessment") while ignoring spammers ... Really, terrible application. Shame on yahoo!</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1366064735237</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 18:25:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366065273464-20</Id><Topic><Title>The Bears are losing their grip.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366036160849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"--The guy who oversees operations (fabs, manufacturing etc)" intel is about manufacturing prowess so who better to lead the company. Besides I heard a long time ago that he was an Outstanding Manufacturing Manager before he moved up.. Will see...... "We should be grateful for JH being the visionary leader guiding NVIDIA through the treacherous waters.....I know I am." Yes he has done a great job for the company and the employees. Admire that old fashion values thingee.....but as for the shareholders, it's still an open question on how great of a job he has done when looking at the share price over the last 2.5 years. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1366065273464</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 18:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366065905350-21</Id><Topic><Title>The Bears are losing their grip.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366036160849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I meant to add a remark that none of the 3 candidates would lead Intel into the next ear - they may have served the company well in the past - as EVEN Otellini said on more than one occasion that: Intel needs to change from GROUND UP, and from INSIDE OUT! Changing the vessel, but not the content, ain't gonna cut it.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366065905350</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 18:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366069265443-22</Id><Topic><Title>The Bears are losing their grip.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366036160849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And talking squat about other companies coming from such a knowledgeable investor as you puts Nvidia in a much more favorable light right......Oh I forgot you've been doing this routinely all the way from $9 to $26 and down from $26 to $12..... nothing ever changes......Have you written your options yet? LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1366069265443</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 19:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366069604548-23</Id><Topic><Title>The Bears are losing their grip.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366036160849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>J seven-packs, I will honor you with one last reply, then you can go hustling for $$$ for buy back you April 13 calls. Check the stock price of NVDA in February 2009 - that;s when I got in (a boat load of it at $7.5). Average cost still way under $10. You aren't the sharpest tool in the shed, but you sure hate well. Bye...you will be headed for oblivion where you belong.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366069604548</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 19:46:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366076910015-24</Id><Topic><Title>The Bears are losing their grip.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366036160849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure ibexx....Always the same. Sorry, I can't resist but I am pretty sure you are still underwater or very close....and you passed on a triple....my my. ....and such a sharp tool as you? Good luck and never deviate from pumping the stock before you write them calls. Novice guy like me can even make money at it. Good Luck</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1366076910015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:48:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366077442316-25</Id><Title>Lets face it folks, tegra is a goner. Flat sales in a fast growing market</Title><Msg>means no one wants it. Maybe tegra 5 could be a hit.. NOT!!</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366077442316</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>