<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-22"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358832403061-1</Id><Title>When do you think is the best time to buy the stock?</Title><Msg>After Earning? After Apple Earnings? After google Earning?</Msg><Username>asianroid</Username><Timestamp>1358832403061</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:26:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358833160730-2</Id><Topic><Title>Best -- Who Are You?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358751739224</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 02:02:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good one! :P</Msg><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1358833160730</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:39:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358834051467-3</Id><Topic><Title>When do you think is the best time to buy the stock?</Title><Username>asianroid</Username><Timestamp>1358832403061</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:26:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like to add shares in the $11.xx range. Good margin of safety there, IMO.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358834051467</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:54:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358836664216-4</Id><Topic><Title>Why the x86 vendors are missing big desktop PC opportunities in race for mobile. Part 1</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358825511153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 22:31:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'One of the biggest textbook mistakes IBM ever made was agreeing with Sun that the mainframe was dead - allegedly to be replaced by PCs and client server computing.' This assertion only exists in the mind of the author, IBM have a 45nm 5.2 GHz quad-core mainframe chip so they never stopped developing and supporting it. Sparc/Solaris has outlasted Sun as Ellison is still very keen on it so they never stopped believing in their enterprise server version either.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358836664216</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 01:37:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358837726770-5</Id><Topic><Title>When do you think is the best time to buy the stock?</Title><Username>asianroid</Username><Timestamp>1358832403061</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:26:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe wait until APPL, GOOG, and MSFT number so we can get a better guess of sales.</Msg><Username>spidey113</Username><Timestamp>1358837726770</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 01:55:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358839227987-6</Id><Title>Tom'sHardware: Hands on with NVIDIA Project Shield (very positive review and informative!)</Title><Msg>Our first stop at this year's CES was Nvidia's suite in the Palms, where company representatives showed off pre-production versions of its Shield handheld. Chris Angelini weighs in with some of the specifics, plus his impressions of Nvidia's effort. We were still in Southern California when Nvidia introduced its Project Shield. But that didn't stop Don and I from following the webcast and posting our initial thoughts online in CES 2013: Nvidia Announces Project Shield And Tegra 4. The next day, the Tom’s Hardware team landed in Las Vegas, ready for the show (more specifically, everyone else landed; I drove). My first stop was Nvidia, where I got to go hands-on with a pre-production version of the Shield. The company was emphatic that what you saw during Jen-Hsun’s introduction was an early version of the hardware; it isn’t expected to ship until the second quarter of this year, and will be among the first devices with Tegra 4 inside. Gaming On Android I’ll preface this with what I told Nvidia: I don’t spend a lot of time gaming on mobile devices. I think I might have a free version of Angry Birds installed on my iPhone, and it’d take something really compelling to make me want to buy a game on one of my Windows 8 or Android tablets. With that said, the build of Hawken the company had running on its Shield looked surprisingly detailed. I figured I could get pretty good at the game using the handheld’s joysticks. It’s a shame that the UDK-based title's free-to-play model is already being derided for goading you into buying upgrades with real-world currency just to stay competitive. We’ll have to see if Meteor’s model carries over from Windows into Android. Nvidia is quick to point out a few other upcoming titles with planned optimizations for Tegra 4: Blood Sword: Sword of Ruin, Real Boxing, and Dead Trigger 2. My only beef with the optimizations developers are making (first mentioned in Nvidia's Tegra 3 Optimizations: THD Android Games, Tested), is that they’re restricted under Android via device detection. But when you play a cross-platform title under iOS or Windows, that detection doesn’t always happen. In some games, you see the same effects on SoCs from Apple, Qualcomm, and Intel. Will the first wave of Tegra 4-optimized titles run smoothly on A6/A6X, Snapdragon S4, and Atom Z2760? Or will Tegra 4’s more powerful graphics subsystem enable games that can only be enjoyed at their highest settings on Nvidia’s Shield? More so now than on the prior generation of hardware, Shield stands to enjoy a notable advantage in Android-based games right out of the gate. The Wizard Behind The Curtain Much of what Shield can do beyond gaming natively in Android is owed to Nvidia’s other technologies. For example, the device is able to access your library of PC games through Valve’s Steam platform and present them neatly on-screen. Actually firing them up and playing them, however, requires a desktop PC with at least a GeForce GTX 650 or a notebook with a GeForce GTX 660M. Nvidia’s requirements also list a Core i5 or equivalent CPU (AMD processors included). Quick Sync does not play a role in this relationship. Rather, the GPU renders the game locally on the PC. Its fixed-function NVEnc logic turns the output into an H.264-encoded video, which is then sent to the Shield over a suitably-fast wireless network. The company says an 802.11a/g/n router should be enough. That makes sense—you shouldn’t ever need 54 Mb/s of throughput for a compressed video stream. But peak performance isn’t the issue. I’m more interested in how high of a data rate the network needs to sustain, at minimum, to achieve smooth playback. Dips in the wireless valley matter most. The Shield does its part with a dual-band 802.11n radio from Broadcom, two transmit antennas, and two receive antennas. If you’re able to match the handset up to a MIMO-equipped router, dual spacial streams should give you higher throughput at any given distance, improving the likelihood you’ll have a fluid experience. At launch, Nvidia says it will support streaming PC games from your PC to the Shield. You will be able to connect an HDMI cable to your TV and mirror the output there. In the future, the company hopes to stream directly from your PC to the TV, using Shield as a controller. What won’t happen, it sounds like, is a wireless link between the PC and Shield, and a wireless link between the Shield and TV, which would introduce too much latency.</Msg><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1358839227987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 02:20:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358843033961-7</Id><Topic><Title>Tom'sHardware: Hands on with NVIDIA Project Shield (very positive review and informative!)</Title><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1358839227987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 02:20:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very positive? I would say neutral.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1358843033961</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 03:23:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358860203305-8</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA may be ended. Find out why.</Title><Username>eddie.flosi</Username><Timestamp>1358856011343</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 07:00:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks man</Msg><Username>pagegeraldo</Username><Timestamp>1358860203305</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 08:10:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358861026219-9</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA may be ended. Find out why.</Title><Username>eddie.flosi</Username><Timestamp>1358856011343</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 07:00:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>report is number 1</Msg><Username>andrewhancock39</Username><Timestamp>1358861026219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 08:23:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358861269376-10</Id><Title>Hey, j7777kxx</Title><Msg>You said that my stock picks aren't good? Let's see. I wrote about both QLogic and Silicon Motion a little while ago. My articles got Pro designation on SA (you know, meaning they were the best of the best), and the stocks are up significantly from publication date. QLogic positively pre-announced a great quarter and Silicon Motion is now paying me a shiny new dividend. I love the dividend...don't you?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358861269376</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 08:27:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358863488283-11</Id><Topic><Title>Tom'sHardware: Hands on with NVIDIA Project Shield (very positive review and informative!)</Title><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1358839227987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 02:20:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tomshardwareDOTcom/reviews/nvidia-shield-tegra-4-gaming,3420.html</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358863488283</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:04:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358865500150-12</Id><Title>which opinion guarantees results?</Title><Msg>none,.......that's why there are so many opinions....no one is accountable...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1358865500150</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:38:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358867599295-13</Id><Title>what if there was a click strike? writers would starve</Title><Msg>and everything else would be the same</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1358867599295</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:13:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358869578738-14</Id><Topic><Title>Integrated Baseband v.s. Discrete?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358639330501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:48:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am sure you can find tons of information if you just google SDR LTE. I don't think there is much discrete opportunity for Nvidia other than Tegra 4 attached solution. I can't imagine A6, Exynos, QCOM etc. solution ever using an Icera solution regardless of how cheap and space efficient the solution is. Like most SDR solution, some host protocol will probably be required to run on ARM core on Tegra itself. Just looking at this objectively - Icera 410, 450 etc. have not found a slot in most Tegra 3 design. The only solution that I am aware of is Asus Vivotab that uses Icera 410. I would like to hear why Nexus 7 did not use Icera (I think they use Intel/Infineon).</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358869578738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:46:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358870200531-15</Id><Topic><Title>Chief Information Officer ...</Title><Username>altheamontijowxpltbru2872</Username><Timestamp>1302875615000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2011-04-15 09:53:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>valuable TA information</Msg><Username>rexlinjkbruce</Username><Timestamp>1358870200531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:56:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358870651313-16</Id><Title>someone new will gain control of this company soon</Title><Msg>to cheap and cash rich for nothing to happen....</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1358870651313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:04:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358871442243-17</Id><Title>huge corp buyback of shares between $12-12.25</Title><Msg>going to have a big impact on eps for Q</Msg><Username>netttrunner</Username><Timestamp>1358871442243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:17:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358871883321-18</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg just in: Apple investors brace for first profit drop since 2003 - a decade ago. Part 1</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358842653329</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 03:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it will be extremely interesting how aapl will attack the low priced market. brcm is doing booming Samsung business with low priced models through their integrated solutions, despite the fact that samsung has app processors and a big fab. If aapl follows with fully integrated solutions, guess analysts will start pushing Jen on when he will get more 'cheap' radios....</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358871883321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:24:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358872007814-19</Id><Topic><Title>huge corp buyback of shares between $12-12.25</Title><Username>netttrunner</Username><Timestamp>1358871442243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:17:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I personally don't think NVDA will do a buyback without a CFO. It would be nice for shareholders if NVDA had bought back 30-40 Mil shares this last qtr but I don't think the share buyback has even started yet.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358872007814</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:26:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358872835729-20</Id><Title>Down from Christmas time of $13.15,</Title><Msg>Worst performer in Nasdaq in the past one time. Most smaller techies up 5% during this time -- mu, mrvl, amat, flex... What justify this?</Msg><Username>coolheadwarmblood</Username><Timestamp>1358872835729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:40:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358876195158-21</Id><Title>google earnings will be huge for nvda tonight</Title><Msg>One word, "Nexus"</Msg><Username>netttrunner</Username><Timestamp>1358876195158</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:36:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358876958306-22</Id><Title>What AMD's Earnings Tonight Mean For Nvidia</Title><Msg>I'm sure we will see postings like this tonight. AMD's graphic Revenue is up....Nvidia is losing GPU market Share! or AMD's graphic Revenue is down....Nvidia is doomed because PC's are going away! JMHO....LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358876958306</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:49:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358878382654-23</Id><Topic><Title>What AMD's Earnings Tonight Mean For Nvidia</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358876958306</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:49:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>everytime...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358878382654</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:13:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358878730554-24</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft getting in on the DELL buyout - to spend $1 - 3 billion</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358875885651</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:31:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there goes the whole PC eco system.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358878730554</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:18:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358879674762-25</Id><Topic><Title>What AMD's Earnings Tonight Mean For Nvidia</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358876958306</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:49:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, it's silly. Nvidia is probably taking market share in GPUs.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358879674762</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:34:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358884431595-26</Id><Topic><Title>charlie_best_here</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358742546670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:29:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whaaaat??? More Nonsensical discussion of Jen's Tegra folly ramping? From getting-paid-for-posting-on-seekingalpha -- engineering student ashraf.eassa. Who now writes, "If you paid attention to past conference calls, like a best-of-the-best securities analyst, you would know that Tegra SoCs are actually higher margin than GPUs on average. This means that once Nvidia can ramp the Tegras to the right revenue level, it will be quite positive for the top AND bottom lines." Son, perhaps you haven't actually READ nvidia's 10Q's? You know, the Report Card on how much money Jen's Tegra/CPB folly is Losing. Here. I've updated it for the Estimated 2013 Tegra losses. Op. Losses ____ Revenues ____ Year Ending ($330,000,000) ___ who cares __ January 29, 2013 Estimate ($207,913,000) ___ $591,166 ___ January 29, 2012 ($153,351,000) ___ $197,613 ___ January 30, 2011 ($94,170,000) ____ $156,047 ___ January 31, 2010 ($52,367,000) ____ $136,334 ___ January 25, 2009 ($836,801,000) ___ Cummulative Tegra/CPB Operating Losses ($367,000,000) ___Plus: The amount of shareholder's cash pizzed-away buying Icera ($1,204,801,000) __ Approximate cummulative Losses on Jen's Tegra folly. Note that the Losses no doubt exceed One Point Two BILLION Dollars, since Nvidia only started to disclose their Tegra losses seperately in 2008. Prior to that they were just swept under the rug. Also note that the more tegra chips they sell, the more nvidia shareholders lose. And now ashraf.eassa posts about this and that potentially, someday, maybe, ramping? HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA! What a hopeless Dreamer that guy is. Seriously. As the nvidia 10Q's clearly show, the only thing Ramping, -- for five (5) straight years now -- are the Tegra Losses. ($1,204,801,000) That's equal to what -- $2 bucks per nvidia share. Gone forever.</Msg><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1358884431595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:53:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358884883400-27</Id><Title>NVDA Buyout</Title><Msg>Any chance of buyout by INTC or Some other Company??? Need serious answer please</Msg><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358884883400</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:01:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358885782299-28</Id><Topic><Title>The Tegra, it is like elephant</Title><Username>naziba.adongo</Username><Timestamp>1349843708263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Best! I now understand why Texas Instruments got out of that awful ARM chip business. NOBODY wants to own an cash-sucking Elephant.</Msg><Username>thanks.best</Username><Timestamp>1358885782299</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:16:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358886176762-29</Id><Topic><Title>charlie_best_here</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358742546670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:29:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's due to increased R&amp;D You know, to fund future growth See, that's why companies exist To take shareholder cash and invest it into initiatives that pay off Do they all succeed out of the gate? No. Sometimes they take time Jen's Tegra has POSITIVE gross margins That means, no, he's not shipping $ with each one sold</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358886176762</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:22:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358886779270-30</Id><Title>Sellers lined up</Title><Msg>its futile to trade NVDA at this point - it can only be hurt by AMD and TXN report I don't think Google will reveal Nexus numbers Semi's have largely not been participating in rallies - maybe trade NVDA after Jan 24th</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358886779270</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:32:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358888500377-31</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Buyout</Title><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358884883400</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:01:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Nvidia doesn't do something with it's cash and cash flow someone will be able to buy the company for nothing...LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358888500377</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:01:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358890423102-32</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG revenue misses, EPS beats, shares rise 4%</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358889417046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:16:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's not how it's being reported, seems more positive than what you post here to me.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1358890423102</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:33:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358892115313-33</Id><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Msg>AMD GPU sales down ~15% Y/Y due to lower unit volumes. Guess who got those units... Can't be AMD's own integrated graphics since, well, that division was down too.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>30</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358892385742-34</Id><Title>Did the DOW close at 52 week high? Anyone with a brain knows the market is over bought!</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/q;_ylt=Av0UBEb.j.3llKnbbv0nqz2iuYdG;_ylu=X3oDMTIyNjl2cnV1BG1pdANGaW5hbmNlIEZQIE1hcmtldCBTdW1tYXJ5IDIEcG9zAzMEc2VjA01lZGlhUXVvdGVzTWFya2V0U3VtbWFyeQ--;_ylg=X3oDMTFpNzk0NjhtBGludGwDdXMEbGFuZwNlbi11cwRwc3RhaWQDBHBzdGNhdANob21lBHB0A3NlY3Rpb25z;_ylv=3?s=^dji</Msg><Username>bucue976</Username><Timestamp>1358892385742</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:06:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358892670295-35</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think we'll see a rally tomorrow for NVDA based on the promising Google numbers and the numbers you referenced above? I always suspected NVDA's earnings would surprise alot of people, but this confirms it.</Msg><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1358892670295</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:11:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358892857330-36</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Buyout</Title><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358884883400</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:01:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what do you mean nothing? please explain. Thanks</Msg><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358892857330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:14:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358892920115-37</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Buyout</Title><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358884883400</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:01:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for your serious thoughts.</Msg><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358892920115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:15:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358893741572-38</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Buyout</Title><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358884883400</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:01:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With cash on the books plus the present rate of cash accumulation Nvidia will have $12/ share cash in 14 quarters. Therefore an acquirer could buy Nvidia for nothing! Hello Carl Icahn....LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358893741572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:29:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358894388089-39</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Earnings don't mean much. Outlook is more important. Just look at NVIDIA's last earnings, outlook and share price reaction.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1358894388089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:39:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358896437541-40</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ibexx88 Considering how dismal the GPU #'s out of AMD were, they're probably not double counting.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358896437541</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:13:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358896517525-41</Id><Topic><Title>AMD hires two key mobile engineers - ex-Apple and ex-Qualcomm</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358888343411</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:59:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If two guys were all it required to run a multi-billion dollar GPU and SoC business, I'd be filthy rich.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358896517525</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:15:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358897618876-42</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD's integrated graphic chipsets moved to the computing solution division over 21/2 years ago. Today their graphics division includes consumer discrete GPUs, Pro-graphic GPU's like Nvidia's Quadro maybe $25M, and their HPC cards like Nvidia's Tesla cards maybe $10M, and their console graphic revenue which is probably around $30Mand rising if rumors are true. In fact I would doubt if AMD's consumer discrete GPU sales is much more than $250M a quarter and approaching the point of no return for continued R&amp;D investment. What was remarkable was their operating income in the graphics division went up from $18M to $22M. Rory did say he wasn't go to try and buy market share anymore. This has been good news because Nvidia doesn't have to try and compete on price like they use to a couple of years ago. Notice the GTX 680 is still selling for the same price as it was launched at 3 quarters ago. They can certainly depend on Intel to crush the price on low end X86 processors and reducing AMD's ability to fund R&amp;D. It's going to be pretty hard for AMD to fund the next leap on GPUs to 20nm. So Nvidia will just continue to accumulate cash to fund who ever makes a run at them for a buyout. Not kidding. I don't think Nvidia has a clue about what to do to avoid this. LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358897618876</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:33:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358898016732-43</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Buyout</Title><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358884883400</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:01:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Need serious answer" NO !!!!! "please" your welcome</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358898016732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:40:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358899785698-44</Id><Title>Any Nexus numbers from Google analyst call?</Title><Msg>Did Google discuss any Nexus device numbers on its call?</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358899785698</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 19:09:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358900001412-45</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction - AMD might sell $2-3M in HPC cards. and one further thought. With Intel's $300M payment before the end of the month and around $200M in Q4 cash flow, Nvidia will have accumulated $6.30 a share in Cash even while paying out $45M in dividends. That's 52% of the share price in Cash. That is unheard of with a company growing revenue and earnings. Note: Intel has 3 more yearly payments of $200M each left to go and I don't think at the end of the agreement they will pull integrated graphics out of their X86 processors do you? I feel that the only thing that can prevent someone from making a run at the company is a REAL SERIOUS SCIENCE PROJECT WITH MUCHO SPENDING INVOLVED. Perhaps that is what Project Shield is meant to be? But alas...Nvidia just may have a winner on it's hand and the cash will just keep rolling in... Carl, Carl Icahn, where are you? Look at IBM - They have paid out 103% of free cash flow in dividends and stock buybacks and the stock price in 4 years and the stock price has risen 2.5 times.Now that's what I call shareholder friendly. LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358900001412</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 19:13:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358902867884-46</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Earnings don't mean much." LOL That's about the richest post I've seen in a long while.</Msg><Username>hendar00</Username><Timestamp>1358902867884</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:01:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358903231091-47</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"who ever makes a run at them for a buyout." No one has stepped up to even hint and an interest in acquisition. This is after years of low stock price and certainly more vulnerability in the past than exists now. Who is going to step up and why? Or are you just wishful thinking?</Msg><Username>hendar00</Username><Timestamp>1358903231091</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:07:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358903442105-48</Id><Title>Potential Takeover Targets: Morgan Stanley Report</Title><Msg>Just search the headline: Potential Takeover Targets: Morgan Stanley Report Here are some of the stocks with higher probabilities of receiving tender offers in 2013 than their peers: Nabors Industries(Energy) Atwood Oceanics(Energy) Walter Energy(Materials) Air Lease Corp. (Industrials) Brinker International (Consumer Discretionary) Fresh Market (Consumer Staples) Gilead Sciences(Healthcare) Express Scripts Holding (Healthcare) Biogen Idec (Healthcare) Celgene Corp.(Healthcare) Intuitive Surgical (Healthcare) SVB Financial Group (Financials) Equity One (Financials) First Solar (Information Technology) Brocade Communications Systems (Information Technology) NII Holdings (Telecommunication Services)</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1358903442105</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:10:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358903560570-49</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh really? Try INTC this year. Mark the post for an easy future reference.</Msg><Username>dd888i8</Username><Timestamp>1358903560570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:12:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358904676205-50</Id><Title>If AMD's discrete GPU sales were down, so will Nvidia's. Ivy Bridge graphics</Title><Msg>is just now, reaching mainstream. And Haswell is being teed up. This company will start reporting losses like AMD in a couple of Quarters.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358904676205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:31:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358905194209-51</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some wishful thinking sure...but WS M/A is coming back on line. At $12 a share with $6:30 a share in cash after 4Q cash flow and Intel royalty. Plus another $1 a share from the 3 remaining years of the Intel royalty agreement, plus annual cash flow cash accretion of $1 to $1.50 a share...at what point does a buyer appear? Think of it this way..... Cash Jan 2013 - $6.30 a share Cash Jan 2014 - $7.50 a share Cash Jan 2015 - $8.75 a share Cash Jan 2016 - $10.25 a share Share price $12 to $13. At what point does a deal look attractive to you? I mean after all the Board of Directors is almost completely Private Equity investor firms. Check it out. The dividend which was shock to me...I never would have thought Nvidia would pay a dividend. Did You? Perhaps the Board suggested it....What might they be worried about? P.S. I never would have thought of Dell going private but it looks like it is going to happen. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358905194209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:39:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358905488383-52</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this POS going higher! Even #$%$ stocks have move up! But this POS is crappier than all and has not moved much.</Msg><Username>wholemole</Username><Timestamp>1358905488383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:44:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358906163335-53</Id><Topic><Title>AMD hires two key mobile engineers - ex-Apple and ex-Qualcomm</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358888343411</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:59:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If two guys were all it required to run a multi-billion dollar ... business " Jobs &amp; Wozniak... Hewlett &amp; Packard... on &amp; on....</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358906163335</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:56:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358906320796-54</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Patience. If you believe in the long term story, who cares? Accumulate on dips, and stick to your thesis. Unless you see evidence that your thesis isn't playing out, you should be grateful that you can add at these low levels. If you're just trying to trade, then why bother talking about the company? Go trade the SOXL/SOXS for some volatile trades.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358906320796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:58:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358907243197-55</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Long term story? I believe the company is worth around $15 to $16. I just see a quick way for management to get it to that price. If dumb ole me sees it that way...then certainly one or two WS wizards see the same thing. Maybe..... 1) Buyback shares starting with say 25 million and top out at 100 million in a year. 2) Juice the dividend Or.....suffer the consequences and have your company bought up. P.S. - True story...I once worked for a semiconductor company where the founder tried to fight off a hostile takeover. It was not a good experience. People didn't know how to act...the Board was divided and long standing relationships were thrown up in the air. When the stock popped I left for greener pastures with the cash from my vested stock options. P.P.S---Ashraf ---I hope you didn't drop out of college to write full time for S/A.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358907243197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:14:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358909269433-56</Id><Title>My my my. The 4Q results are Quite Ugly, boys.</Title><Msg>So many many 4Q reports today, boys. A multitudinous, myriad, mess of 4Q reports. And ALL quite Ugly. Ugly ugly ugly. Let's take a look at the multitudinous, myriad, mess of Ugly reports, shall we? Texas Instruments. ► 4Q profit Plummeted (-11%) ► TI wisely shifts away from the profitless mobile smartphone and tablet market. ► Operating Profit from embedded processor business Skyrockets +33% ► Too bad Jen didn't go into that. ► Outlook: The weak demand environment to continue. Advanced Micro Devices. ► Loss widens due to soft demand. ► 4Q profit Plummeted (-27%) ► Lost ($296 million) more than last year -- but probably less than Jen's Tegra did. ► Revenue Plummets (-32%) ► Rory Read acknowledged the Uncertainty surrounding PC demand. ► Outlook for revenue: MINUS (-9%), +/- 3% ► Took reserve for planned 1Q work force reduction. ► Asks if anybody knows where the heck their 100,000 secret documents went. IBM. ► Three (3) straight quarters of Declining revenues. ► 4Q Revenue falls (-0.6%) ► But earnings are Up +6.3%, due to astute management decision to sell Software. ► Rather than trying to sell beige goods, which are oh so out of fashion. ► To bad Jen didn't buy a software company -- rather than Icera. ► TurboTax® would have been a nice alternative acquisition. Timely. ► Write it once. Sell it for $49.99 to 200 million taxpayers. Whistle to Bank. ► Nice. Google. ► 4Q profit Up +6.7% ► Due to more folks clicking on Google's $5 buck ad words. ► Their mobile device folly was a disaster. ► Yes boys, a Disaster. ► Google's Motorola sink-hole Lost ($353 million) -- just in the 4Q alone. ► Motorola invited 1,183 associates to, well, dis-associate last year. Or be axed. ► No secret documents were stolen and given to nvidia. So far. ► Too bad Jen didn't go into selling $5 search words -- rather than buying Icera. Looks like yet another sleepless night for the nvda bagholders, right boys?</Msg><Username>bestogram</Username><Timestamp>1358909269433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:47:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>27</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358909762345-57</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>j7777kxx Why would I drop out of college to write for SA full time?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358909762345</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:56:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358909809750-58</Id><Topic><Title>My my my. The 4Q results are Quite Ugly, boys.</Title><Username>bestogram</Username><Timestamp>1358909269433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:47:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe try hot coco for that bad mister insomnia? Or perhaps a bedtime lullaby? Here's one -- Perfect for nvda bagholders. Katy Perry : Lyrics for "Wide Awake" Let's sing it together, shall we? I'm wide awake I'm wide awake I'm wide awake Yeah, I was in the dark {about nvidia} It was falling hard With an open heart I'm wide awake How did I read the stars so wrong? I'm wide awake And now it's clear to me That everything you see Ain't always what it seems I'm wide awake Yeah, I was dreaming and so long [Pre-Chorus] I wish I knew then {before I bought} What I know now Wouldn't dive in Wouldn't buy down GRAVITY HURTS They made it sound so sweet 'Til I woke up on On the concrete [Chorus] Falling from Cloud 9 Crashing from the high I'm letting go today Yeah, I'm falling from Cloud 9 I'm wide awake Yeah, I am born again Out of the lion's den I don't have to pretend And it's too late The story's over now, the End [Pre-Chorus] I wish I knew then {before I bought} What I know now Wouldn't dive in Wouldn't buy down GRAVITY HURTS They made it sound so sweet 'Til I woke up on On the concrete [Chorus] Falling from Cloud 9 It's crashing from the high I'm letting go today I'm falling from Cloud 9 I'm wide awake Thunder rumbling Jen's castle crumbling I'm wide awake I am trying to hold on I'm wide awake God knows that I tried Seeing the bright side I'm wide awake But I'm not blind anymore... I'm wide awake I'm wide awake [Chorus] Yeah, I'm falling from Cloud 9 It's crashing from the high You know I'm letting go today I'm falling from Cloud 9 I'm wide awake I'm wide awake I'm wide awake I'm wide awake I'm wide awake A True Classic, right boys? It sure is.</Msg><Username>sing_along_with_best</Username><Timestamp>1358909809750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:56:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>18</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358909868400-59</Id><Topic><Title>My my my. The 4Q results are Quite Ugly, boys.</Title><Username>bestogram</Username><Timestamp>1358909269433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:47:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bravo bravo... great post.. much good it will do.. time well spent... most productive.. applaud your dedication given your importance and status... its time to double your efforts.. you are almost there..</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1358909868400</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:57:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358910052966-60</Id><Topic><Title>If AMD's discrete GPU sales were down, so will Nvidia's. Ivy Bridge graphics</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358904676205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:31:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia took market share from AMD. Did you not listen to AMD's own call?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358910052966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:00:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358910508978-61</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"j7777k.Why would I drop out of college to write full time for S/A?" Ashraf Because If I'm not mistaken your profile on S/A when you started writing said you were attending the University Of Vermont and majoring in Math and Finance. I see it has changed now to full time investor. Hope it is because you graduated? You never know what might happen. No offense meant.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358910508978</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:08:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358910925604-62</Id><Topic><Title>My my my. The 4Q results are Quite Ugly, boys.</Title><Username>bestogram</Username><Timestamp>1358909269433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:47:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow! Gud song, Best!</Msg><Username>gud_song_best</Username><Timestamp>1358910925604</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:15:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358911073852-63</Id><Topic><Title>If AMD's discrete GPU sales were down, so will Nvidia's. Ivy Bridge graphics</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358904676205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:31:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>market share means very little, when the pie of discrete graphics is getting smaller.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358911073852</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:17:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358911823158-64</Id><Topic><Title>If AMD's discrete GPU sales were down, so will Nvidia's. Ivy Bridge graphics</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358904676205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:31:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not sure you can actually come to that conclusion from the AMD numbers. I would, in fact, bet against you there.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358911823158</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:30:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358912163334-65</Id><Topic><Title>If AMD's discrete GPU sales were down, so will Nvidia's. Ivy Bridge graphics</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358904676205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:31:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"market share means very little, when the pie of discrete graphics is getting smaller." Is It? Intel Core Ivy bridge sales were up. Atom and AMU sales were down. Nvidia doesn't sell into these markets. Now let's look back over the last 5 quarters AMD Graphics Division Revenue (Includes gaming consoles, Pro graphics and HPC Graphics) 3Q 2011 - 403M 3Q 2012 - 342M 4Q 2012 - 326M Nvidia's Consumer GPU Division (DOES NOT include Intel Royalty, Quadro, or Tesla) 3Q 2011 - 556M 3Q 2012 - 670M 4Q 2012 - ? Total market has actually grown 5%...Those silly Gamers.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358912163334</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:36:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358912184780-66</Id><Topic><Title>If AMD's discrete GPU sales were down, so will Nvidia's. Ivy Bridge graphics</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358904676205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:31:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bet all you want..</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358912184780</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:36:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358912659632-67</Id><Topic><Title>If AMD's discrete GPU sales were down, so will Nvidia's. Ivy Bridge graphics</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358904676205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:31:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a simpleton.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358912659632</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:44:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358913351409-68</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia gained GPU market share</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358892115313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well earnings do have an impact but he is correct in saying future outlook is often more important as the market is forward looking.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358913351409</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:55:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358914709709-69</Id><Topic><Title>If AMD's discrete GPU sales were down, so will Nvidia's. Ivy Bridge graphics</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358904676205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:31:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am. I own plenty of Nvidia.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358914709709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 23:18:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358916960039-70</Id><Title>I Just Read AMD's Transcript And I Really Don't Know What Rory Is Talking About</Title><Msg>The only clear statement was..."We are Not discussing that" embeded solutions being 20% of the business by Q4 2013 and tablets being 50% in 3 years and something about SeaMicro being the rest. I heard that...wow..that's a transformation if there ever was one. Doubt they will ever go to 20nm for that. TI and Microchip run their embeded processors at 32nm to.130nm. From the financials I did get this. Cash decreased 273M to $1.2B. Yes debt exceeds that, but they are comfortable with $1.1B in cash and their minimum is $700M. What happens then....they go to debtor in possession financing? Other than normal cashless cash flow in q1 they have $175M payment to Global foundries for wafers they aren't taking and $31M in severance costs for employees, but they will stay above $1.1B in cash...Non-Math majors I guess. Oh and revenue is dropping 9% but they are certain that gross margin and operating income will be just as good as Q4. "Next Question please" Looks like the race is on for cash preservation. Shucks I was hoping for dividend and a stock buyback. P.S. read the transcript...They sound like Texas Oilmen talking up their next wildcat well. Oh and they did say that they lost more share in graphics...but they are bundling popular games with their graphic cards so Q4 was the bottom. LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358916960039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 23:56:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>