<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-06"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373084989104-1</Id><Title>JUST IN: Partnership (with NVIDIA) to increase UK computer performance</Title><Msg>SOURCE: labmate-online, July 6 The Science and Technology Facilities Council (STFC) signed an agreement last month with NVIDIA, a world leader in visual and high-performance computing, to develop GPU-based supercomputers that aim to be a thousand times more powerful than any in the UK today. These powerful computers will provide a step-change for researchers and industry in areas such as climate modelling, stress analysis, materials modelling, molecular modelling, and numerical weather simulation. The agreement follows a £37.5m investment in March last year by the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills (BIS) in High Performance Computing at Daresbury Laboratory as part of its UK e-infrastructure initiative. David Corney, Acting Director of STFC’s Department of Scientific Computing, said: “This agreement combines NVIDIA’s leading-edge GPU accelerator technologies and HPC expertise with STFC’s software development expertise. This unique combination will enable the development of next-generation massively parallel applications which will be used for exascale performance levels, or a thousand times more powerful than Blue Joule at STFC, the most powerful computer in the UK today.” Minister for Universities and Science David Willetts said: "The Government is investing in high performance computing to make the UK the location of choice for high tech research and innovation. This partnership will bring together leading researchers and business. It confirms the position of Daresbury and Rutherford Appleton Laboratory as world-class science facilities. It supports our forthcoming Information Economy Industrial Strategy." - See more at the website as shown above. _____ This is a very big deal!</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373084989104</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 00:29:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373110707457-2</Id><Title>If T4 is available right now for Shield, then why is it not available for Nexus?</Title><Msg>If T4 is available right now for Shield, then why is it not available for Nexus especially since they are still selling the T3 version, and not giving any indications of clearing out T3 versions? Could Google have changed their mind regarding Qaulcomm, or could the delay of the Shield be due to T4 being delayed?</Msg><Username>nvdarules</Username><Timestamp>1373110707457</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 07:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373122675953-3</Id><Title>Ouya Dropping Fast, Ouya is now #63 on Amazon's Best Seller List July 6, 2013</Title><Msg>Where's the fella that was pumping Ouya on Amazon's Best Seller List bragging about a #17 spot? Did he leave the country again looking for Ouya on a Best Seller List in Peru or Mongolia this time? Let me see him pump that #63 spot right here. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373122675953</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 10:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373123850632-4</Id><Topic><Title>Add-in board partners plan to launch tablets - even smartphones in selected markets</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373050641229</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 14:57:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>last year with Kia in full swing, Asus in full swing, nothing happened. If this is not a nvda planted story, I'll eat my hat.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1373123850632</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 11:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373123942507-5</Id><Title>Pre-Orders for Xbox One is #5, PS4 is #15 on Amazon's Best Seller List</Title><Msg>Updated July 6, 2013 Both PS4 and Xbox One cost hundreds more than Ouya and neither is available now yet both Pre-Orders are out selling Ouya, which is now #63 on Amazon's Best Seller List. Why is that Nvidia fans? Anyone here have a clue? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373123942507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 11:19:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373124043940-6</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 11 leaked - rumored to be powered by Tegra 4, release date October 2013</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373003023768</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 01:43:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'iactively advertising blah blah blah" all fud. Now for some real hard facts: Q2 '12 Tegra sales $240M. last Q, clinging to live and trying to hold at $100M. sources for both: Jen. that's all you need to know for telling what google is doing with the Nexus 7.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1373124043940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 11:20:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373124334783-7</Id><Title>"Add in board partners plan to launch tablets" FULL TEXT</Title><Msg>"Add in board partners plan to launch tablets" "Even phones in select markets" " It is becoming increasingly obvious that the discrete graphics market is shrinking and companies who traditionally made their living from graphics cards sales have to rethink their future. Many of them went after power supply units, chassis or similar PC related products and in select markets some of them tried to peddle tablets. Our sources admitted that this is a tough market to compete in, but there is some confidence that Nvidia might support some of them in an effort to push more affordable Tegra 4 tablets to the market. Some big names in the graphics already have plans to roll out phones in China, with expansion to the Russia and Eastern European markets at a later date, as they know manufacturing and can believe they can offer a good price. For example, Nvidia currently sells more notebook GPUs than desktop parts and the big hype about Tegra is simply the result of market trends, as the market goes mobile. AMD partners have got a nice boost of sales thanks to Never Settle Reloaded promotions, but the hope of a real next generation Radeon later this year should really help their cause." source: fudzilla</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373124334783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 11:25:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373124585055-8</Id><Topic><Title>"Add in board partners plan to launch tablets" FULL TEXT</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373124334783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 11:25:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't see a need to CUT the parts out about "discrete graphics market is shrinking" or "AMD partners have got a nice boost of sales thanks to Never Settle Reloaded promotions, but the hope of a real next generation Radeon later this year should really help their cause." But you know who did, right? lmao IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373124585055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 11:29:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373124821816-9</Id><Topic><Title>Add-in board partners plan to launch tablets - even smartphones in selected markets</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373050641229</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 14:57:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cut-n-paste boy chopped off the beginning and end of this article because it didn't help him pump Nvidia's cause. lol I put up the FULL TEXT , no spin, no game playing, no BS. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373124821816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 11:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373132441764-10</Id><Title>Xiaomi Mi3 Emerges in Benchmark with Tegra 4 CPU, 1080p Screen</Title><Msg>Google title</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1373132441764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 13:40:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373151672918-11</Id><Topic><Title>Xiaomi Mi3 Emerges in Benchmark with Tegra 4 CPU, 1080p Screen</Title><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1373132441764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 13:40:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The xIaomi Mi3 is a very important win, thanks for posting it. Over the last six months, there have periodic web chatters that hinted the existence of this phone in development, but nothing concrete. Now it seems that real numbers and images have begun its pre-launch leaks as the release date draws near. Based on what I have read, there are likely 2 versions of the Xiaomi Mi3 phones: one powered by Tegra 4 and the other by QC's Snapdragon S800. All indications are that the two have been in development simultaneously and we can probably expect comparable release dates in Q3. Specifically, Tegra 4 powered Xiaomi Mi3 is destined for China Mobile's TD-SCDMA network with more than 60 million subscribers as of 2012, whereas the S800 powered version would go to China Unicom which operates a CDMA/WCDMA network based on Qualcomm's technology. Based on 2012 figures, the wireless subscriber ratio of China Mobile vs China Unicom is approximately 3:2, thus the tegra 4 Xiaomi Mi3 is going to the larger network(s). Lastly, Xiaomi phones may not be the most widely held handsets in China, but definitely the popular brand by any yardstick. The previous two Xiaomi phones are all based on Qualcomm app SoCs, so you can safely say that NVIDIA is beginning to encroach into Qualcomm's turf.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373151672918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 19:01:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373168021443-12</Id><Title>Brit server maker Avantek puts its back into ARM servers</Title><Msg>no wonder nvda/PD gave up on ARM server, Calxeda's chips come with on board interconnect and nvda can't match that. So Jen/PD is now going to do 'HPC'!!! Good luck with that too, Atoms will be coming with qlgc's IB interconnects. No wonder getanid gave it all up instead of 'just wait for PD, that is nvda's future'.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1373168021443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 23:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>