<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-11"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373516469340-1</Id><Title>Chips: Street sees in-line Q2, uncertainties beyond that (4 analysts quoted)</Title><Msg>SOURCE: Barrons just in BlueFin Research Partners: "We’re now two quarters into a mild semiconductor recovery after a sharp inventory correction in 2012. Demand improved in the June quarter, but we did not see the order surge and foundry expedites that occurred last year, as customers and suppliers are behaving more rationally this year. Many believed that the recovery was gaining steam during the quarter, pointing to the recently released Semiconductor Industry Association (SIA) data that showed May revenues spiking above the trend-line on a year-over-year basis. However, much of this reported growth was due to rising NAND and DRAM pricing associated with tight capacity. In fact, we believe growth is decelerating in the industrial and automotive markets, as inventory replenishment almost certainly contributed to the strong growth in the front half of the year." Oppenheimer: ""We see in-line earnings as an unlikely positive stock catalyst and believe the group could trade lower. Group fundamentals continue to improve at a checked pace, with still lean channel/customer inventories and more rational growth expectations reducing the risk of another 2H head-fake. PC, our long-standing least-favorite vertical, has continued to underwhelm as secular decline accelerates. Even in a “back-half-loaded” year, we model 2013 PC units down 10%. Recent years have proven a departure from “normal” seasonality, and absent any go-to consumer products, we expect a more evenly split 1H:2H year for semis as a whole. (To be continued)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373516469340</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 00:21:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373516638348-2</Id><Topic><Title>Chips: Street sees in-line Q2, uncertainties beyond that (4 analysts quoted)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373516469340</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 00:21:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Part 2: Nomura: ""We expect gross margin to improve from 58.0% in Q2 to 61.5% in Q3 and 63.0% in Q4. One of the biggest drivers is the reversal of inventory reserves […] Between 4Q12 and 2Q13E, we estimate that Intel will record inventory reserves of 300bps (Figures 1 and 2). Those charges should largely reverse over the next two periods. In other words, Intel should benefit from the sale of previously written-off inventory to the tune of 150bps per quarter. In addition, Intel should recoup 450bps in startup costs over 2H13."" Wells Fargo: ""Taiwanese foundry composite (TSMC + UMC) revenues increased 4% month- over-month in June (in USD terms), following an increase of 3% in May. On a year-over-year basis sales were up 22% in June, following an increase of 13% in May. Within the composite, UMC’s sales increased 3% month to month while TSMC’s sales increased 4% (in USD terms). Based on the combined monthly sales for the June quarter, we calculate that TSMC’s June quarter sales were NT$155.9 billion, toward the top of TSMC’s original guidance range for sales of NT$154-156 billion. UMC’s sales grew 15% sequentially, above UMC’s original guidance for sequential growth of about 13%. We take this to be an indication that fabless chip companies as a group continued to see improving demand for their products through the June quarter, building our confidence that upcoming June quarter reports from many chip companies will reflect revenues that are in line with or above the midpoint of original guidance […] Guidance midpoints imply 5% sequential growth expectation in June for Broadcom, 2% for AMD, 3% for Xilinx, 2% for Altera and 2% for Nvidia in its July quarter (Nvidia expects 7% sequential growth for its GPU segment). Qualcomm however expects its chipset unit shipments will be flat to down 6% sequentially in the June quarter.""</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373516638348</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 00:23:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373517072373-3</Id><Topic><Title>Chips: Street sees in-line Q2, uncertainties beyond that (4 analysts quoted)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373516469340</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 00:21:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is interesting to note that, under Wells Fargo's estimates, Qualcomm is the only chip company (others include AMD, BRCM, NVIDIA etc) that will show a flat-to-down June quarter. Not really news to this board, but glad that WS pundits agree. SA blogger can spin it anyway he wants...</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373517072373</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 00:31:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373522338406-4</Id><Title>Xolo Play with Tegra 3 is now up for pre-order</Title><Msg>SOURCE: India Times, July 11 Xolo Play is up for pre-order online on the official Xolo site. The most interesting aspect of the phone is the processor. As mentioned above, Xolo Play will feature a Tegra 3 processor. The phone is not a quad-core phone but a 5-core phone! Yes, that’s right. The official specifications list that the phone will come with a quad-core 1.2 GHz processor with a special “5th battery saver processor”. There’s nothing else mentioned so we are awaiting the launch to see what Xolo has managed. Considering the phone is a gaming special phone, the need to save battery is evident and looks like Xolo has equipped the phone with a special processor just to save battery. Our best guess is while the quad-core version will be used for heavy gaming, Xolo Play will relegate the mundane tasks like checking mails and messages, calls, etc to the single “battery saving” processor.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373522338406</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 01:58:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373548543686-5</Id><Topic><Title>Today's report: Q2 PC shipments declined by 11%, AMD will be hardest hit, INTC has deep pockets</Title><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1373498059172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 19:14:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jen is dead sea level and right before the seawall. You seriously think you can banish all negative realities on a msg board regardless how many times you post, how many handles you use, how foul mouthed you get, how many sissy fits you throw, how many other successful mobile companies you bad mouth all day long?? pathetic!! "How do yo model the non-gamer laptop GPU sales?" Boy, X'mas Q/Haswell ramped, it is going to be such a shock to top and bottom line!</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1373548543686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 09:15:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373551924206-6</Id><Topic><Title>LUONGO IS VERY VERY BEARISH ON NVDA</Title><Username>dtwskier</Username><Timestamp>1373504787550</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 21:06:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, go ahead and follow Luongo. He's very objective and well thought of beyond his AMD Fanbois circle of fame . . . BAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!! If you really are serious about investments in semis, you need help . . serious help. Of all the SA writers, this guy is one of the biggest jokes out there.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1373551924206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 10:12:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373551947261-7</Id><Topic><Title>XC 31xx employer please take note</Title><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1373497697226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 19:08:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Click the messages tab to see his posts and report them. Takes just a few minutes. It is spam and will be obvious to anyone that reviews his activity.</Msg><Username>flstf_97</Username><Timestamp>1373551947261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 10:12:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373555205258-8</Id><Topic><Title>Today's report: Q2 PC shipments declined by 11%, AMD will be hardest hit, INTC has deep pockets</Title><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1373498059172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 19:14:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I don't think that high-end PCs are being replaced with $200 tablets. The high-end PCs are the ones with the high margins that keep INTC nicely paid. The low end PCs, with low margins, are where AMD and INTC compete. Those are also the ones that people are replacing with decent tablets.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1373555205258</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 11:06:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373556929062-9</Id><Title>Anyone got a better idea how to play this 'stale" stock?</Title><Msg>A smart investment to profit from Nvidia, albeit one that caps an investors potential upside, would be to sell LEAPS put options. Investors could sell the January 2015 $15 put options and collect a premium of $2.80 per each option sold. If Nvidia shares close above $15 roughly 18 months from now, investors would earn a return of 18.6% prior to taxes and commissions. This is the equivalent of more than a 12% annual return. Conversely, shares could fall as low as $12.20 before investors would see any losses on this trade. With the stock currently trading at ~$14.40, this is the equivalent of a 15% decline from its current levels before this trade would lose any money.</Msg><Username>alaormooch</Username><Timestamp>1373556929062</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 11:35:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373557129347-10</Id><Topic><Title>Sero 7 Pro = Nexus 7 + microSD + 5MP rear camera for $150</Title><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373440859651</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 03:20:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google the Sero 7 Pro review or stop by Walmart have a check youself. Latest review from TabletPcReview 7/9/13 is very good: Source: TabletPC Review Pros Low price Very good screen Expandable memory Dual cameras Good battery life Video-out port Stock version of Android Cons No-name manufacturer Quick Take: An impressive combination of hardware and price point for those who don't mind giving up the security of well-known brands. -------------------------------------------------------- That is the beauty of open platform Android. Once the software and key hardware parts are the same, the rest is build quality.</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373557129347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 11:38:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373558887874-11</Id><Title>Nvda is going nowhere, but</Title><Msg>Trayvon’s Mother Tells Jury ‘He’s In Heaven’</Msg><Username>gutyourbacside</Username><Timestamp>1373558887874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 12:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373559379103-12</Id><Title>Markets soar, yet Nvda folding like an old Mexican fish TACO.</Title><Msg>Tastes like chicken. Going nowhere fast.</Msg><Username>mobammonk</Username><Timestamp>1373559379103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 12:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373560689455-13</Id><Title>QCOM, Intel, AMD and Apple are All Flying Today while Nvidia adds 6 cents!</Title><Msg>Now say it ain't so. Nvidia went from $26 to $14 and you're PROUD of it too, right Nvidia fans? lol HUG that losuy Nvidia you deserve each other. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373560689455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 12:38:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373561211214-14</Id><Title>What did that LYING Nvidia say about LOW MARGIN Game Consoles?</Title><Msg>Where is the 64 Bit 8 Core CPU+GPU SoC that Nvidia had to sell Microsoft and Sony but at the last minute decided NOT to? When did Nvidia REALIZE that they don't have a 64 Bit SoC to sell anyone? Was it when Sony and Microsoft showed Nvidia and that 32 bit Tegra junk the door? Or was it when Nvidia sent a talking head out to the press to start bashing PS4 and Xbox One? Nvidia is a LYING POS. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373561211214</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 12:46:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373561601559-15</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia HEADCASE bashes Every Company that Sells a Chip other than Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373494909753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 18:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they sell a chip your Nvidia board perma pumper HEADCASE has bashed the company while hiding on the Nvidia message board. Well today as his favorite bash targets Intel, AMD, Apple and Qualcomm are FLYING that HEADCASE put a sock in it, didn't he? lol As with most HEADCASES he is CLUELESS. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373561601559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 12:53:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373562417472-16</Id><Title>CLUELESS HEADCASE Bashed AMD and MISSED OUT on 85% YTD Gains</Title><Msg>Now say it ain't so Nvidia fans When has that HEADCASE who bashes EVERY company that sells a chip NOT been CLUELESS? lol AMD UP Over 11% Today. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373562417472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 13:06:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373563968853-17</Id><Title>"Advanced Micro Devices up after analyst upgrades"</Title><Msg>"Advanced Micro Devices up after analyst upgrades" "Advanced Micro Devices gains after analysts up ratings, price targets on Sony, Microsoft deals" "NEW YORK (AP) -- Advanced Micro Devices' stock rose Thursday after several analyst boosted the chipmaker's ratings and price targets, thanks to its deals to supply processor chips for Sony's PlayStation 4 and Microsoft's Xbox One. THE SPARK: Vivek Arya of Bank of America Merrill Lynch lifted Advanced Micro Devices Inc. to "Buy" from "Underperform" and increased its price target to $6 from $2.50. Separately, Canaccord Genuity's Bobby Burleseon upped his rating to "Buy" from "Hold," and hikes his price target to $5 from $3. THE BACKGROUND: Both Sony and Microsoft provided details about their respective new gaming consoles during the E3 video game conference in Los Angeles in June. Microsoft's Xbox One will retail for $499 and looks to serve as an all-in-one device that lets users watch television, play movies, listen to music and browse the Internet as well as play video games. Sony's PlayStation 4 will cost $399, with the company saying that it would basically be a "supercharged PC" much like the Xbox. The use of PC chips means the PS4 won't be able to play games made for any of the three previous PlayStations. Players will have to stream older games over the Internet. Both consoles are set to be released before the holiday shopping season. THE ANALYSIS: Bank of America's Arya said in a note to clients that the agreements with Sony Corp. and Microsoft Corp. could turn AMD "into a profitable, diversified company with a multi-year recurring revenue stream." Arya believes that pent-up demand for new consoles from Sony and Microsoft should help to offset any possible competition from casual gaming done by consumers on their smartphones and tablets. The analyst estimates that AMD may start to reap the financial benefits of the deals as soon as the third quarter. ..." spurce: AP</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373563968853</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 13:32:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373565597320-18</Id><Title>11% for AMD vs 0.8% for Nvidia. 85M AMD Shares vs 3M Nvidia Shares</Title><Msg>Now you tell me which sompany is on FIRE today and which one is a POS everyday. Do you need an iPad to work it out Nvidia fans? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373565597320</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 13:59:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373565941309-19</Id><Topic><Title>Markets soar, yet Nvda folding like an old Mexican fish TACO.</Title><Username>mobammonk</Username><Timestamp>1373559379103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 12:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As of this moment, NVDA is up EXACTLY the same percentage as the Dow.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1373565941309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 14:05:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373566030950-20</Id><Topic><Title>Markets soar, yet Nvda folding like an old Mexican fish TACO.</Title><Username>mobammonk</Username><Timestamp>1373559379103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 12:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At this moment Nvidia is a POS. Did you know that the semi YOU bash are doing better than the DOW? lol IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373566030950</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 14:07:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373566311279-21</Id><Topic><Title>Sero 7 Pro = Nexus 7 + microSD + 5MP rear camera for $150</Title><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373440859651</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 03:20:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Generally positive news for NVDA, but the price is not particularly surprising for its dated specs. It looks like a good entry-level option, but competition with updated hardware is coming soon that I imagine will only retail for about $50 more. It seems like Tegra 3 creeping down-market might be more of a risk for MediaTek that a real win for NVDA. IMHO.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1373566311279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 14:11:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373566538744-22</Id><Title>Nvidia is the Semi POS Today as that other Semi you bash SOARS</Title><Msg>And no amount of BS you Nvidia fans post will make Nvidia's 0.8% add up to AMD's 11%. No amount of BS. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373566538744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 14:15:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373566757997-23</Id><Topic><Title>Every other sentence that HEADCASE post is a noun, a verb and Tegra.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373563523766</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 13:25:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra is a MONEY LOSING POS. And Nvidia won't be able to HIDE the Tegra FIASCO after the Next Nexus 7 is announced. We know a BROKEN SHIELD won't make up for losing the Next Nexus 7, don't we? lol IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373566757997</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 14:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373566929919-24</Id><Topic><Title>What did that LYING Nvidia say about LOW MARGIN Game Consoles?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373561211214</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 12:46:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some smart people on Wall Street think Nvidia was FULL OF IT with that low margin BS as AMD Soars. Now isn't that right? IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373566929919</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 14:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373567195932-25</Id><Topic><Title>11% for AMD vs 0.8% for Nvidia. 85M AMD Shares vs 3M Nvidia Shares</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373565597320</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 13:59:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"11% for AMD vs 0.8% for Nvidia." Can you READ? Today we may need to add, Can you COUNT? How much more market love is 88M shares than 3M shares? Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373567195932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 14:26:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373567752360-26</Id><Title>Cowardly HEADCASE will Bash AMD on Down Days and Hide on UP Days</Title><Msg>The same Nvidia fans who couldn't shut up if AMD drops 5 cents have NOTHING to say about AMD's 11% SURGE or AMD's 85% YTD Gains. Stay in HIDING under that rock as you ponder your own CLUELESS nonsense Nvidia fans IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373567752360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 14:35:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373567971392-27</Id><Title>"Advanced Micro Devices Upgraded to Buy at Canaccord Genuity (AMD)"</Title><Msg>"Advanced Micro Devices Upgraded to Buy at Canaccord Genuity (AMD) " ... "The analysts wrote, “We are upgrading shares of AMD to BUY from Hold ahead of what we expect to be strong performance versus PC-centric names as the company ramps its embedded business and begins to transition away from a near-exclusive reliance on PC demand. Specifically, we believe the embedded opportunity could drive momentum in Q3 as game consoles where AMD supplies custom silicon begin their production ramp ahead of the holiday shopping season. We are increasing our estimates and raising our price target to $5 from $3.”" source: watchlistnews</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373567971392</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 14:39:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373568345280-28</Id><Topic><Title>"Advanced Micro Devices up after analyst upgrades"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373563968853</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 13:32:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where are those CLUELESS AMD bashers Today? Under the same rock hiding or what? lol IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373568345280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 14:45:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373569421806-29</Id><Title>Nexus 7 2 with S4 Pro heading to trouble</Title><Msg>Device companies build 7" tablets with Tegra 4i could easily beat Nexus 7 2 in both performance and cost. Don't get it why GOOG choose the old Snapdragon S4 Pro for their new N7 2!</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373569421806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:03:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373569487283-30</Id><Title>AMD Leading All Issues on the NYSE with over 93M Shared Traded</Title><Msg>AMD UP over 10% and appears to be on track for a 100M Share Day. Now say it ain't so Nvidai fans. Tell us the MARKET isn't BUYING AMD UP Today. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373569487283</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:04:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373569849513-31</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 2 with S4 Pro heading to trouble</Title><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373569421806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Tegra 4i could easily beat " Tegra 4i is NOT FOR SALE Today is it? Google can't build the Next NExus 7 with pictures of Tegra 4i they need a working SoC that is for sale TODAY. Pump that Tegra 4i BS to someone who can't read a calendar. Tegra 4i is DUE NEXT YEAR unless Nvidia pulls a last minute SHIELD almost launch again? IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373569849513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:10:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373570358986-32</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 2 with S4 Pro heading to trouble</Title><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373569421806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One could speculate endlessly, but I have to think that price may have been a factor. QCOM makes a lot of money from a lot of products and can probably afford to buy the spot. NVDA's product plan probably needs to make a little cash from tablets. If GOOG uses an S4 Pro, the cost scenario would be increasingly likely. Remember that the Nexus 7 is a device that defines the low end of spectrum of solid, credible devices. It isn't about being the best or the fastest. It is about being good yet cost-effective.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1373570358986</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:19:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373570894652-33</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 2 with S4 Pro heading to trouble</Title><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373569421806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"One could speculate endlessly," Can you read a calendar? No Specualtion about it. Tegra 4i IS NOT FOR SALE Today. Qualcomm WON because Qualcomm at least showed up for work with a REAL SoC to sell. Nvidia has nothing new to offer. Nvidai can't even get their own Tegra 4 product to market. Is SHIELD fixed yet? IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373570894652</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373571808724-34</Id><Title>Nvidia CAN'T SHIP its own Tegra 4 Product so Forget the Next Nexus 7</Title><Msg>Nvidia can't get out its own Tegra 4 Product out on time. Is that BROKEN SHIELD Fixed yet? Google went with Qualcomm because Qualcomm showed up ready for work with more than just pictures of a SoC. Qualcomm is IN the Next Nexus 7 and Nvidia is OUT And Project Late Tegra is a MONEY LOSING FIASCO that Google was wise to distance itself from. The Next Nexus 7 will be a better product with Qualcomm, HD Screen and No Tegra. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373571808724</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:43:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373571884262-35</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 2 with S4 Pro heading to trouble</Title><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373569421806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google never intended for the Nexus 7 line to have top-tier hardware. The success of N7 was designed and attributed to good performance/ affordability / minimum features / attractive industrial design - all of which were fulfilled by the combo of NV T3, ASUS engineering and Google oversight. The Nexus 7 2 will undoubtedly be more expensive at $229, with less gaming capability and no access to NVIDIA Tegra optimized games and TegraZone. For this alone, it next gen N7's fate is rather uncertain.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373571884262</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:44:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373571958384-36</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 2 with S4 Pro heading to trouble</Title><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373569421806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Next Nexus 7 is a Google Product with a Qualcomm SoC and does not concern Nvidia. eom IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373571958384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:45:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373572212529-37</Id><Title>Microsoft reorganized as announced today</Title><Msg>--Ballmer stays at the top, but organization was altered to blow up the walls between divisions --Purpose of blowing up the silos is to facilitate/speed up product development and to the market --In the past, Ballmer's Microsoft saw too often "self destructions" by feudal lords at Redmond --Analysts still scream: "Where is the strategy?" My personal opinion is that Ballmer has outlived its usefulness - did he ever fulfill this role in the first place?</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373572212529</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:50:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373572461483-38</Id><Title>AMD UP Over 11.5% as Voulme Blows Past 100 Million Shares!</Title><Msg>Over 100 Millions Shares traded with AMD Up 11.5% is SPECTACULAR. AMD is having a day to remember. Congratulations to all AMD Shareholders. And to the AMD nay sayers, blow it out your tail pipe. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373572461483</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:54:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373572621827-39</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft reorganized as announced today</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373572212529</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What was that CLUELESS BS you said about AMD and a $3 hole? Care to repeat your CLUELESS BS today? IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373572621827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:57:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373572794310-40</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia HEADCASE bashes Every Company that Sells a Chip other than Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373494909753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 18:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at the board HEADCASE bashing Microsoft now. But you won't see that HEADCASE bashing AMD today, not with AMD UP Over 11.5%. lmao HEADCASE will wait for AMD to give back a nickel before trying that BS again. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373572794310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:59:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373573566271-41</Id><Title>AMD Leads the NYSE with a DOUBLE TRIPLE? UP 11.8% and 102M Shares</Title><Msg>The DOUBLE TRIPLE that every company on planet earth wants. DOUBLE Digit Share Gains on Heavy TRIPLE Digit Volume. Is there an MVP for stocks? lmao IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373573566271</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 16:12:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373573926858-42</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft reorganized as announced today</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373572212529</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your post about SENSORSHIP and ATTACKING a poster YOU CLAIM TO HAVE ON IGNORE is SPAM so be sure to report yourself. My post are about Nvida and its competition and YOU KNOW IT. If you can READ that is, IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373573926858</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 16:18:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373574514228-43</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia HEADCASE bashes Every Company that Sells a Chip other than Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373494909753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 18:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Asking other posters to attack a poster is ABUSE. A poster you claim to have on IGNOIRE or was that another LIE? IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373574514228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 16:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373574747201-44</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia HEADCASE bashes Every Company that Sells a Chip other than Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373494909753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 18:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>19/20 of the posts on the front of this board are from you, before this post. Yeah.. Ibexx is the headcase..</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1373574747201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 16:32:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373575460844-45</Id><Title>If you can Bash AMD here then its only fair to taut AMD's Success here.</Title><Msg>What's the matter Nvidia fans? Do you think that you can Bash AMD on the Nvidia message board when ever you want BUT NO ONE should mention anything that PROVES you were wrong? Is AMD's 11.8% GAIN today posing a problem for you AMD Bashers and your case for DOOM and GLOOM? Good, it should because just like that Nvidia talking head who bashed Xbox One and PS4 to the press the market made anyone bashing AMD and game consoles look CLUELESS today. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373575460844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 16:44:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373575732315-46</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia HEADCASE bashes Every Company that Sells a Chip other than Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373494909753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 18:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Yeah.. Ibexx is the headcase.." I NEVER CALLED ANYONE A HEADCASE. But you just did. Why did you single out that poster as a headcase when I when I deliberately refused to mention any poster by name? IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373575732315</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 16:48:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373577911480-47</Id><Topic><Title>AMD kicked back to its $3 hole</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372787813677</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 13:56:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"AMD kicked back to its $3 hole" Did you Nvidia fans have a problem with that post? Did you Nvidia fans speak up to say that bashing AMD on the Nvidia board will only encourage AMD supportters to defend AMD on the Nvidia board? This is the Nvidia message board right NOT the Love Nvidia message board or the Bash every other company that sells a chip and NO ONE gets to say otherwise board right? Well Today I get to say otherwise. AMD added 11.8% today on very heavy volume with over 102 Million shares traded. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373577911480</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 17:25:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373578126046-48</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia HEADCASE bashes Every Company that Sells a Chip other than Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373494909753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 18:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did you single out that poster to call a headcase? Do you have a resaon for naming him? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373578126046</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 17:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373578995965-49</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia HEADCASE bashes Every Company that Sells a Chip other than Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373494909753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 18:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>20/20 now</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1373578995965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 17:43:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373579168966-50</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia HEADCASE bashes Every Company that Sells a Chip other than Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373494909753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 18:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you trying to bury your own words? Why did you single out that poster to call a headcase? Why did you do that?</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373579168966</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 17:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373579216242-51</Id><Title>ACER introduces "multimedia monster" desktops (5 SKUs, Haswell + GTX660)</Title><Msg>SOURCE: Toms Hardware ""Acer America launched on Wednesday a new series of desktops promising power, performance and superb audio for games, movies and more. They're "multimedia monsters", packed with options like Sound Blaster Cinema, EAX, fourth-generation Intel Core "Haswell" processors, Nvidia GeForce GTX 660 graphics, two open PCIe slots and two bays for additional hardware and drives, and more, depending on the model. This is the new Predator AG3-605 Series from Acer, and is available now starting at $999.99 USD.""</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373579216242</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 17:46:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373579729501-52</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia HEADCASE bashes Every Company that Sells a Chip other than Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373494909753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 18:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really like digging yourself out of holes huh? 19/20, thank Ibexx.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1373579729501</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 17:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373580642192-53</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Leads the NYSE with a DOUBLE TRIPLE? UP 11.8% and 102M Shares</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373573566271</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 16:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazing how NOT ONE AMD BASHER had anything to say about AMD today WHILE AMD was trading? lol As if the whole trading day went by and NO ONE NOTICED AMD was up a bit on the Nvidia message board? Beautifully Amazing wasn't it? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373580642192</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 18:10:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373586539143-54</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 2 with S4 Pro heading to trouble</Title><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373569421806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The first Nexus 7 started off a little on the high side, price-wise, so I wouldn't worry about the price holding it back overall. Remember the elimination of the 8GB and the re-pricing of the 16 GB, only a few months after sales started? I would also not guess that too many potential buyers are concerned about TegraZone. What would be a bigger issues is that all of the Nexus 7 buyers still have their Nexus 7s, and it isn't clear what compelling features the Nexus 7 2 will offer to convince them that they need a replacement at the one year point. I have a 7 myself, and I have no plans to replace it. The Nexus 7 and the Kindle Fire HD hit a certain point of price and ability that had not been touched previously. The next generation offers only incremental improvements, and is not compelling to current owners. That is the trick about low and mid-range tablets. A newish tablet has all the power it needs to surf the web, watch Netflix, read ebooks, etc, but it isn't (currently) even close to being able to replace a laptop, a desktop, or a console. So, Nexus 7 2 versus 7 looks nice for some, but it is nothing that current owners need. This may not be true in another generation. Of course, that may not be NVDA's problem, since they do not appear to have been invited.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1373586539143</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 19:48:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373588179328-55</Id><Topic><Title>AMD kicked back to its $3 hole</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372787813677</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 13:56:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"AMD kicked back to its $3 hole Where it rightly belongs. Stock dropped 3% when earnings cc approaches.....a good reality check." Really, where did AMD close today just one week before that earnings report? Want a laugh? Read this thead carefully and pay attention to all the know-it-all AMD bashers as they pat each other on the back for knowing exactly what AMD's stock would not do. Then read the Barons's article titled: "AMD Offers Potential for Huge Gains" That article and an 11.8% gain today on heavy volume with an 85% YTD showing should have you rolling on the floor laughing at a bunch of CLUELESS AMD bashers . lol IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373588179328</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 20:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373588453720-56</Id><Title>Barrons's: "AMD Offers Potential for Huge Gains"</Title><Msg>"AMD Offers Potential for Huge Gains " "Advanced Micro Devices' new game-console chip contracts could prove to be a game changer for investors. The potential from this business, amid a weak personal computer market, is the basis of why Bank of America Merrill Lynch upgraded shares Wednesday to Buy from Underperform. Canaccord Genuity also upgraded the stock, to Buy from Hold. Advanced Micro Devices (ticker: AMD) shares jumped 10%, or 46 cents, to $4.45 in midday trading Thursday. While AMD is known as one of the largest global suppliers of PC microprocessors and graphics microprocessors, its exclusive wins in processor chips for next-generation Sony PlayStation 4 and Microsoft Xbox One game consoles could be "transformative." BofA Merrill, which thinks AMD could stop bleeding money by year end, more than doubled its price target to $6 from $2.50. With seven years of pent-up demand for next-generation game consoles, the upside from Sony's (SNE) and Microsoft's (MSFT) custom processor contracts should improve "operating margins, free cash flow [and] interest coverage, and strengthen the balance sheet, helping offset continued market share losses and weakness in PCs and servers to Intel," writes analyst Vivek Arya at BofA Merrill. Game consoles can have long life cycles, as game players upgrade and add features. While many other analysts seem unmoved by the game business, Canaccord's Bobby Burleson thinks AMD will benefit as "the company ramps its embedded business and begins to transition away from a near-exclusive reliance on PC demand." ..." source: barron's</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373588453720</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 20:20:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373590638914-57</Id><Title>New Analysis Casts Doubt On Intel's Smartphone Performance vs. ARM</Title><Msg>SOURCE: Thursday, July 11, 2013 A few weeks ago, the analyst company ABI Research published a report claiming that Intel's new CloverTrail+ platform (dual-core Medfield) for smartphones was significantly faster and more power efficient than anything ARM's various partners were shipping. If you follow the smartphone market, that was a very surprising claim. Medfield was a decent midrange platform when it launched in 2012, but Intel made it clear that it's goal for Medfield was to compete with other platforms in its division -- not seize the performance crown outright. The dual-core / quad-thread CloverTrail+ has improved on Medfield's performance, but it's still based on 2008-era microprocessor technology. Qualcomm, Samsung, and Apple, meanwhile, have not stood still. Last year, Cortex-A9 phones were still at the top of the market; now there are multiple devices using A15-class parts. Claiming that the Intel chip is head-and-shoulders above everything else was extremely odd. Further investigation by other analysts has blown serious holes in the ABI Research report. Not only does it focus on a single, highly questionable benchmark (AnTuTu), the x86 version of that benchmark is running different code than the ARM flavors. Furthermore, the recently released Version 3.3 of the test is much faster on Intel hardware than on any of the other platforms. This sort of cherry-picking and suspicious optimization makes ABI Research look foolish and raises questions about whether or not Intel has returned to its old tricks. As analyst Jim McGregor writes, "The only clear conclusions that should be drawn are that the leading ARM-based processors still have a performance lead over the latest Intel processor." **Unexpected Consequences: SoCs Make Benchmarking More Difficult** (To be continued)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373590638914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 20:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373590766159-58</Id><Topic><Title>New Analysis Casts Doubt On Intel's Smartphone Performance vs. ARM</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373590638914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 20:57:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Part 2: (SOURCE: Hot Hardware) One thing we want to highlight, however, is that benchmarking really has gotten more difficult in this brave new era of SoC products. Smartphones and tablets are essentially closed systems. Even laptops are more flexible -- a strict apples-to-apples comparison between notebooks could use identical external displays and the same RAM between multiple systems. There are also only two CPU vendors; an Intel quad-core is an Intel quad-core, regardless of whether it's in a Dell or an HP system. SoCs are different. Every phone has a different chip and every chip is configured slightly differently, with various I/O blocks, offload processors, screen technologies, manufacturing nodes, and leakage characteristics. It's further complicated by the fact that mobile usage models are still evolving, as are the underlying technologies and capabilities of the devices themselves. But even with those caveats in place, the ABI Research report is bad science. Single-source performance comparisons almost inevitably are. Even an extremely comprehensive suite of tests like SiSoft Sandra is a starting point for evaluating performance, not a single end-game metric. The ABI Research team undoubtedly knew that -- which raises questions about their objectivity and intent when writing the report. In the interest of full disclosure, ARM expressed dissatisfaction with the ABI Report when we met with them in late June and the author of the EETimes article, Jim McGregor, was also at that meeting. In this case, however, the problems with the ABI Research report are self-evident. ARM's own benchmark data comparing the Cortex-A15/A9 to Atom has to be taken with a substantial grain of salt but that doesn't change the fact that ABI is single-sourcing their conclusions from a version of a benchmark that boosts x86 performance far more than ARM. Clover Trail+ is a good chip. We expect Bay Trail, when it launches late this year, to be a far better mobile solution...</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373590766159</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 20:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373590770455-59</Id><Topic><Title>Barrons's: "AMD Offers Potential for Huge Gains"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373588453720</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 20:20:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wall Street analyst did not buy Nvidia's LIES about Game Consoles even though Nvidia's nonsense went over big on the Nvidia message board. Nvidia lost out on BILLIONS of DOLLARS in Game Console business because Nvidia does not have what Sony or Microsoft want, a real 64 Bit APU SoC. Nvidia does not have a 64 Bit 8 Core CPU+GPU SoC to offer anyone. So all Nvidia could do was LIE about not wanting BILLIONS of DOLLARS in new business after being rejected even though they have no competing product to offer. Then after telling that LIE Nvidia cites the PS3 GPU licensing deal as precedent for their poorly recieved GPU IP scheme. But the low point was when Nvidia management sent an Nvidia talking head out to bad mouth PS4 and Xbox One. Keep in mind that both Microsoft and Sony are currently Nvidia CUSTOMERS. Still wondering why some don't like Nvidia? Nvidia management proved that they are a bunch of LIARS. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373590770455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 20:59:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373591564018-60</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia HEADCASE bashes Every Company that Sells a Chip other than Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373494909753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 18:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Someone acting like a HEADCASE" already started bashing another Nvidia customer. He is bashing Google now with NONSENSE about the Next Nexus 7. lol Google hasn't even launched the Next Nexus 7 and "Someone acting like a HEADCASE" is bashing Google for reportedly doing business with Qualcomm. lmao Now bashing Google, Microsoft, Sony, Intel, AMD, Qualcomm, Apple, Rambus, ... And he thnks that helps Nvidia how? LOST in Nvidia land. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373591564018</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 21:12:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373593999176-61</Id><Title>Whats the news on tegras. Are they delayed again?</Title><Msg>Does anyone see tegra4 products around.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1373593999176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 21:53:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373594292887-62</Id><Topic><Title>New Analysis Casts Doubt On Intel's Smartphone Performance vs. ARM</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373590638914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 20:57:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no surprise there. thanks, good find.</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1373594292887</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 21:58:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373594973371-63</Id><Title>Regreted did not dump all NVDA and exchanged them to US solar</Title><Msg>One Dime vs One $ upside per month. What really pissed me off is that 1/4 billion shares waiting for distribution - What a Free Lunch! Cheers!</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1373594973371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 22:09:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373595551340-64</Id><Title>What Shield console device that JHH showed off on Youtube?</Title><Msg>Wow what a showcase! He looked fired up! "Nvidia CEO Jen Hsun Huang shows off the final production version of the Project Shield gaming handheld during a Taipei news conference on June 4, 2013" I could not see any bandage on that console. Cheer!</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1373595551340</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 22:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373598497007-65</Id><Title>Acer tablet benchmark leaked - Tegra 4 is a beast</Title><Msg>Acer tablet benchmark leaks with 2560×1440 WQHD display and Tegra 4 4 Comments BY CORY GUNTHER ON 11 JUL, 2013 Rate This 1 0 The next wave of true HD is arriving with tablets breaking out past the 1080p HD level and reaching into WQHD, or as some say, Retina display. Today we’re seeing some benchmark results that have revealed Acer‘s upcoming 2560×1440 HD display, complete with NVIDIA’s quad-core Tegra 4 processor under the hood. Sounds impressive right? We haven’t heard much from Acer so far this year, save for a few budget tablets shown off earlier this year. NVIDIA’s upcoming Tegra 4 quad-core also hasn’t been in the news too much either, as they prepare their wave of processors for the next-gen smartphones and tablets. However, Acer might have one beast of an Android device in the works. At Computex the folks from ASUS announced a Tegra 4 and ‘Retina’ display Transformer Pad Infinity, and now it looks like it will have some stiff competition from Acer. If the leaked benchmarks revealed today are to be believed. According to NotebookItalia that’s exactly what’s coming. The benchmark result shown above is an unknown Acer tablet running Android 4.2.2 Jelly Bean, and also is powered by NVIDIA’s quad-core Tegra 4 chip. Then you’ll notice not only a hugely high score, but a resolution coming in at 2560 x 1344. The dip is mostly for the on-screen navigation bar. That isn’t all either, there’s another result they’ve dug up and you can see its high score below. This score you can see the new tablet more than doubling the performance of the Tegra 3 powered Nexus 7, even with a bigger and HD display on board. So clearly this has some serious horsepower. As a reminder, benchmark results don’t mean this device will ever see the light of day on a consumer shelf, but we have a feeling it will. The results are calling it the Acer TA272HUL and we’ll update when we learn more.</Msg><Username>tegrapower2013</Username><Timestamp>1373598497007</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 23:08:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373601026586-66</Id><Topic><Title>101 students and chaperones kicked off a Airtran plane</Title><Username>mel_gibson111</Username><Timestamp>1373600841687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 23:47:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now they are are claiming antisemitism by the airline crew... What a surprise...</Msg><Username>pat_buchanan101</Username><Timestamp>1373601026586</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 23:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>