<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360560481171-1</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Getanid61</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360460299515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 20:38:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I find it somewhat remarkable that Ashraf as young as he is writes about value and growth and income stocks such as INTC and NVDA rather than chearing MOMO stocks like ARMH and Netflix. " I find it somewhat remarkable that Ashraf keeps bashing the winners... Calls folks out when they make money... those fools in industry...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360560481171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 00:28:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360561074926-2</Id><Topic><Title>Shouldn't Jen be announcing an acquisition?</Title><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1335019532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-04-21 10:45:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those are Very Good questions, Best. Quite timely too.</Msg><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1360561074926</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 00:37:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360562898290-3</Id><Title>Ouya CEO Reveals Plans For Yearly Hardware Refreshes</Title><Msg>"Nvidia has a team dedicated to the OUYA console" "marketplace will be packed full of games at launch." And those Android games will run on Shield... !! --------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- This should be a little annoying to customers who have been eying the Android-powered OUYA console. Company CEO Julie Uhrman confirmed with Joystiq that unlike the traditional console that sees a new hardware set every five to seven years, OUYA plans to take the mobile route and release a new console every year. That's right: the OUYA you purchase in June will be obsolete this time next year. "Our strategy is very much similar to the mobile strategy," she said. "There will be a new OUYA every year. There will be an OUYA 2 and an OUYA 3. We'll take advantage of faster, better processors, take advantage of prices falling. So if we can get more than 8 GB of flash in our box, we will." At $100 a pop, buying a new OUYA every year doesn't seem quite so drastic compared to tablet, smartphone and even console prices. And if anything, the older models will make great media players on other HDTVs in the house once they've been replaced with new models as the primary Android gaming machine. And like Google Play and Amazon's Appstore, all games will be linked to the user, not the machine. They'll also be backward compatible so that you don't have to keep buying the same titles over and over. On a performance level, Uhrman said that Nvidia has a team dedicated to the OUYA console for getting the Tegra 3 running at optimal levels. The quad-core A9-based chip is clocked at 1.6 GHz and backed by 1 GB of RAM, 8 GB of internal storage (or 5 Gameloft games), 802.11 b/g/n connectivity, Bluetooth and HDMI output. It won't have a rechargeable battery, but instead will plug into the wall like every other living room console. The first wave of OUYA consoles will head out to the Kickstarter backers in March followed by a full-blown public release in June at retailers like Best Buy, GameStop, Target and Amazon. Additional controls will also be made available, costing $49.99 per unit. Uhrman also said the OUYA's marketplace will be packed full of games at launch.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360562898290</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 01:08:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360565863291-4</Id><Title>Digitimes research: global (brand) tablet shipments expected to decrease 20% in Q1 of 2013</Title><Msg>Part of the reason is that major vendors (ASUS, Lenovo, ACER etc) may be waiting for Tegra 4's mass availability. SOURCE: digitimesDOTcom/news/a20130208PD204.html However, pent up demand will be met in Q2 and Q3....meanwhile, Tegra 3 is selling into the white-box market, which is larger and fastest growing on the global scale.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360565863291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 01:57:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360567270481-5</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes research: global (brand) tablet shipments expected to decrease 20% in Q1 of 2013</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360565863291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 01:57:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 20% is forecast for q/q, reflecting the traditional seasonality change.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360567270481</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 02:21:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360568583155-6</Id><Title>Dozens of Tegra powered mobile devices (mostly phones) currently on the Chinese market</Title><Msg>A very interesting list....worth a look: aliexpressDOTcom/wholesale/wholesale-tegra-phone.html The list, while by no means being completely inclusive, is much longer than I thought.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360568583155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 02:43:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360570592178-7</Id><Topic><Title>The growth of the chromebook market</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360374381518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 20:46:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Moronsavin, Seriously, there is no reason to mess your khakis...I have no doubt that you've been tweaking batch files, maybe even tossed together a basic program or two, possibly dating back to am era in computing when 5 1/4 floppys were all the rage. Now that being said, I will conced my professional career hasn't transcended that many decades. However, and I do have to give you kudos for using the term, I am not a hand waiver (lol) by profession, and more importantly that doesn't change the fact that you are glorified pc repair man. The evolutionary precursor to the geek squad if you will... :) You don't have to state that my retort is wasted on you - your deluded and evasive responses have clearly demonstrate that. I NEVER WROTE THAT HT IS NOT SMT. Again, what I stated was HT was and said HT is not the same as a physical core but instead is a virtualized core. I was very detailed in my description of HT and never once did I state it wasn't an SMT implementation - despite the parallelism occurring at the instruction level? By the way guess which architecture (RISC or CISC) was the first to implement a superscalar architecture? Heres a hint... it wasn't x86! Now just as an added bonus do you (mr pc repairman) know how intel achieved this (going superscalar on the x86)....?? (cue theme from jeopardy) - what is micro-ops translation. Yes sir by translating those big bad complex disc instructions to more atomic, essentially RISC like, instructions. There you have it - not only is HT not the same as a second core but in order for x86 to implement it and virtualize a second core it has to transform itself into a RISC processor (sort of :p) first. Now, do YOU still want to argue with me about scale? As for performance as I've said lets wait until we have a true compatible piece of silicon. There are so many things inherently wrong with this test. The least of which of is running a parellel workload (EP is the one you called out i assume as it was the one that didnt require any communication between cores) designed to work on an isolated system on a distrubted one. There are inate effeciencies when you run this all on the same piece of slicon and to make the assumption that just because each baord ran its own copy of code then its the same as if all the cores were on the same piece of silicon is rather naive and honestly moronic. if this were the case then why didnt they just measure the equivalent number of atom boards in the same manner - after all they are similar class and core configuration - btw arm crushed it in compute per watt. For one thing although you may be running indepent copies of the EP code you are also running independent copies of the os. In those terms the intel proc had a 6x advantage. I can go on and on but im tired, however, if you reply to this, I will be happy to go into more technical detail as to why the phoronix benchmark was more of an exercise in 'can do' than apples to apples comparison. From the load to how they measured power draw. I might even pull one of our veteran EE's into this (the one who use to build processors) just for fun. :)</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1360570592178</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:16:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360573432402-8</Id><Topic><Title>The growth of the chromebook market</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360374381518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 20:46:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stupidagain, ] You are still going down diversionary strawman routes to avoid data that does not back up your theoretical ramblings. If it makes you feel better ignore the cluster and just take a native dual or quad benchmark of your own choosing and multiply it up, I gave 3 links which included an A15 test too. Find me some data that proves a theoretical 16 core A9 or A16 will have a material impact on a Xeon server chip in some important metric to server users. p.s. you still don't understand my computing experience. I have had nothing to do with PC maintenance. I have designed, wrote and tuned company's core business computer systems that actually run their businesses like their financials, stock control/replenishment and other bespoke essential business functions. Started in Cobol and now on Oracle with various OLTP/DWH languages in addition. Worked on Mainframes, VAX, Alphas and Superdomes and tuned the enterprise servers running all the computer systems not just the ones I designed and wrote. If you think that equates to a PC repairman you are even more stupid than I thought.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360573432402</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 04:03:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360587822034-9</Id><Title>Titan benchmarks impressive</Title><Msg>Google NVIDIA GeForce Titan Specifications and Synthetic Benchmarks</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360587822034</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:03:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360587957151-10</Id><Topic><Title>IMPORTANT REPORT ON NVDA (MUST SEE)</Title><Username>jaredmurray772</Username><Timestamp>1360272322771</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:25:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one</Msg><Username>bryantford</Username><Timestamp>1360587957151</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:05:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360588163538-11</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA GPUs Accelerate Adobe Creative Suite 5.5 Production Premium</Title><Username>bulademple442</Username><Timestamp>1302536061000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-04-11 11:34:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clear analysis.</Msg><Username>ameliajoshep</Username><Timestamp>1360588163538</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:09:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360588603544-12</Id><Topic><Title>New NVDA Analyst Report (MUST SEE)</Title><Username>xandergray279</Username><Timestamp>1360256445162</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:00:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one</Msg><Username>bryantford</Username><Timestamp>1360588603544</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:16:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360588646163-13</Id><Topic><Title>New NVDA Analyst Report (MUST SEE)</Title><Username>richardortiz868</Username><Timestamp>1360262158446</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one</Msg><Username>bryantford</Username><Timestamp>1360588646163</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:17:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360588707161-14</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think NVDA is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>missionmildred</Username><Timestamp>1360080660065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:11:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just read your article. Nothing else.</Msg><Username>lowlineslourdes</Username><Timestamp>1360588707161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:18:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360589552454-15</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this report yet? (NVDA)</Title><Username>screamymelba</Username><Timestamp>1359744825161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:53:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have entered my email address. Waiting for the update.</Msg><Username>referancesdelores</Username><Timestamp>1360589552454</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:32:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360590152253-16</Id><Title>Is Nvidia going to have a baby?</Title><Msg>intel is the father?</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1360590152253</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:42:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360590927467-17</Id><Topic><Title>Is Nvidia going to have a baby?</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1360590152253</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:42:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blue-Green Man Group?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360590927467</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:55:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360592053499-18</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes research: global (brand) tablet shipments expected to decrease 20% in Q1 of 2013</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360565863291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 01:57:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if I take that as face value, I arrive at this model fro Tegra: Q3 '12 sales $240M lose $40 (actual results) Q4 '12 sales $160M (co. est.) lose = close to $100M since nvda said they are ramping expenses for the Q? Q1 '13 sales $128M (-20% from Q4) lose $100M for sure. Q2 '13 = ?? Nexus 7 refresh comes out with Snapdragon, nvda not in any of the top 4's tablets.... Ah reality, tough to stomach, isn't it? better hide head in sand......</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1360592053499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:14:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360592311979-19</Id><Topic><Title>The Tegra, it is like elephant</Title><Username>naziba.adongo</Username><Timestamp>1349843708263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's say that the dawdling board has finally decided to kill Jen's horrendous loss-making ARM chip folly. You know, like Texas Instruments and Freescale have already done. How much might the Giant One-Time Charge be to close-down the Tegra? Anybody know? If it's more than say, $500 million, it could wipe-out the entire year's profits, right?</Msg><Username>best.again</Username><Timestamp>1360592311979</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:18:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360592989942-20</Id><Topic><Title>The Tegra, it is like elephant</Title><Username>naziba.adongo</Username><Timestamp>1349843708263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like Intel did in the ultra portable sectors. Keep dreaming!</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1360592989942</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:29:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360594311281-21</Id><Title>Vanguard files 13G today</Title><Msg>nice vote of confidence By signing below I certify that, to the best of my knowledge and belief, the securities referred to above were acquired in the ordinary course of business and were not acquired for the purpose of and do not have the effect of changing or influencing the control of the issuer of such securities and were not acquired in connection with or as a participant in any transaction having such purpose or effect.</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360594311281</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:51:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360597015723-22</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360282938040</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:22:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!" Be careful of those who will say anything trying to boost their under water shares in Nvidia and then walk away from their own words when caught lying. The truth is Apple has $42.40 Cash Per Share (mrq), Nvidiia has $5.50 Cash Per Share (mrq) Don't be fooled by BS. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360597015723</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:36:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360597194907-23</Id><Topic><Title>Apple has $42.40 Cash Per Share (mrq), Nvidiia has $5.50 Cash Per Share (mrq)!</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360288104528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:48:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"He said "Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!" And that is a flat out LIE, no ifs ands or buts it." So where is the correction for that flat out lie? These pumpers will post lies and then walk away when caught? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360597194907</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:39:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360597453878-24</Id><Title>Nvidia has to report to its shareholders on 2/13</Title><Msg>Can you think of a few questions for that conference, I bet you can. What happen with the NEW Microsoft RT 2 tablet Nvidia? What happen with the NEW Google Nexus tablet Nvidia? What happen with Tegra 4 Nvidia? Why is Qualcomm cleaning your clock Nvidia? Say what? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360597453878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:44:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360597828645-25</Id><Topic><Title>Vanguard files 13G today</Title><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360594311281</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:51:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good stuff.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360597828645</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:50:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360598266199-26</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia has to report to its shareholders on 2/13</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360597453878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:44:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those questions shows your naivety. There isn't any answer but "We don't comment on rumours".</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1360598266199</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:57:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360598515319-27</Id><Title>Titan</Title><Msg>That's it Titan if you dont know what it is, you'd better figure it out ASAP</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360598515319</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:01:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360598732624-28</Id><Topic><Title>Titan</Title><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360598515319</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Titan 235W faster than 7970 230W "60%"</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1360598732624</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:05:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360598797826-29</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia has to report to its shareholders on 2/13</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360597453878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:44:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Those questions shows your naivety. There isn't any answer but "We don't comment on rumours"." Really? If Microsoft and Google told Nvidia that they are passing on Tegra 4 in favor of another chip for the NEW tablets that wouldn't be a rumor would it? You don't know what Nvidia knows or if Microsoft and Google told Nvidia they're passing on Tegra 4? Microsoft and Google have NEW products in the works and if Nvidia ain't in them Nvidia would know even though you are clueless. Did you know that? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360598797826</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:06:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360599266230-30</Id><Title>How many here missed that $26 boat believing that $30, $50 and $100 NONSENSE?</Title><Msg>Don't feel bad, I bet the pumpers who put up that $30, $50 and $100 NONSENSE wished they had put there own silly post on ignore and sold that junk at $26. lol You know what to do next time IF there is a next time. BTW What is it now? Is it less than half $26 or what? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360599266230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:14:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360599640803-31</Id><Title>NVIDIA Tegra 4: the future of mobile computing?</Title><Msg>A balanced article from ITProPortal SOURCE: itproportalDOTcom/2013/02/11/nvidia-tegra-4-future-mobile-computing/ Last month, Nvidia surprised roughly no-one by announcing the successor to Tegra 3, the processor at the heart of the Asus Transformer line of tablets, the Google Nexus 7, Microsoft’s Surface, HTC’s One X and a whole line-up of Android smartphones and slates. At the end of this month, we expect to see the Tegra 4 appearing in new smartphones and tablets at Mobile World Conference 2013, potentially including HTC’s rumoured flagship 5in phone, the M7, and tablets from Asus, Toshiba and Vizio. It’s unquestionably one of 2013’s most exciting mobile chips. There’s also no doubt of its power. Where the Tegra 3 was built around quad-core ARM Cortex A9 architecture, Tegra 4 brings us a quad-core architecture based on ARM’s next-generation Cortex A15 design. A shift from TSMC’s 40nm LPG process to 20nm LPC helps Tegra 4 reach 1.8GHz – 200MHz faster than Tegra 3 – without blowing heat and power budgets. Like Tegra 3, Tegra 4 features a fifth companion core for background tasks, though again it’s moved from A9 to A15, but now supports dual-channel DDR3 RAM. Nvidia estimates that Tegra 4 is about 20 times faster than Tegra 2 and six times faster than Tegra 3; that’s not to be sniffed at. Admittedly, there are some disappointments. In terms of GPU power, Tegra 4 is a big step up from Tegra 3. With six Vec4 vertex units and four 3-deep Vec4 pixel units, for a total of 72 cores, Tegra 4 has six times the number of Arithmetic Logic Units (ALUs) dedicated to graphics of Tegra 3, all running at a higher clock speed than they did on Tegra 3. In desktop PC terms, it’s close in power to the GeForce 7 series, including the RSX chip found in Sony’s PlayStation 3. However, those expecting a more efficient unified shader architecture, as found in the GeForce 8 line and upwards, not to mention a shared architecture with Kepler, may be underwhelmed. Tegra 4’s GPU architecture is understood to be an extension of Tegra 3’s with key enhancements, rather than a wholesale reinvention/...... _______ Note: The "criticism of non-unified shaders in Tegra 4 has been addressed by NV management. It is a tradeoff for greater energy efficiency, rather than an issue of technical feasibility.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360599640803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360599691862-32</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia has to report to its shareholders on 2/13</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360597453878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:44:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As long as it's not public, it's just a rumour. I think it's easy to get it. Your "IFs" are baseless, and Jen would comment only publicly available data. Still, you can ask him, but no chance you can get an answer different then "We don't comment on rumours". Kapish?</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1360599691862</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:21:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360600072546-33</Id><Title>Project shield comes next quarter to Europe,US and Canada</Title><Msg>and rest of world...Project Shield: Turbo charged gaming handheld coming to the UK!Are you itching to getting your hands on Nvidia’s lightning fast gaming handheld, Project Shield? You won’t have to wait too long, as the company is moving fast to get the console to the UK as soon as possible. Best known for its graphics cards, Nvidia surprised many at CES last month with its clamshell gaming console that can play Android games and stream even demanding PC games. While the console is set to hit the US and Canada between April and June, the company is keen to get the handheld out the door and into gamers’ hands worldwide. Wikipad gaming tablet slims down: Seven inch PS Vita rival on the way! According to Nvidia’s director of product marketing Jason Paul, the company wants to sprint to get it into Europe and Asia. “Since the announcement we’ve had people knocking on our door. So there’s interest in distributing the product. Shield is targeting Android and PC gamers, so we are looking for people who can sell into that market.” Game systems live and die by the number of games available for them, and that depends on the numbers sold – a real chicken and egg situation Nvidia will be keen to solve quickly with a global release it seems – so look out for Project Shield on these shores soon.</Msg><Username>daysofshred30000000000</Username><Timestamp>1360600072546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:27:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360600210787-34</Id><Title>Apple has made the transition from "growth" to "value" stock</Title><Msg>SOURCE: Barrons this morning By Tiernan Ray Here are some things going on this morning in your world of tech: Shares of Apple (AAPL) are up $7.31, or 1.5%, at $482.29as the Street continues to contemplate the prospect of enhanced payouts raised by David Einhorn’s protests last week. On Sunday, ISI Group’s Brian Marshall reiterated a Strong Buy rating on the stock and a $600 price target, saying he’d spoken with AAPL’s CFO (Peter Oppenheimer) this past Friday and found the conversation helpful “we are starting to field calls from “smart money” investors who are building positions in AAPL at current levels based on the belief that: 1) AAPL has *already* made the transition to a “value play” (from a growth story), and 2) a favorable capital allocation update will be the next catalyst for share.” Jim Stewart was on CNBC this morning to talk about the failure of the Apple bulls, as laid out in his “Common Sense” column from Friday in The New York Times. “I went back to look at the absolute peak, it was overwhelmingly Buy and Strong Buy. I was seeing the same old herd instinct all over again. There’s this trading desk problem, if you put out a buy, everyone can go buy and generate selling commissions.” In case you missed it, Bloomberg’s Peter Burrows writes that the drop in Apple’s profit margin to 39% from 45% a year earlier means that “Unless Chief Executive Officer Tim Cook unveils a revolutionary new gadget with premium pricing, Apple shares will remain under pressure.” Cook is scheduled to speak at the Goldman Sachs tech conference, tomorrow afternoon, at 1:15 pm, Pacific Time.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360600210787</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:30:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360600273573-35</Id><Title>a 4 for 1 reverse split would squeeze us up nicely</Title><Msg>make this a $50 stock with 150M float and we end the endless sale of shares</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1360600273573</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:31:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360600277631-36</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Tegra 4: the future of mobile computing?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360599640803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Asus MeMO Pad Smart ME301T official with Nvidia Tegra 3, Android 4.1 for $299 And yet the wins keep coming!</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1360600277631</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:31:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360600453575-37</Id><Title>You may not know if Google and Microsoft passed on Tegra 4 for NEW Tablets but Nvidia knows?</Title><Msg>Sure, you can call it a rumor now but can Nvidia? Nvida would know if Tegra 4 made it into the NEW Surface RT 2 tablet or NOT wouldn't they? Nvidia would know if Tegra 4 made it into the NEW Google Nexus tablet or NOT wouldn't they? Do you think Nvidia could win or lose these two high profile customers and NOT know it? And you know Nvidia tried to sell Tegra 4 to Microsoft and Google because if they didn't the CEO should be fired. Do you think Nvidia is that clueless? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360600453575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:34:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360600683194-38</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Tegra 4: the future of mobile computing?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360599640803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What hapen to that other id you use to post with ibexx88? Was ibexx88 you or another ibexx? I don't see thatother ibexx88 id posting as of late? Are you donw to just one Id now?</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360600683194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:38:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360600687709-39</Id><Topic><Title>Titan</Title><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360598515319</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>super high margins equal to 690 GTX but with only 1 GPU , not 2 as you said, lower power and sceaming perf. released in 2 weeks Damn I couldnt keep my mouth shut , now everyone knows</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360600687709</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:38:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360601098299-40</Id><Topic><Title>Apple has $42.40 Cash Per Share (mrq), Nvidiia has $5.50 Cash Per Share (mrq)!</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360288104528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:48:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no, i'm not. you're looking at yahoo's keys statistics page which only looks at cash &amp; equivalents. you need to look at their balance sheet. They do the same thing MSFT does, and keep the majority of their cash in what are considered "long term investments" by GAAP accounting, but are actually highly liquid investments. That's why you hear analysts and more informed investors quoting the $137B in total cash figure. My numbers reflect that.</Msg><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1360601098299</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:44:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360601222294-41</Id><Topic><Title>You may not know if Google and Microsoft passed on Tegra 4 for NEW Tablets but Nvidia knows?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360600453575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:34:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The world will find out when the NEW Microsoft Surface RT 2 ships and the NEW Nexus tablets ships which ARM SoC chip is on board right? Or the world will find out if Tegra 4 made the cut or NOT if Nvidia announces a design win or loss, right? Which one do you think will happen first Nvidia fans? Either way, It won't be a secret forever, will it? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360601222294</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:47:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360601254114-42</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Tegra 4: the future of mobile computing?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360599640803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Worth highlighting: "we expect to see the Tegra 4 appearing in new smartphones and tablets at Mobile World Conference 2013, potentially including HTC’s rumoured flagship 5in phone, the M7, and tablets from Asus, Toshiba and Vizio. It’s unquestionably one of 2013’s most exciting mobile chips."" ______ Regarding Tegra 4's design wins in phones and tablets, the hired bashers on this board can choose to believe in the hedge fund run by Pacific Crest - after all, they may be fed by the same filthy hand - but I think ITProPortol is a much more credible source.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360601254114</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:47:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360601812261-43</Id><Topic><Title>How many here missed that $26 boat believing that $30, $50 and $100 NONSENSE?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360599266230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:14:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't you call the ones who said $26 was a gift BASHERS ? And you called the ones who said $26 was just the beginning BRILLIANT right? Well if $26 was the beginning, it was tthe beginning that trip back down to reality. lol Say hello to some real $12s Nvidia fans. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360601812261</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:56:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360602553375-44</Id><Topic><Title>Project shield comes next quarter to Europe,US and Canada</Title><Username>daysofshred30000000000</Username><Timestamp>1360600072546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:27:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if its $40 GM per unit Shield is a home run Closer to $80 - $100 is my guess Not shabby..</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360602553375</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:09:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360603233632-45</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia has to report to its shareholders on 2/13</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360597453878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:44:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Still, you can ask him, but no chance you can get an answer different then "We don't comment on rumours". Kapish?" The world doesn't need an answer from Jen on the NEW Microsoft and Google tablets. Microsoft and Google will answer that question in their own time. Tegra either kept these 2 high profile customers or loss them to a better part. And Jen can't hide that fact with a "no comment" can he? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360603233632</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:20:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360603416136-46</Id><Topic><Title>"Microsoft Eyes 3 New Surface Tablet Servings for 2013"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358193453852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 14:57:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Most notable of the planned release is the 8.6-inch Surface RT 2, which will do away with the Nvidia Tegra chip that used with the first iteration. This new Surface RT is set to be deployed with Qualcomm chipset." Who thinks this topic will come up on that conf call? lol Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360603416136</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:23:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360603827837-47</Id><Topic><Title>How many here missed that $26 boat believing that $30, $50 and $100 NONSENSE?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360599266230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:14:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stock will be back to $15-$16 pretty soon imho</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360603827837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:30:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360604066251-48</Id><Title>NVDA short play</Title><Msg>look out for disappointment when NVDA reports. NVDA tends to sell off at least 10% after qtr earning report - I have no reason to believe that this time will be different. Increasing competition from Intel, AMD on traditional front and execution problems on Tegra front. Time to start building a short position -</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1360604066251</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:34:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360604593391-49</Id><Topic><Title>You may not know if Google and Microsoft passed on Tegra 4 for NEW Tablets but Nvidia knows?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360600453575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:34:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Most notable of the planned release is the 8.6-inch Surface RT 2, which will do away with the Nvidia Tegra chip that used with the first iteration. This new Surface RT is set to be deployed with Qualcomm chipset." Did you see that story in the auDOTibtimes? I bet Nvidia management saw it? Don't know if they liked it but I bet they saw it? What do you think Nvidia fans? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360604593391</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:43:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360605526710-50</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia has to report to its shareholders on 2/13</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360597453878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:44:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No matter how many "lols" you add, you've finally realized your original questions for NVDA conference were pure nonsense. Congrats!</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1360605526710</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:58:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360605654020-51</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA short play</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1360604066251</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:34:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good luck!</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360605654020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:00:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360605953908-52</Id><Topic><Title>How many here missed that $26 boat believing that $30, $50 and $100 NONSENSE?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360599266230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:14:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Stock will be back to $15-$16 pretty soon" How long have you been singing that same tune? If you owned an iPod you would have a wider selection of iTunes to sing sport. What is it now? Is it less than half that $26 that wasn't god enough then? But now $16 is golden right? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360605953908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:05:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360606223333-53</Id><Topic><Title>How many here missed that $26 boat believing that $30, $50 and $100 NONSENSE?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360599266230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:14:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I probably would've been shorting at $26 if I were trading back then. Bubbles always pop.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360606223333</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:10:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360606537016-54</Id><Topic><Title>"Next-gen Nexus 7 could see Nvidia ousted in favor of Qualcomm"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360286488125</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:21:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The next-generation Nexus 7 tablet could see Nvidia's Tegra 4 System-on-a-Chip (SoC) ousted in favor of Qualcomm's Snapdragon S4 Pro silicon." Will Nvidia comment on this story on that conf call? Maybe if Nvidia pretends Qualcomm doesn't exist the story will go away right? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360606537016</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:15:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360607546184-55</Id><Topic><Title>How many here missed that $26 boat believing that $30, $50 and $100 NONSENSE?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360599266230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:14:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe we could see an Armh like multiple for a while.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1360607546184</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:32:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360607729904-56</Id><Topic><Title>IMPORTANT REPORT ON NVDA (MUST SEE)</Title><Username>jaredmurray772</Username><Timestamp>1360272322771</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:25:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great update</Msg><Username>leeryan723</Username><Timestamp>1360607729904</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:35:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360607751649-57</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Tegra 4: the future of mobile computing?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360599640803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it does sound like Nvidia lost the design win in the Nexus 7 refresh, based on more reports from other connected folks (see Fudzilla's article on Friday, for example) that have come out after the Pac Crest note -- but this might be pretty insignificant in the scheme of things. The unit volume lost from losing a nexus 7 design could easily be made up elsewhere, e.g. just a single high-volume tablet or smartphone with the complete reference designs Nvidia is supposedly preparing to target primarily the lower price points in the international market.</Msg><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1360607751649</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:35:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360608193050-58</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Tegra 4: the future of mobile computing?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360599640803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nvidia is supposedly preparing to target primarily the lower price points in the international market." Tegra 4 is only 80 sq mm...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360608193050</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:43:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360608367598-59</Id><Topic><Title>New NVDA Analyst Report (MUST SEE)</Title><Username>xandergray279</Username><Timestamp>1360256445162</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:00:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good report. Keep it coming</Msg><Username>leeryan723</Username><Timestamp>1360608367598</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:46:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360608398032-60</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this report yet? (NVDA)</Title><Username>screamymelba</Username><Timestamp>1359744825161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:53:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just received your first email. It's very informational. Love it.</Msg><Username>potinkanisha</Username><Timestamp>1360608398032</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:46:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360608458154-61</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Tegra 4: the future of mobile computing?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360599640803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pacific Crest that small west coast brokerage house is the one that started the story about Nexus 7 and Qualcomm. Be advised that this exact same time last year they were flogging the rumor that Nvidia won the Kindle Fire HD application processor slot. They tend to bat 50-50 on rumors. Probably has something to do with their book. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360608458154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:47:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360608861605-62</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Tegra 4: the future of mobile computing?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360599640803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Pacific Crest that small west coast brokerage house is the one that started the story about Nexus 7 and Qualcomm." Do give credit where credit's due. That 'rumor' was accidentaly leaked out a qcom roadmap slide. Love that pumper who said that losing the Nexus 7 is insignificant.... absence of a backbone and no shame, I guess.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1360608861605</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:54:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360609191633-63</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Tegra 4: the future of mobile computing?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360599640803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Do give credit where credit's due. That 'rumor' was accidentaly leaked out a qcom roadmap slide.' The Who Was that right before the Huge Insider Selling Dump by QCOM execs?....see Yahoo Finance</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360609191633</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:59:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360609805981-64</Id><Title>If this thing reaches $13 bucks sell the hell out of it</Title><Msg>The good news only keeps this turd afloat for a few days, then it gets flushed again.</Msg><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1360609805981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:10:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360609869128-65</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA short play</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1360604066251</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:34:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The market may have treated NVDA wrong for the past 2 years. Watch for a pop into 20s , building a short position here is totally nonsense.</Msg><Username>guy_8619</Username><Timestamp>1360609869128</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:11:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360609946992-66</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA short play</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1360604066251</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:34:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree $19/- end of the year.</Msg><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1360609946992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:12:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360610087638-67</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Tegra 4: the future of mobile computing?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360599640803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only article from Fudzilla about this subject on a 'Friday' was posted January 11th, not last Friday. And I was aware of this for a while. This is why any news about the Nexus 7.7 is really either a way to make news (in other words negative news) with little else to write until MWC. I didn't expect many new launches until the 2nd quarter myself but thought the announcements of what's ahead would be during MWC. They had working chips at CES, but the mass production wasn't ready yet, totally understandable and not surprising. I've counted about 2 (maybe three) articles for every one that still thinks the next Nexus 7 (7.7) still has Tegra 4. It all depends on when Google wants to get this upgrade version out to market. If it's before Q2, then we may have lost that tablet design. However, I'm wondering in all this speculation if Google isn't using a stopgap here with no intention of keeping the Qualcomm chip long-term . . if the PC note is at all accurate.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1360610087638</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:14:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360610211790-68</Id><Topic><Title>If this thing reaches $13 bucks sell the hell out of it</Title><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1360609805981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:10:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks so much for your concise input amdsh!t. Now get back to work cleaning toilets.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber22</Username><Timestamp>1360610211790</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:16:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360610306429-69</Id><Title>#$%$.D. keeping lid on until Wed AF</Title><Msg>NVDA is still growing revenue in in PC market ?? come on, you've got to be kidding me. Everyone is saying the PC sector is in decline :-) lol</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360610306429</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:18:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360610924705-70</Id><Title>amdshortsrfools famous last words...lose both ways</Title><Msg>Re: What kind of person pumps AMD as it falls all the way from 42 to 8? by amdshortsrfools . Jun 17, 2008 9:15 AM . Permalink Go to topic A smart investor who gets in when AMD stock is cheap you fool!</Msg><Username>moorall</Username><Timestamp>1360610924705</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:28:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360611056147-71</Id><Topic><Title>If this thing reaches $13 bucks sell the hell out of it</Title><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1360609805981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:10:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You still here chit4brains? Those unemployment checks haven't run out yet huh? Glad to see you can still afford that 256k dsl line and the mobile home. I heard Obama gave ya a raise, that must have helped.</Msg><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1360611056147</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:30:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360611710982-72</Id><Topic><Title>If this thing reaches $13 bucks sell the hell out of it</Title><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1360609805981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:10:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm hoping for $25.00, I plan on putting 10k in for every dollar it goes up til then, starting at $13.00. If it jumps 2.00, I'll add 20k.</Msg><Username>johnnygreenapple</Username><Timestamp>1360611710982</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:41:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360611796276-73</Id><Title>the shorts' chanting has begun, like clockwork</Title><Msg>even some washed out oldies have come back</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1360611796276</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:43:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360612119090-74</Id><Title>Question: If you shorted a ton of shares</Title><Msg>and are losing on the trade and earnings are going to be announced with a large increase in revenue and a growth in earnings quarter over quarter what do you do? Answer: START A RUMOR. Look at all these bashers.....desperate times I guess. The smart shorts who are in a winning position can easily hit the buy button leaving those who sell low to buy high.</Msg><Username>moorall</Username><Timestamp>1360612119090</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:48:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360612397075-75</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think NVDA is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>missionmildred</Username><Timestamp>1360080660065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:11:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have it already. It's the best.</Msg><Username>proselytizeddebora</Username><Timestamp>1360612397075</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:53:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360613474085-76</Id><Topic><Title>If this thing reaches $13 bucks sell the hell out of it</Title><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1360609805981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:10:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see you are still incapable of coming up with original lines. What else could expect from a putz as yourself.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber22</Username><Timestamp>1360613474085</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:11:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360613789832-77</Id><Topic><Title>If this thing reaches $13 bucks sell the hell out of it</Title><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1360609805981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:10:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You realize everyone thinks you are an idiot..... why bother posting.. cry like a baby because you hitched to a dead horse... take it and get oveover it.. AMD lost...</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1360613789832</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:16:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360613802839-78</Id><Topic><Title>If this thing reaches $13 bucks sell the hell out of it</Title><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1360609805981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:10:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I'm hoping for $25.00, I plan on putting 10k in for every dollar it goes up til then, starting at $13.00. If it jumps 2.00, I'll add 20k." Thats nice but whats the plan IF it tanks? It has been known to tank after an earnings call in the past right? Do you have a backup plan or are you going for broke as they say? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360613802839</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:16:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360614215083-79</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360282938040</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:22:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!" He has to know that post was not true by now and yet he won't post a correction. He won't admit he was wrong? Whay is that? What is to be gained by posting a lie? Those who would post lies and then act as if their own post doesn't exist when caught lose respect. The FACTS say: Apple has $42.40 Cash Per Share (mrq), Nvidiia has $5.50 Cash Per Share (mrq) imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360614215083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:23:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360614406527-80</Id><Topic><Title>Apple has $42.40 Cash Per Share (mrq), Nvidiia has $5.50 Cash Per Share (mrq)!</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360288104528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:48:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone tried to float this lie: "Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!" But he got caught and the lie was exposed for the NONSENSE it was. And that someone now acts as if someone else posted that NONSENSE since he can't or won't admit he was wrong. The FACTS say: Apple has $42.40 Cash Per Share (mrq), Nvidiia has $5.50 Cash Per Share (mrq)! Now say it ain't so. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360614406527</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:26:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360614589455-81</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA short play</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1360604066251</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:34:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not sure about the timing, hold it for a few more years, this is a pure Lynch and Fisher play, classic, a 3 to 5 bagger from here.</Msg><Username>guy_8619</Username><Timestamp>1360614589455</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:29:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360614689280-82</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Tegra 4: the future of mobile computing?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360599640803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The numbers of which websites saying what don't always count - only the ones with credibility should carry some weight. That said, I did notice there were a couple of more sharing the views of Fudzilla.....</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360614689280</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:31:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360614696261-83</Id><Topic><Title>If this thing reaches $13 bucks sell the hell out of it</Title><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1360609805981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:10:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bought the other day at 12.36, if it goes 10% below that, I'll take a small loss.</Msg><Username>johnnygreenapple</Username><Timestamp>1360614696261</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:31:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360615073087-84</Id><Title>We don't have to agree on OPINIONS but you don't get to make up your own FACTS</Title><Msg>Posting NONSENSE with no basis in truth as if it were a fact does not help Nvidia. No matter how much junk you make up or how many times you post it. Yahoo has a "Key Statistics" link to he right that works wonders at sorting out BS from FACT. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360615073087</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:37:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360615628201-85</Id><Topic><Title>You may not know if Google and Microsoft passed on Tegra 4 for NEW Tablets but Nvidia knows?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360600453575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:34:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did Tegra 4 land the NEW Microsoft RT 2 tablet and the NEW Google Nexus tablet? Just because you don't know and I odn't know doesn't mean Nvidia doesn't know, you know? I don't know how they could win or lose two large customers and not know, you know? Who knows what won't remain secret forever if Microsoft and Google intend to sell those NEW tablets, you know? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360615628201</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:47:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360615965467-86</Id><Title>Set for earnings surprise and stronger guidance?</Title><Msg>They didnt clean AMDs clock on high end GPUs : -) PC Gaming in China didnt grow much :-) : -) Tesla didnt sell more GPUs on HPC computers :-) :-) : -) Pro Graphics mkt was static :-) :-) : -) Tegra 3 mobile chips didnt sell much :-) :-) : -): -) Tegra 4 is failed chip out of gate :-) :-) :-) :-) : -): -) Consumers gave up spending on PC gaming :-) :-) :-) :-) : -): -) They didnt take much mkt share on Tablets :-) :-) :-) :-) : -): -) -) Titan looks to be a failure too :-) :-) :-) :-) : -): -) -) Apple not forcasting to sell many Macs with NVDA graphics chips :-) :-) :-) :-) : -): -) -) yep things are down right dismal yes, a very low point indeed and I'm miserable right ? Afterall who wants a company stuffed with cash, no debt , with kick butt mobile parts and high margin SKU's sold wordwide with growing market share in every segment . Did I mention superior technology ? Thats too much to comprehend</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360615965467</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:52:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360616483262-87</Id><Topic><Title>We don't have to agree on OPINIONS but you don't get to make up your own FACTS</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360615073087</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:37:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one should be trying to defend a lie. And that post claiming: "Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!" is a lie. You can't crush the truth with lies or spin. FACTS say: Apple has $42.40 Cash Per Share (mrq), Nvidiia has $5.50 Cash Per Share (mrq) And thats not an opinion, Its not made up junk for purposes of posting BS. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360616483262</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:01:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360616846577-88</Id><Topic><Title>Look for Nvidia to miss estimates and give poor guidance</Title><Username>swims48184</Username><Timestamp>1360369110610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 19:18:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! Okay, whatever you say, champ.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360616846577</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:07:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360616975806-89</Id><Title>IPhone 5 trails four other Android phones for user satisfaction</Title><Msg>Apple fanboyz read it and weep. Everybody's grandma has an iPhone....not cool anymore. intomobileDOTcom/2013/02/11/iphone-5-trails-four-other-android-phones-us-user-satisfaction/</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360616975806</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:09:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360617760480-90</Id><Topic><Title>Old ibexx88 claims "This is a $100 stock in due time - before 2014"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1324150752000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2011-12-17 14:39:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Less than a year away from 2014 for that $100 prediction. So will it go straight UP from here at $12.51 or what? Wouldn't that be like UP $10 a month for the rest of this year? UP $10 a month Every month for the rest of this year? lmao That's all it would take right? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360617760480</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:22:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360618019233-91</Id><Topic><Title>You may not know if Google and Microsoft passed on Tegra 4 for NEW Tablets but Nvidia knows?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360600453575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:34:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never have I seen anyone type so many words on a message board without having any real point. You assert that NVDA management knows who is ordering from them... yes. Okay... well then...</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1360618019233</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:26:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360618339216-92</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a $30 stock?</Title><Username>axelmy</Username><Timestamp>1297974788000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2011-02-17 15:33:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did he say $100 BEFORE 2014? OK, Lets see how this plays out shall we? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360618339216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:32:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360618679129-93</Id><Topic><Title>You may not know if Google and Microsoft passed on Tegra 4 for NEW Tablets but Nvidia knows?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360600453575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:34:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You assert that NVDA management knows who is ordering from them... yes. Okay... well then..." Some here are in DENIAL and calling the NEW Microsoft RT 2 tablet article with a Qualcomm part and the NEW Google Nexus article rumors, didn't you know that? But if Nvidia is not in these new products don't you think Nvidia would know that? And if Nvidia knows either way it wouldn't be a rumor to Nvidia's management, would it? lol You wouldn't be in DENIAL too, would you? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360618679129</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:37:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360619589322-94</Id><Topic><Title>"Next-gen Nexus 7 could see Nvidia ousted in favor of Qualcomm"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360286488125</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:21:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""Summary: Being pushed out of the next-generation Nexus 7 could result in a revenue dent for Nvidia in the region of $200-250 million, according to one analyst." Do you think Nvidia'a management can clear this analyst opinion up on the conf. call? Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360619589322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:53:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360619705173-95</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think NVDA is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>missionmildred</Username><Timestamp>1360080660065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:11:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good move. I will be expecting for more news.</Msg><Username>screenblasteradriana</Username><Timestamp>1360619705173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:55:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360619736891-96</Id><Topic><Title>"Microsoft Eyes 3 New Surface Tablet Servings for 2013"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358193453852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 14:57:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Most notable of the planned release is the 8.6-inch Surface RT 2, which will do away with the Nvidia Tegra chip that used with the first iteration. This new Surface RT is set to be deployed with Qualcomm chipset." Do you think Nvidia's management can "add some color" to this story as the analyst like to say on the conf. call? Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360619736891</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:55:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360620486478-97</Id><Topic><Title>You may not know if Google and Microsoft passed on Tegra 4 for NEW Tablets but Nvidia knows?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360600453575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:34:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Last year, on many occasions, Jen Hsun openly expressed surprise in Microsoft choosing Tegra 3 in Surface RT. NV was not exactly consulted nor informed much earlier than the general public. In fact, in January 2012, QC's marketing department put out a Win 8 on ARM campaign (that was the term used then) implying that Snapdragon S4 was the "designated" one - it probably was, only that QC couldn't step up to the plate with the appropriate qualifying drivers. Even as early as in June, 2012, Engadget and Anandtech published big "hands on" articles heralding the arrival of a new age (S4 in Win Surface leading the charge) which, embarrassingly, did NOT happen. As NVDA longs, we need to be more discriminating about QC's marketing rhetoric, both directly and thru third parties, as well as the paid to write/talk, high-profile tech pundits like A and E - in some ways they are only a shade better than the hired bashers on this board, in that they are more technically knowledgeable. Still they likely got paid to write what they did.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360620486478</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:08:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360620901188-98</Id><Topic><Title>IMPORTANT REPORT ON NVDA (MUST SEE)</Title><Username>jaredmurray772</Username><Timestamp>1360272322771</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:25:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report.</Msg><Username>markreed158</Username><Timestamp>1360620901188</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:15:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360621275852-99</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this report yet? (NVDA)</Title><Username>screamymelba</Username><Timestamp>1359744825161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:53:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have it already. It's the best.</Msg><Username>midshipsleigh</Username><Timestamp>1360621275852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:21:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360621339525-100</Id><Topic><Title>New NVDA Analyst Report (MUST SEE)</Title><Username>richardortiz868</Username><Timestamp>1360262158446</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report.</Msg><Username>markreed158</Username><Timestamp>1360621339525</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:22:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360621754088-101</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Tegra 4: the future of mobile computing?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360599640803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not sure why Google is even considering Qaulcomm with the distinct gaming &amp; cloud advantages, along with the continuity of very successful Nexus sales and performance? Perhaps Qaulcomm is low-balling on pricing, or G wants to keep Nvidia honest by including Q in the mix?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1360621754088</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:29:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360623812656-102</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Tegra 4: the future of mobile computing?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360599640803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These decisions were not always made on technical merits. In the case of MS and QC, Microsoft, like Google, would like to play the musical chairs and spread its gospel around - well you can't really fault them for this - and MS specially needs QC chips for its Win Phones. Besides technical merits and business strategy, there is also the image issue - in that MS considers QC its equal in bigness. Ballmer probably fantasizes a similar duopoly with Qualcomm just like the fading Wintel empire.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360623812656</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:03:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360625340907-103</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a $30 stock?</Title><Username>axelmy</Username><Timestamp>1297974788000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2011-02-17 15:33:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very true.</Msg><Username>barjonicat</Username><Timestamp>1360625340907</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:29:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360626530896-104</Id><Topic><Title>Titan</Title><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360598515319</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>:You meant TITANIC, rilght?</Msg><Username>jermeoff</Username><Timestamp>1360626530896</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:48:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360627127919-105</Id><Topic><Title>Titan</Title><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360598515319</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On ignore . . looking at other comments they are just as ignorant as your bad spelling here. T4, as you call it, had design wins even at CES and normally has the major ones announced later in the year around MWC. So T4 does have design wins right now and will have more.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1360627127919</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:58:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360628453731-106</Id><Title>Lets face it folks, tegra is finished. Nvidia can increase profits if</Title><Msg>it dumps this loss leader tegra. No one seems to like or want the tegra4. There is a reason for this. It is based on the A15 and runs too hot and slow. Just claim victory with tegra, dump it and move on.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360628453731</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 19:20:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360629673116-107</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Tegra 4: the future of mobile computing?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360599640803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The tegra4 is a DUD. For a 7" tablet, tegra4 runs too hot.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360629673116</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 19:41:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360631312286-108</Id><Title>My, My, My The Gang's All Here!</Title><Msg>please short more because we don't want the stock to Pop until after earnings although I suspect the reaction will be tame either way unless Nvidia plays the X-Card..... .....Share buybacks last quarter and this quarter......just saying you know!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360631312286</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:08:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360631403079-109</Id><Topic><Title>Titan</Title><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360598515319</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:01:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The bashers. shorties, and some skeptic long traders seemed to forgot that Qualcomm announced Snapdragon 600 and 800. but neither has claimed any design wins. The analysts never commented on this either. The playing ground is certainly not level....</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360631403079</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:10:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360634174215-110</Id><Topic><Title>You may not know if Google and Microsoft passed on Tegra 4 for NEW Tablets but Nvidia knows?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360600453575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:34:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except this time Nvidia is the current supplier for the first generation Surface RT tablet so Nvidia would or should know if orders have come to a trickle to make room for the NEW supplier, wouldn't they? Microsoft and Google will eventually sell those NEW tablets and when they do ALL will know if Tegra 4 made the cut or NOT. Every article I've seen says Qualcomm pushed Tegra out. What did you see that said otherwise? The au ibtimes said: "Most notable of the planned release is the 8.6-inch Surface RT 2, which will do away with the Nvidia Tegra chip that used with the first iteration. This new Surface RT is set to be deployed with Qualcomm chipset." If you discard every article that doesn't make nice about Tegra 4 then you must be in DENIAL. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360634174215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:56:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360635225757-111</Id><Topic><Title>You may not know if Google and Microsoft passed on Tegra 4 for NEW Tablets but Nvidia knows?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360600453575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:34:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In denial because of an unsubstantiated rumor? Can't tell if you believe the stuff you write or not... Rumors are just that, rumors. Might be true, or might not.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1360635225757</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:13:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360635379399-112</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia has to report to its shareholders on 2/13</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360597453878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:44:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who else thinks Nvidia will get away with a "no comment" about reports of TWO HIGH PROFILE CUSTOMERS being poached by Qualcomm on that conf call? How is this for a follow up: Do you expect orders for the old Surface and Nexus tablets to continue at current levels through out 2013? (Would you call that a rumor question? or a legitimate business question?) How do you think a "no comment" will go over with that friendly group of analyst? It should be a laugh a mnute if they try to defend Tegra 4 with a "no comment". imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360635379399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:16:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360637003765-113</Id><Title>Good luck into earnings, longs</Title><Msg>Good luck, everyone. I assume we'll all be here to discuss the earnings call :-) Let's hope that Jen and his team: - Continued to take market share from AMD in GPUs - Scored some nice design wins with Tegra 3/4 in China phones - Nailed a high profile tablet design or two with Tegra 4 - Saw a recovery in the workstation market + strong ramp in Tesla Most of all, let's hope Q1 guide is strong.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360637003765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:43:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360637448151-114</Id><Topic><Title>Good luck into earnings, longs</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360637003765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope so too... but NVidia's announcement for earnings was delayed to the last possible moment... usually translating that the Q was on the edge...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360637448151</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:50:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360637539512-115</Id><Topic><Title>Good luck into earnings, longs</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360637003765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wouldn't count on Jen Hsun discuss details of design wins with names and dates and all. They rarely did; most legitimate companies do not discuss the business plans of their customers. (You could lose this customer or be sued later if your partner changes its mind). You should know that - if not, then you should as a regular SA writer.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360637539512</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:52:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360638395826-116</Id><Topic><Title>Good luck into earnings, longs</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360637003765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is just looking for something to write the next article on. Sorry to say but they all just blur into the horizon. Too bad stock investing isn't judged on points and language skills! JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360638395826</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:06:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360638686115-117</Id><Topic><Title>Good luck into earnings, longs</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360637003765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course, NV can discuss design wins COLLECTIVELY in very general terns, and product releases in very vague timeframes; ie Q1, Q2, 2H etc, but do not expect specifics. Naturally they could discuss their own product like Project Shield should they choose to do so. However, I doubt you would learn too many specifics....not smart to show your hand in such a highly competitive space.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360638686115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:11:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360638687183-118</Id><Topic><Title>Good luck into earnings, longs</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360637003765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"He is just looking for something to write the next article on." Already suggested, on this board, that the tech press write that Project Denver might appear in NVidia's GTC in March...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360638687183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:11:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360639406610-119</Id><Topic><Title>Lets face it folks, tegra is finished. Nvidia can increase profits if</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360628453731</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 19:20:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra4 was designed for 10" tablets and PC's. JenSun was seeing pots of gold everywhere. Both are out of reach at this time. I am glad you mentioned turkey, because by thanksgiving, Jensun will see the light.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360639406610</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:23:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360639490748-120</Id><Topic><Title>Lets face it folks, tegra is finished. Nvidia can increase profits if</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360628453731</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 19:20:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Tegra4 was designed for 10" tablets and PC's. " Provide a shread of info... or as usual, you have NO CLUE... NONE !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360639490748</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:24:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360639600098-121</Id><Topic><Title>Good luck into earnings, longs</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360637003765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Steve Jobs was well known for firing/dismissing any component supplier if the latter leaked any technical information or marketing plans before the product release. I heard that it was even written into their respective contracts.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360639600098</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:26:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360639850920-122</Id><Topic><Title>Old ibexx88 claims "This is a $100 stock in due time - before 2014"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1324150752000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2011-12-17 14:39:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This is a $100 stock in due time - before 2014 when Stark is upon us... " This an example of clueless day dreaming and complete DENIAL about what Nvidia is and is not. Who else thinks Nvidia will be any where near $100 before the end of 2013? Who thinks a $12 Nvidia will add $88 in 10 months? When was the last time Nvidia added $88 in ANY YEAR EVER? Keep looking OK? That $100 nonsense will silly then and even sillier now. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360639850920</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:30:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360642010004-123</Id><Topic><Title>Good luck into earnings, longs</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360637003765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Jen can share design wins COLLECTIVELY in very general terms, or course. Vaguely. Oh so vaguely. Without too many specifics. Like what the heck they purport to have maybe won -- or not." -- ibexx. Kumbaya my Lord, kumbaya Kumbaya my Lord, kumbaya Kumbaya my Lord, kumbaya Oh Lord, kumbaya Someone's crying, Lord, kumbaya Someone's crying, Lord, kumbaya Someone's crying, Lord, kumbaya Oh Lord, kumbaya Someone's praying, Lord, kumbaya Someone's praying, Lord, kumbaya Someone's praying, Lord, kumbaya Oh Lord, kumbaya</Msg><Username>cosmic.best</Username><Timestamp>1360642010004</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:06:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360642202581-124</Id><Topic><Title>Good luck into earnings, longs</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360637003765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's already been revealed in the tech press that Project Denver will not be targeted at servers... but HPC... which is what GTC is about... "Maybe that's why they have gone Radio Silent!" Blackout period before earnings...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360642202581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:10:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360642733639-125</Id><Title>GTC Is Expanding</Title><Msg>GTC is evolving and expanding. Like previous years, GTC 2013 will continue to deliver the same great content for domain scientists and researchers, but will also focus on the dramatic changes happening in computer graphics, cloud graphics, game development, and mobile computing, and how the GPU is central to innovation in all areas. GTC IS DESIGNED FOR Computational Researchers and Application Developers in HPC pursuing the latest in scientific discovery and innovation in life sciences, oil &amp; gas, defense, finance, and more. By attending GTC, you'll discover convincing content focused on best practices and trends, tools, research findings, and next generation products. Learn more. Computational Researchers and Application Developers in HPC Designers &amp; Engineering Workgroup Managers in Manufacturing virtually prototyping products using the latest 3D design, visualization and simulation tools in order to speed up their workflow. By attending GTC, you'll discover a broad perspective of all the latest design techniques and tools available. Learn more. Designers &amp; Engineering Workgroup Managers in Manufacturing Visual Effects Artists &amp; Independent Creatives in the Media &amp; Entertainment Industry creating video, animations, 3D, and motion graphics content. By attending GTC, you'll discover how GPU technology helps speed production times and helps produce state-of-the-art effects. Learn more. Visual Effects Artists &amp; Independent Creatives in the Media &amp; Entertainment Industry Cloud Developers, Enterprise CIOs, and Data Center Management moving to a cloud-based virtualized computing infrastructure or developing new SaaS offerings. By attending GTC, you'll discover perspectives on the best interactive desktop experiences only enabled by GPUs, and visibility into the future of cloud graphics. Learn more. Cloud Developers, Enterprise CIOs, and Data Center Management Game and App Developers in Mobile Computing needing to stay up-to-date on the latest development tools and techniques, technology roadmaps, and ROI business trends. By attending GTC, you'll gain a valuable perspective into the convergence of mobile across verticals, and discover accelerated mobile application and game development techniques for faster time-to-market cycles. Learn more. Game and App Developers in Mobile Computing PC &amp; Console Game Developers creating next generation games in a highly competitive market place. By attending GTC, you'll discover world-class content showcasing state-of-the-art development techniques and tools. Learn more. PC &amp; Console Game Developers Startups and Investors interested in promoting and discovering promising companies developing disruptive technologies revolutionizing the computer industry. By attending GTC's Emerging Companies Summit, you'll watch CEO presentations, see amazing product demos, and have valuable opportunities for networking among companies, investors, key decision makers, and leading consumer, business, and trade press. Learn more. ______________________________________________________________________ 1/3rd is on Gaming....Back to the Future</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360642733639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:18:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360643032250-126</Id><Topic><Title>GTC Is Expanding</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360642733639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:18:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually it looks like about half the conference is on Gaming. Ties well with reports of $1000.00 Single GPU Gamer Cards. Remember the 8800 Ultra at $850 in 2007 when the stock hit $36. Nvidia Grid on Amazon Web Services. Could happen...Wouldn't it be nice to the CNBC Fast Money Clowns talking about Nvidia as the "Netflix of Gaming" Who will be the first in the Tech Press to write about it?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360643032250</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:23:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360643572515-127</Id><Topic><Title>Good luck into earnings, longs</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360637003765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh you forgot to add a couple of Chromebooks here and there a couple of $125 T4 game consoles here and there a couple of new Grid Server wins a couple of new 10K nodes HPC wins ....... abd nore</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1360643572515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:32:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360644185551-128</Id><Topic><Title>Good luck into earnings, longs</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360637003765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>j7777kxx, You must feel really tough hiding behind a screen name, don't you? :)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360644185551</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:43:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360644185565-129</Id><Topic><Title>Good luck into earnings, longs</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360637003765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't see that at all. This earnings call is at about the same point in the earnings season it has always been. And if they were going to miss, they have usually given an early warning or adjustment to their projected earnings two to four weeks beforehand.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1360644185565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:43:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360644490329-130</Id><Topic><Title>Good luck into earnings, longs</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360637003765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not talking about when is the earnings call... but when they announced the earnings call... history tells me they truly didn't know... so delayed that till the last possible moment...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360644490329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:48:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360644579418-131</Id><Topic><Title>Good luck into earnings, longs</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360637003765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Master? Maybe Jen could refer to those Tegra #4 wins as being "innumerable and uncounted." You know, appropriately vague -- without too many specifics. And the CFA's with the folding hatchets will be rolling in the aisles!</Msg><Username>best.clone185</Username><Timestamp>1360644579418</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:49:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>