<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-13"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365828292436-1</Id><Title>Who is killing the PC? Blame the cloud,,</Title><Msg>Interesting read... zdnetDOTcom/whos-killing-the-pc-blame-the-cloud-7000013954/</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365828292436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:44:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365829003475-2</Id><Title>EETimes: TSMC to start FinFET in 2013 (crucial for NVIDIA Parker SoC)</Title><Msg>4/11/2013 8:18 AM EDT SAN JOSE, Calif. – Facing heated competition from Globalfoundries and Samsung, TSMC pulled in plans for initial production of its 16-nm FinFET process to the end of 2013. In addition, it hopes to adopt extreme ultraviolet lithography to make 10-nm chips starting in late 2015 but is still researching e-beam as an alternative. Company executives detailed the new processes and how they aim to get there at an annual symposium here. They also provided an update on their work on 3-D chip stacks and their ongoing ramp of today’s 28-nm process node. “It looks like we have another 7 to 8 years ahead in advances -- maybe more -- we can see in technology down to 10 and even 7 nm,” said Morris Chang, founder and chief executive of TSMC, speaking to a small group of press after a keynote here. “Moore’s Law is going to go on and we will be there -- if anyone pursues it, we will pursue it,” he told an audience of several hundred chip designers. Chang, a veteran of more than 50 years in semiconductors, forecasts four percent growth for the industry this year. “Fabless companies probably can enjoy nine percent growth this year, and we are also optimistic about ourselves -- we expect growth in the teens,” he said. He said TSMC will spend more than $9 billion in capex in 2013. That’s up from $2 billion in 2009.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365829003475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:56:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365863270643-3</Id><Title>so what has changed in the business?</Title><Msg>absolutely nothing - nvda targeted the high end market dominated by two guys who roll their own. It's either one Nexus tablet one an app processor supplier rotation basis or nothing. Guys like Toshiba, or even Asus Transformer, mean absolutely nothing because the volume invs olved is nothing. Tegra is a failure today as it was 2 day ago. The PC market is still in a decline as 2 day ago. Using cash on hand to prop up the stock price is exactly that and that only. Does absolutely nothing for the biz. Only thing this move tells you: the business is not going to turn and grow any time soon, otherwise they would not be making this move. Best case study: aapl hording so much cash when the biz was growing fast. They didn't have to think about propping up the stock price with that cash did they? And now when the stock price is moving down, suddenly there's talk on the cash pile.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1365863270643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 10:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365866620189-4</Id><Topic><Title>EETimes: TSMC to start FinFET in 2013 (crucial for NVIDIA Parker SoC)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365829003475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:56:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what it means is that Intel will never lose in mobile. Either intel pushes x86 into mobile, or else intel can use its processing advantage to play king maker to fab ARM. I doubt they will just play ARM foundry. More likely, it they see they will never be able to push x86 into mobile, intel will merge with either qcom or brcm who have something to bring to the party AND also a seasoned CEO who has success in building a strategy. Unlike Jen who is still trying to push into high end merchant ARM, a non-existing market. wow, an intel/qcom or intel/brcm will be a tank that will run over everybody.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1365866620189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365866684122-5</Id><Topic><Title>EETimes: TSMC to start FinFET in 2013 (crucial for NVIDIA Parker SoC)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365829003475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:56:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>an intel/qcom will make more sense - two 'monopolies' under one roof, high margins, what else to not like.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1365866684122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:24:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365868343239-6</Id><Topic><Title>so what has changed in the business?</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1365863270643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 10:27:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You probably would have said the same about ARM in the early days when Intel and AMD were the dominate force.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1365868343239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365868829348-7</Id><Topic><Title>EETimes: TSMC to start FinFET in 2013 (crucial for NVIDIA Parker SoC)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365829003475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:56:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That combo would still have an inferior graphics solution to Nvidia. I still would like the chances of Nvidia in having more desirable features, along with the only soft-modem solution that has a smaller die size, consumes lower power and offers greater implementation flexibility compared to competing LTE modems.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1365868829348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 12:00:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365869064121-8</Id><Topic><Title>EETimes: TSMC to start FinFET in 2013 (crucial for NVIDIA Parker SoC)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365829003475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:56:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An whosunw/xc3155 combo will make more sense - two idiots under one roof, high level of stupidity and dishonesty, what else to not like.... BTW, are you two employed by the same hedge fund?</Msg><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1365869064121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 12:04:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365870059897-9</Id><Title>Any rumor who will roll out gadgets w/ T4i this summer</Title><Msg>Silicon production up by 2 Qs - there must a demand for it to come to decision? Amazon?</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1365870059897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 12:20:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365872074946-10</Id><Topic><Title>EETimes: TSMC to start FinFET in 2013 (crucial for NVIDIA Parker SoC)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365829003475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:56:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tomasmann, good to hear from you again. You should post more often. It seems like the idiot patrol is getting increasingly desperate, and even more stupid these days. Did you get a chance to view the 4/11 analyst presentation?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1365872074946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 12:54:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365873232327-11</Id><Topic><Title>Selling your Shares to Nvidia at $12s would be seling for a LOSS for most PUMPERS on this board</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1365780728482</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 11:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good thing many of us didn't buy at $16.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1365873232327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:13:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365873424289-12</Id><Topic><Title>It's above 13, sell while you can...</Title><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1365782324544</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 11:58:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And we should listen to somebody who can't spell and?</Msg><Username>dyk742000</Username><Timestamp>1365873424289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:17:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365875815693-13</Id><Title>Apple should buy nvidia</Title><Msg>I think I would be a great idea for apple especially. An iTV with a processor powerful enough to compete with computer/console gaming. It could possibly put Samsung in a tougher position with apple as well. Thoughts?</Msg><Username>njrocker26</Username><Timestamp>1365875815693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:56:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365877214684-14</Id><Topic><Title>Any rumor who will roll out gadgets w/ T4i this summer</Title><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1365870059897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 12:20:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about apple? When showing off Logan against the ipad he said he would like to help them with better graphics.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1365877214684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:20:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365877695403-15</Id><Topic><Title>$800 million share buyback</Title><Username>salemthecat100</Username><Timestamp>1365796740007</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 15:59:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Jen says this year does he mean Calendar or Fiscal? Wouldn't that be something?</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1365877695403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:28:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365878199883-16</Id><Topic><Title>Any rumor who will roll out gadgets w/ T4i this summer</Title><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1365870059897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 12:20:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>T4i - NOT at ATT - certification just take too long - just need to go through with it like a bowel movement - it just need to go through the process and come out at the other end :) Hopefully other carriers are a lot quicker US or internationally. That's the only hope of T4i going into production in Q3. ATT stuff at best would go into production late Q4 towards the end of the certification process. Perhaps internationally they can release it into non LTE markets.</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1365878199883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:36:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365878882049-17</Id><Topic><Title>Apple should buy nvidia</Title><Username>njrocker26</Username><Timestamp>1365875815693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:56:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple is penny penny wise POUNDS and POUNDS foolish! They rather have little PO$ patents like slide to ON rather own the patents for say Gorilla Glass or the IGZO LCD technology where they can literally KILL Samsung! You know why ... because PO$ patents like Slide to ON cost nothing! Gorilla Glass or IGZO cost Billions! They would rather spend $278m for PA Semi for a one trick pony than NVDA which would cost $BB. Got it? Suits JH fine - they can license GPUs as JH suggested.</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1365878882049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:48:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365884972935-18</Id><Topic><Title>Apple should buy nvidia</Title><Username>njrocker26</Username><Timestamp>1365875815693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:56:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As I mentioned before, as future generations become more advanced with more desirable features, and since Samsung is now out-innovating Apple, they will be very compelled to consider custom Tegra versions. This will probably happen around the time Apple switches all production from Samsung to TMSC.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1365884972935</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:29:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365891951528-19</Id><Topic><Title>Apple should buy nvidia</Title><Username>njrocker26</Username><Timestamp>1365875815693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:56:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NVDA powered the first iTV for apple. Apple makes an offer for NVDA and you get what, 60% premium? NVDA continues on the path they're on and you may see a 600% premium, or more. Patience is the ally of the investor. Looking for a quick buck? Keep wishing and holding your breath.</Msg><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1365891951528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:25:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365892267509-20</Id><Topic><Title>so what has changed in the business?</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1365863270643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 10:27:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>perception</Msg><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1365892267509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:31:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365896244019-21</Id><Topic><Title>Apple should buy nvidia</Title><Username>njrocker26</Username><Timestamp>1365875815693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:56:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One can only hope they wake up quickly and utilize people like NVDA to get it done better and quicker, for the sake of American Jobs! Samsung is out innovating them eventually through fundamental patents and technology - Apple need to do it not just through the "soft" patents but also through fundamental technology and own it - these kinds of patents can be a huge barrier - there are a million ways around a soft patent - not so for a fundamental technology and working around it can be very expensive. If you look at A5, A6 etc - hardly any originality in there - BIG Licensed GPUS! What's so innovative about that?</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1365896244019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 19:37:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365898024741-22</Id><Topic><Title>Apple should buy nvidia</Title><Username>njrocker26</Username><Timestamp>1365875815693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:56:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Up to now the A5, &amp; 6 have been good enough. It will be interesting to see to what extent Apple can develop future chips after the support and engineering is cut-off from Samsung? With Apple wanting to expand more into gaming it makes more sense to work with Nvidia to do battle with their mutual enemy. As chips advance Apple's engineering would be more effective if it worked alongside Nvidia which is 25 miles down the road. Perhaps Apple is developing their own console?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1365898024741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 20:07:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365905404166-23</Id><Topic><Title>Apple should buy nvidia</Title><Username>njrocker26</Username><Timestamp>1365875815693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:56:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As long as Tim Cook is at the helm, it would be a bad idea for NVIDIA to be acquired or merged with Apple. I wouldn't want to see it happen.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365905404166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 22:10:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365906502937-24</Id><Title>Samsung could buy Nvidia. If not some Chinese</Title><Msg>company that needs graphics, could buy Nvidia.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1365906502937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 22:28:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365907934811-25</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung could buy Nvidia. If not some Chinese</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1365906502937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 22:28:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAM</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1365907934811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 22:52:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365908063332-26</Id><Topic><Title>Apple should buy nvidia</Title><Username>njrocker26</Username><Timestamp>1365875815693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:56:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>25 Miles down the road - you must be Nu Jeursy. It's barely 5 miles!</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1365908063332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 22:54:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365908733890-27</Id><Title>loss of nexus overblown</Title><Msg>Google just started selling the 7 with tegra in India. Where else will they still sell it.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1365908733890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 23:05:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365909922368-28</Id><Topic><Title>Apple should buy nvidia</Title><Username>njrocker26</Username><Timestamp>1365875815693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:56:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google is known - has been known all this time - that it wants to rotate among component suppliers as well as mobile manufacturers. This would best serve their interest of expanding the presence of Android in the mobile world. El Goog would probably never want to stick with the same partner for the same line of products if it could help it. Those who assumed that NVIDIA would automatically get the N7 next gen-slot regardless of product cycles considerations are plain NAIVE about the competitive environment NV is in. It wasn't a disappointment for me at all because I never expected it.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365909922368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 23:25:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365911149059-29</Id><Topic><Title>Apple should buy nvidia</Title><Username>njrocker26</Username><Timestamp>1365875815693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:56:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The previous post was intended as a response to the thread "Nexus loss is overblown" Sorry about the mix-up. The new Yahoo format is really messy. They should send their SW staff to study information architecture first ..... the new Y message boards truly leave much to be desired. Dear Madame CEO, I mean Marisa Mayer, I sincerely hope that someone will bring the users feedback to your attention. Thank you in advance for any improvement.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365911149059</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 23:45:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>