<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-22"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366610999405-1</Id><Title>Forbes: Is Apple looking for a replacement for CEO Cook? (Yes....big investors want him out!</Title><Msg>forbesDOTcom/sites/genemarcial/2013/04/21/is-apple-looking-for-a-replacement-for-ceo-cook/</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366610999405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:09:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366611253827-2</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Is Apple looking for a replacement for CEO Cook? (Yes....big investors want him out!</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366610999405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's hope that Apple board doesn't make Jen Hsun an offer that he can't refuse.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366611253827</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:14:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366612816579-3</Id><Title>Problem with Project Grid</Title><Msg>Yes, latency for industry has improved, but is it enough ? During Jens presentation, grid seems to be working fine when playing graphics intensive games. Problem is during presentations, the grid servers is placed very near the player and the consoles. Hence low latency. But in real life, the servers will be far. Once this can be solved convincingly, Nvidia will be the Netflix. Else, its all hyped again.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366612816579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:40:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366613796881-4</Id><Topic><Title>Problem with Project Grid</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366612816579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:40:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If this post doesn't make it clear how stupid you are to everyone, including the gang of bashers keeping you company this weekend, then nothing will . . how old are you anyways? Man, you are dumb.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366613796881</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:56:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366615402799-5</Id><Topic><Title>Problem with Project Grid</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366612816579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:40:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huh? Who's the stupid one again? Why u just rant rant rant crying father crying mother .....with zero arguments based on facts. I named facts during my arguments. I wish Nvidia really solved latency problems totally, however its really difficult. U know why? In urban cities there are lots of buildings. And how can data transmit so fast through it? Do u surf internet dude? Currently loading pages already has some delays at times, playing games? The answer is common sense. Look, another common sensical answer to Nvidia $1b spending is obvious. U think if their business is growing well, they will give out this $1b? They have been so reluctant to do this. Once they announced the leaving of tegra chief, followed by nil consoles win, then weak tegra 4, then a sudden project shield, and finally this $1b, I know it is in trouble. Trying to play magiC. Keep coming out with new tricks.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366615402799</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 03:23:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366630985849-6</Id><Topic><Title>Problem with Project Grid</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366612816579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:40:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes latency will be a priority for the gaming aspects of Grid, but not for the Grid VCA or Grid enabled enterprise servers. I am curious as to how big of a latency factor you are expecting here, specially since the only data that will be transmitted over the internet will be video basically just live streaming a 1080p video. The real issue would be on the server side of things, making sure that the graphics card can render and toss the next frame back quickly enough, which I think Grid clearly accomplished</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1366630985849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 07:43:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366632652039-7</Id><Topic><Title>Problem with Project Grid</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366612816579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:40:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aside from being a total ignoramus, chrissy needs to address his severe latency problem. Perhaps he and the other bash-bots here can get a group discount for some professional help they obviously need?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1366632652039</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 08:10:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366633563331-8</Id><Topic><Title>Problem with Project Grid</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366612816579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:40:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I dun proclaim to know. The problem with graphics intensive games are such that I its not just a video steaming. In video streaming, its a one way street data transfers. In gaming, its server to gamer, gamer to server and back to gamer. Not gonna be easy. Heard of apps not running on apps store anymore, but on html pages running on internet? This sounds like great idea as developers can skip paying Apple or Google for apps. Ain't taking off big time cos webpages takes time to load. Well, at least irkbik talks fact and debate. Not like the useless Roundhouse &amp; chitownbarber, just like mad dog barking senselessly with no facts, no substance. At least ibexx knows how to talk facts. Or at least have class to ignore negative comments and bashers. Show some class like ibexx, stop being like mad dog, roundhouse and chitownbarber!!</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366633563331</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 08:26:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366634355745-9</Id><Topic><Title>Problem with Project Grid</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366612816579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:40:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think lrkbik4 didn't realized to what extent of an imbecile you are. What does the word "dun" mean that you used at the start of your last post? Perhaps it's some kind of slang used in trailer parks?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1366634355745</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 08:39:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366634710955-10</Id><Topic><Title>Problem with Project Grid</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366612816579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:40:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Useless guy, dun know social media's short messages. Must be too grandpa to decipher.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366634710955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 08:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366635754976-11</Id><Topic><Title>Problem with Project Grid</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366612816579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:40:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there is another problem with alll server side processing - the bandwidth required must be something else to behold. I hate to have to pay the monthly bill on that internet account. min 10G to 20G of data per day X 30 days ..... your ISP loves yar.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1366635754976</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:02:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366644218882-12</Id><Topic><Title>Yes Ladies and Gentlemen, It's Up To Project Shield</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1366512499822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:48:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much did you lose betting on that Nvidia dog? lol</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366644218882</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:23:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366644632131-13</Id><Topic><Title>"Nvidia scores sole Tegra 4 design win, courtesy of ZTE"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366410986010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:36:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not even the rags are counting project SHIELD as a design win. lol Because project SHIELD is a joke. Tegra 4 is DOA. When the largest customer accounting for 60% of Tgera 3 sales walks away from Tegra, the entire Tegra line is DOA. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366644632131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:30:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366645014213-14</Id><Title>Losing Google's Nexus tablet was the NAI LIN THE COFFIN for Tegra</Title><Msg>Tegra 4, 5 or Whatever is DOA. Nvidia could NOT afford to lose its LARGEST Tegra customer and then make noise about NOT wanting to sell Sony or anyone else parts. Tegra will quietly go away. QCOM has WON the ARM SoC battle for THOSE OEMs NOT SELLING THEIR OWN ARM SoC. There is no market for Tegra imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366645014213</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:36:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366645145803-15</Id><Topic><Title>"Google's next Nexus 7 tablet will shun Nvidia in favour of Qualcomm"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1365008441897</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 13:00:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"HARDWARE DESIGNER Google is working on a sequel to its Google Nexus 7 tablet, which won't have an Nvidia Tegra 3 chip but rather a Qualcomm processor." This NEWS marks the end of the Tegra line. QCOM is the winner. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366645145803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:39:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366645803723-16</Id><Topic><Title>Yes Ladies and Gentlemen, It's Up To Project Shield</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1366512499822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:48:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well isn't this special, we have most of the mentally challenged bashers discussing Project Shield. Do you losers live in the same trailer park?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1366645803723</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:50:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366647373789-17</Id><Topic><Title>Yes Ladies and Gentlemen, It's Up To Project Shield</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1366512499822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:48:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's very hard to keep 35 Senior Vice Presidents satisfied." Does that include the SVP talking head in charge of claiming Nvidia does NOT want to sell Sony 64 bit CPU+GPU parts because it would cost to much, since Nvidia DOES NOT HAVE A 64 bit CPU? lmao That SVP is worth every penny in laughs. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366647373789</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:16:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366648028873-18</Id><Title>How will Nvidia replace the one customer accounting for 60% of Tegra 3 sales?</Title><Msg>Nvidia won't replace Google. Nvidia will NOT find another customer to take 60% of Tegra chips again. When Google took its Nexus business to QCOM the Tegra line was sentenced to a slow death. Other OEMs are asking themselves now, why didn't Google want Tegra 4? Google is a leader and Google is leading the ARM SoC parade to QCOM. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366648028873</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366648758605-19</Id><Topic><Title>How will Nvidia replace the one customer accounting for 60% of Tegra 3 sales?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366648028873</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:27:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Other OEMs are asking themselves now, why didn't Google want Tegra 4?" They could be, but they will just sample the chip for themselves. "Nvidia will NOT find another customer to take 60% of Tegra chips again." Very likely, but they could find 3 customers to account for 20% of Tegra chips each, or 4 for 15% etc.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1366648758605</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:39:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366650226213-20</Id><Title>What's up with this PPS action, kvimax1?</Title><Msg>The lack of follow-through is a bit discouraging, no?</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1366650226213</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:03:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366651240402-21</Id><Topic><Title>What's up with this PPS action, kvimax1?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1366650226213</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:03:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mslans....I'm not sure. The volume disappeared, again, which is quite surprising to me. I appears we'll likely have to wait until the next news catalyst of some sort, or possibly earnings. Unless we see volume consistently over 10mm shares, none of the action is significant. M</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366651240402</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:20:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366652072089-22</Id><Topic><Title>Problem with Project Grid</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366612816579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:40:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Facts :)? Please, every time you post it's getting more entertaining. Again, look at yourself in the mirror. No ranting from anything I post. There's no need to list any facts since your comments are so silly, no one thinks it's needed to discredit your posts. Notice any of the other long-term investors who regularly post factually based data and articles aren't replying to you? That's because they put you on ignore. When you get a job and leave your parents' house and live on your own, then you can start learning about the facts I think . . good luck as you entertain yourself and the bashers that are getting some company with you on the ignore list . . dude. Bye bye.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366652072089</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:34:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366654833283-23</Id><Topic><Title>How's that paint drying or grass growing?</Title><Username>gorunhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366653495384</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:58:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or you could have added it's like watching air slowly leak out of the tires in the mobile home you live in.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1366654833283</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 14:20:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366656242291-24</Id><Title>A busy week for earnings, especially the mobile/telco stocks - AAPL, QCOM, BRCM etc on tap</Title><Msg>--Tuesday, 4/23 Apple: Wall Street expects eps $10.07 on $42.5 billion revenues Also reporting: ARM Holdings,, ATT, Broadcom, RFMD --Wednesday, 4/24 Qualcomm, Sprint-Nextel --Thursday, 4/25 Amazon, InterDigital, Cirrus Logic (a major AAPL supplier, already pre-warned), Skyworks Solutions _____ PS: In fact, AAPL's numbers would almost seem irrelevant to its stock price, as Apple's decline is due to its falling behind in innovation - particularly bad for a growth company with high expectations.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366656242291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 14:44:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366665525387-25</Id><Topic><Title>GAWD ALMIGHTY</Title><Username>roundhose_c</Username><Timestamp>1366665291000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:14:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is there any hope you get a job and start making regular mortgage payments again on your mobile home?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1366665525387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:18:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366670005355-26</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Is Apple looking for a replacement for CEO Cook? (Yes....big investors want him out!</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366610999405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Basically. this can be viewed as an attempted CHECKMATE on Tim Cook. At the earnings cc tomorrow, Apple may be forced to declare one or all of the following to stabilize stock price: -- A special one-time (and hefty) dividend --increased (regular) dividend --accelerated stock buy-back Interesting to see how it will play out....there are really no fast fix for Apple's dilemma as innovation takes time. Tim Cook is a manager, not a leader. That is the peril of a mega-sized, high-profile company who put an operations manager in charge.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366670005355</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 18:33:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366671172110-27</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Is Apple looking for a replacement for CEO Cook? (Yes....big investors want him out!</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366610999405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wouldn't you think the only way Jen would go to Apple is if Nvidia being bought by Apple would be part of the deal?</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366671172110</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 18:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366673778966-28</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Is Apple looking for a replacement for CEO Cook? (Yes....big investors want him out!</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366610999405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Roundhouse, mine may be a minority opinion compared with others on this board, but I will offer it regardless. I think it would be bad news if Jen went to Apple as TC's replacement, even as a related event, Apple acquired NVDA. My long-term understanding is that the ultimate dream of JH/NVIDIA will be to revolutionize the tech world with visual computing. Ideally; they will clearly be aiming at the universal adoption of their GPGPU technologies by all major vendors, OS publishers and HW designers. A lock-in with one company - even Apple - would be in serious conflict with this ideal. Sure, Apple's resources and gigantic marketing presence would be tempting, but I am not sure if an offer did come JH's way (unlikely to begin with) he would definitely say yes. He hasn't struck me as the kind of leader who places $$$ and power above all.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366673778966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 19:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366674087350-29</Id><Title>Qualcomm founder Irwin Jacobs gives $133 million to Cornell's Technical Campus to be located in New York City</Title><Msg>As a New Yorker, thank you Irvin! SOURCE: Bloomberg just in bloombergDOTcom/news/2013-04-22/qualcomm-s-jacobs-gives-133-million-for-cornell-s-tech-campus.html</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366674087350</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 19:41:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366675180897-30</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Is Apple looking for a replacement for CEO Cook? (Yes....big investors want him out!</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366610999405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Although the future looks as promising than ever for Nvidia, but the old phrase of "what have you done lately" comes into play as the Apple board will surly be looking at if they are looking for a replacement? Jobs left enough direction before he died. In the next couple years Jen needs to execute on the vision that he started before he gets any kind of respect from the tech world and Wall street.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1366675180897</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 19:59:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366676341398-31</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Is Apple looking for a replacement for CEO Cook? (Yes....big investors want him out!</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366610999405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2 points: 1. Jobs did not leave a playbook that would last for years. According to pundits as well as what Apple has offered in the last 12 months, the script is just about to be played out except for the TV part. Just to make devices thinner and lighter is NOT innovation, nor any of the rumor gimmicky stuff like watch or other wrap-around devices. 2. NVIDIA is a new comer enbarking on a field that has been dominated by Qualcomm for more than 25 years. Anyone claiming NV isn't executing is out of his/her mind - pardon the strong language - I hear many expert reports (linley, for example) saying that it is AMAZING what NV has accomplished in 2 or 3 years. I owned both QC and BRCM years ago, and I knew what snails paces they were crawling along.....and they were the pioneers with no pressure from competition. Anyone having no confidence or respect for NVIDIA should not own the stock. As to WS - they are a fickle bunch. Do you remember that as recent as six months ago that 90% of WS analysts had BUY ratings on AAPL? THOU SHALT NOT INVEST BY WS SELL_SIDE ANALS!</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366676341398</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:19:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366677040064-32</Id><Title>Nvidia must grow fast, Intel cash running out</Title><Msg>I think Intel cash royalties is running out like in 2 years time. Nvidia wasted last 3 years having it shares price dropping. Now market will be more demanding to see good growth for Nvidia since revenue profits and cash in dropping in 2 years. Spending $1 b on buybacks ain't enough. Lat 2 years Nvidia tegra looked so promising. First to launch quad core. But yet, mediatek kicked Nvidia to the curb big time. I recalled posting about mediatek months ago. Permabulls commented that I should wait for tegra 4, that it is a game changer. Bashers disagreed, and said tegra is a waste. I believed in bulls then. Now that tegra 4 is out. Omg, its really a waste. And hearing Jen talked again about the future. Tegra 4i, tegra 5. ! F him man. Enough is enough. Heard of promises from kids? Daddy daddy, I promise my next semester will show better results, teacher teacher I promised to be a good student next time. After many promises, all just listen and lose faith. No longertrust the words. TThat's right, this is what's happening to Nvidia. Jen, he should be an Oscar actor, not CEO.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366677040064</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:30:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366677819230-33</Id><Title>Seeking Alpha article on NVIIDA - not by those two</Title><Msg>known to this board. Thus, I am willing to give it the benefit of a doubt. :) seekingalphaDOTcom/article/1359811-reevaluating-nvidia-amidst-stock-stagnation?source=google_news</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366677819230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366678068756-34</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Is Apple looking for a replacement for CEO Cook? (Yes....big investors want him out!</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366610999405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think the TV will not play-out very well since the music content that was done with the iPad is being reported as being in very distant negotiations with the video content owners/providers who are a bit apprehensive about Apple disrupting things. The watch is a gimmicky item that will appeal to current Apple users, and not something as a must have item. I agree with you that Nvidia has come a long way. Unfortunately Wall street is taking a wait and see posture.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1366678068756</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:47:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366678194050-35</Id><Title>Seeking Alpha And Motley Fools are as good as forumers</Title><Msg>Honestly, people who follow their posts know they are just paid editors to get eyeball to their websites. Their forecasts are hardly accurate. Seeking alpha have bulls and bears on Nvidia. If u listen to the bulls , u would have lost big bucks last few years. That's right, seeking alpha. Always seeking, just seek, never delivering.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366678194050</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:49:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366678384824-36</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia must grow fast, Intel cash running out</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366677040064</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You thought wrong once again. Haven't you learned by now to look-up things before you spout your blather?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1366678384824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:53:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366678495370-37</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Is Apple looking for a replacement for CEO Cook? (Yes....big investors want him out!</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366610999405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big money sez: "Show me the money!" and they should. Small investors can afford a little time wasted, get there and wait awhile....fat cats don't have this luxury; their money has to work every minute of it just because of its size.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366678495370</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:54:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366679122320-38</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia must grow fast, Intel cash running out</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366677040064</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5 instalment from Jan 2011. Do the counting . Chitown, u mentioned in one post Nvidias looks as promising as ever . Omg, haven't u got it, just only promising. Always remember, investing 101, check against what management says and examine if they deliver. Beware of over promises and underdelivery. Eh, project Denver, no updates at all. Delivery incompetency . Nvidia should be a markting company instead.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366679122320</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 21:05:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366680007762-39</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Is Apple looking for a replacement for CEO Cook? (Yes....big investors want him out!</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366610999405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jensen has more money than he and his family could spend in several lifetimes. Years ago the company use to talk about "Crush" I finally asked at a stockholders meeting i attended as to what they meant by "Crush", the answer was to crush Intel. I believe that's where Jensen hart is. Kvimax, he's been around probably as long as I, he can probably attest to this.</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1366680007762</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 21:20:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366680476488-40</Id><Topic><Title>How will Nvidia replace the one customer accounting for 60% of Tegra 3 sales?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366648028873</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:27:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Very likely, but they could find 3 customers to account for 20% of Tegra chips each, or 4 for 15% etc." But Nvidia hasn't found a Google replacement yet have they? When Google walked 60% of Tegra sales went out the door. Tegra 4 is DOA. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366680476488</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 21:27:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366681351347-41</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Is Apple looking for a replacement for CEO Cook? (Yes....big investors want him out!</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366610999405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The guy to ask is the GraphicBast*rd, he knows who I am talking about, he post here occasionally!</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1366681351347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 21:42:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366684076520-42</Id><Topic><Title>Stop listenimg to the lies that tegra is great.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366512549020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Well, that's not a fact, you just made that up. Google repeatedly changes vendors on their products " Can you read? Pull your head out of the sand. Tegra was given its walking papers over at Google for a while now. Google "Nvidia OUT", "QCOM IN the NEW Nexus" and come up with a new line of BS. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366684076520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 22:27:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366684586772-43</Id><Title>Who would hire the clown who took Nvidia from $26 to $12 to run Apple? lol</Title><Msg>Pull your head out of your rear Nvidia fans. Nvidia's shareholders have had enouigh of Jen and his BS. What on earth would a $372 Billion outfit need with a clown who took mickey mouse Nvidia from $26 to $12. $26 to $12 says Jen is a Joke. Google going with QCOM says Tegra is a Joke. Jen is LUCKY to STILL have a job. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366684586772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 22:36:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366684643695-44</Id><Title>PWER is up 57% - Solar is a comeback story</Title><Msg>I said so!! Eyeing on WFR and SPWR - only US companies. Chinese solar companies are folding up. Chinese government has too much burden dealing with the real estate that can rupture with any minor misstep - If you missed watching 60-Minutes a couple months ago - just search for "China ghost town". Do your DD! I'm not a pro analyst. Cheers!</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1366684643695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 22:37:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366684837488-45</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Is Apple looking for a replacement for CEO Cook? (Yes....big investors want him out!</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366610999405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel officially still owes a lot of money to Nvidia from suit. Am I wrong? Tim Cook is managing Apple as best he can. He's simply taking care of business. Nvidia's clean extraordinary patents are worthy of consideration. Nvidia has 4i for example. Nothing on the planet quite like it. Unfortunately, presently worthless in Wall Street's perception. Wall Street HATES uncertainty and cannot even perceive any future for Nvidia; yet, Mr. Jen Hsun's Nvidia still keeps tantilizing this world with unbeknown with already astonishing advances. Wait and see.</Msg><Username>audiogenx</Username><Timestamp>1366684837488</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 22:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366684889682-46</Id><Title>$12.59 says anyone who paid OVER $16 will be here EVERYDAY posting LUV notes to Nvidia</Title><Msg>And bashing every company eating Nvidia lunch. WAS $26 but is $12.59 TODAY. Is it sinking in yet. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366684889682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 22:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366685892540-47</Id><Title>What happen to all the SHIELD NOISE?</Title><Msg>After Nvidia was PASSED OVER by EVERY Game Console OEM known to man all the talk was about a SHIELD toy right? Where is that SHIELD toy at that will save Nvidia? Nvidia should build 50 Million SHIELD toys with shareholder money and stock pile them for the Apple size crowds that will line up over night to own a new SHIELD toy. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366685892540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 22:58:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366687542376-48</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Is Apple looking for a replacement for CEO Cook? (Yes....big investors want him out!</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366610999405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WS analyst held that view for Qualcomm decades ago - they couldn't foresee what CDMA would do and how the David then (QC) could beat out the Gorilla at the time (NOK) until one day shortly before y2k - boom! QC's business strategy was validated and the stock skyrocketed from under $100 to almost $1000 within months. My point is that WS would change its perception on a dime. (Yes, they need to see $$$ on the table first for the smaller challenger; a different standard is used for incumbents....</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366687542376</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:25:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366687633030-49</Id><Topic><Title>What happen to all the SHIELD NOISE?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366685892540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 22:58:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia is #$%$ with owners like Microsoft, that flops it rt. Fed up with owners like Google that changes suppliers. So they decided to be owners. By doing what? By innovating what? A gaming console call shield? Now they offend Sony and Nintendo. Jen &amp; co is losing it already. They are out of their mind. Can't deliver growth and hence trying all funny tricks. Innovation is good, plus please innovate something that works well and customers clamour for!</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366687633030</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:27:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366688025571-50</Id><Topic><Title>What happen to all the SHIELD NOISE?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366685892540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 22:58:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Innovation is good but please innovate something that works well and customers clamour for. Oh, my typing have lots of mistakes right? Cos I am using HTC one x. The one running on tegra that isslow and ununresponsive! Can't wait til contract is over.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366688025571</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366688122207-51</Id><Topic><Title>Seeking Alpha article on NVIIDA - not by those two</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366677819230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:43:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ibexx, c'mon. I looked at this article and it's fine, but it's also by a newbie to SA. I think you have a bad attitude towards at least one of the other authors that you hint at here, and it really isn't justified. That author is better informed than many on this board who are long-term investors and easily is one of the better on SA. I'm not a big fan of SA either but you seem to make some odd decisions on who is okay and who is not . . imo.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366688122207</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:35:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366689305390-52</Id><Topic><Title>Who would hire the clown who took Nvidia from $26 to $12 to run Apple? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366684586772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 22:36:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jensen was an engineer at amd, now can affrod to buy amd, what have you done?</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1366689305390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:55:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366689360215-53</Id><Topic><Title>Seeking Alpha article on NVIIDA - not by those two</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366677819230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:43:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get off your high horse, roundhouse! Did I endorse the article? - I just posted it so other SA fans can read and compare! Ok, grandpa, you can stop being a Board Police and take your nagging elsewhere.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366689360215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:56:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366689430234-54</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Is Apple looking for a replacement for CEO Cook? (Yes....big investors want him out!</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366610999405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Impossible - as in a Cheapskate negotiating at Tiffany's!</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1366689430234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:57:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>