<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373603732146-1</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 2 with S4 Pro heading to trouble</Title><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373569421806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ditto for me. I own a N7 from the first month a year ago, and have no plans to upgrade to the next gen. No meaningful advantages to me.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373603732146</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 00:35:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373609730879-2</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Leads the NYSE with a DOUBLE TRIPLE? UP 11.8% and 102M Shares</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373573566271</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 16:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good news is that Nvidia won't see a dime of that Game Console money that's driving AMD UP and they shouldn't. Nvidia should NEVER be in an Xbox or PS again after the way they bad mouthed those products. But the better news is Nvidia fans who spend their days bashing AMD didn't see a dime of that 11.8% on Thurs or 85% YTD and they shouldn't. HEADCASES get to continue posting BS and patting each other on thet back for being CLUELESS. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373609730879</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 02:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373610471260-3</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia kicked OUT of Xbox, OUT of PS, OUT of MacBook AIr, OUT of Mac Pro, OUT of Nexus 7.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371386665544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:44:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They started bashing Google and the Next Next 7 as soon as they stop denying Qualcomm WON the Next Nexus 7. lol Anyone who uses or sells a chip NOT from Nvidia is a bash target on this message board. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373610471260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 02:27:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373611596844-4</Id><Title>Qualcomm WINS the Next Nexus 7 DENIAL is over and the Google Bashing begins. lol</Title><Msg>Look at Nvidia fans bashing Google and the Next Nexus 7 even though the Next Nexus 7 includes many IMPROVEMENTS over the old Nexus 7. "The latest talk of the specs brings mention of an LCD display with a resolution of 1920 x 1200 along with a 1.5GHz Snapdragon S4 Pro (APQ8064) processor. This new Nexus 7 is also expected to include LTE support. Some of the other specs look to include a 3,950 mAh battery, 1.2 megapixel front-facing camera, 5 megapixel rear-facing camera, 2GB of RAM and storage options of 16GB and 32GB." source: androidcommunity Did the OLD Nexus 7 have an HD Display and LTE ? But the biggest improvement has got to be a Snapdragon S4 Pro replacing an outdated Tegra 3, wouldn't you agree Nbidia fans? lol IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373611596844</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 02:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373611863833-5</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia HEADCASE bashes Every Company that Sells a Chip other than Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373494909753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 18:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look likes we can add Google to the list of companies bashed on the Nvidia board now. As soon as the DENIAL ended that Google dumped Tegra for a Qiualcomm part the Google bashing began. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373611863833</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 02:51:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373657280324-6</Id><Title>The Motley Fool's latest PUMP , mover over loser AMRC...lol</Title><Msg>Tom and David the lates Internet Snake Oil Salesman via the prescription model? Beoow is the latest hoax, pump, fleecing or GIFT of the Gardner Brothers'? AMRC was the only energy compnay you will need" PUMP, it isn't fairing to well. Sort of like Cramers' "SEVEN SAMURAI" OR "INTERNET TUSNAMI". Is there anyone in the financial industry who isn't a psuedo-journalist advancing his own agend and that isn't afraid to call out their sponsors who are part of the rigged game in fear of losing sponsor dollars in advertisement? Why listen to basically men and women on their meal ticket? NVIDIA might seem like an odd choice for investors looking to profit from the mobile boom. After all, of all things, its bread-and-butter product is graphics processors found in PCs. How can a company reliant on PCs be anything but a sitting duck for the coming mobile revolution? In the case of NVIDIA, it's not a sitting duck because the company saw a changing market and started adapting years before the competition. Its main competitors -- processor giants AMD and Intel -- pushed deeper and deeper into PCs in recent years. Intel sold off its mobile processing line in 2006 to focus on processors made for PCs and is finally trying to catch up by throwing billions into the market. AMD's CEO was forced to resign in 2011 after the board became dissatisfied with the company's lack of direction in mobile. Neither of NVIDIA's direct peers foresaw a shift in technology the way NVIDIA did, yet NVIDIA gets lumped into the same basket as them, beaten down whenever negative PC news hits the presses. That's a mistake that you can profit off. NVIDIA's not only is a dominant player in mobile, but it's also prospering from emerging market growth and has established itself as a central figure in high-end computers ranging from workstations to supercomputers, a lucrative offshoot of the PC era that should provide high profits for decades to come. Let's dig into in to the ways that NVIDIA is.....</Msg><Username>jforuus</Username><Timestamp>1373657280324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 15:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373657417704-7</Id><Topic><Title>The Motley Fool's latest PUMP , mover over loser AMRC...lol</Title><Username>jforuus</Username><Timestamp>1373657280324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 15:28:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please share this with others and let us collude upon the truth as they collude upon the lies!! This is why you take the pleged and pass it on to others. This will be the sign for the US Citizen to rise and bring order to a political system that is submerged with self interest groups, lobbyists, corp america and carreer politicians. I __________________ pledge the next time DOW is brought down by 50% or more, I shall show up in less then 48 hours at Washington DC wearing a white feather and surround the White House with locked arms with my fellow US Citizens of all races. To correct what should have been corrected almost a century ago. No longer will we the US Citizen allow men who elected by the US Citizen yet at every turn illustrate their allegiance to be for the primary interest of Corp-America, lobbyists and foreign institutions with the interest of the US Citizen as an auxiliary motive to be financial terrorists to this nation. This political regime which describes itself as "Republican and Democrats" we the US Citizen shall help exit in a non-violent yet immediately out of the White House and Congress since our judicial system has been handcuffed and become obsolete to address this nation's needs and the SEC can no longer certainly safeguard the future's of this great nation any longer, if ever. Non- democrat and non-Republican representatives currently serving at the local level will be elevated to newly vacated ranks Last names from A to F will be assigned 18th St. NW Last names from G to K will be assigned H St. NW Last names from L to S will be assigned 14th St. NW Last names from T to Z will assigned at Constitution Ave. NW Thereafter on the 50th hour we shall start to move non-violently but certainly marching to the White House if a formal press conference has not been held announcing the resignation of all current Republican and Democratic regime members. Please copy, paste to other (message boards) and email this to other US Citizen</Msg><Username>jforuus</Username><Timestamp>1373657417704</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 15:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373657528031-8</Id><Topic><Title>The Motley Fool's latest PUMP , mover over loser AMRC...lol</Title><Username>jforuus</Username><Timestamp>1373657280324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 15:28:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oops...SUBSCRIPTION.</Msg><Username>jforuus</Username><Timestamp>1373657528031</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 15:32:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373657679049-9</Id><Title>Best buy doesn't have any tegr4 tablets. Are the tegras delayed or what.</Title><Msg>Seems to me there should be plenty of tegras around.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1373657679049</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 15:34:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373661268808-10</Id><Title>New Dow High, Naz up 26 pts, best in 4 years and NVDA up a cent? (0.01)</Title><Msg>what a DOG.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_cc</Username><Timestamp>1373661268808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 16:34:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373670597667-11</Id><Topic><Title>New Dow High, Naz up 26 pts, best in 4 years and NVDA up a cent? (0.01)</Title><Username>roundhouse_cc</Username><Timestamp>1373661268808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 16:34:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you are a flea-gag!</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1373670597667</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 19:09:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373676310390-12</Id><Title>Processor Testing Fudged to Give Intel Advantage</Title><Msg>"many technology analysts disagree with Mielke’s findings and are questioning the benchmark standards used to justify ABI Research’s conclusion." My OH my, how the mighty have fallen. Kinda sucks to have to step in the muck, hey INTC PR team? What a fire drill they must be going through today, LOL. story on wall st cheat sheet</Msg><Username>hendar00</Username><Timestamp>1373676310390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 20:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373677580233-13</Id><Title>EETimes: ARM beats Intel in revised Antutu benchmark (newest article published July 12)</Title><Msg>Jim McGregor The AnTuTu Benchmark, a benchmarking tool for Android smartphones and tablets, has been revised following some discrepancy over whether the latest Intel Atom processor outperformed ARM-based chips from several vendors in key aspects of the benchmark. Under the revised benchmark, overall scores for the Atom Z2580 dropped by about 20 percent. As I indicated in a post on EE Times earlier this week, there appeared to be some discrepancies with the AnTuTu benchmark in relation to older versions of the benchmark and other benchmarks. (See: Has Intel Really Beaten ARM?) Technical consulting firm BDTI pointed out that the compiled code for the Intel processor was not executing all instructions that were intended for the RAM test. This artificially improved the results for the Lenovo K900 smartphone and the Intel Atom processors. The problem appears to arise from the ICC compiler introduced around version 2.9.4 of the AnTuTu benchmark and used just for the Intel processors. Code for all other processors uses a different compiler, called the GCC. To rectify the situation, AnTuTu issued revision 3.2.2 to the benchmark Wednesday evening. The revision still uses the ICC compiler, but the resulting scores are drastically different for the Intel processor. The AnTuTu CPU and overall scores dropped by approximately 20 percent, while the AnTuTu RAM score plummeted by approximately 50 percent, as shown in the figure below. All other scores for the Intel processor remain relatively the same. Similarly, scores for the Samsung S4 Oct and Qualcomm Snapdragon 600, both used in the Samsung Galaxy S4, remain relatively unchanged. (To be continued)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373677580233</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373677749120-14</Id><Topic><Title>EETimes: ARM beats Intel in revised Antutu benchmark (newest article published July 12)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373677580233</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>part 2: As a result of the revised scores, the AnTuTu benchmark is no longer an outlier from the other benchmarks and paints a competitive picture similar to the other benchmarks, with the Samsung Exynos 5 Octa processor outperforming the Intel Atom Z2580 processor (see the figure below). But, are these numbers valid? It is unclear what changes were made to revision 3.2.2 the benchmark. However, AnTuTu did indicate that new testing standards would be issued in August, presumably with the next major revision of the benchmark. At that point, it will be interesting to see the new "standards" and the resulting changes in the benchmark scores. Suddenly, the battle between smartphone processors looks much different than all the hype that was floating around because of the AnTuTu benchmark. It's clear that the ARM processors still hold a significant advantage over the Intel processors, whether you include the new AnTuTu scores or just eliminate them completely from the evaluation. The current and upcoming revisions to the AnTuTu benchmark will also drastically alter the scores of Intel's upcoming Bay Trail Atom processor. As with the Atom Z2580, many in the press prematurely proclaimed it the victor over the next-generation ARM processors. Now that also appears to be highly questionable. So, will all the sensationalistic bloggers retract their stories about Intel beating ARM? Likely not, but this definitely questions their credibility just as it does benchmarks. The moral of the story is that you have to question all benchmark data and use many data points from different sources before drawing a conclusion. It's clear that Intel still has an uphill climb to catch the ARM camp, much less surpass it. It is also clear that we need better benchmarks for mobile devices that test for platform efficiency and usage models. — Jim McGregor is founder and principal analyst at Tirias Research.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373677749120</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373685557762-15</Id><Title>Microsoft teasing 2 new Surface models for fiscal year 2014</Title><Msg>SOURCE: Tom's Hardware ""There's a good chance the next Surface Pro will be based on Intel's new "Haswell" fourth-generation Core processors given that the chips are now appearing in Windows 8-powered Ultrabooks. As for the next-generation Surface RT, last month reports surfaced (no pun intended) that Microsoft has added Qualcomm as a Surface RT supplier. Sources indicated that the Snapdragon 800 will be the chip of choice for the LTE models while Nvidia will likely supply Tegra 4 for the Wi-Fi only models."" ______ --Microsoft fiscal year starts on October 1 and ends on July 31 --I am willing to bet that the WiFi model of Surface RT 2 will sell a lot more than the LTE version.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373685557762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 23:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>