<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-15"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358226860889-1</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia - It's Time To Raise The Dividend</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358223260438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 23:14:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you try getting down on one knee and begging for that dime? Maybe they're out buying games with that money. Remember, they have to make sure EVERY GAME PLAYS as designed on that SHIELD toy right? What Is that called regression testing or playing with your money? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358226860889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 00:14:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358227272496-2</Id><Topic><Title>"Microsoft Eyes 3 New Surface Tablet Servings for 2013"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358193453852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 14:57:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"See Jen Grovel for Work -- Now with Exotic Casino Dancing Girls" But will he dance in heels too while begging for biz? Too funny. lmao</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358227272496</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 00:21:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358229094218-3</Id><Title>Will that SHIELD toy fit in your pocket or will you need a new back pack?</Title><Msg>You Nvidia fans will be the BIG MEN on campus with that SHIELD toy stuffed in your pockets right? Is everyone here planning on buying a SHIELD toy to go along with your Tegra based Android phones and Tegra based tablets? Cool stuff right? Maybe you can stuff it all in your pants pockets and impress everyone you meet. Hey, who ever thought the world needs another pocket toy over at Nvidia headquarters needs to back away from the keyboard and go outside. Enjoy your Nvidia purchase imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358229094218</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 00:51:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358230796620-4</Id><Topic><Title>"Microsoft Eyes 3 New Surface Tablet Servings for 2013"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358193453852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 14:57:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This thread is pointless because nobody's going to buy the Surface anyway, so no loss for Nvidia.</Msg><Username>barjonicat</Username><Timestamp>1358230796620</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 01:19:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358250747235-5</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes: Tegra 4 stands good chance of becoming a new platform for Win RT</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358188670849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 13:37:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I had some extra time and so I spent an hour this weekend getting familiar with the Surface at a Microsoft Kiosk ( I already own an iPad) My take away is that sales will pick up in 2013, the device is actually very sweet. Physically it feels well engineered and made of high quality material, the keyboard snaps into place effortlessly using magnets as does the power cable. The user experience is functionaly rich and very smooth and the inclusion of Office Suite is very desirable. Many features over the iPad including a native HDMI out ( not a #$%$ adapter) and a USB port you can use for a mouse, local storage etc. The fact that the iPhone 5 is seeing less sales that anticpated shows Apple is vunerable and folks are not buying Apple blindly as they once were. Still, Microsoft faces an uphill battle to garnish mind share, but the Surface is worthy of consideration and I suspect the Microsoft "fly wheel" will gain some momentum thru 2013. For one thing, the guys at the Kiosk need to be more direct about competitive against iPad. I saw a lot of lookers but not many buyers. They need to turn those lookers into Surface adopters. Apple can afford to Mr. and Mrs nice guy in retail because demand exists but if Microsoft wants to sell some Surfaces they need to step it up and go right after Apple and not be shy about it. Tegra 4 will be a nice addition , and I can see Microsoft adding XBOX type controllers via USB to lure PC gamers. The Tablet wars are not over, its only begining</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1358250747235</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 06:52:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358253632578-6</Id><Title>NVIDIA Corporation - Read Immediately!</Title><Msg>If you are looking for info about the stock market, then you can see this.. xoltoday . biz/info-NVDA</Msg><Username>orlando.dimattia</Username><Timestamp>1358253632578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:40:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358256079002-7</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation - Read Immediately!</Title><Username>orlando.dimattia</Username><Timestamp>1358253632578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:40:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Puma 7, bighouse. Tag team spam. Perps "orlando.dimattia" and a "haleharley611". Book 'em, Danno. Over.</Msg><Username>bnh.police</Username><Timestamp>1358256079002</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 08:21:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358258502483-8</Id><Title>Change of Pattern....</Title><Msg>Hopefully a lower open with a higher close for a change.</Msg><Username>muskiebear63</Username><Timestamp>1358258502483</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:01:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358260641827-9</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation - Read Immediately!</Title><Username>orlando.dimattia</Username><Timestamp>1358253632578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:40:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Puma 7, this is Bighouse. We have perps in visual range, and will do the app when they exit their residence. Over.</Msg><Username>best.duck</Username><Timestamp>1358260641827</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:37:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358261808944-10</Id><Title>FB News Gaming?</Title><Msg>Haven't they been distancing themselves from Zynga? Maybe they'll start with a new controller? I know someone who could help them.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1358261808944</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:56:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358261945761-11</Id><Title>Wasn't that Best guy pumping Apple?</Title><Msg>$700 - $490...</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358261945761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:59:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358262145093-12</Id><Topic><Title>"Microsoft Eyes 3 New Surface Tablet Servings for 2013"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358193453852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 14:57:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jeepers Best, It appears that Apple would like to buy the entire 8:00 pm show. That's right, Best -- the Entire 8:00 pm show. For "See Jen Grovel for Work -- Now with Exotic Casino Dancing Girls" 'Cause they heard tickets were limited. And Apple would like to entertain their army of Purchasing people attending the 2013 CES. Hey! Maybe Jen could add some material about that great nvidia warranty? To customize the experience for the special audience.</Msg><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1358262145093</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:02:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358262949957-13</Id><Topic><Title>Wasn't that Best guy pumping Apple?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358261945761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:59:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The BEST guy lost all his money (and pride) in RMBS... He is bitter over the NVDA win over RMBS in the courtroom... I personally am fascinated by him... how one coud waste so much of their time and effort..</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1358262949957</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:15:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358263372850-14</Id><Topic><Title>Wasn't that Best guy pumping Apple?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358261945761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:59:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I personally am fascinated by him." So Best? Weren't you going on a cruise soon? Some of the day traders here would like to know. So they could buy a little retail lot of nvda. While you're away.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1358263372850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:22:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358263430196-15</Id><Title>Anyone buying here?</Title><Msg>Directionally NVDA seems to be headed back to 11s. I am looking for a break and close below 12 as a sell indication. This is not just CES related, I think market expects weakness in their core PC graphics market.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358263430196</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:23:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358263759240-16</Id><Title>Nvda is about the only downers for past weeks</Title><Msg>Look at mu, mrvl, intc, amd, flex or any semis while Nvda went down from $13s.</Msg><Username>coolheadwarmblood</Username><Timestamp>1358263759240</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:29:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358263761598-17</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone buying here?</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358263430196</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:23:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there is much fear that INTC eranings will reveal mucho trouble and all chips stocks will sell hard after ok gains. THAT is what is happening here. I have to admit I feel real good about taking my gain in high 12's. Thought I missed out on much more but I expect the INTC to loom until anncmnt.</Msg><Username>nvda_4_ever</Username><Timestamp>1358263761598</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:29:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358264775584-18</Id><Topic><Title>Wasn't that Best guy pumping Apple?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358261945761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:59:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A submissive guy masking his obsession by hate. A guy without live.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1358264775584</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:46:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358265155630-19</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes: Tegra 4 stands good chance of becoming a new platform for Win RT</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358188670849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 13:37:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1M units for Q4 '12, that's with X'mas and device/OS launch. That's pretty sad. No doubt after X'mas/newness wears off, the volume will just fall off the cliff. While 'Samsung has shipped 100M Galaxy, including 40M Galaxy III' - no aapl, no sammie, no amzn, not enough integration to get into the low ends, nvda has no chance of Tegra ever breaking even with the size of the R&amp;D Jen is running now. Tegra changes none of the realities above regarding accessible TAM.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358265155630</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:52:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358265781316-20</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone buying here?</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358263430196</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:23:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well its making TXN look like geniuses with their OMAP exit strategy still waiting for credible benchmark results for Tegra 4</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358265781316</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:03:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358266019543-21</Id><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Msg>I love Nvidia, the company, but this stock has to be among the worst performers in the S&amp;P 500 over the past few years. Very frustrating... When will things change???</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358266164019-22</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No idea, but I'm with you on feeling like #$%$ holding this stock.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358266164019</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:09:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358266271614-23</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia DOWN over 7% since that SHIELD toy fisaco?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358198351614</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 16:19:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia is DOWN more 8% with todays spanking but whats another point or so amongst loyal Nvidia fans, right? Enjoy your Nvidia purchase and happy playing with that SHIELD toy. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358266271614</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:11:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358267022722-24</Id><Topic><Title>The market voted on that SHIELD toy announcement, results to the right in that weekly chart</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358106784843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 14:53:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems the market isn't done telling Nvidia how silly that project name like a condom is, hmm? A Tegra phone in one pocket, a SHIELD toy in the other and a tegra tablet in hand is just what every Nvidia fan needs to go with those empty back pockets where a fat wallet once lived until that Nvidia stock purchase. Here's to many enjoyable hours of playing with your portable pocket SHIELD toy Nvdia fans. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358267022722</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:23:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358267168802-25</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LIke you, I like the company, and I think it has a future. Tegra 4 was just announced, and I expect we'll see some product announcements in the lead up to the MWC next month. Earnings probably won't be stellar, but should meet estimates at least. But, I'm getting beat up pretty bad here on this recent decline. I'm sitting on some serious losses after CES, and I'm afraid that without some type of positive development, the short sellers are going to run it into the ground. By the time we get to earnings and MWC I could be looking at some pretty substantial losses. I too feel like a chump for hanging on to a stock that the world says is trash. We've seen 8 or 9 straight days of losses. Where does it end?</Msg><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1358267168802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:26:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358267700021-26</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why they pay you dividend now, so you can. Don't worry leaks about upcoming phones and tablets will start to appear soon!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358267700021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:35:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358267733921-27</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it will only end if and when the board declares Tegra as what it is - Jen's hobby, without any chance of ever breaking even because the accessible TAM is way too small compared to the huge R&amp;D program. That is, never. BTW, just curious, do you ever read the arguments presented by the negative posters here or do you just pass them by because they are just 'bashing'? Give you another hint: an R&amp;D effort 5 yrs in the making, into the 4th generation of devices, and the loses, instead of getting smaller, is getting bigger and bigger every quarter. This thing has no chance.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358267733921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:35:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358268012171-28</Id><Topic><Title>Wasn't that Best guy pumping Apple?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358261945761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:59:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since nobody in their right mind will hire me, what else do I got to do all day in my mobile home after Jerry Springer and the cartoons are over but to annoy everybody here with all my 50+ aliases.</Msg><Username>bestisapest</Username><Timestamp>1358268012171</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:40:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358268212527-29</Id><Topic><Title>"Microsoft Eyes 3 New Surface Tablet Servings for 2013"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358193453852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 14:57:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you see all the nonsense about that article Nvidia fans are posting. They act like some so called basher wrote it just to get at Nvidia. The article isn't about Nvidia, its about Microsoft's new products and any mention of parts suppliers is tangential. What, in the entire article Nvidia and/or Tegra show up ONE time? lol I put it up without comment just as I found it and no JUST IN nonsense or MUST READ nonsense and no insults. If you Nvidia fans find information in news articles useful then why all the whinning? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358268212527</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:43:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358268697441-30</Id><Title>You can't profit from gaming hardware</Title><Msg>Just look at the flop PS Vita is. This will be single digits by next week.</Msg><Username>iamaf0rk</Username><Timestamp>1358268697441</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:51:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358268752026-31</Id><Topic><Title>HOT NEWS: Nexus 7.7 specs (Tegra 4 on board) leak online; may debut at Google I/O event</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358268231048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:43:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great, so with the 7.7 as successful as the 7.... for Q3 '12, including winRT launch, nvda lost $40M on sales of $240M for Tegra. That's how out of whack the R&amp;D program is. It will take 2 Nexus 7 for tegra to break even, since nvda will never sell to aapl, sammie, nor amzn. That's txn's reality that forced them out. That is also nvda's reality, except Jen wants to continue to cough shareholders' blood each Q instead of folding.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358268752026</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:52:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358268923636-32</Id><Title>going private only way at this time,,</Title><Msg>been saying this for 2 years...the ceo/board must now move or be degraded even further..</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1358268923636</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:55:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358269146651-33</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will end when nvda show a modest encroachment into Qualcomm's piggybank. End of year when lte is intergrated.</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1358269146651</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:59:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358269308122-34</Id><Topic><Title>HOT NEWS: Nexus 7.7 specs (Tegra 4 on board) leak online; may debut at Google I/O event</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358268231048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:43:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leaks are coming right on schedual. Should be getting those GlBenchmarks soon showing Tegra 4 doesn't have a chance...LOL Nothing ever changes...then we get the HTC flagship phone at MWC after Jensen says at the earnings cc. good things are coming after posting better than expected earnings with decent guidance. But then someone says Nvidia is dead because GPUs are no more. Love the dividend....Don't you?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358269308122</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:01:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358269565254-35</Id><Topic><Title>HOT NEWS: Nexus 7.7 specs (Tegra 4 on board) leak online; may debut at Google I/O event</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358268231048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:43:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Folding is hardly an option at this stage - PC Graphics market share will continue to shrink, Nvidia game plan has been to offset PC losses with Mobile gains. If they fold Tegra, they might as well sell the company. Lets see if there are some flagship smartphones announcements with Tegra 4. Google Nexus reporting is too sketchy, its based on a Korean message board posting.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358269565254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:06:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358269680854-36</Id><Title>Do you really think this market would take Apple down and Nvidia higher?</Title><Msg>Do you? Really? Dream on. No free lunch for the Apple copycat groupies. If the NUMBER ONE supplier of all things with an ARM chip in it is down what do you think that means for Nvidia? Don't know? Take a look at that chart to he right, Nvidia is DOWN over 8% since Jan 4th 2013, (pre CES) DOWN 6 out of 7 trading days. Is it sinking in yet? You should be rooting for Apple to take tech higher AGAIN. Apple is a tech market leader. Do you really want Apple to lead tech lower? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358269680854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:08:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358269911150-37</Id><Title>Did you ask for a size ELEVEN madam in green? Well, you're in luck.</Title><Msg>We have something new in just today for you dear in your size 11s and its on sale to boot. lmao Enjoy your Nvidia purchase. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358269911150</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:11:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358269984180-38</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The dividend is hardly a consolation prize...</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358269984180</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:13:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358270113384-39</Id><Topic><Title>HOT NEWS: Nexus 7.7 specs (Tegra 4 on board) leak online; may debut at Google I/O event</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358268231048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:43:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So should Intel fold as well?</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358270113384</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:15:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358270201537-40</Id><Topic><Title>HOT NEWS: Nexus 7.7 specs (Tegra 4 on board) leak online; may debut at Google I/O event</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358268231048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:43:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PC Graphics has not shrunken, o.investor. That being said, I agree that folding Tegra is NOT an option. Without it, the company has no real large growth venue other than Tesla.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358270201537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:16:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358270388405-41</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's all about growth - you either grow in new market segments or, you grow by gaining market share against competitors. At this point both avenues are questionable though there is potential. - new market segments: HPC, gaming - market share gain: smartphones, server</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358270388405</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:19:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358270627020-42</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" this stock has to be among the worst performers" cool stuff... weak execution... products miss their target window... roadmap has shifted out a full year... "When will things change???" Project Denver... all new markets NVidia will own the high ground, the push out from there... The ARM64 era hasn't started yet...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358270627020</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:23:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358271386427-43</Id><Topic><Title>HOT NEWS: Nexus 7.7 specs (Tegra 4 on board) leak online; may debut at Google I/O event</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358268231048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:43:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PC Graphics for Nvidia may not be shrinking but PC Graphics is shrinking just on the basis of PC segment shrinking. I just got a top line Dell Latitude laptop with Intel HD 4000. In past years this used to come with Nvidia or, ATI Graphics. So don't believe that Nvidia is not being impacted by Intel GPU progress.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358271386427</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:36:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358271547190-44</Id><Topic><Title>HOT NEWS: Nexus 7.7 specs (Tegra 4 on board) leak online; may debut at Google I/O event</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358268231048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:43:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure why anyone responds to o.investor anymore and doesn't put him on ignore. He isn't worth the time, he really isn't.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1358271547190</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:39:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358271724215-45</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation - Read Immediately!</Title><Username>orlando.dimattia</Username><Timestamp>1358253632578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:40:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold faster</Msg><Username>benjamincordes</Username><Timestamp>1358271724215</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:42:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358271795647-46</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>R&amp;D is a necessary expenditure when breaking into a new market. I agree that it has weighed on earnings, but that is expected. Out of their PC peers that have had the know-with-all to start diversifying earlier on in the cycle and that has paid off with 16% Android market share. How has AMD, Intel, Dell etc done in this space. I have no reason to believe they couldn't steal a good portion of the smartphone segment from QCOM. At this point it is only QCOM and NVIDIA left among the independents. Now, that being said it does bother me they aren't pushing their LTE technology harder...that is a point of concern and I can't tell if that is subtle hint or just logistics.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358271795647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:43:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358272716554-47</Id><Topic><Title>Wasn't that Best guy pumping Apple?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358261945761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:59:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>English if you please mssr. bestie!!!</Msg><Username>strawman_best</Username><Timestamp>1358272716554</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:58:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358272840055-48</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation - Read Immediately!</Title><Username>orlando.dimattia</Username><Timestamp>1358253632578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:40:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>attack of the shorts</Msg><Username>ragsdale_robert</Username><Timestamp>1358272840055</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:00:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358273026147-49</Id><Topic><Title>HOT NEWS: Nexus 7.7 specs (Tegra 4 on board) leak online; may debut at Google I/O event</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358268231048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:43:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought the Leap frog kiddie tablet was more suited for you?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber22</Username><Timestamp>1358273026147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:03:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358273203365-50</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, R&amp;D is a necessary expenditure but you have to question the area of investment. The market was ripe to reward a credible QCOM competitor. Instead of Icera 500 focus, Nvidia seems to have been distracted by Project Shield. Now, Nvidia is a large 7000 employee company - you would think that they will be able to chew gum and walk at the same time. But at this time, absent any market indications, I have to believe that Icera acquisition is a bust. Remember that at the time of acquisition Icera was touted as earnings accretive in 2012.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358273203365</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:06:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358274001123-51</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NVidia had the right strategy, right investment, just didn't execute and missed many of their opportunities. Long term... PD cores in Tegra Stark...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358274001123</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:20:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358274157524-52</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's way too early to say Icera is a bust. You should know that and I think that is more emotion than rationale. R&amp;D efforts take time and often have setbacks and thus timelines get pushed especially considering the overzealous nature of Jen. So, I am curious to what your rationale is behind it being a bust? Being a large company is not in and of itself a favorable asset and often leads to political roadblocks but I do agree they should have enough resources to right a listing ship (if that be the case). I absolutely agree that Icera should've been a bigger focus at CES and I am disappointed in the blurry timelines given and I am not sure what to make of shield at this point. I think more time is needed to let things play out. All things considered, I will agree their timeline is about 12 months behind schedule but I am not sure that it's because of shield or viability as you are suggesting. The way things are playing out (and this is why i emphasize more patience) is a bit odd. You have a company that breaks into the mobile segment does well in the tablet space, seemingly has all the tools to start stealing smartphone market share but seems to have been rather muted. Their track record at a minimum would tell me they would at least make a strong go at it before giving up.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358274157524</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:22:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358274404048-53</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: S&amp;P cut AMD rating by 2 notches...into junk territory</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358273879841</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:17:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It wasn't junk already?</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358274404048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:26:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358274567236-54</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Project denver should arrive soon, what's you expectation? 2 years ago it was announced at the ces and jensen said, I believe he said, 18 months out.</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1358274567236</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:29:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358274672639-55</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bought this early last year they kept saying this will hit 20 bucks at end of 2012 i dont know if i should sell now and buy amd</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1358274672639</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:31:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358274872024-56</Id><Topic><Title>HOT NEWS: Nexus 7.7 specs (Tegra 4 on board) leak online; may debut at Google I/O event</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358268231048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:43:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It also says Tegra 4 could be in Nexus 5 which is pretty cool!</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1358274872024</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:34:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358275097805-57</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>o.investor Nvidia is taking market share from AMD in graphics. I also expect Tegra 4 to do quite well in Android tablets. High end phones + i500 should be more attractive than what Nvidia has for phones now. 2014 should be when "Grey" should take some real smartphone share from QCOM.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358275097805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:38:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358275309019-58</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation - Read Immediately!</Title><Username>orlando.dimattia</Username><Timestamp>1358253632578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:40:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow amazing report</Msg><Username>eugenewindsor</Username><Timestamp>1358275309019</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:41:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358275536006-59</Id><Title>NVIDIA</Title><Msg>P-I-E-C-E O-F #$%$</Msg><Username>yantonego</Username><Timestamp>1358275536006</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:45:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358275623802-60</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brokeagain - you are too hardcore Nvidia believer. Even after 2 years, Nvidia has not been able to bring a single product from Icera to market. Mind you this in the middle of roaring mobile growth. And you question if my response if more emotion than rational? Did you know that QCOM has already investigated SDR modems and decided against that approach? There is nothing new in Icera technology - I was hoping that at least they will be quick to market but even that didn't happen. Icera had some success in USB data only modem. After Nvidia acquisition they started focusing seriously in voice support. Well that requires many protocol stacks and it has to run somewhere. SDR modems are science projects and will never beat a good ASIC solution. Thats just basic science - it was laughable when Nvidia compares LTE die-size as a differentiation.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358275623802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:47:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358275909588-61</Id><Topic><Title>HOT NEWS: Nexus 7.7 specs (Tegra 4 on board) leak online; may debut at Google I/O event</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358268231048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:43:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google would never use another Tegra product after the disastrous sales of the T3 powered tablet fiasco.</Msg><Username>rambesty2</Username><Timestamp>1358275909588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:51:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358276205988-62</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Icera is a bust: A reasonably generous chip design cycle is about one year. Deal went through 1 year and 9 months ago, almost two whole design cycles ago. Now, they are still not registering any meaningful modem sales, either discrete or integrated, and promise is a still full design cycle off. The discrete part is the telling story. People like aapl and samsung are just dying for a second source to escape the qcom monopoly pricing. Just talk to brcm on that one. If Icera discretes are not good enough to go into any device, what makes you think they are good enough to be integrated into anything. Jen bought a lemon.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358276205988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:56:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358276223846-63</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation - Read Immediately!</Title><Username>orlando.dimattia</Username><Timestamp>1358253632578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:40:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>best report out there</Msg><Username>luis.goodman</Username><Timestamp>1358276223846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:57:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358276343545-64</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A reasonably generous chip design cycle is about one year." More crow for whosunw...!!!!! You should write articles for SA...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358276343545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:59:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358276498783-65</Id><Topic><Title>HOT NEWS: Nexus 7.7 specs (Tegra 4 on board) leak online; may debut at Google I/O event</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358268231048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:43:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is o.investor? I have so many best clones on ignore that all I ever see is Ibexx, ashraf, roundhouse, and johnny..... :)</Msg><Username>ugs</Username><Timestamp>1358276498783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:01:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358276499398-66</Id><Title>Does anybody have a truck I could borrow?</Title><Msg>I need to move my mobile home down by the river? The landlord said they finally got fed-up with me molesting all the pets in the trailer park. If you don't hear from me for a while I will be looking for a new library to loiter and post from.</Msg><Username>trailertrashbest</Username><Timestamp>1358276499398</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:01:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358276705989-67</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Project denver should arrive soon, what's you expectation?" My guess is GTC in March... "2 years ago it was announced at the ces and jensen said, I believe he said, 18 months out." As I said, everything is behind... weak execution... however, ARM64 market hasn't started, and is gonna grow throughout the decade... So late by their roadmaps... but not late compared to anyone else entering the ARM64 market...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358276705989</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:05:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358277056049-68</Id><Title>Tegra breakeven level?</Title><Msg>Does anybody have the approximate rev # at which the Tegra division is expected to break-even? If we could see that by next year, it could seriously juice EPS.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358277056049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:10:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358277084134-69</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation - Read Immediately!</Title><Username>orlando.dimattia</Username><Timestamp>1358253632578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:40:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>show me something better</Msg><Username>williammiller840</Username><Timestamp>1358277084134</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:11:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358277226698-70</Id><Title>Project Shield Will Come With An Over Clocked GPU</Title><Msg>I bet Nvidia will revert to what they and AMD do well with their graphics chips....i.e.overclock the GPU in the Tegra 4 for the Project Shield and put up some Monster benchmark numbers. I mean after all their target market is Gamers for heavens sake. Why else would they have a heat sink with a small fan? Quad core A15 CPU is fine as is. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358277226698</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:13:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358277252161-71</Id><Topic><Title>Do you really think this market would take Apple down and Nvidia higher?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358269680854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:08:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia's stock bleeds just as red as Apple's stock doesn't it? Now where did you say you wnat Apple o lead this market again? Because Nvidia will follow the leader. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358277252161</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:14:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358277396347-72</Id><Topic><Title>Did you ask for a size ELEVEN madam in green? Well, you're in luck.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358269911150</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:11:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When its Nvidia's stock doing the falling its just not as funny as it is when its some other stock, is it Nvidia fans? lol</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358277396347</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:16:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358277490368-73</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra breakeven level?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358277056049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:10:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That depends on whether Project Shieldis accounted for in the Consumer Products Division. If it is then this Division could break even with as little as 500K units sold a quarter. Probably less. But since it will sell for a 10X multiple of just a chip, with a 5X to 10X multiple on gross profit.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358277490368</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:18:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358277638497-74</Id><Topic><Title>"Microsoft Eyes 3 New Surface Tablet Servings for 2013"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358193453852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 14:57:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can post Nvidia love notes all day and bash every other tech stock on the planet but your Nvidia made one big mess of your investment after CES didn't it? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358277638497</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:20:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358277762449-75</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra breakeven level?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358277056049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:10:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jen said it needs revenue of $1B.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1358277762449</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:22:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358278050608-76</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra breakeven level?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358277056049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:10:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$1B was before Icera, many many moons ago. zero need to go with what Jen says: from 10Q last Q, $240M sales, $40M loses. Take 50% margin, you have breakeven sales of $1.3B. And nvda is still ramping Tegra R&amp;D.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358278050608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:27:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358278086528-77</Id><Title>throw in the towel and stock will go up...</Title><Msg>this is how it works on the street....why does it even hold 11.94???</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1358278086528</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:28:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358278300822-78</Id><Title>SHIELD couldn't shield you from that 9% market slap DOWN since 1/4/13, could it?</Title><Msg>Nvidia closed at $13.15 before the SHIELD show and tell at CES, didn't it? Enjoy your Nvidia purchase. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358278300822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:31:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358279037901-79</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra breakeven level?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358277056049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:10:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From 10Q CPB Rev: $180M Operating Loss: ($90M) Its hard to say what the operating costs are @CPB without accounting for 1-time expenses I think QCOM has mentioned 40% margins (on products), I would imagine NVDA margins are closer to 30%. So everything else being equal CPB Qtr revenue $400 - $500M will be needed for breakeven.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358279037901</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:43:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358279581894-80</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra breakeven level?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358277056049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:10:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$00M - $500M/Q to break even... ouch! ah, how the truth hurts.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358279581894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:53:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358279970338-81</Id><Title>Told you under $12.</Title><Msg>I won't buy NVDA again over $11.00 -- See you then. NVDA = DOG</Msg><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1358279970338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:59:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358280958061-82</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra breakeven level?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358277056049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:10:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sisula, Thank you. Do you have a link to this?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358280958061</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:15:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358281007708-83</Id><Topic><Title>Told you under $12.</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1358279970338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you so much Nostradamus. IROQ = PIG</Msg><Username>chitownbarber22</Username><Timestamp>1358281007708</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:16:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358281551231-84</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra breakeven level?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358277056049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:10:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, I don't have such a link. I think it was mentioned on one of the past earnings call confs. I only found this: androidandmeDOTcom/2011/10/news/will-nvidias-2-billion-dollar-bet-on-tegra-pay-off-next-year/ "Company CEO Jen-Hsun Huang has previously said that if you want to build and sustain a world-class SoC (system-on-a-chip) business, then you need that business generating up to $1 billion in revenue to remain competitive."</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1358281551231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:25:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358282629436-85</Id><Title>Small short %, but</Title><Msg>seems to be enough to control the pps. Apparently there are about 20 million shares short and a short interest of 3.43%. So we have about 600 million shares out and can't seem to get traction. The S@P seems to think we will go to 17 bucks, but we can't get close. It really seems odd that such a small shorting % can keep the pps down, but they seem to be able to do it. Maybe if Nvidia would start buying they could crush the damn shorts, but no such luck. I would bet that more money is made on shorting stocks that the pie in the sky, buy low and sell high method. The way things work in the market I am surprised that the gurus on Wall Street can't figure out why the little guy won't buy into the market. It is crooked as a dogs hind leg. JMHO</Msg><Username>dyk742000</Username><Timestamp>1358282629436</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:43:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358283332215-86</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think NVDA is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>lucile.whitaker113e</Username><Timestamp>1357926007106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 12:40:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool picks. I love it.</Msg><Username>natasha.house441v</Username><Timestamp>1358283332215</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:55:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358283893826-87</Id><Topic><Title>Told you under $12.</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1358279970338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad to hear we won't be seeing you again!</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1358283893826</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 16:04:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358284408722-88</Id><Topic><Title>throw in the towel and stock will go up...</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1358278086528</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:28:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right. It will change it course now.</Msg><Username>sam_boy4u</Username><Timestamp>1358284408722</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 16:13:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358286415653-89</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'A reasonably generous chip design cycle is about one year.' About 1.5-2 for a licensed design, 3-4 for your own.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358286415653</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 16:46:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358287007846-90</Id><Title>From Jan 4, 2013 $13+ down to now at $11+. Anyone can see this is way oversold</Title><Msg>I can feel a bounce is coming......</Msg><Username>autoblast123</Username><Timestamp>1358287007846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 16:56:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358287622018-91</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Although, I believe in NVIDIA, and not just for it's mobile prospects, don't get ahead of yourself and think that my belief is that of blind faith. I question your perspective only because being delayed is not in and of itself a reason to discount it's delivery to the market. I have been part of many projects that have seen significant delays but still came to fruition. I don't think the delay is enough to say it's a bust. I did not know that QCOM attempted an SDR technology however, I would caution and remind you that QCOM's core competencies DO NOT include software. Need I say anymore than the RT driver debacle. If it truly was going to be a bust I am not sure why they keep highlighting it whenever Tegra is mentioned - I would think they would move away from that. "SDR modems are science projects and will never beat a good ASIC solution. Thats just basic science - it was laughable when Nvidia compares LTE die-size as a differentiation." This is a bit myopic don't you think? As an example the same argument was used against hypervisors particularly those hardware zealots who lived and died by the metal. I could be proven wrong and that is ok but technology is meant to evolve and that is what I think will happen - hardware only solutions are becoming less and less ubiquitous.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358287622018</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 17:07:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358288682633-92</Id><Topic><Title>HOT NEWS: Nexus 7.7 specs (Tegra 4 on board) leak online; may debut at Google I/O event</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358268231048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:43:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Internet may be flooded but they are sourcing the same Korean message board posting - that is hardly bankable. Remember how the market had it all figured out with Kindle Fire HD. It ended up being TI OMAP. Google Nexus 4 has some sort of supply problem. It has been out of stock for too long. I think it was meant to be a showcase/platform device - not really designed for high volume. So maybe a Nexus 4.2 is in works but this will make people who ordered Nexus 4 in Dec and are still waiting for delivery really mad. On a positive note - anandtech is debunking the so called leaked glbenchmark results anandtechDOTcom/show/6666/the-tegra-4-gpu-nvidia-claims-better-performance-than-ipad-4</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358288682633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 17:24:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358293436819-93</Id><Topic><Title>OT/ New York State Legislature passes the nation's 1st gun-control bill after Newtown killings</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358288126931</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 17:15:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's funny and sad seeing how all the political hacks are trying to pass stricter gun laws to make it look like they are doing something while Chicago has the toughest gun laws in the country, but holds the number one position in gun related murders in the country.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1358293436819</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 18:43:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358294915128-94</Id><Title>"Advanced Micro Devices Inc (AMD): Today's Featured Technology Winner"</Title><Msg>"Advanced Micro Devices Inc (AMD): Today's Featured Technology Winner" "Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) pushed the Technology sector higher today making it today's featured technology winner. The sector as a whole was unchanged today. By the end of trading, Advanced Micro Devices rose 4 cents (1.5%) to $2.68 on average volume. Throughout the day, 23.6 million shares of Advanced Micro Devices exchanged hands as compared to its average daily volume of 28.2 million shares. The stock ranged in a price between $2.60-$2.70 after having opened the day at $2.62 as compared to the previous trading day's close of $2.64." source: TheStreet Wire</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358294915128</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:08:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358295025816-95</Id><Topic><Title>Do you really think this market would take Apple down and Nvidia higher?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358269680854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:08:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Do you really want Apple to lead tech lower?" Did you get your wish Nvidia fans? Apple was down. Did it help Nvidia? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358295025816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:10:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358295355878-96</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ok brokeagain - I am not calling you a die-hard Nvidia homer like some others on this board. I understand the thrill of nailing the next big stock before the market has it all figured out. And Nvidia over the years has been one heck of a tease. SDR as a technology solution has been around for many years but it has never made it much beyond experimental phase. Sandbridge Tech was pursuing SDR approach (funded by Samsung) when they were scooped by Qualcomm. Most likely to restrict options for Qualcomm rather than for the technology. Icera founders are great minds - if anyone could pull out a competitive SDR solution, they were the team to do it. I don't know what has happened to that team after Nvidia acquisition. But 2 years and no new product is not a good sign. We will have to wait for MWC to see if any of this is real. Obviously CES was a disappointment from an investor point of view. By announcing Tegra 4, Nvidia has basically put the brakes on consumers looking to buy tablets with Tegra 3 - this always happens. That is why you see Apple announce products with pricing and launch dates. Unlike the stuff that Nvidia tried to pull at CES.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1358295355878</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:15:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358295714959-97</Id><Title>"AMD alleges former managers copied 100,000 confidential files before joining Nvidia"</Title><Msg>"AMD alleges former managers copied 100,000 confidential files before joining Nvidia" "Summary: AMD believes that a former vice-president and three managers handed trade secrets to Nvidia, after they jumped ship to join a rival hardware-making firm." "Chipmaker AMD is taking four former employees to court, one former vice-president and three former managers from the firm's Boxborough plant, who left the company to go and work for rival Nvidia last year. AMD believes that as they left the company, the four employees copied more than 100,000 confidential documents and trade secrets to take with them. The suit, filed in the U.S. District of Massachusetts, claims former vice-president Robert Feldstein, along with managers Manoo Desai, Nicolas Kociuk and Richard Hagen, took the files before the four left the company. AMD wants to recover the files, which the company claims covers everything from upcoming AMD technology and contracts with large and enterprise customers. Along with the lawsuit, the court also sanctioned a temporary restraining order against the four former employees, ordering the preservation of any copies of AMD materials they may have, any computers or devices they may own, and must not divulge or use any AMD confidential information. " Source: zdnet</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358295714959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:21:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>27</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358297027506-98</Id><Topic><Title>Wasn't that Best guy pumping Apple?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358261945761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:59:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>aapl goes the rim way eventually, survival of the fittest</Msg><Username>daysofshred30000000000</Username><Timestamp>1358297027506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:43:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358297037509-99</Id><Title>Ibexx, you dislike me, a long term shareholder..</Title><Msg>look, Jen gets the same treatment Michael Dell gets..all the good things you post about are disregarded by the wall st thugs. Jen needs to do the same thing. Give us shareholders a premium to today's holders and may we all succeed from there. If Jen does nothing but stay the course, then he only hurts shareholders and makes the thugs more powerful and ultimately, destroying his own company. If this buyout happens with Dell, the pressure will increase to do the same, and I will be at the forefront of the #$%$... you should too. it's over, the old days are forever gone..</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1358297037509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:43:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358297504244-100</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can agree with much of this. I may be a bit more positive on SDR technology but also also understand that is has limited commercial success. As for the tech savvy consumer I agree the announcement will be an impediment for purchasing a T3 powered device. I don't think it matters for devices that are less transparent to the hardware like automotive and for the consumer who just cares about the branding or product around the guts of it (the non tech savvy consumer ). One more thing - I do like the company and I feel like I understand their vision but that won't stop me from mitigating the impact owning the stock has on my portfolio. I am not emotionally attached to NVIDIA. That being said I have done well with NVIDIA, in part, because it has been beat down so much. I reduced my position a bit in order to reduce my exposure to the PC segment of NVIDIA in case Intel's earning come in below expectations. We both know what kind of impact that could have on a company like NVIDIA.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358297504244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:51:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358297555586-101</Id><Topic><Title>So who's depressed?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1358266019543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:06:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for the nth time I'll repeat myself: I don't think an integrated solution is absolutely necessary at this pt, aapl/sammie are still using discrete solutions. But it is essential to announce a package deal, one promises that the app processor WILL work with the modem/one neck to choke. We did not get that at CES. So if it won't work together separately, why would it work together on the same die??</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358297555586</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:52:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358300132663-102</Id><Title>Focus On The Positive</Title><Msg>1) Nvidia became the leading independent tablet processor company in 3Q with 17% market share. Will only get better with Tegra 4 2) Tegra 4 is a killer chip...like the smartphone camera exotic stuff. Surely LG and HTC will announce phones in MWC. 3) Nvidia dominates the gamer GPU market and it's not going away. 4) No competion in Pro Graphics and Tesla is expanding rapidly. 5) Project Shield opens up a whole new way to sell chips. 6) Nvidia Grid has huge potential!! 7) Started paying a dividend in November...only up from here. and at least one other semiconductor company takes Nvidia's entry into the console gaming market very seriously...Yes AMD..just sued 4 former employees who now work for Nvidia. One was the ex ATI vice president of engineering that got AMD all those standard console contracts. Apparently he and the other 4 know too much......LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358300132663</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:35:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358300160140-103</Id><Title>Like it or not, Nvidia is headed for the single digits. Fair value is</Title><Msg>$7. Tegra is a bust.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358300160140</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:36:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358300945054-104</Id><Topic><Title>"Advanced Micro Devices Inc (AMD): Today's Featured Technology Winner"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358294915128</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:08:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>History say AMD is an easy double</Msg><Username>blu_is_cool</Username><Timestamp>1358300945054</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:49:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358304695146-105</Id><Topic><Title>"Advanced Micro Devices Inc (AMD): Today's Featured Technology Winner"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358294915128</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:08:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure, it has doubled it's chances of bankruptcy.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358304695146</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 21:51:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358310659178-106</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA has nothing to do with the alleged, illegal transfer of data by former AMD employees...</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358304946016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 21:55:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My my my. My hands feel, well, unclean, merely reading about it. I'll go scrub them now.</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1358310659178</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 23:30:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>25</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358311535190-107</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD alleges former managers copied 100,000 confidential files before joining Nvidia"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358295714959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:21:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"AMD believes that a former vice-president and three managers handed trade secrets to Nvidia. AMD believes that as they left the company, the four employees copied more than 100,000 confidential documents and trade secrets to take with them." Hummm. And we thought last year's insider trading case was interesting, right boys?</Msg><Username>bestogram</Username><Timestamp>1358311535190</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 23:45:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358312372955-108</Id><Topic><Title>Like it or not, Nvidia is headed for the single digits. Fair value is</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358300160140</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:36:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have $5 per share cash in the bank, the bust is your brain.</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1358312372955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 23:59:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>