<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363754521109-1</Id><Title>Piz Daint supercomputer announced, powered by NVIDIA Tesla K20X - will be Europe's fastest suprcomputer)</Title><Msg>Along with NVIDIA’s keynote this morning (which should be wrapping up by the time this article goes live), NVIDIA also has a couple other announcements that are hitting the wire this morning. The first of which is the announcement of NVIDIA landing another major supercomputer contract, this time with the Swiss National Computing Center (CSCS). CSCS will be building a new Cray XC30 supercomputer, “Piz Daint.” Like Titan last year, Piz Daint is a mixed supercomputer that will pack both a large number of CPUs – Xeon E5s to be precise – and of course to great interest to NVIDIA, a large number of Tesla K20X GPUs. We don’t have the complete specifications for Piz Daint at this time, but when completed it is expected to exceed 1 PFLOPS in performance and be the most powerful supercomputer in Europe. SOURCE: Anandtech anandtechDOTcom/show/6844/piz-daint-supercomputer-announced-powered-by-tesla-k20x</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363754521109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 00:42:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363757385484-2</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 5 in 2013?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363722356668</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not a trader; just not a blind pumper. Nvidia is my largest position and I took the opportunity to add today. No intention of selling anytime soon.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363757385484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 01:29:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363758146859-3</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 5 in 2013?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363722356668</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Google dropped Tegra 3 and passed on Tegra 4 for a QCOM part for their nex-gen Nexus tablet.” The reason is because Tegra 4 consumes more power than competitor's at benchmark clock speed and unlike Snapdragon the Tegra 4 doesn’t come with an integrated LTE modem. These are the key factors that handset device manufacturers (smartphones, phablets, tablets, etc.) are looking for. However, Tegra 4i which will only be available in limited release in Q1 2014 has a built-in modem from Icera i500 with Software-Defined Radio running on a Cortex A9 processor instead of the A15 and uses 60 cores GPU instead of 72. In the meantime, manufacturers such as Google (Nexus 7) ain’t going to wait till 2014. I am not sure how Tegra 5 fits in but perhaps someone got confused with Tegra 4i with Tegra5.</Msg><Username>cj_observer</Username><Timestamp>1363758146859</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 01:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363758576885-4</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 5 in 2013?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363722356668</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After listening to the investors call (and the keynote earlier), I'll be really interested to see what kind of notes or comments are made by analysts (if any) the next few days. I suspect we'll have at least a couple of announcements through next week about product launches with Tegra 4/4i . . maybe not major ones, but I think the next month or so is when we should expect what Jen inferred for the second half to be announced. I appreciated most the comments by Jen about the expanded approach to have two versions of the same series, with and without integrated modem, from now on . . and how that had a direct affect on the delay between 3 and 4 with all the added R &amp; D expenses. The strategy to break the yearly cycle and volatile swings in revenue (and get WAY ahead of the curve) is the right course to take imo.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1363758576885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 01:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363758817325-5</Id><Title>N7</Title><Msg>It's not because the other S4 Pro is lower cost, on the contrary it's higher. It's not because S4 performs better than T4 or T4i, on the contrary - it's a tired old dog that is barely better than the 1.7 GHz T3. So what is it? Production quantities 500K+ availability is just not there until July at the earliest and it's got to go to a number of takers. T4/T4i basically missed the boat on the current cycle of new products. It'll catch up in the off cycle products particularly Chinese phones and Xmas phones/tablets.</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1363758817325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 01:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363758951204-6</Id><Topic><Title>N7</Title><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1363758817325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 01:53:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the production cycle is a little earlier then July, but the point is well taken. I think Google is aiming before June for launch date, aren't they?</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1363758951204</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 01:55:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363759380867-7</Id><Topic><Title>N7</Title><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1363758817325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 01:53:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it's going to be on Playstore in July - they have to have the parts in hand by May in hundreds of K quantities - pretty steep challenge. And if N won the N5 and the X - and they are supposed to be available July in Play store - you have no choice but to loose some. So N5 &amp; X will be interesting. If they took all 3 including N7 - they would need to have available1M units between May and June alone. NOT Possible to do a step function manufacturing on an early product - too risky.</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1363759380867</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 02:03:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363770750213-8</Id><Topic><Title>How NIVIDIA plans to oust Intel and power nearly every device your own</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363748786802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 23:06:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>world domination. I like it! I get the sense there may be a sea change coming. The bashers may be right pointing out Sammie apple are using their own chips. Anyone competeing must use their own chip. Conversely we must make our own end product. Sheild, tablet, phone. That also seems where we are headed. No time to be shy.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1363770750213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 05:12:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363772017548-9</Id><Topic><Title>N7</Title><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1363758817325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 01:53:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you nailed it</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1363772017548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 05:33:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363773195367-10</Id><Title>Enterprise Computing - Nvidia Grid - A Very Nice Business</Title><Msg>A much more profitable and stable source of revenue. Certainly Nvidia can generate more in revenue and profits from Nvidia Grid than from Tegra. Just the small and medium size Grid VCA - remote workstation) remote to any display alone could out do Tegra in one or two quarters. Just some easy math numbers. Factoids: Jon Peddie reports 1M+ workstations sold every quarter. VCA is the equivalent of 16 workstations concurrent users...unlimited access numbers. But the really value added idea is...you don't have to lug around you 15 pound $7,500 workstation laptop. Visit your customer with your 2 lb. mac air. Just some random numbers to put this is perpective: 10,000 VCA = $39,800 x 10,000 = $398M yearly software license = $4,800 x 10,000 = $44.8M Gross Margin high 50's on initial sale PLUS AN ADDITIONAL 12 POINTS MARGIN every year from recurring software licenses. Enterprise Grid backed by IBM, HP, Dell, Cisco, VMWare, and Citrix. Uh I think Nvidia will receive quite a few dollars from this part of the business don't you. Cloud Gaming - It's coming for sure!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363773195367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 05:53:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363773326604-11</Id><Topic><Title>Windows RT is a DUD, not merely because of compatibility, but because its SLOW.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363748691746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 23:04:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jen publically agrees with you and and what I said even before winRT came out, while completely contradicted ibeey - winRT is a dud.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1363773326604</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 05:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363781582541-12</Id><Topic><Title>How NIVIDIA plans to oust Intel and power nearly every device your own</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363748786802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 23:06:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you expect Nvidia (without any experience) to succeed in the same field where giants like Nokia, HTC, Ericsson, Motorola have struggled for years or even failed?</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1363781582541</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 08:13:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363782034742-13</Id><Topic><Title>Enterprise Computing - Nvidia Grid - A Very Nice Business</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363773195367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 05:53:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you think Nvidia will succeed in the market with specialized graphics appliances? The same market in which SGI or Sun failed.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1363782034742</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 08:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363783423889-14</Id><Title>revenge time for tdfx and voodo fans.</Title><Msg>i get the feeling nvidia is now spread out all over the map. tegra is up agains qcom. discrete graphics left behind by haswell stories about nvidia making their own cloud enterprise gpu boxes. have they just lost focus in the face of competition in all these market segments?</Msg><Username>tired_and_un_wired</Username><Timestamp>1363783423889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 08:43:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363783622363-15</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fantastic. I will check it out.</Msg><Username>mimjunie</Username><Timestamp>1363783622363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 08:47:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363784143216-16</Id><Topic><Title>Enterprise Computing - Nvidia Grid - A Very Nice Business</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363773195367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 05:53:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Why do you think Nvidia will succeed in the market with specialized graphics appliances? The same market in which SGI or Sun failed." Because Nvidia owns the Workstation GPU market and this is just workstation GPU computing power over the network with a lot convenience. Cuts down on the number of intel CPUs needed too just like HPC GPU accelerated processing does. IBM, Csco, HP, and Dell like it so there must be something to it!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363784143216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 08:55:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363784913463-17</Id><Topic><Title>Enterprise Computing - Nvidia Grid - A Very Nice Business</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363773195367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 05:53:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the truth of nvda is: with the size of the Tegra cash drain, nothing matters to the stock price until nvda can sell minimum 15 to 20 million Tegras a quarter. And that takes many many Nexus 7s while nvda does not have even one. "I have a dream...... " (with your money.....).</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1363784913463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363785715657-18</Id><Topic><Title>Enterprise Computing - Nvidia Grid - A Very Nice Business</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363773195367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 05:53:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whosunw, I'm sure you have already figured that 10,000 VCA's is equal to 100 million cheap radios!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363785715657</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:21:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363786496429-19</Id><Topic><Title>Enterprise Computing - Nvidia Grid - A Very Nice Business</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363773195367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 05:53:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well put</Msg><Username>ugs</Username><Timestamp>1363786496429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:34:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363786778115-20</Id><Topic><Title>Enterprise Computing - Nvidia Grid - A Very Nice Business</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363773195367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 05:53:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who said they like it? They just don't want to miss the train in case this obscure product is successful. By the way, Nvidia doesn't "own" the workstation GPU market more than SGI used to own graphics workstation market. Still, it failed terribly.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1363786778115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363787303728-21</Id><Title>And the hits just keep coming!</Title><Msg>Another hpc deal. The best partners out there. And all the bashers money can buy! Luke i am your faaaather. lol</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1363787303728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:48:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363787840800-22</Id><Title>Nvidia's road map drives graphics, ARM into enterprise</Title><Msg>eetimesDOTcom/electronics-news/4410199/Nvidia-drives-graphics-into-the-enterprise-at-GTC?pageNumber=0</Msg><Username>bobsumrall1961</Username><Timestamp>1363787840800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:57:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363787869440-23</Id><Title>Wall Street only understands $$$</Title><Msg>And that's what Jen has to understand. These guys aren't smart enough to get Nvidia's ambitious strategy, so the stock will only move when earnings growth accelerates nicely. The company clearly isn't going to get the benefit of the doubt. The long bear market in NVDA shares seems likely to continue for a while, unfortunately...</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363787869440</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:57:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363788519514-24</Id><Title>Nvidia Tegra 4 schedule points to late Q2 availability</Title><Msg>4i carrier certification also expected in Q2 Tegra 4 is a couple of still months away, but now we have a slightly clearer picture of what to expect, and when. Nvidia plans to start churning out Shield consoles in Q2 and partners are expected to start producing phones and tablets based on the new chip at about the same time. This means we won’t see any products in retail before the latter half of Q2 at the earliest, while some might appear in Q3. As for 4G tablets using the Icera i500 modem, they are being certified by carriers as we speak and they should go into production in Q4. Tegra 4i should get certified by carriers in Q2, but the first phones should enter production in Q1 2014. Nvidia describes Tegra 4i phones as “mainstream” phones, which means they should end up rather cheap. At this point it is not easy to say how T4i chips will measure up to the competition, as we have no idea what Qualcomm and Samsung have lined up for next year. Although it’s not an A15 chip, the Tegra 4i is still a rather interesting piece of silicon. It’s Nvidia’s first chip with integrated LTE and it should end up tiny, less than half of the size of Tegra 4, and that’s with an LTE modem on the die. In terms of power consumption, T4i should have a TDP of up to 1W, while the burly Tegra 4 hits 5W, sans modem. With four A9r4 cores clocked north of 2GHz and a 60-core GPU, the T4i should be quite snappy, despite the fact that it’s not an A15 part. However, although it looks good on paper right now, we still have no idea what the competition will come up with over the next nine months.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363788519514</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:08:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363788632619-25</Id><Title>Nvidia sheds more light on Tegra 5</Title><Msg>While we wait for fourth gen parts Nvidia decided to shed more light on upcoming Logan and Parker SoCs at the GPU Technology Conference on Tuesday. The move is bound to raise some eyebrows, as Nvidia is getting into a rather bad habit of talking up Tegra chips months before they actually show up. Still, there is some interesting stuff to report. Logan, or Tegra 5, will feature CUDA 5 and a Kepler class GPU. Nvidia hopes the combination will help it drastically improve GPU performance, by a factor of three over rival GPUs. Logan will also support Open GL 4.3. Moving along to Parker, which might be the Tegra 6. It is said to feature more advanced Denver CPU cores and it will be able to use 64-bit ARMv8 cores, so it will be Nvidia’s first 64-bit SoC. It will also feature Maxwell GPU cores, which should deliver twice as efficient as Kepler cores. It all sounds nice but we won’t see the chips anytime soon. The first Tegra 4 products should show up in a couple of months, followed by Tegra 4i phones in late Q4, or possibly even early 2014. Tegra 5 should launch in about a year, in early 2014. Parker, or Tegra 6, will show up in 2015. So why on earth is Nvidia spilling the beans on its upcoming SoCs? Some investors might like it, but that doesn’t explain it. Nvidia always had a public Tegra roadmap, but it did not go into detail. Perhaps it is just leaking like a sieve and instead of plugging the leaks it just decided to confirm them.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363788632619</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:10:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363788784321-26</Id><Title>Nvidia updates its GPU roadmap at GTC 2013</Title><Msg>Volta GPU coming after Maxwell Nvidia has officially and publicly updated its GPU roadmap to show what to expect after we are done with the Maxwell GPU family, the Volta GPU family. Named after one of the great Italian physicists, Alessandro Volta, known among other things for the invention of the battery, the Volta GPU family will bring an impressive new feature - stacked DRAM. Since we are still far away from the launch of Volta GPU family Nvidia did not reveal that many details but it has detailed one of the key features of the Volta GPU family, the stacked DRAM concep. The reason, or simply put the advantage behind stacked DRAM is to place the DRAM close (on the same package) to the GPU and connect it, according to Nvidia, by cutting a hole through the silicon layer placed between the GPU and stacked DRAM. By doing this, Nvidia should be able to improve both bandwidth and latency by getting rid of the standard/external memory bus. According to what Jen-Hsun Huang revealed at GTC 2013, Nvidia aims to achieve a 1TB/sec of bandwidth on Volta which ends up around three times what we are now seeing on the GTX Titan. Jen-Hsun Huang noted that with this kind of bandwidth it is possible to move the equivalent of a full Blu-Ray disc worth of data in just 1/50th of a second. It all sounds quite impressive but since Maxwell is expected in 2014, we will not see the Volta GPU family before the 2016, at least if all goes well and Nvidia follows its standard two year GPU schedule. Bear in mind that Nvidia did want Kepler to be the 2011 rather than the 2012 product and Maxwell slipped from 2013 to 2014, so we certainly hope that Volta will not share the same fate.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363788784321</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:13:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363788958069-27</Id><Topic><Title>Enterprise Computing - Nvidia Grid - A Very Nice Business</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363773195367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 05:53:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Who said they like it? They just don't want to miss the train in case this obscure product is successful." sisula3 Sure...Cisco spends millions just on the off chance something might be successful, IBM too along with HP and Dell and everyone else. "By the way, Nvidia doesn't "own" the workstation GPU market more than SGI used to own graphics workstation market. Still, it failed terribly." Wasn't SGI a CPU company back in the day. Risc vs. X86 before GPU's were even around. Looks like the ratio of CPUs to GPUs is going to go from the old days of 1 to 0, through 1 to 1 today, to 1 to 4 tomorrow...Same thing happened in supercomputing........X86 or Risc who cares!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363788958069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:15:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363789378892-28</Id><Title>Analysts: Nvidia Can Enter New Markets</Title><Msg>Fidelity National Information Services (NYSE:FIS): FIS entered into a seven-year agreement with FirstBank Puerto Rico under which it is to assume full on-site operational responsibility for the bank’s IT operations and staff. FIS is to gain operational control of FirstBank Puerto Rico’s IT operations, and this includes hardware and software upgrades, application management, skilled operations personnel, help desk and desktop services. NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA): After Stifel Nicolaus saw NVIDIA’s presentation at a conference, the firm believes that the company’s new products may allow it to address $20 billion of new markets by the year’s end. Furthermore, the firm says that the company’s investments in mobile and data centers have the potential to reach an inflection point for growth this year, and it reiterates its Buy rating on the stock.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363789378892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:22:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363789791929-29</Id><Title>Presentations yesterday:</Title><Msg>investor meeting was solid GTC keynote was boring !!! The first half was slow moving...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363789791929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:29:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363790499904-30</Id><Title>What if...</Title><Msg>Some one...A Hedge Fund or a company, wants to launch a hostile take over this POS company And shake off and kick out this mgmt? I want to understand what strategy, or better...what "EXCUSES" the mgmt will put on the table to avoid it? That they're "creating" some kind of shareholder value in first place? This company have all the right "numbers" for someone to take it over... 1- About $4B. Cash equivalents 2- Is generating good amounts of cash-flows 3- Virtually very little or no debt 4- Current assets nearly 5 times current liabilities 5- Excellent market penetration and scalable technology But this stock is stuck in the $12 range since more than a year or 2 and mgmt and CEO seems that they don't care absolutely of what is going on. So I will be glad when some one will come and start kicking some bu.t.t here.</Msg><Username>misterx.herrx</Username><Timestamp>1363790499904</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363790643405-31</Id><Title>There Goes The Enterprise PC Market!</Title><Msg>"Live systems featuring NVIDIA GRID K1 and K2 boards will demonstrate how NVIDIA Kepler™ architecture-based technology maximizes server utilization and, when scaled out, can support over 600 users per 42U rack in existing reference designs, and with a forthcoming 4U FatTwin configuration can support 1,800+ users per rack. Combined with increased security and system manageability, NVIDIA GRID delivers the most flexible, accelerated VDI experience for end users. In addition to the demos, Supermicro executives will present strategies and server architecture designs to consider when selecting GPU platforms for HPC, cloud and workstation applications. "Supermicro is a leader in GPU computing solutions," said Charles Liang, President and CEO of Supermicro. "We truly focus on hardware optimization to maximize performance per watt, per dollar, per square foot. With platforms ranging from 12 GPUs in our 4U power saving FatTwin to the widest variety of 3U, 2U and 1U SuperServer solutions, Supermicro has the reach to provide the absolute best GPU cluster solutions quickly for any customer requirement. With virtualization at the forefront of this year's GTC, Supermicro will be showing our expertise and readiness for this new revolution in GPU computing." "NVIDIA and Supermicro are bringing to market a high-density server platform for virtual desktops and applications," said Ed Ellett, Senior Vice President of NVIDIA's Professional Solutions Business. "The Supermicro servers set a new standard for high-density NVIDIA GRID deployments, delivering high user densities with maximized performance, power conservation and ROI, thus removing conventional barriers to VDI deployments." ________________________________________________________________________ Gee - Two of the Big 4 pushing this Nvidia Grid are PC makers----HP and Dell. I wonder what they know? This company has a presence and want's in too! Wonder what IDC's take on this regrading the Enterprise PC market will be latter</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363790643405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:44:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363792414559-32</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia updates its GPU roadmap at GTC 2013</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363788784321</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:13:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't wait for Volta.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363792414559</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363793083323-33</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>rotten1mable1</Username><Timestamp>1363793083323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363793698919-34</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's road map drives graphics, ARM into enterprise</Title><Username>bobsumrall1961</Username><Timestamp>1363787840800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:57:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Dell, Hewlett-Packard and IBM are among companies who will make Grid Enterprise servers and appliances for large and small businesses. Citrix, Microsoft and VMWare are among those making the software. The move is a small step toward greater head-to-head competition between the graphics chip maker and the x86 giant. In the background, Nvidia is still developing its Project Denver a suit of ARM-based SoCs intended to enable a full range of systems from notebooks to supercomputers. Nvidia will pave the way for such chips this week, announcing its Cuda software for general-purpose graphics (GPGPUs) computing is now running on ARM processors. At least one supercomputer developer will talk about using Cuda on ARM at GTC." _________________________________________________________________________ Of course EEtimes goes right to the heart of the matter. This could get very ugly for Intel.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363793698919</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:34:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363793783119-35</Id><Title>Bloomberg: NVIDIA' next mobile chip to enable PC graphics</Title><Msg>........ Logan’s Capability Huang said the next version of Nvidia’s Tegra mobile processor, called Logan and due in 2014, will feature the graphics capability usually found in full-sized personal computers. "It does everything a modern computer ought to do,” he said yesterday. “We should see Logan in production early next year.” Under Huang, who co-founded the company in 1993, Nvidia has pushed into new areas, seeking to shore up sales as other companies’ semiconductors take on more of the graphics processing once done by Nvidia’s chips. As part of the company’s diversification, Nvidia will begin selling a server built around its processors that will let companies turn their network PCs into more powerful workstations by streaming computing to them, Huang said. Nvidia also said it has signed up Hewlett-Packard Co. (HPQ), Dell Inc., Cisco Systems Inc. and International Business Machines Corp. to build servers on its graphics chips. Nvidia, based in Santa Clara, California, was a pioneer of specialized chips that improved graphics and brought lifelike images to computer screens. Its newer products are used in mobile phones, tablets and cars, and the company plans to begin selling a portable gaming console. Nvidia gets more than 60 percent of sales from the graphics processors it makes for other companies’ PCs, consoles and tablets. bloombergDOTcom/news/2013-03-19/nvidia-ceo-says-next-mobile-chip-to-enable-pc-caliber-graphics.html</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363793783119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:36:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363796961489-36</Id><Title>Nice price action</Title><Msg>Any takers on an explanation for the very nice price action all of a sudden today?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363796961489</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363797021412-37</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job. Informational article.</Msg><Username>nanakusaclaire</Username><Timestamp>1363797021412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363797053950-38</Id><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Msg>"It's an investment thesis so simple it could be written in a Google (GOOG) doc. Short or sell Nvidia (NVDA). The upcoming Tegra 4 from Nvidia is not going to be powering the next version of Google's Nexus 7 tablet. And, frankly, it's really no surprise because, despite the hyperventilating of Nvidia's PR staff, the Tegra 4 is the wrong SoC for pretty much anything below a 10" or bigger specialty tablet, and even then it is iffy. Qualcomm (QCOM) is, a Snapdragon 600, and likely would have had won both the original Nexus 7 and the Microsoft (MSFT) Surface RT last year had TMSC's 28 nm process not been having yield trouble, delaying the Snapdragon S4 rollout. Now that is behind them and Qualcomm can and is shipping seemingly billions of its Snapdragons in all variants, there is little to no room for the Tegra 4 in the market place. Even if the Tegra 4 is faster at some level than the best Qualcomm has to offer, it is yet again another iteration of the Intel (INTC) vs. AMD (AMD) debate of building a faster path to a dead end. Who cares if you can eke out slightly better SunSpider scores if your SoC uses twice the power and costs four times as much to make? This question is the bane of enthusiasts and most of the tech press - cool technology does not equate with good product. And from where I sit, the Tegra 4 is the blocked punt in the CPU equivalent of a three and out in football. Look at the reasons cited by Google as to why it chose the Snapdragon over the Tegra 4 - cost, integrated LTE and, most importantly, availability. Simply put, in every way, Qualcomm's SoCs are simply better value and more reliably available than anything Nvidia has or will have anytime soon. Nvidia doesn't have TMSC to help prop them up for another four quarters."</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363797135668-39</Id><Topic><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, yeah, short Nvidia. $6/share in cash, no debt, $1/share per year in FCF, expanding graphics business, compelling Tegra roadmap (if a bit too aggressive), and strong management. Short away!!!</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363797135668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:32:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363797208047-40</Id><Title>Tom L article #2</Title><Msg>Look at the reasons cited by Google as to why it chose the Snapdragon over the Tegra 4 - cost, integrated LTE and, most importantly, availability. Simply put, in every way, Qualcomm's SoCs are simply better value and more reliably available than anything Nvidia has or will have anytime soon. Nvidia doesn't have TMSC to help prop them up for another four quarters. Simply put, I have to agree with Charlie over at Semiaccurate who has been pounding the table for a long time saying that the 4+1 core structure started with the Tegra 3 was not only a poor design choice but it was also the third in a series of under-delivered promises made to phone and tablet OEMs. Quad core SoCs running Android in 2012 were a stupid marketing ploy. And then they made things worse by adding another core to manage, driving up complexity to "plaid." The 4+1 core is vastly more complicated than a properly constructed dual core or even vanilla quad-core processor. Complexity adds to cost and cost equals no uptake by OEMs in phones because there is no room for being outside of design spec. Even the mighty Samsung (SSNLF.PK) had to turn to Qualcomm to power some of the latest Galaxy S4 line because big.LITTLE is hard to pull off and the Exynos Octa is not ready. So, not only did Nvidia not learn from the Tegra 3 -- taking those 10 million pity sales thanks to a screwed up 28nm marketplace as a sign of a job well done - it repeated it because nothing says success like failure. Since then, it has tried to tell everyone it's something it isn't, namely capable of competing with anything else on the market. And when the customer that handed you 6 million of those 10 million in sales bolts for your rival, someone has to be willing to finally yell, "Iceberg dead ahead."</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797208047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363797312816-41</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg: NVIDIA' next mobile chip to enable PC graphics</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363793783119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:36:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA): After Stifel Nicolaus saw NVIDIA’s presentation at a conference, the firm believes that the company’s new products may allow it to address $20 billion of new markets by the year’s end. Furthermore, the firm says that the company’s investments in mobile and data centers have the potential to reach an inflection point for growth this year, and it reiterates its Buy rating on the stock.</Msg><Username>blulackao</Username><Timestamp>1363797312816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:35:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363797324597-42</Id><Title>Tom L hit piece #3</Title><Msg>And it's not only Google that has shunned Nvidia here. So has Asus and other OEMs that bought into the hype of the Tegra 3 only to have it fail to live up to expectations and cost them money. In order to even get the Nexus 7 and Surface RT contracts, Nvidia had to build them the reference platform to prove it could hit a design spec which was realistic; down-clocking the Tegra 3 to the point of making it painful to use in an 11" form factor. Honestly, while I really like a lot of what Microsoft has done in the past year, the Surface RT was a sincere mistake in every conceivable way. But, given the state of tablet SoC's last year, there wasn't much for it to work with. They didn't have the clout in the channel to pry some of those precious Snapdragons away so they settled for the least ugly solution available. Honestly, Nvidia is the easiest short idea in technology. Its main business in discrete cards is dying. Games are moving to mobile. Even consoles are going to be a tough sell this winter at any price point above $399. Its primary partner in crime, Intel, is likely going to throw it under the bus with Broadwell only kind of sort of supporting a wide enough PCIe bus to allow discrete cards to function. It has no prayer of competing long-term in the ARM SoC world, regardless of how good its engineers are, and will not be dictating the path of graphics software development for games since it had no viable solution for any of the next generation game consoles. It should say something loud and clear when AMD in 2012 was viewed as more reliable and more capable than Nvidia to Sony (SNE), Nintendo (NTDOF.PK) and Microsoft. How many Tegra 4's will Nvidia sell this year if it even ships working silicon? How many Jaguar-cores will AMD? There is a reason why AMD won all three of them and it isn't because Nvidia didn't want the business.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797324597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:35:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363797453685-43</Id><Topic><Title>Nice price action</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363796961489</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yesterday's presentations...;) I think the BIG PMs were too busy to watch, yesterday, and finally looked at last night or this morning. ANYONE who watched HAD to be WOWED, unless they're blind, dumb, or have NO vision. Grid VCA is a HUGE "surprise". There had been NO rumors about this, and once it sinks in, people will realize that Jen has once again REINVENTED the company and opened a HUGE NEW market for the company. Volume is picking up, too, and I won't be surprised if we see it accelerate to 12-15mm, late today, and the price should go with it to 12.75-12.85, at a minimum. As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. M</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1363797453685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:37:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363797491794-44</Id><Title>Tom L hit piece #4</Title><Msg>"Then let's watch the carnage in the graphics space as AMD continues to work towards mobile dual graphics with first Richland and then Kaveri, which should bury any thought of a place for Nvidia at that table either. It's not that all of its products are bad, it's that not enough of them will be good enough real soon now. I have to laugh at the latest report from Trefis trying to tell us that Nvidia's chips are close to competitive from a cost perspective. $25 for a Tegra 3? A 2012 SoC selling at a comparable price to a 2013 one from Qualcomm is going to seriously accrete to the bottom line? Does it even make any money on those at that price? The Tegra 4i is a quad A9 with an LTE modem that the market has moved on by before it has even shipped. Where will that compete at the price it'll cost to make? Nowhere close to the cost of a quad-core A7 like MediaTek is producing for the low-end of the market, but that's where it will have to compete to get wins. Nvidia is not Intel. It can't buy its phone design wins with inferior chips and buy media coverage with it. Nvidia may still be making money but it will not be for long if it cannot sell its flagship product and at this point who will buy it? HP is rumored to be kicking the Tegra 4 tires but it is seriously cozying up to AMD for Kabini and Temash allocations. Somehow the price and margin conscious HP (HPQ) and Tegra 4 just don't seem like a good fit, no matter how desperate HP is to make an Android tablet. The Tegra line was supposed to be Nvidia's way out of this mess all those years ago, but after you've ticked off the OEMs three times for not delivering on your promises that path is now honestly closed. Nvidia should have let Intel buy it when the rumors were floating around a few years ago. By now the two could have merged into a formidable opponent to Qualcomm, Apple (AAPL) and Samsung. As it stands now I fully expect it to be sold for parts and IP by the time the dust settles on this era of computing"</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797491794</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:38:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363798111435-45</Id><Topic><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf, I was on that article's comment section and Josh P responded to him, well I think, but this author's response along with the article showed a lack of understanding about the company and the products in play now, especially the GRID VCA. This author also says he respects your writing and you guys have a cordial relationship .. I 'm sure you get along fine with all the SA writers as you should but this guy is a good example of why I don't have a lot of respect, really negligible at best, for SA. He isn't writing an article with decent research or conclusions that are remotely objective.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1363798111435</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:48:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363798776222-46</Id><Topic><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right from the start he was wrong for saying that Qaulcomm likely would have had won both the original Nexus 7 and the Microsoft (MSFT) Surface RT last year had TMSC's 28 nm process not been having yield trouble, delaying the Snapdragon S4 rollout.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363798776222</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:59:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363798796816-47</Id><Topic><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Roundhouse_c The method of payment is clicks on SA....driven by Title first and foremost. Everyone needs to make a living. Need I say more?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363798796816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:59:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799330250-48</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg: NVIDIA' next mobile chip to enable PC graphics</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363793783119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:36:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Logan with Kepler CUDA core @28nm or 20nm will widen the gap from competitors. To be a winer in the long run, NV has doing a good job in plan out product roadmap and leverage GPU's capability to create new market. And the beauty of Tegra 5 is its product schedule is much more attractive for device makers.</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1363799330250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:08:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799999641-49</Id><Topic><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With NVDA product roadmap and their ability in creating new markets, to short NVDA at current price will make you not comfortable to sleep at night.</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1363799999641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:19:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363800835115-50</Id><Topic><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My issue is that he didn't cite any real market data + he seems to blindly champion AMD. Discrete GPUs have grown over the last couple of years quite nicely despite Ivy Bridge/Sandy Bridge/Llano/Trinity, and they will continue to do so.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363800835115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:33:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363800905340-51</Id><Title>More about Kayla, the world's fastest ARM computer</Title><Msg>SOURCE: Slashdot and JH Huang keynote "...Nvidia wanted to enable ARM computing as soon as it could. “So the guys went and said, we want to see CUDA in ARM right now, so we did,” Huang added. “We went out and built a new GPU, a GPU that you guys have never seen, and we’re going to combine it with ARM to offer the world’s most powerful ARM computer.” And what was it? “Kayla,” a board combining Nvidia’s Tegra chips, which will merge both Logan and a Tegra 3 with PCI Express. Huang said that Logan will be the size of a dime and require no fans or heat sinks; he demonstrated the system’s ability to perform real-time ray tracing, just like its desktop GeForce chips. Will Kayla enable a new breed of GPU-powered, low-power computers? Time will tell. Nvidia didn’t give a release date for Kayla—but if it is anywhere near Logan’s release date in 2014, things could get interesting. slashdotDOTorg/topic/datacenter/nvidia-tegra-to-add-cuda-parallel-processing-technology/#.UUnn4Erv37c.twitter</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363800905340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:35:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363801098698-52</Id><Topic><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He also doesn't seem to understand the gaming world or the enterprise world for smaller businesses because he lumps the console business for AMD in with the GRID VCA which really is intended for more than the gaming world. Jen made that plainly clear with the companies that joined him in demonstrations of the real product in use at the keynote.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1363801098698</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:38:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363801280904-53</Id><Topic><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Makes me want to write an article for SA titled 'Nvidia bought Apple and Made Ballmer Chairman of the Board' so I could get some extra cash :). Insert your best title in your reply here for extra cash . .</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1363801280904</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:41:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363801485467-54</Id><Title>Whats Tegra Rev Outlook for 2013</Title><Msg>Did Jen say if he expects growth in Tegra this year ? I know its largely 2014 story now but wondering how the revenue is being modeled for 2013</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1363801485467</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363801501127-55</Id><Title>Tegra Stark vs Parker</Title><Msg>Previously, Jensen said Stark would be the first to get PD cores... Now it's Parker... The good news is they are making many variants of Tegra to go after more markets... Moving away from the one size fits all...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363801501127</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:45:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363801667854-56</Id><Topic><Title>Whats Tegra Rev Outlook for 2013</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1363801485467</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:44:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Always a spin of doom from you... He previously said Tegra revenue would 2H loaded for 2013... Tegra 4i is 2014, Tegra 5 is 2014</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363801667854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:47:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363801802869-57</Id><Topic><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Enterprise Computing is Dead - Short Oracle" "Nvidia Grid Cloud Brings Steve Jobs Back To Life" of course then we can have the good old S/A cat fight between authors to build up those clicks. I even go into the list of articles now and refuse to even click on certain authors.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363801802869</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363802003337-58</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got it. Good job mate.</Msg><Username>oz11evelyn</Username><Timestamp>1363802003337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363803477662-59</Id><Title>NVIDIA Grid milestones (for all 3 market initiatives)</Title><Msg>.......................................Q1.................................Q2..................................Q3.....................................Q4 Grid Gaming...............6 partners......................................................................................................production .....................................20 trials............................................................................................................................. Grid Enterprise.........VDI &amp; OEM....................................................................................................................... .....................................production........................................................................................................................ ....................................75 trials.............................................................................................................................. Grid VCA...................Grid VCA &amp; ISVs.........VAR program.......................................................................... ....................................announcement............launch...................................................................................... ...................................15 trials..........................production............................................................................... SOURCE: NVIDIA Investors: GTC 2013 Analyst Presentation</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363803477662</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:17:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363803632919-60</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Grid milestones (for all 3 market initiatives)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363803477662</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:17:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Format all messed up, sorry. Information came from Slide #26 of the Analyst presentation, March 19.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363803632919</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:20:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363803835438-61</Id><Title>The meaning of Samsung's 4K TV - it will cost you $40K</Title><Msg>cnetDOTcom/8301-33199_7-57575315-221/samsung-4k-tv-itll-cost-you-$40k/</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363803835438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:23:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363805401205-62</Id><Topic><Title>Tom L hit piece #4</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797491794</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:38:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Best bashers money can buy? Must not have much money after their losing short positions.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1363805401205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363805781724-63</Id><Title>MUST SEE video: Project Shield powers a Parrot AR Drone at GTC 2013</Title><Msg>Were you one of the people that thought Project SHIELD was pointless? Prepare to eat your words. Here at GTC, I caught a glimpse of an NVIDIA employee flying his new Parrot AR Drone, running on Project SHIELD. Flying the drone is cool all by itself, but with SHIELD, you are able to view what the drone sees on that crisp 720p display, and control the drone much more accurately with the SHIELD’s joysticks. droid-lifeDOTcom/2013/03/20/video-nvidias-project-shield-powers-a-parrot-ar-drone/</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363805781724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363805818472-64</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good move. I will be expecting for more news.</Msg><Username>olgerdlorena</Username><Timestamp>1363805818472</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:56:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363807632706-65</Id><Title>$1 trading range for half a ear</Title><Msg>What stock does that???!!</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1363807632706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363807832068-66</Id><Title>Still no volume, kvimax1...</Title><Msg>Waiting for a breakout in NVDA is like waiting for Godot...</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363807832068</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:30:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363809110918-67</Id><Topic><Title>More about Kayla, the world's fastest ARM computer</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363800905340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:35:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They showed a demo of a working Kayla... it's a development platform for Logan... When Logan launches, developers could already have their CUDA on ARM running...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363809110918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363809120652-68</Id><Topic><Title>Still no volume, kvimax1...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363807832068</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:30:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>msians, Max was kind enough to share with us his market views, all of us as, public forum participants, should use our own discretion in using any information posted in such context. You sounded like you were holding someone responsible for lack of volume, price pop, etc - such "pseudo" harassment responses could really stifle useful discussions in the future.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363809120652</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:52:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363809485973-69</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one. I will subscribe now.</Msg><Username>pc2141tasha</Username><Timestamp>1363809485973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:58:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363809936449-70</Id><Topic><Title>$1 trading range for half a ear</Title><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1363807632706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:27:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dividend helped give it a floor... the stock being stuck represents NVIdia being a year behind their roadmap...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363809936449</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363809939504-71</Id><Topic><Title>Still no volume, kvimax1...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363807832068</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:30:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harassment? Give me a break, dude. I'm just frustrated, like all longs, that there's still no volume or confidence in Nvidia's prospects. I appreciate kvimax1's posts, actually, and hope he keeps them coming.</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363809939504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:05:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363810613238-72</Id><Title>NVIDIA VCA + AWS, or how to turn your ipad into a workstation</Title><Msg>NVIDIA VCA + AWS or How to turn an iPad into a Workstation #GTC2013 On the same day I was shown NVIDIA’s VCA cloud graphics hardware platform I was briefed by AWS (Amazon Web Services) and the two offerings seemed natural for each other. Amazon’s services have advanced significantly since their launch and they now sport customers in Pharma and Government, two of the most secure segments. NVIDIA graphics appliance is designed to host up to 16 virtual sessions and in a cloud service could provide workstation performance on any supported internet device like an iPad. Separately these two offerings are very powerful but together, woof. Sources: suliaDOTcom/channel/all-tech-science/f/d8063e5d-ff57-49e7-a682-74b33fcced39/?source=twitter itbusinessedgeDOTcom/blogs/unfiltered-opinion/nvidia-vca-aws-or-how-to-turn-an-ipad-into-a-workstation.html</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363810613238</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:16:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363813376117-73</Id><Topic><Title>$1 trading range for half a ear</Title><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1363807632706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:27:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>btw, if you want encouragement... Have you noticed Best's employer has given him a holiday...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363813376117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363813848476-74</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fantastic. I will check it out.</Msg><Username>museumsssheryl</Username><Timestamp>1363813848476</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:10:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363814292247-75</Id><Topic><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Short Nvidia: Graphics Cards Are Dead, Man"</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363814292247</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:18:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363815153337-76</Id><Topic><Title>$1 trading range for half a ear</Title><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1363807632706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:27:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All of you guys and ladies "owe me one". After agonizing and wrestling for the past 5 months with this stock, I decided today to get out. By getting out it's a lead-pipe-cinch the stock will now begin performing, and no longer trade like a typical garden variety, go nowhere fast, stock. It wore me out, and too there are simply too many other opportunities to invest in.</Msg><Username>rlday2010</Username><Timestamp>1363815153337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363816526852-77</Id><Topic><Title>$1 trading range for half a ear</Title><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1363807632706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:27:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"After agonizing and wrestling for the past 5 months with this stock" Then why did you get in when NVidia lowered guidance... what did you expect ??</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363816526852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363817827866-78</Id><Topic><Title>$1 trading range for half a ear</Title><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1363807632706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:27:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually I was in prior to the guidance announcement. And what did I expect? In a market such as we have enjoyed, I expected the stock to not be a dud, and was wrong. My bad.</Msg><Username>rlday2010</Username><Timestamp>1363817827866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:17:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363818638434-79</Id><Topic><Title>$1 trading range for half a ear</Title><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1363807632706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:27:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I expected the stock to not be a dud, and was wrong. " NVidia knew it wouldn't have much for a year, and lowered their guidance... so declared a dividend to keep the stock from plummeting... the stock NVDA, is subject to NVidia's lack of execution on their roadmap... when NVidia actually starts selling the new products we've been hearing about since forever... the stock will mirror it...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363818638434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:30:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363826619107-80</Id><Topic><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf, think you should use this title and leave the text space blank, just to see how many comments you get . . :). Seriously though as I checked on the SA article, your 'colleague' Tom Loungo just stated very clearly again in the comments section that the T4i is dead on arrival and won't be used by anyone even with plenty of indications in the press, not by Nvidia, that the chip is sampling really well and is likely to be announced in some phones as early as 3Q this year. Honestly, what's the point of responding to such an author if his statements lack any real data or facts to back it up? I'm refusing to add comments to that article, except for the one to support Josh P, because the guy shouldn't be benefiting from an article bordering on willful negligence.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1363826619107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363827178313-81</Id><Title>Tom Luongo Article</Title><Msg>1. "Opportunity loss" if he were to spend 5 seconds to short 100K shares of Nvidia and according to his computation - he would make unlimited amount of $$$. Really boils down to him being a Chicken Hawk! All YOU People should short it .... YOU definitely will make a ton of $$$ ... yeah ... while I hide in the bunker! Talk about lame, spineless and moronic 2. AMD is going to conquer the world ..... yeah right! Stooopidestest comment - how many times have we heard that in the last 20 years .... from people who have more GREY stuff up there than this tomcat. Each time they said that, AMD seems to sink a deeper. Right AMD is almost up to their ears in the BOG! And this moronic writer tells YOU to jump in while he stays on the sideline because he's got other stuff to make money off that may cause another "Opportunity Loss" .. how very laughable. Other bigger opportunities ??? DON"T make me laugh - A GUY WHO MAKES pennies PER PAGE BY WRITING PAGES AND PAGES OF GARBAGE ON SA - WOW - THIS WOULD BE A big LOST Opportunity if he were to spend 5 seconds shorting NVIDIA instead of another SA Garbage, and MAKE THE BIG BUCKS LIKE HE CONCLUDED. Chicken $#$%. Beware of the garbage man who's trying to sell you his thrash as an investment opportunity! 3. May be he is a little smarter than we give him credit for - may be he's paid by some of these guys - in which case he is getting DIMES instead of PENNIES. May be it's Barclays or may be it's AMD or may be it's both. This is pure speculation due to a loss of convincing supporting research in the article. 4. SA in some instances like the FOOL is a license for very low quality hit jobs. This is one of them.</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1363827178313</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:52:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363827484400-82</Id><Title>HTC One (S600) delayed because suppliers think it is no longer a tier-one customer</Title><Msg>""HTC One fans were disappointed to learn last week that the phone had been delayed to late March or early April. Now,The Wall Street Journal reports that the flagship meant to turn around HTC's performance is being hampered by its past defeats. "The company has a problem managing its component suppliers as it has changed its order forecasts drastically and frequently following last year's unexpected slump in shipments," says an unnamed executive. He and others blamed the One's delay on shortages, particularly of the metal casing and camera parts. "HTC has had difficulty in securing adequate camera components as it is no longer a tier-one customer." SOURCE: thevergeDOTcom/2013/3/19/4122798/htc-one-delayed-because-of-component-shortage PS: Snubbed by component suppliers? - that's a first. PPS: WSJ just reported that HTC CEO might be let go if the ONE phone turns out to be a flop. Nice start for Snapdragon 600.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363827484400</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:58:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363828352839-83</Id><Topic><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Roundhouse, Just a heads up Digitimes is saying AMD is cutting AMU prices. If you comment just go back a post gibberish against his baby.....but why bother...just doesn't make any sense to pay attention to free advice that is paid by how controversial it is. Citi cut Intel's price target tonight and I expected Barrons tech trader to provide his usual roundup of analyst comments on Nvidia but he didn't. Very strange, Seen 3 so far Evercore Partners Patrick Wang currently with a sell rating just said Conference was encouraging but wanted to see trends...He was referring to enterprise Nvidia Grid. He is the guy that keeps calling Nvidia as a PC graphics company. Nomura - reiterated buy Stiefel - reiterated buy still waiting for Nvidia's Investment banker who ever they might be...Morgan Stanley, GS, Barclays, UBS, Merril Lynch/B of A, Jeffries to come out and say something. Oh was I just listing some of the sponsors of the GTC conference. Can't wait to find out he is handling the ASRs. I thought they had to put the info in the 10Q's, 10K's but it wasn't there for 4Q...just the amount and the number of shares and the price paid. First time I have ever seen the investment bank left unnamed.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363828352839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:12:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363829682813-84</Id><Topic><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>roundhouse_c, I'll try to get an article out at some point to try to clean up that mess. I try not to write too much about Nvidia these days, but when I see stuff like Mr. Luongo's short recommendation, I usually find it in me to put something together.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363829682813</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:34:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363830518107-85</Id><Title>Nvdia dissappointed with Window's RT sales.</Title><Msg>Saw this note on Bloomberg TV.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363830518107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:48:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363832394404-86</Id><Topic><Title>Nvdia dissappointed with Window's RT sales.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363830518107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:48:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like intel is giddy with their surface sales "Paul"? Windows8 is a debacle, that's all there is to it. After two more full revisions, MSFT MAY get it right.</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1363832394404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:19:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363834529030-87</Id><Topic><Title>Nvdia dissappointed with Window's RT sales.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363830518107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:48:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the score on WinRT vs WinPro was ... 1,000,000 to 500,000</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1363834529030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363835024707-88</Id><Topic><Title>More about Kayla, the world's fastest ARM computer</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363800905340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:35:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>32-bit wth 2G memory running parallel? How far can it go in term of performance?</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1363835024707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 23:03:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363836873474-89</Id><Topic><Title>More about Kayla, the world's fastest ARM computer</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363800905340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:35:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 32Bit Tegra CPU is like the slow moving prop planes on the Titan HPC called Intel. The GPU on Kayla/Logan is like the Mach 5 jets called Tesla K20s. Together they make Beautiful Music ... sorry I mean TeraFlops.</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1363836873474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 23:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>