<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366114583045-1</Id><Topic><Title>Does anyone else have problems with Yahoo message boards?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366048613715</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:56:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i've been having problems with yahoo in general since Monday afternoon, looks like a DNS issue.(??)</Msg><Username>hochborland</Username><Timestamp>1366114583045</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 08:16:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366118637174-2</Id><Topic><Title>Lets face it folks, tegra is a goner. Flat sales in a fast growing market</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366077442316</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:57:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Strange message, strange indeed</Msg><Username>jtjgmtbt</Username><Timestamp>1366118637174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 09:23:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366120320185-3</Id><Topic><Title>Lets face it folks, tegra is a goner. Flat sales in a fast growing market</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366077442316</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:57:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Smartphone market is not growing fastly.. its rather mature... plus, tegra missed an entire quarter of sales and yet entire sales remain flat.. thus, tegra growing greater than 25%... smartphone market growing greater than 25%?</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1366120320185</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 09:52:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366120757404-4</Id><Topic><Title>The Bears are losing their grip.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366036160849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The bears look to have tightened their grip again. Drat! Back under $13...</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1366120757404</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 09:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366125012044-5</Id><Title>Icera Co-Founder No longer With Nvidia</Title><Msg>"Boland co-founded phone baseband chipmaker Icera in 2002, heading up the company as president and CEO for nine years. In 2011, Nvidia — anxious to add radio chips to its mobile processor portfolio — acquired it for $367 million in cash. Boland stayed on as Nvidia’s SVP of mobile communications, but according to his LinkedIn profile Boland left the company in October." gigaomDOTcom/2013/04/15/icera-founder-stan-boland-leaves-nvidia-to-head-up-u-k-wireless-startup-neul/ ______________________________________________________________________________ I hadn't heard about this...wonder why he left?...he had a large yearly retention payment good for four years. Wonder who else he will be taking with him?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1366125012044</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:10:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366127262227-6</Id><Topic><Title>The Bears are losing their grip.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366036160849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're not serious, are you? The ONLY reason the stock didn't recover, yesterday, was the attack in Boston. The entire market was trying to rally back when the news hit at 3PM, and so, given it was The Final Hour, and no one knew what had really happened, ALL the bids disappeared. We've already been back over 13 multiple times, today, and I think we're likely to close over that level unless the market completely fades lower. That said, as long as INTC's earnings are NOT MUCH worse than expected, I believe both stocks, and maybe a few others, will rally in the after hours and then again, tomorrow. As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. Max</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366127262227</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366129517848-7</Id><Topic><Title>The Bears are losing their grip.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366036160849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I'm serious. Seems like someone is trying pretty hard to keep this under $13...</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1366129517848</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:25:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366130056482-8</Id><Topic><Title>The Bears are losing their grip.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366036160849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree there's been a monumental effort to keep this below 13 for some time now !!</Msg><Username>apoplectichun</Username><Timestamp>1366130056482</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:34:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366130440767-9</Id><Topic><Title>The Bears are losing their grip.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366036160849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course, they are!! If you've read my posts from last week, this week's OpEx is MUCH more "significant", since there are still 3.7mm shares short via the April 13 calls. They will try or do ANYTHING to keep the stock at 13 or lower, and maybe they'll succeed...I doubt it. And, if they FAIL, we'll be over 13.23-25 and they will realize that it's "game over" for the "selling calls with impunity" trade, and like some on this board, they will have to buy those calls back or buy more stock against them or just lose their stock as it flies to 14 and then 15. Volume on yesterday's "sell off" was relatively light...10.5mm shares, with 1.5mm shares in the LAST 10 MINUTES. Today's volume, however, is already higher than it was at 2:30PM, yesterday, and I suspect we'll see it get to 12+mm, today. I don't know how long you've been involved with the markets, but I've been around since late 1977. I've "seen it all", so to speak, and it was VERY clear that the "tenor" of the trading in this stock changed DRAMATICALLY last week. As some people panicked when Jen announced the sacrifice of 1 quarter of Tegra sales to bring Tegra 4i 2 quarters CLOSER, the "strong hands" buyers bought their shares. That's what I meant when I said it was like "changing partners" at a dance. Unless this is your ONLY stock, and you NEED to get your money out, now, just sit back, relax and enjoy the ride higher. I have really tried to help you and others understand what's going on, but I won't continue to respond to you if you show no patience at THIS critical moment. The BAD NEWS IS OUT...NO BAD news left to reveal. THAT means, we're headed higher, but, no, it's not likely to be just a straight line, although a couple of major 10-20% spikes are quite possible. As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. Best, Max</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366130440767</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:40:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366131647879-10</Id><Topic><Title>The Bears are losing their grip.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366036160849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok, kvimax1, I appreciate your thoughtful posts. I'll try to be patient and enjoy the ride upwards. Wake me up when we take out our record high of near $40...</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1366131647879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:00:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366132299281-11</Id><Topic><Title>Icera Co-Founder No longer With Nvidia</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1366125012044</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:10:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uhm, one of the main presenters at the analysts/investors day conference was the other co-founder, who has stayed with the company . . maybe we are pressing a little bit, ehh? During quiet periods, writers are always looking for some edge in an article.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366132299281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:11:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366132544224-12</Id><Topic><Title>The Bears are losing their grip.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366036160849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would "guess" that if Jen Hsun is successful at what he's working on, now, that that kind of price will be possible in 2015 or 2016...maybe sooner. M</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366132544224</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:15:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366144876046-13</Id><Title>WSJ: pressure on Intel increases as CEO question looms...</Title><Msg>",,,,Current CEO Paul Otellini has disclosed his plans to retire, with his final day set for the company's May 16 annual meeting. There is significant speculation around Silicon Valley right now as to who might land the top job, but the company has made no announcements yet. Most analysts agree on the need for the company to find a leader who can grow the Intel's mobile business. "So while we expect management to reaffirm its growth targets for the year on Tuesday's [conference] call, we don't expect the stock to outperform the market until consumers become more excited about new PC categories or the company lands a high-volume design win in mobile," Ed Snyder of Charter Equity wrote in a note to clients Monday."" SOURCE: WSJ onlineDOTwsjDOTcom/article/BT-CO-20130416-706815.html?mod=WSJ_qtoverview_wsjlatest</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366144876046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366145598988-14</Id><Topic><Title>Icera Co-Founder No longer With Nvidia</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1366125012044</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:10:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just seeing the press release on Boland leaving . . doesn't even bother to mention that the CTO at Nvidia for modems was a co-founder of Icera along with two others and that the CTO Allpress made the best presentation of the speakers at Investor's Day (imo). How much you wanna bet that Boland's decision was based on the fact that his co-founder(s) had a more serious role to play by staying at Nvidia and he had little room to be a key player, so he moved on? This is truly non-news in terms of it's effect on Nvidia. It probably makes it easier to incorporate Icera into the soc and diversify the technology.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366145598988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:53:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366146176620-15</Id><Topic><Title>Icera Co-Founder No longer With Nvidia</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1366125012044</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:10:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is more of a rule, rather than an exception, that the CEO/founder of an acquired company leaves in 2-3 years, if not immediately. This type of "news" is no news, as you properly phrased, and Wall Street analysts won't even think twice about it. However, desperate bashers or those who bet against the stock would try to blow it out of proportion. Futile efforts by the traders who swung the wrong way.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366146176620</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 17:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366150639893-16</Id><Title>Anyone see any news on TXN? Down 2% AH.</Title><Msg>I've looked, but haven't found any news, but there are 5-10k share pieces trading at 35 since 5:10 and just a few minutes ago. It's offered below yesterday's close. M</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366150639893</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366156906417-17</Id><Title>google Glasses, whose processor?</Title><Msg>my guess is the T3. That's right folks, you heard about here first.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1366156906417</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:01:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366157979609-18</Id><Title>new iphones delayed 1 Q</Title><Msg>is it going to benefit samsung and Exynos octo - yes! is it going to benefit qcom and S600 - yes! is it going to benefit nvda and Tegra - NO! such is the sad state of affairs of Jen targeting the wrong market. Sad, real sad.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1366157979609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:19:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366162591263-19</Id><Title>Are there any phones with Icera around? Or is it just Jensen's BS.</Title><Msg>What the heck, may as well pump the sucker up.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366162591263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 21:36:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366168568560-20</Id><Topic><Title>Are there any phones with Icera around? Or is it just Jensen's BS.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366162591263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 21:36:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Posting this for your enlightenment: Based on Intel report today, AMD's market share of all x-86 parts (including PC client, Data center, etc) has been REDUCED to a grand total of 5%. Something for you guys to think about - or rejoice over, eh? lol</Msg><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1366168568560</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 23:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>