<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363407035043-1</Id><Topic><Title>Using "Opportunity cost" as an excuse in this context doesn't make sense</Title><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1363347764260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>J7, I sort of share that hunch. I think that all industries, over time, become stagnant, vanilla and dated and need some kind of "disruptive" refresh in order to breathe new life into them. So, I am definitely a proponent of cloud gaming, as gaming has become stale, but any guess I have as to it's rate of adoption would be pure conjecture at this point. I think the most limited factor is performance - if GRID works well then so will cloud gaming. I see things like this; I think Nvidia has solid product footprint in several if not all of the areas of content delivery and consumption. There isn't one single player in the P.C., Mobile or Enterprise domains that has as complete or as complimentary of a product offering as Nvidia when it comes to gaming and media. It seems obvious to me that Nvidia, unlike it's competition, is in a unique position to leverage all of it'[s technology/IP/products to provide a unique user experience as it pertains to media and games. I think streaming games to shield on your own "private cloud" via your PC is the start of that and possibly GRID on top of shield will become the next. You can look at this way by asking this question; if cloud gaming does gain traction wouldn't it stand to reason that Nvidia "marks" it's Tegra silicon in such a way that it has a SIGNIFICANT technological advantage when used with GRID over the competition? So, as to make sure that more and more devices (mobile, set top boxes, t.v.s etc) have a Tegra chip in em'. Keep in mind; that is just one of many points of differentiation Nvidia has over its competition when it comes to media and a great example of their product synergy (sorry for the buzzword). That is why I bought Nvidia over it's competition. :-)</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1363407035043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 00:10:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363408093948-2</Id><Topic><Title>Using "Opportunity cost" as an excuse in this context doesn't make sense</Title><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1363347764260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>two thumbs up-great post</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1363408093948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 00:28:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363409774168-3</Id><Topic><Title>Using "Opportunity cost" as an excuse in this context doesn't make sense</Title><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1363347764260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brokeagain 73 I very elucidate and informative post. Thanks for taking the time to write it. I completely agree. Thanks P.S. A Long time ago during the dawn of the Internet age, There were a number of companies that skyrocketed in price. Two that I remember very personally were Cisco and JDS Uniphase.. Both provided the infrastructure for the Internet Boom. Cloud Gaming could be the next big thing and what ever company dominates the infrastructure will do very well indeed! P.S. You have to go back to the 1998 to 2000 prices on these stocks to understand where I am coming from.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363409774168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 00:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363409949502-4</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA: We Let AMD Power the PS4</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363377088856</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you forget when you and ibexx posted the same message exactly down to the miss spellings and links within 20 sec. of each other. Ever since then you have been Ibexx to me. Peace</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363409949502</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 00:59:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363415935789-5</Id><Topic><Title>Using "Opportunity cost" as an excuse in this context doesn't make sense</Title><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1363347764260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"stand to reason that Nvidia "marks" it's Tegra silicon in such a way that it has a SIGNIFICANT technological advantage when used with GRID over the competition?" Not in a devious way to exclude competition, but definitely to emphasize the strengths of Tegra. The Tegra / Cloud will have gone thru extensive testing and a better term of tuning both the HW and SW. Also, The GRID is worth more if it works with all devices... not just Tegras....</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363415935789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 02:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363436073395-6</Id><Topic><Title>Detailed NVDA Research Report !</Title><Username>danieljones497</Username><Timestamp>1363186107555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:48:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks !</Msg><Username>philip.durham</Username><Timestamp>1363436073395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 08:14:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363439109357-7</Id><Topic><Title>Detailed NVDA Research Report !</Title><Username>danieljones497</Username><Timestamp>1363186107555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:48:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good one !</Msg><Username>markchester919</Username><Timestamp>1363439109357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:05:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363439331118-8</Id><Title>Galaxy S4 vs. HTC one vs. Tegra 4 - embarrasing for "you know who"</Title><Msg>androidauthorityDOTcom/u-s-galaxy-s4-vs-htc-one-vs-nvidia-tegra-4-benchmark-comparison-172700/</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1363439331118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:08:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363439553085-9</Id><Title>Yet another Chinese phone on T4 in addition to ZTE</Title><Msg>gizchinaDOT/2013/03/15/5-7-inch-1080-beidou-little-pepper-3-will-run-tegra-4-cpu-lte-nfc/</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1363439553085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:12:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363442395368-10</Id><Title>Best Video I've Found On Nvidia Grid - Specs and Potential Business Model</Title><Msg>10 minutes or so note: at time 6:50 - "Tegra optimized for Cloud Gaming. It does a little bit better job of decoding video." youtubeDOTcom/watch?v=k6zwCwUgeGM</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363442395368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363444335441-11</Id><Topic><Title>Galaxy S4 vs. HTC one vs. Tegra 4 - embarrasing for "you know who"</Title><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1363439331118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:08:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm an Nvidia bull, but this comparison is not really legitimate; the T4 is running in a tablet, likely power unconstrained to get those A15's running full throttle. We need to see how T4 performs in a real-world device with a battery ;)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363444335441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 10:32:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363444363569-12</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA compares PS4 specs with a "low-end" CPU</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363393310859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 20:21:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia must be getting some grief from large shareholders about their lake of participation. Everyone knows consoles are not the most profitable business, but it's good for mind-share. The integrated APUs from AMD are really good and the specs may not be top of the line, but they run in parallel and multiply nicely. It not over all power that matters these days, it's how you use the processing power. AMD has it nailed. I built a Trinty based box last november and run a vid card in dual graphics mode and it's VERY smooth. Framerates are not as high as my best machine, but the perceived performance is better in some ways. The the texture quality is remarkable.</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1363444363569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 10:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363444487323-13</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA: We Let AMD Power the PS4</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363377088856</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nvda msg board is unique among yahoo msg boards: Jen has got such an arrogant personality that he would actually pay a brown noser to post here and bash the competitions. Tegras losing $100M a quarter for 2013 while all of nvda's competitors are making good money growing their biz. That says it all.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1363444487323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 10:34:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363444543400-14</Id><Topic><Title>Is IBM WHINING about losing the PlayStaion CPU business like Nvidia is with the GPU business?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363390345665</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 19:32:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD APU chips are no joke.</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1363444543400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 10:35:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363445261867-15</Id><Topic><Title>Galaxy S4 vs. HTC one vs. Tegra 4 - embarrasing for "you know who"</Title><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1363439331118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:08:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure your comment is correct. Just out of curiosity I went to Geekbench2 website to see if there were any noticeable differences between benchmarks in tablets vs. phones. So far I haven't found any. For example below is the Samsung Exynos 4412 1400Mhz dual core processor. Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 Samsung Exynos 4412 1400 MHz (4 cores) 1684 Samsung Galaxy S III (Korea) Samsung Exynos 4412 1400 MHz (4 cores) 1673 As to your battery comment - I doubt even Nvidia marketing would have the Tech journalists run benchmarks and try to fool them with a secret hidden power cord. Some day, oh some day, oh some day, there will be a phone with Tegra 4 in it and it will pop up on Geekbench2 website. browserDotprimatelabsDotcom/android-benchmarks</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363445261867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 10:47:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363446473938-16</Id><Title>GTX TITAN - #1,#2, #9 Top Sellers At Tiger Direct</Title><Msg>Top 10 Sellers 1.EVGA GeForce GTX TITAN 2.EVGA GeForce GTX TITAN.. 3.EVGA GeForce GTX 650 4.EVGA GeForce GTX 680. 5.EVGA Geforce GTX 660. 6.XFX Radeon HD 7970 ... 7.Sapphire Radeon HD 5450 8.EVGA GeForce GTX 660 9.ASUS GeForce GTX TITAN.. 10.EVGA GeForce GTX 690 Source: tigerdirectDOTcom/applications/Category/guidedSearch.asp?CatId=28&amp;name=Video-Cards&amp;cm_sp=Masthead-_-Computer%20Parts-_-Spot%2017 ________________________________________________________________________ That is truly impressive for a $1000 video card!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363446473938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 11:07:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363446749318-17</Id><Topic><Title>GTX TITAN - #1,#2, #9 Top Sellers At Tiger Direct</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363446473938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 11:07:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>j7777kxx, I can tell you as someone who is quite deeply entrenched in the gaming community that the gamers with money are buying these in droves. And they ain't just buying one - they're picking up 2-3 and showing off their beastly new systems on the gamer forums. There will always be a demand for the best-of-the-best flagship GPU, and seeing how "out of stock" these cards are everywhere, I think the folks predicting the demise of the discrete GPU business are sorely mistaken.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363446749318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 11:12:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363447352904-18</Id><Topic><Title>Galaxy S4 vs. HTC one vs. Tegra 4 - embarrasing for "you know who"</Title><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1363439331118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:08:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>j7777kxx, Nvidia is positioning the Tegra 4i for phones - and for good reason. The Cortex A15 really is not a design that will be able to clock high in the phones. See Samsung's "Exynos 5 Octa" - the A15's run at a mere 1.2GHz!</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363447352904</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 11:22:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363447650500-19</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA: We Let AMD Power the PS4</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363377088856</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>J7, you forgot that you left a huge paper trail of misrepresented facts and fabricated numbers, about NVDA and others. Even XC caught you in the act. Remember? just add more to it - it's in your character.</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1363447650500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 11:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363447714498-20</Id><Topic><Title>GTX TITAN - #1,#2, #9 Top Sellers At Tiger Direct</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363446473938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 11:07:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually not a gamer myself. Just do research on the stocks I own. I believe Nvidia is simply put a gaming hardware company and I think of their push into mobile as just a vehicle to sell more gaming hardware. It's obvious to me that Nvidia is trying to catch the Gaming Craze that is exploding. Smartphones are just phones to me unless you have a killer app! Like what they are doing with Nvidia Grid...Cloud Gaming could be the next big thing. Project Shield will make money too, but I they have to get it into the market place soon. Sammie is Coming along with Amazon Cloud Services (Hope they use Nvidia Grid). If not it might be game over. Speed is of the essence.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363447714498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 11:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363449643189-21</Id><Topic><Title>Galaxy S4 vs. HTC one vs. Tegra 4 - embarrasing for "you know who"</Title><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1363439331118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:08:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf, "Nvidia is positioning the Tegra 4i for phones - and for good reason. The Cortex A15 really is not a design that will be able to clock high in the phones." Perhaps....Perhaps not. Anyway......It's apparent to me that the phone market is not where Nvidia is headed this year. One or two design wins with Tegra 4 and then we can all go to Geekbench2 website and see the result. (I actual used it when upgrading my desktop PC and am quite pleased with the result.....A no spin zone if you will). As to battery life......will see but liked what I saw on the MWC videos. Both on Tegra 4I and Tegra 4 phone. Anyway tegra 4i is a ways away....1st thing that has to happen is that PR release saying At&amp;T has certified I500 for VoLTE. But back to my original them - Nvidia is a gaming hardware company and I simply believe Cloud Gaming is about to explode. Time is of the essence. Heck even staid old Intel and AMD recognize this and have made venture capital investments with two separate Cloud gaming companies. AMD went with CIINOW and I forget who Intel went with. As you know Nvidia is lined up with 6 and you might not know this but Amazon Cloud Service is hiring for a potential run at cloud gaming. Sammie introduces Galaxy S4 with a Gamepad controller attachment due in May. Even good old Qualcomm announced last month they were hiring 35 game developers. Hoping Nvidia catches the wave....Take a look at the Youtube video I posted. Nvid'a's lower level marketing person makes an excellent presentation on Nvidia Grid.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363449643189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 12:00:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363453558205-22</Id><Topic><Title>Best Video I've Found On Nvidia Grid - Specs and Potential Business Model</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363442395368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks j777kxx, no doubt you'll jump out of your chair with unbridled enthusiasm when I mention cloud gaming... back to the video 7M bit / sec 30ms lag 720 p some heavy compression going on there... nevertheless, they think they can do it.... going after cable &amp; telco</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363453558205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 13:05:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363454723788-23</Id><Topic><Title>Best Video I've Found On Nvidia Grid - Specs and Potential Business Model</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363442395368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With all the collaberation with amazon on cloud computing over the last year i'm surprised they haven't come out of the shadows for cloud gaming yet.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1363454723788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 13:25:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363454749706-24</Id><Topic><Title>GTX TITAN - #1,#2, #9 Top Sellers At Tiger Direct</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363446473938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 11:07:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>j7, you seem to know what you're writing about, which is incredibly appreciated vs an onslaught of bs on this board. I'm long NVDA several months,and am slowly becoming frustrated with meeker rallies, and then the expected sell off. Yesterday I was reading that in 2019, yada yada, all with be good, while I don't invest to sit around waiting (6) years.</Msg><Username>rlday2010</Username><Timestamp>1363454749706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 13:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363455425180-25</Id><Topic><Title>Detailed NVDA Research Report !</Title><Username>danieljones497</Username><Timestamp>1363186107555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:48:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report !</Msg><Username>oyolam</Username><Timestamp>1363455425180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 13:37:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363455955581-26</Id><Topic><Title>GTX TITAN - #1,#2, #9 Top Sellers At Tiger Direct</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363446473938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 11:07:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>j7777kxx, "Nvidia is simply put a gaming hardware company and I think of their push into mobile as just a vehicle to sell more gaming hardware. It's obvious to me that Nvidia is trying to catch the Gaming Craze that is exploding. Smartphones are just phones to me unless you have a killer app!" Well, think about it - in a world where most apps will run on cheap, "good enough" hardware, what is the ONE consumer market segment impervious to this "good enough" phenomenon? Gaming.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363455955581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 13:45:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363461501406-27</Id><Topic><Title>Best Video I've Found On Nvidia Grid - Specs and Potential Business Model</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363442395368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>J7, This is a great a video and super informative for anyone interested in what the possibilities are for cloud gaming. I really wanted to comment on this post as a epilogue to our conversation yesterday. There are two things that stuck out to me in this video which I think are very important mentions. 1. Nvida mentioned GRID working over LTE (4?) and not just wired broadband. So, WOW! That is the first time I heard that from "horses" mouth and I really think (coming from a technology background) that running over LTE is a testament to the validity of the technology. If you recall in my post yesterday I commented that I thought if the tech was good it would be adopted - well, I think this opens even more doors and WILL amplify the adoption very possibly on an order of magnitude than if it were wired only. Secondly, having this work over LTE, further amplifies the synergy between GRID- Shield- Tegra. 2. Another point I made was the unique product offering Nvidia has over its competition and thus the technical/product leverage they have (could have) specifically in the gaming/media consumption domain. Well, at about 6:50 seconds in while demonstrating GRID on the (ASUS I believe) T3 tablet he (and I will paraphrase here comments; "...this has a T3 processor in it and it is optimized for cloud gaming because it does a better job of decoding the video." I think that comment speaks volumes - although the stream is simply an H.264 stream which could be decoding on any proc( CPU/GPU) either on the die or in the software stack it shows me that from, at least a marketing perspective, Nvidia is attempting to leverage it's branding and the perception that its in house products compliment one another better than the competitions. Not much unlike Qualcomm and the marketing/tech/advantage it had with an on die base-band.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1363461501406</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 15:18:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363462838655-28</Id><Topic><Title>Detailed NVDA Research Report !</Title><Username>danieljones497</Username><Timestamp>1363186107555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:48:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks</Msg><Username>roger.morris</Username><Timestamp>1363462838655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 15:40:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363464376445-29</Id><Title>Do you want to pay $70 for 1 game?</Title><Msg>In fact, price and underlying costs have become a key factor behind the success of gaming consoles going forward. And this is closely linked to the price and availability of gaming titles. Publishers have disagreed over the development costs of the next generation PS4 and Xbox games, leading to concerns that the cost of these titles will rise. An analyst from Wedbush Securities Research has predicted that these games will cost around $70. SCEA CEO Jack Tretton says PS4 titles will not cost more than $60. But that has done little to allay these concerns. This may directly affect sales of the new consoles because many of the new titles can be played on both current as well as next generation consoles. This means that only staunch loyalists will buy these consoles when they are first introduced. Instead, they are likely to wait for prices to drop. This is far from good news for console makers. Console-makers have already made key decisions to drive down costs. Unlike, the past where consoles ran on custom made chips, both Sony and Microsoft will use off-the-shelf chips produced by chip maker Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (AMD). AMD’s chips are able to deliver the required visual horsepower using accelerated processing units or APUs. The risk here is that the success of these platforms is now closely tied to the fortunes of AMD. This negates the need to set up dedicated chip manufacturing facilities or ordering custom made chips as was done in the past from the likes of IBM (IBM). Besides, focus has shifted from raw processing power to the versatility of these chips. Consoles are increasingly being used to play audio and video content as well, morphing into a central entertainment hub for the home. This fits into the trend where tablets and smartphones are changing the face of gaming, at least of mobile gaming at any rate. They are also being viewed as versatile entertainment devices. They have also popularized casual gaming which is growing as a category, giving traditional console makers much food for thought.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1363464376445</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 16:06:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363465074354-30</Id><Topic><Title>Best Video I've Found On Nvidia Grid - Specs and Potential Business Model</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363442395368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>brokeagain73 Your right about LTE Did you catch the part where the Nvidia guy in answering a question said something about how it would work and then said "even If we decide to do it ourselves, this is how it will work". 2nd time I heard that kind of reference to the possibility Nvidia might do it themselves. Jensen in an interview at CES mentioned Amazon Cloud Services in passing and then said something like it could be co-hosted or we could do it ourselves! I can't imagine the potential of this on say Verizon, At&amp;T, etc. and Amazon Cloud Services.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363465074354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 16:17:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363467372378-31</Id><Topic><Title>Best Video I've Found On Nvidia Grid - Specs and Potential Business Model</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363442395368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's hard to wrap my head around how big this could be. As big as or bigger than Netflix? Every kid in America plays some sort of video game at some point.</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1363467372378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 16:56:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363471704454-32</Id><Topic><Title>Best Video I've Found On Nvidia Grid - Specs and Potential Business Model</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363442395368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, there's probably a lot of money in selling these things...</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363471704454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 18:08:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363473741107-33</Id><Topic><Title>Best Video I've Found On Nvidia Grid - Specs and Potential Business Model</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363442395368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia is extremely well positioned across the board, and ahead of the competition in many ways for when cloud gaming really takes off. The fact that they initiated the dividend in the face of increasing R&amp;D funding shows how confident that they are in the future. I think the first substantial release of in-depth cloud related information and initiatives will be released next week during the GTC conference.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363473741107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 18:42:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363473993720-34</Id><Topic><Title>Detailed NVDA Research Report !</Title><Username>danieljones497</Username><Timestamp>1363186107555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:48:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for sharing .</Msg><Username>brian.rossi</Username><Timestamp>1363473993720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 18:46:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363475614436-35</Id><Topic><Title>Best Video I've Found On Nvidia Grid - Specs and Potential Business Model</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363442395368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>t's hard to wrap my head around how big this could be. As big as or bigger than Netflix? Every kid in America plays some sort of video game at some point. bigonnvda Not making fun of you bigonnvda because in my secret heart of hearts I can see Nvidia discussed on the CNBC Half Time Show With the Fast Money boys debating whether a PE of 40 still makes Nvidia a Buy. Oh look on Comes Topeka Captial with a price target of 1111. Well in reality maybe 30, but that's alright with me. All Nvidia has to do is Catch The Wave! and for gosh sakes speed up before Sammie or someone else get's in front. Just put the hammer down and go for it!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363475614436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 19:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363476792870-36</Id><Topic><Title>Best Video I've Found On Nvidia Grid - Specs and Potential Business Model</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363442395368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From your mouth to gods ears!</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1363476792870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 19:33:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363480593270-37</Id><Topic><Title>Best Video I've Found On Nvidia Grid - Specs and Potential Business Model</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363442395368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brokeagain73 It's coming. Ubitus uses Nvidia Grid &amp; now has 1 million LTE gaming customers! "TAIPEI, Taiwan, Feb. 26, 2013 /PRNewswire/ -- Ubitus Inc., the worldwide technology leader in cloud gaming solutions, today announced its GameCloud solution has empowered worldwide leading carriers to reach one million LTE cloud gaming users spanning across the United States, Japan, South Korea and Hong Kong. Ubitus GameCloud, a holistic turnkey solution designed to support simple adaptation of original PC/MMO games to run across multiple device platforms overcloud and most concurrent users support with lowest power consumption, has successfully enabled multiple global top-tier LTE carriers, including but not limited to Verizon Wireless, NTT DoCoMo, LG U+, and One2free, to commercially bring their cloud gaming services to the market since September 2011.The "one million" record to date alsomarks Ubitusas the dominant cloud gaming provider in Android-based LTE phones and tablets. "It's truly amazing to see howfast the one-million-user milestone has reached in such a short period of time,and this again proves that consumers would embrace new way of gaming experienceas long as the service adds value to their lives," said Wesley Kuo, CEO of Ubitus. "We are extremely proud to work with our customers in shifting to a newgaming paradigm for the masses."</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363480593270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 20:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363480837232-38</Id><Title>Before you get Cloud gaming, you need to be able to talk uninterrupted on</Title><Msg>your cellphones first.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363480837232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 20:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363481372521-39</Id><Topic><Title>Before you get Cloud gaming, you need to be able to talk uninterrupted on</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363480837232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 20:40:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>irrelevant</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1363481372521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 20:49:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363491000261-40</Id><Topic><Title>Best Video I've Found On Nvidia Grid - Specs and Potential Business Model</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363442395368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>J7, I did catch that but wasn't sure what to make of it. It seems that Nvidia is being purposefully coy when it comes to its future plans except the occasional slip of the tongue (though I am not sure that isn't purposeful either) . Honestly, I am not sure how to read into any of the comments about them hosting it themselves. I suppose, depending on how you spin and sentiment, it I think it could be a positive, negative or benign indicator of it's future. One possibility for them doing it themselves is to overcome industry inertia - in my experience I have found that people don't know they want something until they are able to have it. Before Apple made smart phones main stream and cool how many people thought they needed a phone that was also media device/computer/navigation system etc?</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1363491000261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 23:30:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363491960831-41</Id><Topic><Title>Best Video I've Found On Nvidia Grid - Specs and Potential Business Model</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363442395368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"One possibility for them doing it themselves is to overcome industry inertia" It's a new business model for all....</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363491960831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 23:46:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>