<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-27"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372309330610-1</Id><Title>Nvidia Should Put Up a Webpag: Shield Has Internal Troubles Expect Repairs Soon</Title><Msg>Don't you think they owe it to Nvidia fans to keep them informed and up to date on the latest SHIELD REPAIRS? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372309330610</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 01:02:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372334062311-2</Id><Topic><Title>Can you CANCEL a Pre-Order and get back Pre-Money for Pre-Production Quality BS?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372296569852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 21:29:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the box your SHIELD Toy arrives in has been open before and upon inspecting the SHIELD Toy inside you notice that parts seem crazy glued together, don't worry its one Nvidia had FIXED. As long as the glue is dry you can begin play and enjoy your NEW and IMPROVED SHIELD Toy. lmao imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372334062311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 07:54:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372334874840-3</Id><Title>short interest down to 52.5 millon</Title><Msg>as of the 14th. Thanks Nasdaq for that timely reporting of data! You bunch of crooks. Seems I have to mark all my short trades as such when traded. What's the problem with your accounting procedures?</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1372334874840</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 08:07:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372338099559-4</Id><Topic><Title>short interest down to 52.5 millon</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1372334874840</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 08:07:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what are you really? Strong Sell or Strong Buy? or Does it really matter to you?</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1372338099559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 09:01:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372340351292-5</Id><Title>Markets open much HIGHER</Title><Msg>Nvda opens in the RED!! Rising tide raises all ships unless you're the TITANIC (nvda). WHATAPOS.....IT'S TRUE!</Msg><Username>roundhouse_cc</Username><Timestamp>1372340351292</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 09:39:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372341306822-6</Id><Title>They have to execute better...</Title><Msg>These screw-ups just give the shorts more ammo...</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1372341306822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 09:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372341807949-7</Id><Title>Wells research note on NVDA</Title><Msg>from David Wong: Nvidia has a strong presence in the tablet applications market, being the largest merchant vendor of tablet applications processors (excluding Apple’s captive processor position) with a 16% overall unit share in 2012. Nvidia had significant early success in tablets, winning a majority of the early Android and essentially all the initial Windows RT tablet processor sockets. We think that the Android tablet market may have developed to a point at which it could gain some growth momentum. TI is exiting the tablet applications processor market, vacating sockets that remaining players such as Nvidia could win. However, we think it is an open question as to whether the Windows RT tablet market will blossom or fade, and if the Windows RT tablet market fails to develop this would be a headwind to Nvidia’s applications processor sales. Within the Android tablet market, it appears that Nvidia may have been displaced at some tablet makers such as Lenovo and Samsung [...] ========= Hmm, NVDA is the largest SoC tablet vendor in Android, and the market has developed to a point it should see momentum growth, but NVDA's tablet future is dependent on RT? Don't think so. Article on barrons</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1372341807949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 10:03:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372343672756-8</Id><Topic><Title>They have to execute better...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1372341306822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 09:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My #$%$ meter is off the scale as I don't believe you find a mechanical problem 1 day before release. I love most everything about this company and believe they will again blow away numbers. But this just stinks.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1372343672756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 10:34:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372344786010-9</Id><Topic><Title>They have to execute better...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1372341306822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 09:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many scenarios could be related to the delay. Perhaps they found a defect in one of the components and the vender is reworking them, or could not get revised parts to the contract manufactured in time? It's good they are being prudent in implementing the delay so they get it right.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1372344786010</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 10:53:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372345591706-10</Id><Title>Another month without SHIELD Revenue is a few thousand bucks left on the table? lol</Title><Msg>You know no one was waiting for that SHIELD Toy anyway right Nvidia? Take all the time you and that 3rd party think you might need to fix that BROKEN Toy OK? lol IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372345591706</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 11:06:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372345603654-11</Id><Topic><Title>They have to execute better...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1372341306822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 09:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They didn't find the issue 1 day before ship. They announced they weren't going to ship one day before ship. Having worked in this type of environment, I can confidently speak to the fact this issue has been on the radar for some time, probably weeks. It just bubbled up to the point they needed to take action on it. Their decision was correct, wait and get it right rather than ship and taint your product. In a few weeks it won't matter.</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1372345603654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 11:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372346168310-12</Id><Topic><Title>They have to execute better...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1372341306822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 09:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They have to execute better..." You not the boss of Nvidia. Let Nvidia excute the way they want to execute. Do your thing Nvidia and be sure to llet us know when that Toy is finally fixed or when you plan to have another IP Bake Sale. Carry-on Nvidia. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372346168310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 11:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372346714199-13</Id><Title>Oh, oh $13.98</Title><Msg>Not looking good for Nvda here. Shorts are piling on, key support broken!</Msg><Username>helleapoopn</Username><Timestamp>1372346714199</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 11:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372347377444-14</Id><Topic><Title>Oh, oh $13.98</Title><Username>helleapoopn</Username><Timestamp>1372346714199</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 11:25:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvda is down 10%+ Fromm it's recent high and been going down the past few days while the market is going up, very disturbing.</Msg><Username>wugooey</Username><Timestamp>1372347377444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 11:36:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372348889869-15</Id><Topic><Title>They have to execute better...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1372341306822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 09:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Believe it or not, this decision of delaying for quality purpose will actually strengthen NVIDIA's brand image, although initially it might look like a black eye to some....</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372348889869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 12:01:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372349258334-16</Id><Title>Just one month until your Recently Repaired Marked Down SHIELD Toy ships Nvidia fans</Title><Msg>Aren't you Nvidia fans so lucky Nvidia didn't cancel all Pre-Orders when they discovered SHIELD was BROKEN and give customers a chance to rethink that purchase? Its stll $299 working or not right? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372349258334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 12:07:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372349829130-17</Id><Topic><Title>HOT NEWS: Samsung Has A Bunch Of New Cheap Android Tablets That Start At $199 (All 3 powered by Tegra 3 SoCs)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372267292845</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:21:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do not see the point in your minor ad hominem attack... The business insider author stated that pre-orders would be starting on June 25, yet I do not see them anywhere... If Nvidia did get this business, it would be great; the article just seems suspect to me.</Msg><Username>morrowltd</Username><Timestamp>1372349829130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 12:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372350076922-18</Id><Topic><Title>They have to execute better...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1372341306822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 09:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think Nvidia claimed they found the problem one day before SHIELD was to go on sale. They probably knew about it for a while and tried to to find a feasible work around. When engineering failed to come up with a work around the problem wass escalated to severity 1 status which imposed a STOP SHIP on the product. If you know anything about product dev cycles the process leading up to a STOP SHIP had to reach the highest levels of management. The QA Team cannot make the call to STOP SHIP that is what management is paid to do which means in a company the size of Nvidia the problem was known for at least 2 weeks. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372350076922</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 12:21:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372351258877-19</Id><Title>I don't see Nvidia out Bad Mouthing Xbox One or PS4 Today. What happen? lol</Title><Msg>Maybe Nvidia woke up today and suddenly discovered what the phrase "Peoiple who live in glass houses shouldn't throw stones" really means? IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372351258877</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 12:40:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372353557576-20</Id><Title>Anyone buying this crappola......er stock?</Title><Msg>Just asking</Msg><Username>frobehinder</Username><Timestamp>1372353557576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 13:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372354521330-21</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone buying this crappola......er stock?</Title><Username>frobehinder</Username><Timestamp>1372353557576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 13:19:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's wrong shortly, make a bad bet?</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1372354521330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 13:35:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372358952067-22</Id><Topic><Title>HOT NEWS: Samsung Has A Bunch Of New Cheap Android Tablets That Start At $199 (All 3 powered by Tegra 3 SoCs)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372267292845</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:21:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$99 tablets are in a different class than $199+ tablets. They are okay, $149 tablets are better, and overall you get what you pay for.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1372358952067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 14:49:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372360083461-23</Id><Title>loving my android phone</Title><Msg>I recently upgraded my cell phone to a galaxy note 2 this thing is unbelievable I can't tell you people just how great phone this is just how amazing Android has become. by the way I'm dictating this from my Galaxy Note 2.</Msg><Username>hydroponic_tomatoes</Username><Timestamp>1372360083461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 15:08:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372362121656-24</Id><Topic><Title>They have to execute better...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1372341306822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 09:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed. I would imagine they were hoping to fix the issue before the ship date and simply ran out of time, so had to do minor delay.</Msg><Username>morrowltd</Username><Timestamp>1372362121656</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 15:42:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372364803628-25</Id><Topic><Title>They have to execute better...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1372341306822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 09:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Patrick Moorhead at Forbe said about the same. NVDA only has one chance to make the first impression.</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1372364803628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 16:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372364833368-26</Id><Title>Market up.. nvda down.</Title><Msg>Typical day right?</Msg><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1372364833368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 16:27:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372365697193-27</Id><Title>Taken Down a Notch and Marked Down too the Problematic SHIELD is DOA</Title><Msg>SHIELD was never going to be a hit but now Nvidia is about to learn an expensive lession in Market Perception. As far as consumers are concerned now SHIELD is that Toy Nvidia is FRANTICLY TRYING TO FIX. Before it was some expensive novelity item but now its an expensive DOA novelity item. Iits real easy to take a PASS on a problematic $299 Toy when that phone in your pocket WORKS. Real Easy to keep walking and keep $299 in your pocket. If you don't think so then just sit back and watch Nvidia get schooled. Sony and Micorsoft put in the hard work learning the fickle business of consumer electronics and they have the Betamax and Zune scars respectively to prove it too, don't they? PS4 and Xbox One will not limp out of the gate the way SHIELD is doing now. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372365697193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 16:41:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372366297480-28</Id><Topic><Title>I don't see Nvidia out Bad Mouthing Xbox One or PS4 Today. What happen? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372351258877</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 12:40:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today's word just for Nvidia is: Humulity Before bragging about how well your new toy will do in the market try selling one working unit first Nvidia. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372366297480</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 16:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372369016978-29</Id><Topic><Title>Market up.. nvda down.</Title><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1372364833368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 16:27:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like it's a typical day for you shuffling shopping carts all day at Wal Mart.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1372369016978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 17:36:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372373219932-30</Id><Title>Forbes comments on NVIDIA Shield delay, with reference to Microsoft XBOX 360 launch</Title><Msg>SOURCE: Forbes The article starts with a comparison of Shield delay with the xbox 360 launch (and the fiasco shortly after) more than six years ago: ""Imagine if Microsoft had discovered and addressed the sub-par heat sinks which caused a deluge of “RROD” errors in their Xbox 360 console just days before it launched. A large cross-section of consumers would have been disappointed, but it certainly would have improved the system’s brand image early on, and saved Microsoft the estimated $1 billion it forked out in overall replacement and warranty costs."" Yeah, agreed. Better to fix the problem before launch than after release. More from Forbes: "".....I pressed my NVIDIA rep to go into further detail regarding the mechanical issue, but the company is remaining tight-lipped. They’re usually extremely forthcoming, so I’m sure their reasoning is sound. It’s worth noting that I haven’t experienced any unusual or defective behavior in my review unit. Certainly NVIDIA will lose some cash on promotions that need to be scrapped or altered, and the first batch of units off the assembly line. In the end, hopefully the adjusted retail price of $299 and a commitment to quality will ensure a healthy launch for the SHIELD in July. In my brief time with the device, it’s a high-quality piece of hardware that all gamers should be excited about. Besides, the killer app for me is latency-free streaming of my games via Steam’s Big Picture Mode. Who doesn’t want to play Borderlands 2 and Skyrim in bed?""</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372373219932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 18:46:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372375022806-31</Id><Title>WSJ just in: Google is developing Android video game console</Title><Msg>SOURCEE: WSJ Google Inc. is developing a videogame console and digital wrist watch powered by its Android operating system, according to people familiar with the matter, as the Internet company seeks to spread the software's domination beyond smartphones and tablets and build the company 's reputation as a hardware maker. With the watch and game console, Google is hoping to combat similar devices that Apple Inc. AAPL -1.08% may release in the future, the people said. Google is also preparing to release a second version of a Web-connected, Android-powered media-playing device, called Nexus Q, that was unveiled last year but not sold to the public, the people said. The Internet giant hopes to design and market the devices itself and release at least one of them this fall, they added. The hardware plans are the latest sign of Google's determination to build on the success of Android, the software it launched in 2008 that powered 75% of all smartphones and 56.5% of tablets shipped globally in the first quarter, according to the research firm IDC. Games that run on Android software have proved particularly popular, and they are growing much more quickly than games made for the big-name consoles supplied by Microsoft Corp., Sony Corp. and Nintendo Co. The appeal of such games has prompted the development of new devices aimed specifically for Android by other hardware companies. The people briefed on the matter said Google is reacting in part to expectations that rival Apple will launch a videogame console as part of its next Apple TV product release. .......(Snip)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372375022806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 19:17:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372381169073-32</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: Google is developing Android video game console</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372375022806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 19:17:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ibexx, taking into consideration Nvidia's recent timing of the licensing initiative, what do you think about Google, Apple, &amp; Samsung using Nvidia in the future? In my opinion Google appears to be a yes, but not sure if Apple wants to compete on the high end, or just continue on with relatively simple mid-range games that Apple can continue on using Imagination? It appears that Samsung is interested in gaming, but not sure to what extent? They surly wouldn't want to be left behind especially with their line of advanced LCD/LED's . This could be a clean sweep for Nvidia as it was for AMD?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1372381169073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 20:59:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372383068097-33</Id><Topic><Title>Shield Out Until Repaired (SOUR) Lemon ought to be how Nvidia markets SHIELD now. lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372297502138</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 21:45:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did they get it FIX yet? Any word from HQ on Project SOUR Lemon Nvidia fans? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372383068097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 21:31:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372383251341-34</Id><Topic><Title>They have to execute better...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1372341306822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 09:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kudo - They executed successfully in getting the 1/4 Billion Share dilution in the proxies approved! You do not have to sweat to find a good place for a nice return of your investment - just put the money in S&amp;P 500. Cheers!</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1372383251341</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 21:34:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372383515964-35</Id><Title>When are they going to release good news on Tegra 5?</Title><Msg>Prior to the next proxy? Cheers!</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1372383515964</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 21:38:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372384351686-36</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: Google is developing Android video game console</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372375022806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 19:17:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chitown, that was a loaded question! However, I'd be happy to share with you what my speculations are - in fact, pre-speculation is the right word. --I think Samsung could become the first SoC suppler who licenses NVIDIA's GPU, having the resources, interest (driven by pragmatism), and the capacity of producing SoCs across all price ranges and market breadth. Most importantly, Samsung is focused on profits - not being burden by image problems as to whose app chips they are using. --Apple could become one in due time when (and if) it becomes clearer that Kepler and future GPUs based on Maxwell will out-perform Imag's PowerVR SGX 6xxx (based on the Rogue architecture) significantly. I suspect Apple will be slower to make the transition (if it does) than Samsung for reasons other than technical. As a reference, IMG currently has more than 8 licensees for its PowerVR SGX 6xx. They include: ST-Ericsson Texas Instruments Renesas Electronics MediaTek HiSilicon Huawei LG Etc (to be continued)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372384351686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 21:52:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372384607885-37</Id><Title>Wuh oh or Whoopee? Google making game console, watch - report</Title><Msg>Feel free to discuss. Article from marketwatch. Making there own or buying one already made? Who would they use? Oh Yeah. They would want to use the best most forward thinking unable to meet deadline company there is.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1372384607885</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 21:56:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372385883394-38</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: Google is developing Android video game console</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372375022806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 19:17:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>--Lastly, about Google. I personally think that Google, currently, is developing at least 2 products with NVIDIA SoCs which are yet to be announced. Whether Google will use Kepler or higher NVIDIA GPUs for its rumored video controllers will depend on a few factors: 1. What kind of gaming market is it aspiring to partake in? - enthusiasts or midrange casual gamers"? I personally suspect it would be the latter, judging from the way El Goog developed its tablets and other devices. 2. Next comes the question of timing. For a high end game console to be competitive with xbox one and running on Android, Google will need Denver + Maxwell (Tegra 6, arriving in 2015/2016, via 14nm -16nm FinFET, 64 bit). For a video console of midrange performance, Tegra 5 (Kepler + Cortex A57) might do - which should come a year earlier. Since Google doesn't design its own SoCs, it seems entirely possible that NVIDIA would do a custom version for them if it fits NV's strategic plan and the price is right.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372385883394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 22:18:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372387262074-39</Id><Title>"Early Ouya Reviews Trickle In And They're Not Pretty"</Title><Msg>"Early Ouya Reviews Trickle In And They're Not Pretty" "I’ve been a long-time, unabashed skeptic when it comes to the Ouya console, a $99 Android-based system that promises to bring those games you know and love from your smartphone to your TV. Torment Closes as the Best Funded Game in Kickstarter History Paul Tassi Paul Tassi Contributor Words From The Wasteland: InXile CEO Brian Fargo Talks Tides and Torments Daniel Nye Griffiths Daniel Nye Griffiths Contributor Valve's Steam Box Might Be Moving Faster than We Thought Dave Thier Dave Thier Contributor New Game Console Success Isn't a Foregone Conclusion Patrick Moorhead Patrick Moorhead Contributor After reading The Verge’s Ouya review, many of my concerns appear to be justified. The publication gives the system a 3.5 out of 10, writing:" source: forbes</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372387262074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 22:41:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372390634850-40</Id><Title>Ouya now #17 on on Amazon from #40 as of yesterday</Title><Msg>Xbox One bumped off from #1 to $3 Playstation 4 bumped off from #4 to #8</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372390634850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 23:37:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372390748378-41</Id><Topic><Title>Ouya now #17 on on Amazon from #40 as of yesterday</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372390634850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 23:37:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Honeymoons for the big boyz in consoles are fading.....rather quickly!</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372390748378</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 23:39:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372391241048-42</Id><Topic><Title>Market up.. nvda down.</Title><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1372364833368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 16:27:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Loser douche bag. . You are a POS</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1372391241048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 23:47:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>