<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373774933841-1</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Leads the NYSE with a DOUBLE TRIPLE? UP 11.8% and 102M Shares</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373573566271</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 16:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes amazing !!</Msg><Username>oroplata68</Username><Timestamp>1373774933841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:08:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373808146800-2</Id><Topic><Title>EETimes: ARM beats Intel in revised Antutu benchmark (newest article published July 12)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373677580233</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This'll hurt hard to AnTuTu's creditbility. High level optimized compiler will remove the dummy codes. If the benchmark test with whole lots of redundant code , people will question its validity. Does it measure the performance of activities that ever happen in the real applications? This also wake up Intel lovers to face reality - INTC still had some room to improve in mobile processor.</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373808146800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:22:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373836135424-3</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 2 with S4 Pro heading to trouble</Title><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373569421806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The mobile processor chip is fast becoming like those of PCs. Adding more ARM cores reaches point of diminishing return and eventually all high end mobile chips have to add GPU. Since Nvidia is licensing out Kepler, it will add value to mobile IC makers that adopt Nvidia graphics. Graphics will be the achilles heel of Qualcom Snapdragon and Samsung Exynos. Consumer cannot tell an excellent communication chip from a good enough one, but everybody can tell the difference in graphics.</Msg><Username>edgary2013</Username><Timestamp>1373836135424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:08:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373857239108-4</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 2 with S4 Pro heading to trouble</Title><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373569421806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just as a reference point, shares of Imagination Technologies (IMAG.L) have dropped 12% in value in 4 weeks since NVIDIA announced GPU licensing initiative on June 16. Wall Street is voicing its opinion on NV/IMG's relative competitive position. It will be very interesting when NV;s licensing business moves to high gear... PS: Yahoo has financial data and charts on London-traded Imagination Technologies. It's fun to take a quick look..</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373857239108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 23:00:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373860102251-5</Id><Title>Microsoft to reduce Surface tablets by up to 30%.....</Title><Msg>Will this help NVDA?</Msg><Username>real_estate_bobby</Username><Timestamp>1373860102251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 23:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373860461250-6</Id><Title>Microsoft to reduce Surface RT price by up to 30%</Title><Msg>sorry about that 1st post.....Hope this helps NVDA stock price.....</Msg><Username>real_estate_bobby</Username><Timestamp>1373860461250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 23:54:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373860672249-7</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 2 with S4 Pro heading to trouble</Title><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373569421806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is irrelevant. Microsoft reduced Surface RT price (1st generation) to clear remainder inventory for the launch of next-gen Surface RTs of which NVIDIA has at least one, likely two models. Microsoft is NOT going to buy more Tegra 3 to manufacture more of 1st generation product The Nexus 7 is a different story. While rumors have it that Nexus 7 2 is ready to go, Google, however, is still actively marketing the T3 powered Nexus 7 in many parts of the world such as the emerging markets in S America, Asia and Mid-east. At the same time, Nexus 7 may not vanish from the shelves in US or Canada, as it is reportedly being positioned as a lower priced alternative with gaming prowess. Thus it looks like Google will continue to purchase T3 chips from NVIDIA and this would definitely help the top and bottom lines.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373860672249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 23:57:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>