<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-23"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361603392324-1</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the interesting Via story. Nvidia can still get their x86 license, they just need to buy Via to do it ;-). Intel got more than just buying off an obsolete chipset business for their $1.5bn, they also got the total freedom to develop their own gpu chipset to the extent that it raises the silicon bar at which a discrete gpu becomes necessary at every generation. Nvidia in return get their Tegra losses funded every year which is a fair exchange I suppose. S800 Krait is 1.5 sq mm bigger than ARM A9 per core (minus the L2 cache) according to Nvidia's numbers so a quad-core S800/Tegra 4 SoC will be about 60 sq mm and 70 sq mm with LTE which is not too bad and still smaller than Intel's Clovertrail+ which will be closer to 90 sq mm. blogs-imagesDOTforbesDOTcom/jasonevangelho/files/2013/02/4i-CPU-Comparison.png</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1361603392324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 02:09:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361610104586-2</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel got more than just buying off an obsolete chipset business for their $1.5bn, they also got the total freedom to develop their own gpu chipset" INtel had that already before the lawsuits... and NVIdia was building chipsets for INtel...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361610104586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 04:01:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361622021158-3</Id><Topic><Title>Therer´s also been rumblings over the past couple of days that Apple views Nvidia as a possible takeover target.</Title><Username>clark.kent251</Username><Timestamp>1361531551977</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 06:12:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can guarantee you Larry Ellison would love to grab a piece of Mobile Oracle needs more fuel for its growth engine</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1361622021158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 07:20:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361623962356-4</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not with total unfettered access to any Nvidia gpu patent. Considering how well Intel's gpu is improving each generation, which will actually allow them to say goodbye to PowerVR next Atom generation, Intel clearly got the better deal out of this as $1.5bn is like one quarter's dividend or buyback to Intel, just noise while Nvidia has now been forced off x86 to ARM and been forced to fight to make discrete gpus still relevant going forward.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1361623962356</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 07:52:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361630700080-5</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation featured on MAD MONEY!</Title><Username>browndavid977</Username><Timestamp>1361452514381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:15:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome!</Msg><Username>coreypeterson181</Username><Timestamp>1361630700080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 09:45:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361631340106-6</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Intel license is non transferable if AMD or Via is sold. With most all the Transmeta engineers heading over to Nvidia, I'm sure Jen might have something up his sleeve in regards to x86 code morphing technology being used to some extent in project Denver and Boulder?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1361631340106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 09:55:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361631475626-7</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel clearly got the better deal out of this as $1.5bn " INtel used to have it for free... now they pay $1.5B "Nvidia has now been forced off x86 to ARM" Agree... "been forced to fight to make discrete gpus still relevant going forward" Where are the INtel discrete CPUs going ?? INtel forced to put GPUs on their products to stay relevant...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361631475626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 09:57:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361634297747-8</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only way Intel can exist and grow revenue going forward is to fill their Fabs with very high priced chips. Things like server chips sure, things like gaming extreme CPUs for desktops/ laptops and things like super premium Apple or Apple like laptops, and Xeon processors for workstations. What's missed is how Intel and Nvidia essentially need each other in all of the above segments except servers. Intel sells the $400 to $1000 CPU and Nvidia sells them $400 to $3000 GPU. The other business - cheap PC's is almost gone replaced by tablets with $25 processors. Nvidia sells them for $25 and Intel sell them I'm not sure but around $60. And then there are phones. Nvidia sells them for $15-$20 processor only or $30 to $40 with modem. Qualcomm sells, them at a higher price, and Intel just matches bids to get into the business. My point really is that even if Intel is a resounding success in phones, they cannot fill their Fabs and maintain high margins. Only the server market, workstation/HPC market , gaming PC's, and luxury name brand laptops provide Intel with high margin markets. It's ironic...but Intel drove Nvidia out of the bargain low price segment and then paid them a gift of $1.5B and that market no longer exists.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361634297747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 10:44:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361636915510-9</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nvda already said their 5 yr $b effort won't be aimed at the huge server market, but at the punny 'HPC' market. Interest income from that $1B will dwarf the sales.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1361636915510</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 11:28:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361637855938-10</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"nvda already said their 5 yr $b effort won't be aimed at the huge server market" after the intro that it was...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361637855938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 11:44:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361639831264-11</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'The Intel license is non transferable if AMD or Via is sold. ' No longer strictly true, Under a FTC agreement Intel has to negotiate in good faith with any buyer.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1361639831264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:17:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361640082663-12</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel does not need discrete gpus, it's a tiny market. After all Intel gives away more in dividends and buybacks in one quarter than Nvidia make in a whole year.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1361640082663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:21:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361640828075-13</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is still in the low price x86 segment, there is a $200 Chromebook with a Sandy Bridge Celeron in it. Intel's PC asps are only about $100 contrary to all the wild rumors about how they need ultra-expensive processors to survive. They have enough performance advantage and sku and price elasticity to maintain their high GMs ( greater than 50%) and fill their FABs going forward. Atom will only be icing in this main cake.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1361640828075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:33:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361641933291-14</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel does not need discrete gpus, it's a tiny market. After all Intel gives away more in dividends and buybacks in one quarter than Nvidia make in a whole year." Marsavian True but it's all about relative size. But my point was Intel and Nvidia both make their money selling extreme priced chips...Intel CPU's and Nvidia GPU's and their business is complementary....No one thinks of putting an AMD CPU in a workstation over a Xeon chip and the same is true for a workstation GPU...i.e. Nvidia owns the market. Both Intel with Atom and Nvidia with Tegra are attacking the low priced tablet market but in this case Nvidia has an advantage....lower cost. Intel cannot support the cost of their Fabs selling $25 chips when they were built for $300 to $1000+ CPUs. Case in Point - Bestbuy announced today an across the board $100 cut on all Windows 8 touchscreen laptops. In their press release they said this was funded by Intel, Microsoft, and the PC makers. In the meantime those cheap $200 tablets keep selling out. Stretegy Analytics says that tablets are already selling in greater numbers than PC's are and the drop in PC's is in the lower end, not the high end. It is unrealistic for Intel and Microsoft to expect PC manufacturers to stay in the business with Intel and Microsoft maintaining their high margins. Case in point...HP said they are embarking on a multi-O/S, multi chip strategy. I read that as free android operating system and cheap tablet processors along with maintaining a high end presence in PC's. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361641933291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:52:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361641939581-15</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation featured on MAD MONEY!</Title><Username>browndavid977</Username><Timestamp>1361452514381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:15:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report, thanks</Msg><Username>petersullivan767</Username><Timestamp>1361641939581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:52:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361642209532-16</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation featured on MAD MONEY!</Title><Username>browndavid977</Username><Timestamp>1361452514381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:15:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361642209532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:56:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361642502214-17</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation featured on MAD MONEY!</Title><Username>browndavid977</Username><Timestamp>1361452514381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:15:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361642502214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 13:01:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361644852654-18</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation featured on MAD MONEY!</Title><Username>browndavid977</Username><Timestamp>1361452514381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:15:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361644852654</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 13:40:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361644906238-19</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation featured on MAD MONEY!</Title><Username>browndavid977</Username><Timestamp>1361452514381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:15:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361644906238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 13:41:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361646674562-20</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation featured on MAD MONEY!</Title><Username>browndavid977</Username><Timestamp>1361452514381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:15:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361646674562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 14:11:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361651730278-21</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't really agree with your logic as an Intel FAB is not inherently more expensive than a TSMC fab. All that matters is good GMs and volume to fill your FABs. Intel's asp is about $100 not $400 to $1000 just as Nvidia's is not in that range. Even if you lost a few expensive processors from your mix it would not make a big difference to your asp. Intel's prices have remained static for years with new processors just replacing the old, the only thing they got wrong recently was 22nm demand but that is not a big long term issue as they will just convert some of the expected 22nm space to 14nm space as they have the process already ready. The PC market has temporarily stalled and not crashed while it goes through a normal hardware/software upgrade cycle and there is no other processor architecture on the horizon that threatens the prices Intel charges. If Intel's expensive processors are earmarked for extinction then so are Nvidia's expensive gpus from the same good enough theory but I don't believe either are as customers will always pay top dollar for the top performance.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1361651730278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 15:35:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361655756531-22</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes Customers will always pay top dollar for top performance. True Yes Intel will just convert their Fabs down to 14nm from 22nm. True But as they shrink the die at a huge cost the number of chips that need to sold increases at exactly the same rate. Worked like a charm in the past when demand was growing for consumer PCs and took all of the market share and has for all practical purposes forced AMD to leave the field. But now there is nothing left for Intel to take. Consumer PC sales peaked last year are on a decline according to all the market strategists. The only thing that is in doubt is how steep the decline is and will be. Without massive price cuts from Intel and Microsoft there just is no way to reignite the demand in my opinion now that tablets have truly taken hold. Luxury PC's like Apple's and a few others along with powerful gaming PC's, servers, and workstations are still growing but not nearly as large enough to provide sockets for all those expensive Intel best in class CPUs. At the last earnings call for Intel the stock was up until Intel said they were expanding Fab capital equipment expenditures by 25% this year. All the analysts thought where are they going to sell all those expensive X86 chips they are going to make and the stock fell. TSMC - spreads their capacity across 50 customers at least, and never expands the latest process node to a point where their prices per wafer have to drop rapidly. Nvidia only participates in the High End Luxury consumer PC market, Gaming and Workstations but they are in tablets in a pretty good way and cost effective way.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361655756531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 16:42:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361656418891-23</Id><Topic><Title>I've begun accumulation mode 12.28 first chunk buy</Title><Username>nvda_4_ever</Username><Timestamp>1361477211112</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:06:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So far so good. Up already with 2 more chunks in wings waiting for 5% total move up add'l to go in. With already a grand to the good I'm likin' the 'vibe'! A year or two out I expect to post the incredible return achived The saftey factor here allows for pretty serious postion building. It will be fun to link back to this post. 4ever!</Msg><Username>nvda_4_ever</Username><Timestamp>1361656418891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 16:53:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361656873136-24</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'At the last earnings call for Intel the stock was up until Intel said they were expanding Fab capital equipment expenditures by 25% this year. ' No it was EUV and 450nm R&amp;D both of which are purely a luxury Intel can easily afford. Once again the ANALysts misunderstood and thought it was some sort of expansionary measure when it is merely an R&amp;D measure to maintain Intel's 2-year process change cadence which is not really necessary anyway as Intel is so far ahead of AMD, VIA or ARM that they could afford to stay on 22nm for years if they wanted to. 'Nvidia only participates in the High End Luxury consumer PC market, Gaming and Workstations but they are in tablets in a pretty good way and cost effective way.' Tegra division has yet to even break-even in its first 3 iterations, here's hoping for the fourth huh ? ;-) If it was your only division you would be trading at below your cash value !</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1361656873136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 17:01:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361659467451-25</Id><Topic><Title>Meg says arm for servers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361543013796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel's stock will go up when they announce a capital budget cut this August. Just like the last two times. Tegra does lose money but hopefully this is the year of breakeven. Perhaps Project Shield can push it over into the green in Q3. Take alook at how Nvidia reports it's business's now. Opaque as everyone else which is new but all that anyone will see is the Tegra Division (Includes Project Shield) is showing a huge relative jump in revenue from ASPs going from $25 to Prject Shields transfer price of around $200) and look the Tegra division is profitable. Both Intel's capex cut and Tegra Division into the green should happen in Q3. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361659467451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 17:44:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361661146878-26</Id><Title>Nvidia Grid---Perhaps At the Right Place At The Right Time</Title><Msg>Note: Gaikai uses Nvidia Grid GPUs as do all the others. The Sony PS4 console may house a premium subscription service allowing members to play as many games as they want for a monthly fee, according to the president of Sony Worldwide Studios. Shuhei Yoshida said Sony has many options with regards to subscription platforms, thanks to the acquisition of Gaikai - the cloud-gaming company that will power and pioneer the PS4's online offerings. Some observers had expected Sony to reveal a Netflix-for-gamers style service at Tuesday's launch event, but for now that's a 'dream' dependent on digital content flourishing on the console, Yoshida-san said. He told The Guardian: "As more and more services and contents become available digitally, we'll have more of an option to create attractive packages. So hypothetically we can look at different models – like a cable TV company. We could have gold, silver or platinum levels of membership, something like that. "We can do subscription services when we have more content – especially now that we have the Gaikai technology available. With one subscription you have access to thousands of games – that's our dream." techradarDotcom/news/gaming/consoles/sony-ps4-all-you-can-eat-game-subscriptions-may-be-in-the-works-1133334</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361661146878</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:12:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361666738579-27</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation featured on MAD MONEY!</Title><Username>browndavid977</Username><Timestamp>1361452514381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:15:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>lucianoanderson120</Username><Timestamp>1361666738579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 19:45:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361667584451-28</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia Grid---Perhaps At the Right Place At The Right Time</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361661146878</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:12:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This was the icing on the cake for me when I was looking at semis. NVIDIA, unlike almost all of its peers, is uniquely situated to drive the user experience forward by having a foothold in virtually all of the computing space. Mobile, PC, consoles/handhelds, and the cloud with grid and this only the consumer end of things. Who else has this kind of end-to-end technological leverage (specifically with games). Not intel, not amd, not ms, not apple and certainly not Qualcomm.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1361667584451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 19:59:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361668354860-29</Id><Title>Samsung Galaxy S4 delayed due to Exynos 5 issues?</Title><Msg>We have definitely seen our fair share of rumors concerning the next flagship from South Korean smartphone powerhouse Samsung, where among them include a bumper case, launching with 5G Wi-Fi, and a March 14th release date to name a few. Well, a rather interesting report from South Korea has just appeared, touting that Samsung’s Exynos 5 octa-core processor has run into production issues, and that this is serious. In fact, it would be the reason why Samsung has not closed the door on Qualcomm Snapdragon SoCs to be in the innards of their upcoming Galaxy S4 smartphone. We are not quite sure just how true this particular report from South Korea is, and whether it might actually see Samsung ditch the entire Exynos 5 effort from their future devices, but we guess there is always the Great Teacher (some say Great Destroyer), Time, to show us the way. I do suppose that executives over at Qualcomm must be singing, “Happy days are here again…”, keeping their fingers crossed that Samsung will fail with the Exynos 5. Publisher’s note: while this is a post discussing the alleged Exynos production issues, it is worth nothing that it is very unlikely that Samsung would “ditch” it altogether. While production issues often happen early in a chip’s life cycle, most of those problems are worked out and given that Samsung has already demonstrated working samples, the chip logic (design) seems out of danger. Now, the question is whether or not Samsung can produce enough of these chips to meet demand. SOURCE: Ubergizmo PS: I posted this rumor a few days ago, now it appears to be a virtual fact - reports on Samsung chip issues are all over the web.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361668354860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 20:12:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361669655795-30</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung Galaxy S4 delayed due to Exynos 5 issues?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361668354860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 20:12:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some websites also reported that Exynos 5 Octa is incompatible with LTE.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361669655795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 20:34:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361670257936-31</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung Galaxy S4 delayed due to Exynos 5 issues?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361668354860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 20:12:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it the same websites that said Tegra 4 is incompatible with LTE? Qualcomm Marketing perhaps!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361670257936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 20:44:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361670712959-32</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia Grid---Perhaps At the Right Place At The Right Time</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361661146878</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:12:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As Jen said about building the shield "we were the only ones who could build it"! Just a thought. We could white box the shield just as easy as our phoenix phones. Lots of space for a Sony,Msft,Google or wait for it.... Apple logo. I'm not saying we can't do it ourselves. Just that opportunities exist. I'm thinking the hesitancy and waffleing on the CC about the guidance could be a big grid deal. Maybe Sony wasn't signed yet.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361670712959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 20:51:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361671705600-33</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung Galaxy S4 delayed due to Exynos 5 issues?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361668354860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 20:12:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""Sammobile weighed in on the problems Samsung is having with Exynos 5 stating that the real issue is with LTE connectivity. The site also stated that there is a possibility that Samsung could launch a non LTE version that uses the Octa-core chip"". globalDOTchristianpostDOTcom/news/galaxy-s4-release-date-delayed-due-to-issues-with-exynos-5-chipset-90642/#TTXkK9LCM0qOUzvu.99</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361671705600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 21:08:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361671740474-34</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung Galaxy S4 delayed due to Exynos 5 issues?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361668354860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 20:12:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did we ever hear what chips we were working on with Samsung at their Texas fab?</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361671740474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 21:09:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361672340404-35</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia Grid---Perhaps At the Right Place At The Right Time</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361661146878</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:12:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take a look at Nvidia's GPU Tech Conference schedule of presentations in March. It is almost all Gaming, Cloud, and Game Developers. Project Shield reveals etc. It's well over 75% of the conference. Obviously Nvidia is making a big push for a new business. Reminds me of GPU Tech Conf in 2011 when they introduced GPU HPC compute with Tesla. And that worked out very well.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361672340404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 21:19:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361674129624-36</Id><Title>No Tegra 4i in Samsungs new tablet?</Title><Msg>Saw the specs, who or what is that Enyxos chip?</Msg><Username>real_estate_bobby</Username><Timestamp>1361674129624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 21:48:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>