<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361336888693-1</Id><Title>Could Nvidia Sell Their Phoenix Tegra 4i Phone Direct to Telcos?</Title><Msg>I am wondering if Nvidia might plan on selling their Phoenix Tegra 4i reference phone direct to carriers world wide. It seems that not long ago every carrier had feature phones and low end smartphones made by known phone manufacturers but branded as "AT&amp;T, Verizon, T-Mobile, etc. " phones. I have even seen China Mobile branded phones. Of course that would be a big leap for Nvidia to contract unit production with a contract electronics manufacturer, but they do have a lot of experience with their AIB GPU partners especially in the Quadro and Tesla lines. If that was the case how long would you think a carrier would take to go thru the quals if they were getting a pretty good deal...i.e. decent phone without having to pay the huge Apple or Samsung subsidies? Just curious.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361336888693</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 00:08:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361337757667-2</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 4i - 60 mm2?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361327524767</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 21:32:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just read where Broadcom expects to sell their stand alone LTE modem chip no app processor integration in the high teens to $20 each. Add in say $20 for the app processor and your talking $35+. I wonder what Qualcomm is getting for their integrated modem chip...$35 to $40? If Nvidia only got in the high $20's for the Tegra 4i, it would be a huge money maker! And then there is the RF transceiver chip but I think those go $3 to$4.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361337757667</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 00:22:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361339106715-3</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 4i - 60 mm2?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361327524767</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 21:32:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 60mm2 source - AnandTech ? Why is it that we don't see him say anything about the S4 duo or S4 Quad die sizes? Is it that he is too embarrass to state the facts? Same pattern I would predict for the S600 and 800.</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361339106715</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 00:45:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361343668764-4</Id><Topic><Title>Hold onto your wallet when you read pumping post filled with LIES</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361308539839</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:15:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pumpers still at it. Trying to lift Nvidia with nonsense. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361343668764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:01:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361343760491-5</Id><Title>"WSJ: PlayStation 4 will have AMD silicon, cloud gaming"</Title><Msg>"We've heard it before, and now, the Wall Street Journal has echoed the rumor: Sony's PlayStation 4 will have AMD inside. "Based on prototypes shown to employees and partners," says the Journal, "Sony's new PlayStation is expected to run on chips made by Advanced Micro Devices Inc." The word "chips" implies that the system could feature multiple slices of AMD silicon—perhaps both a CPU and a discrete GPU. It's hard to say for sure based on just one sentence, though."</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361343760491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:02:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361343883693-6</Id><Title>NVIDIA positions Tegra4i as Snapdragon slayer (A very good summary)</Title><Msg>Today NVIDIA revealed its first mobile rocessor with a fully integrated 4G LTE modem, the NVIDIA Tegra 4i, which finally places them on an even playing field with Qualcomm. The Tegra line of chips have been successful in capturing a good chuck on the Android tablet market, but the lack of an integrated modem has slowed the adoption of Tegra in smartphones. Tegra 4i should instantly increase the number of smartphone design wins for NVIDIA since it finally features an integrated LTE modem. Other highlights of the chip include a quad-core CPU based on ARM’s newest and most efficient core — the R4 Cortex-A9 CPU — with a fifth battery saver core, 60 custom NVIDIA GPU cores, and a unique computational photography architecture called Chimera. **Tegra 4 Performance in a Smaller, Cheaper package"" We find the design of Tegra 4i interesting since it uses “R4″ Cortex-A9 CPU cores. This is a new revision of an older architecture, but it was jointly designed by NVIDIA and ARM who claim this is the “most efficient, highest performing CPU core on the market.” “Tegra 4i demonstrates the ability of ARM and our partners to continue to push the performance of technology and create exciting user experiences,” says Tom Cronk, executive vice president and general manager, processor division, ARM. “ARM and NVIDIA worked closely to further optimize the Cortex-A9 processor to drive performance and efficiency in areas such as streaming and responsiveness.” Even though the “R4″ Cortex-A9 CPU cores will run at 2.3 GHz, they still fall behind the newer 1.9 GHz Cortex-A15 CPU cores found in Tegra 4. We expect a newer CPU architecture to outperform an old one, but we note this because of the difference in clock speeds. Compared to Tegra 4, the Tegra 4i chip features fewer GPU cores (60 vs 72), lower output resolutions (1080p vs 4k Ultra HD), and support for less memory (2 GB vs 4 GB). NVIDIA is positioning Tegra 4i as a cheaper alternative to Tegra 4, so that is why these sacrifices have been made. **World’s First Mobile Computational Photography Architecture** When NVIDIA announced Tegra 4 at CES, they showed off a new computational photography architecture. This cutting edge camera experience is also coming to Tegra 4i, but it has now been branded as Chimera. Chimera Computational Photography enables the first always-on high-dynamic range (HDR) photos and video, HDR panoramic photos, and persistent tap-to-track capabilities. “NVIDIA’s Chimera architecture takes mobile imaging far beyond what consumers have come to expect from the phones and tablets,” said Brian Cabral, Vice President of Computation Imaging at NVIDIA. “Capabilities that until now have been reserved for professional photographers – like instant HDR and HDR panoramic shots and flawless image tracking – are now within easy reach for the rest of us.” The camera demos we witnessed at CES really impressed us, so it’s nice to see these features come to mainstream Android smartphones. **Unique Software-Defined Radio (SDR) Technology** Another cool feature of Tegra 4i is the Icera i500 LTE modem that has been optimized for integration. The i500 modem is a “future-proof platform” since it uses software-defined radio technology that can be upgraded over-the-air. This means the modem will ship with support for LTE speeds up to 100 Mbps, but it will receive a future update that enables speeds to 150 Mbps. A software defined radio could also receive updates that tune the modem to work best in specific geographical locations. For example, one modem “profile” might be optimized for the best performance in an dense metro area, while another could be tuned to extend coverage in flat terrains. ""Faster Than Qualcomm’s Snapdragon?** The war of words between NVIDIA and Qualcomm continues with today’s announcements. NVIDIA takes a shot at Qualcomm by calling Tegra 4i the “Highest performing single-chip smartphone processor”. Both companies are telling us that they have made the best mobile chip of 2013, so we are closely watching both platforms as they come to market. According to results from R&amp;D and publicly available data, NVIDIA claims that both Tegra 4 and Tegra 4i will outperform Qualcomm’s upcoming Snapdragon S800. NVIDIA says their chips offer more performance per clock, higher max performance, and greater efficiency. Qualcomm recently said that they clean Tegra 4′s clock, so it will be ineresting to see their response to the performance scores that NVIDIA is releasing. **Attack of the Cores** Qualcomm is still the king when it comes to single-chip solutions with an integrated modem, but today’s news is likely to become significant in the coming years for several reasons. Hardware OEMs will now have another single-chip solution to choose from and consumers will get premium camera capabilities in a device priced for the mainstream.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361343883693</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:04:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361343896873-7</Id><Topic><Title>"WSJ: PlayStation 4 will have AMD silicon, cloud gaming"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361343760491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:02:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PS4 will be a REAL game console not that SHIELD toy junk. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361343896873</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:04:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361344128182-8</Id><Topic><Title>"WSJ: PlayStation 4 will have AMD silicon, cloud gaming"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361343760491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:02:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SOURCE of the foregoing article: ANDROIDANDME androidandmeDOTcom/2013/02/news/nvidia-reveals-tegra-4i-chip-with-integrated-lte-positions-chip-as-a-snapdragon-slayer/</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361344128182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:08:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361344208021-9</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA positions Tegra4i as Snapdragon slayer (A very good summary)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361343883693</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:04:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Market said "NVDA Feb 19 12.555 -0.18 -1.38% 12.48 12.75 10,838,822 10,842,800 7.79B QCOM Feb 19 65.67 0.24 +0.37% 65.31 65.88 7,488,641 11,997,200 112.83B" Is it sinking in yet? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361344208021</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:10:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361345183292-10</Id><Title>Rumor has it that Apple is sniffing around</Title><Msg>they have plenty of cash and both are in silicon valley......would make sense for Apple</Msg><Username>tim35473</Username><Timestamp>1361345183292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:26:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361345266362-11</Id><Title>Folks, Qualcomm has cornered the smartphone market. Its chips are better than Nvidia's</Title><Msg>and it has lots of "phone" experience. Snapdragon kicked tegra3 butt. Snapdragon will kick Tegra4i butt, because its just another tegra3. Tegra4i is just another of Jensuns song and dance.. By the time it comes to market it will be too little too late.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361345266362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:27:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361346518295-12</Id><Title>Tegra 4i: quad-core, under $200 smartphones without contract - highest "performance per square millimeter"</Title><Msg>SOURCE: PCMag "Tegra 4i more than holds its own in performance, but what really matters in this market is performance per square millimeter," which translates to cost, said Matt Wuebbling, the director of Nvidia's mobile business. Tegra 4i has that nailed down. It's half the size of competing chipsets like the Tegra 4 and Qualcomm's Snapdragon 800, and according to Nvidia it's up to 2.5 times as efficient per square millimeter, which means it's able to deliver the performance we think of from top-end phones in devices that will cost $100-200 without any subsidy.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361346518295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:48:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361358093530-13</Id><Topic><Title>Apple should take out NVDA with a $12 billion offer -- for their graphics/LTE chip processors</Title><Username>coldwintergas</Username><Timestamp>1361332741988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 22:59:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forbes; NVIDIA (NASDAQ: NVDA): market cap $8.0 billion. One hears a lot of loose talk that the graphics card is dead, thanks to on-board graphics on Intel's Ivy Bridge chips. What the tech pundits don't see is that the graphics card has been integrated onto the SOC; and in this role, graphics processors, whether in Intel or ARM based SOCs, are very much alive. In this application, NVIDIA excels as well. More relevant for Apple, though, is NVIDIA's expertise in building ARM processors. NVIDIA's new quad core Tegra 4 represents the absolute state of the art for ARM processors. Apple currently designs their own dual core ARM processors, but if they wanted to be truly ahead of the pack, buying NVIDIA would put them there. The discreet graphics chip business could even be spun off if Apple decided it wasn't worth keeping. Operating income growth was flat at $648 million for NVIDIA's most recent fiscal year (ending 1/27/13) with basically flat revenues in NVIDIA's operating segments except Tegra, which grew 90% y/y in the fiscal fourth quarter.</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1361358093530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 06:01:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361358436351-14</Id><Topic><Title>Apple should take out NVDA with a $12 billion offer -- for their graphics/LTE chip processors</Title><Username>coldwintergas</Username><Timestamp>1361332741988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 22:59:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IMO we are quickly moving to an era in which Google and Microsoft have no choice but to produce branded mobile devices to compete with Apple. The question is, who needs NVIDIA more? Apple, Google or Microsoft? Its not so much the revenue or lower cost an acquisition would bring, but by capturing NVIDIA the acquirer makes QCOM the only option and thus higher prices for those needing to buy LTE SOCs on the open market.</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1361358436351</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 06:07:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361361756726-15</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 4i: quad-core, under $200 smartphones without contract - highest "performance per square millimeter"</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361346518295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:48:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why NVDA like the low-end tablet market like Nexus 7? $200 why NVDA like the low-end phone market ?? $100-$200 iphone is selling at $700</Msg><Username>new_day_low</Username><Timestamp>1361361756726</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 07:02:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361363707677-16</Id><Topic><Title>Could Nvidia Sell Their Phoenix Tegra 4i Phone Direct to Telcos?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361336888693</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 00:08:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Makes good sense. Getting more experience with Shield. How about throwing a phone chip in the shield for a few grins!</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361363707677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 07:35:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361368290582-17</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 4i - 60 mm2?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361327524767</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 21:32:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't know but Anand always jumps out with a die size estimate on Nvidia. One thing is certain though the Tegra 4i with integrated LTE modem (14 x 14 sq. mm.) comes in a smaller package than Tegra 4 without integrated LTE modem (12 x 12 sq. mm.). I have no idea how much area in a package must be open to make the connects, but I think I'll look around the internet to see what I can find.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361368290582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:51:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361368358552-18</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 4i - 60 mm2?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361327524767</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 21:32:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>my bad. reverse that the Tegra 4i is in a 12 x 12 sq. package. The Tegra 4 is in a 14 x 14 package</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361368358552</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:52:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361369032681-19</Id><Title>Tegra 4i based cheap iphone</Title><Msg>I think this would make good sense, Apple could finally release a $200-$300 cheap iphone for Asia market and still keep their differentiation for high-end iphone. I still need to see a successful standalone i500 release to buy into SDR modem concept.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1361369032681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:03:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361370111848-20</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 4i based cheap iphone</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1361369032681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:03:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>QCOM: Bernstein Sees Upside as China 3G Hits ‘Inflection Point’ "Bernstein Research’s Stacy Rasgon today reiterated an Outperform rating on shares of wireless chip maker Qualcomm (QCOM), and an price target, writing that China may have reached an “inflection point” in its shift of subscribers on older technology, dubbed “2G” to the newer technology of 3G cellular, and that such a shift may benefit the chip maker. ". As ibey was so fond of always reminding us, LTE is N.American story. N.America is dominated by aapl and Sammie. Sammie will never use this chip cause they have their own LTE and now an empty fab. aapl might be a bluebird for their cheap iPhone that is supposed to be due out this July. The main story, AGAIN, is still 2G/3G. Can i500 do 2G/3G? i400 was DOA and generated zero revenue the last two years for this reason. Is the i500 any better than 2G/3G? If not, will aapl pick up the T3i, its proper name, just for N.America and go elsewhere for rest of the world? Unlikely. anybody knows if this thing is any good at 2G/3G? grabbing the headlines has zero relationship wrt grabbing the bottom line.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1361370111848</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:21:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361370291409-21</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA: Tegra 4i appears to outperform the leading LTE integrated chip significantly, will showcase it at MWC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361328343278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 21:45:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so the emphasis at MWC will be the T3i..... guess should not expect much fanfare on T4 announcements then..... the T3 - T4 sales transition will be a sight to behold.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1361370291409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:24:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361370430315-22</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think NVDA is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>missionmildred</Username><Timestamp>1360080660065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:11:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love this report.</Msg><Username>null3francisca</Username><Timestamp>1361370430315</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:27:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361371131492-23</Id><Title>Let's break the 200DMA!</Title><Msg>Ok, everybody push!</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1361371131492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:38:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361371290772-24</Id><Title>Gaikai to Sony</Title><Msg>Okay You tell yourself. Good sales of grid to Gaikai. But now you ask yourself Sony bought them. Don't they have a larger base to work from? How big? How many grid servers would it take to service a Sony streaming service? may know more at 1800 today.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361371290772</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:41:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361371363038-25</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA: Tegra 4i appears to outperform the leading LTE integrated chip significantly, will showcase it at MWC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361328343278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 21:45:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra 4i is faster, smaller and cheaper than competition. Scroow Broadcom, Scroow Qualcomm!</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361371363038</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:42:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361372487700-26</Id><Topic><Title>Gaikai to Sony</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361371290772</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:41:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do not think Gaikai use Nvida any longer since Sony Buy-out I could be wrong but the tech was repurposed to streaming old playstation games for easy back compatability. Remember , Grid is PC games I don't see Sony streaming PC games</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1361372487700</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:01:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361374016707-27</Id><Title>The Bank of Nvidia Raises Nvidia To A Strong Buy!</Title><Msg>Is there any doubt The Bank of Nvidia is buying today?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361374016707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:26:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361374739679-28</Id><Topic><Title>The Bank of Nvidia Raises Nvidia To A Strong Buy!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361374016707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:26:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>j7777kxx, I can't wait for the day to be able to say to you, Congrats for remaing optimistic about NVDA stock. But so far it continues to a great disappoinment despite all the very positive news coming out. Let's see what Fate may have in store for us longs</Msg><Username>jtjgmtbt</Username><Timestamp>1361374739679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:38:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361375018438-29</Id><Topic><Title>The Bank of Nvidia Raises Nvidia To A Strong Buy!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361374016707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:26:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Csco and Yahoo are hitting 52 week highs caused buy their share buyback programs. Nothing is more positive when cash rich company's get serious about returning capital to their share holders. Heck IBM has made it into a science.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361375018438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:43:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361375074841-30</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA: Tegra 4i appears to outperform the leading LTE integrated chip significantly, will showcase it at MWC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361328343278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 21:45:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why can't you accept how awesome the nvda tegra is?? AND they power super computers!! Does qcom or brcm power super computers??? Just imagine what nvda could do if they focused SOLELY on mobile!!!!! Like qcom/brcm. .... Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha....</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1361375074841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:44:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361376272325-31</Id><Topic><Title>"WSJ: PlayStation 4 will have AMD silicon, cloud gaming"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361343760491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:02:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SHIELD this Nvidia fans. lol</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361376272325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:04:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361376730480-32</Id><Topic><Title>Gaikai to Sony</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361371290772</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:41:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>go to wwwDOTnvidiaDOTcom/object/cloud-get-startedDOThtml and GaiKai is no longer listed as a partner. Neither is Sony. Maybe that'll change after announcements later today, but I wouldn't bank on it. There's plenty of other good news to be optimistic about, though.</Msg><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361376730480</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:12:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361376743507-33</Id><Title>"Sony set to make pre-emptive strike on Microsoft with PS4"</Title><Msg>"TOKYO (Reuters) - Sony Corp is expected to showcase a new PlayStation console on Wednesday in a pre-emptive strike against Microsoft Corp's bid to make its Xbox the world's leading hub for household entertainment." NO SHIELD toys are DOA imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361376743507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:12:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361377247281-34</Id><Topic><Title>Did The Bank of Nvidia Start Buying Again?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360958594460</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 15:03:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that source must not have paid attention to the earnings release last week, or read the CFO commentary, or any of the reporting covering the results, since they very clearly did confirm purchasing $100M of stock last quarter, and returning another ~$47M via the dividend. And there's another dividend coming shortly. So so you've got almost $200M in cash returned to shareholders that's well-known... and more than $1B in share buybacks still approved by the board that they could execute on at any time.</Msg><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361377247281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:20:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361377453473-35</Id><Title>nvda's tegra 4 gives smartphone players a quantum leap in camera quality</Title><Msg>goog nexxus already bragging about having best pic quality ever seen in coming device. I wonder what chip? Technically nvda has broken a downtrend line and significant resistance at 12.75. A close above an nvda screams..............U heard it here first</Msg><Username>netttrunner</Username><Timestamp>1361377453473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:24:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361377523355-36</Id><Topic><Title>nvda's tegra 4 gives smartphone players a quantum leap in camera quality</Title><Username>netttrunner</Username><Timestamp>1361377453473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:24:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$14 by friday</Msg><Username>netttrunner</Username><Timestamp>1361377523355</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:25:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361378346852-37</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA: Tegra 4i appears to outperform the leading LTE integrated chip significantly, will showcase it at MWC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361328343278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 21:45:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Scroow whoo\osunw too. You wouldn't want to leave her out</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1361378346852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:39:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361380773302-38</Id><Title>Pondering Sony's Expected Streaming of PS3 Games to PS4 Using Gaikai Tech</Title><Msg>It's been reported in the Tech Press that Sony intends to use Gaikai cloud streaming service to make PS4 backward compatible with their new PS4 console. When Sony changed architecture for PS3 from PS2 for a few years they included the PS2 chipset in the new PS3 model so it was backwards compatable for PS2 games. After a few years they discontinued the PS2 chipset in PS3 and just continued selling PS2. Now it's been reported that they will again change processor architecture from the IBM cell processor and Nvidia RSX graphics to and AMD CPU/GPU combination and PS3 games will not be backwards compatible on PS4. Enter Gaikai and their Cloud streaming service which partnered with Nvidia Grid before it was purchased by Sony last July. So how is Gaikai going to render PS3 games in the cloud before streaming to the PS4? It seems to me they will have use the IBM cell processor Nvidia RSX graphics to do this in the cloud. It's been reported that Nvidia has an extremely lucrative royalty payments from Sony on the PS3. Would not those same royalty payments continue if the same architecture is used by Gaikai to render the PS3 games? Plus is it not a potential blockbuster break through of the feasibility of Cloud Gaming if Sony does in fact embrace Cloud gaming. Currently Nvidia has partnered with 6 other Cloud gaming services world wide using Nvidia Grid. In addition On-live uses Nvidia grid. I suspect we will all know the details at the Sony PS4 launch this afternoon but looking at the stock price moves of Nvidia and AMD todayI have a hunch where WS is putting their money. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361380773302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:19:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361384758299-39</Id><Title>Wireless Carriers Yearn to Cut Massive Smartphone Subsidies</Title><Msg>Dow Jones story. Plays right into our hands. We can save them a lot of money as most people don't buy a specific phone. They would accept any cheap good phone.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361384758299</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:25:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361385027976-40</Id><Title>apple cannot continue to develope processors on their own</Title><Msg>continuing to do so will put their entire business at risk....</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1361385027976</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:30:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361385055261-41</Id><Title>another hit piece by SemiAccurate</Title><Msg>i don't have "professional" membership, and won't pay a dime to semiaccurate to get it, but it from the portion of the article freely available it doesn't seem to contain any new news, and Charlie himself seems to be saying he thinks the modem and GPU will do just fine... which, given his bias, to me suggests he thinks it'll be quite a compelling offering. lol. it seems he takes issue with the naming scheme and that said name should be a warning sign to the financial community, which makes no sense to me but that's just my opinion.</Msg><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361385055261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:30:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361386133379-42</Id><Topic><Title>Pondering Sony's Expected Streaming of PS3 Games to PS4 Using Gaikai Tech</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361380773302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:19:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gaikai uses native hardware, previously a Nvidia GPU to render the game into a frame buffer, and then compresses using the CPU. Their approach is believed to require both a Nvidia GPU and the speed plus extended instructions available only in recent high-end Intel CPUs. This is in contrast to OnLive, which uses custom hardware to compress the video and thus can work with any hardware with a video out connector. It will be interesting to learn how Sony has worked with Gaikai to make their version of grid gaming work with PS3 games. The PS3 uses a modified PowerPC with Cell, combined with a Nvidia GPU. Emulating Power and Cell at the correct speed is pretty much infeasible. My guess is that Sony designed a new PCIe card that implements a full PS3, and modified the frame buffer to be accessible to the x86 host over PCIe. They then used the existing Gaikai compression software. This maintains Gaikai's advantage of better quality compression and being about one frame better on latency compared to the OnLive solution. (OnLive could improve their hardware for better quality, but can't solve the latency problem.) It's still about a frame higher latency than what Nvidia can achieve with their hinted-at compress-while-rendering approach. And Nvidia has the potential to further improve the compression quality and data rate because the GPU "understands" the objects it is rendering (motion tracking and fixed background are easy to understand, but the GPU also knows about more difficult to compress features such as the fog and focus effects it is rendering). So what does this mean for revenue? My guess is that it means more to Intel than anyone else. Sony has to buy high-end Intel CPUs at channel retail, while the PS3 chipset is sourced internally. Nvidia probably gets a royalty payment for each PS3 chipset, but it's not a huge volume. And who knows, they might be claimed as internal development machines, with no royalty payment. (Sony plays Hollywood Accounting with the best of them.) So imagine that grid gaming with PS3 games works. You don't really need a PS4. You only need a good low-latency video decoder and good game controller interface. You probably can even make do with a mediocre video decoder as found on most smartphones and every tablet. If you could only find a way to integrate a game controller...</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1361386133379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:48:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361386498899-43</Id><Topic><Title>another hit piece by SemiAccurate</Title><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361385055261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:30:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Charlie sounds like a bitter soul who lost a lot of money on NVDA stock over the years. Anyone who was buying based on hype and losing money because the company underperformed would share this viewpoint. But that aside - most of what he has written is true. Nvidia has the distinct honor of being very destructive to the OEMs that adopt its Tegra processor. I had posted a list of products few months ago - Zune, Ken, Moto etc. But at the end of the day - its all noise, if Nvidia has changed its tune and actually delivers good products on time - the stock will be rewarded, they are after all targeting a very large market with room for growth.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1361386498899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:54:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361386905589-44</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA making high</Title><Username>plazekgregory80</Username><Timestamp>1361374371273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great share. Many thanks</Msg><Username>gotbauma47</Username><Timestamp>1361386905589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:01:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361386917412-45</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA making high</Title><Username>plazekgregory80</Username><Timestamp>1361374371273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great share. Many thanks</Msg><Username>gotbauma47</Username><Timestamp>1361386917412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:01:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361387548905-46</Id><Topic><Title>This BS announcement of Grey, won't be available until next year?</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361303888273</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 14:58:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This BS announcement of Grey, won't be available until next year?" Nvidia fans don't seem to care when it comes out. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361387548905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:12:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361387818137-47</Id><Topic><Title>another hit piece by SemiAccurate</Title><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361385055261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:30:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>also this is totally my opinion but his last two articles feel like they could be responses to his professional subscribers saying "dude i thought you said the company is doomed, why are we losing money on our shorts... do something so we can cover!"</Msg><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361387818137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:16:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361387843552-48</Id><Topic><Title>Hold onto your wallet when you read pumping post filled with LIES</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361308539839</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:15:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every day same old BS. They make up junk to post here by the pound. They claim to know before PS4 is launched how Sony will do cloud gaming. NONSENSE They claim Nvidia is a bank. NONSENSE They claim Nvida has twice the cash per share that Apple has. NONSENSE A board full of NONSENSE. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361387843552</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:17:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361388136992-49</Id><Topic><Title>Folks, Qualcomm has cornered the smartphone market. Its chips are better than Nvidia's</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361345266362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:27:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Folks, Qualcomm has cornered the smartphone market. Its chips are better than Nvidia's" They'll figure it out one year. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361388136992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:22:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361388199177-50</Id><Title>T4i on Barrons</Title><Msg>Barrons article excerpts - S800 ~ 2X T4i size that's before you pay for their overpriced LTE "Miller Tabak’s Brendan Furlong reiterates a Buy rating on Nvidia as well, and a $17 price target, writing that “Nvidia is very well positioned to capture the high end of the Android and Windows 8 handset and Tablet opportunity.” In addition, the company is ideally placed to capture what could be a significant market opportunity in ARM based notebooks. The redesign of the Windows OS to work on ARM processors (WoA) has opened a high value market to Nvidia. We see the company exploiting WoA in coming years with future iterations of the current Tegra chip […] An important point on T4i is that the chip is half the size of QCOM (QCOM $65.67) Krait/S800 integrated chip. In addition, NVDA cited performance statistics that also put T4i ahead of the S800. For example NVDA says that SpecINT measures have the T4i 2.75x (** he misinterpreted this benchmark**) higher than the S800. Many of the recently announced enhancements to T4 have made their way into T4i. Computational photography image processing architecture call Chimera, High Dynamic Range (HDR) and Tap to Track photography all come as part of the T4i package […] High end smartphones and tablets will still be targeted with higher end A15 based T4. For the mid range smartphone market with expected prices in a range of $100-$199 super phone processors like T4 will not be required. If NVDA can gain entry to the higher volume mid-range smartphone market it could grow smartphone revenues significantly. We think the T4 processor will stay focused at the tablet market and T4i will target smartphones. T4i has the size and power characteristics to win share in mid-range smartphones and the addition of an integrated baseband makes the offering very attractive to phone OEM’s."</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361388199177</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:23:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361388375204-51</Id><Topic><Title>Pondering Sony's Expected Streaming of PS3 Games to PS4 Using Gaikai Tech</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361380773302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:19:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia's grid does not use a CPU for the encoding...all done on GPU I think...but will see. Anything that brings Cloud gaming closer to reality is a plus for Nvidia!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361388375204</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:26:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361388989361-52</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360282938040</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:22:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!" He put up this LIE on Feb 7 and ran away from it when caught. What LIE is he working on now? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361388989361</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:36:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361389149335-53</Id><Topic><Title>Apple has $42.40 Cash Per Share (mrq), Nvidiia has $5.50 Cash Per Share (mrq)!</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360288104528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:48:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So where the correction for that BIG LIE claiming: "Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!" He ran away form that LIE when caught . imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361389149335</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:39:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361391046844-54</Id><Title>NVDA's Stock</Title><Msg>Same old song. Tomorrow they'll announce a new chip capable of curing the common cold and the stock will still behave like a loser. I am selling, wish all the long the best and humbly bow to the sellers. They were right. Best regards to all.</Msg><Username>jtjgmtbt</Username><Timestamp>1361391046844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:10:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361392878036-55</Id><Title>What No buying on weakness or selling on silliness list nonsense today?</Title><Msg>Did the market dole out enough weakness for you Nvidia fans or would you like a lillte more to make a list? lol</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361392878036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:41:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361393357935-56</Id><Title>What happened to AMD's PPS</Title><Msg>They have great news coming out in 2 hours!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361393357935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:49:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361393482900-57</Id><Topic><Title>another hit piece by SemiAccurate</Title><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361385055261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:30:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>guess i struck a cord with SA, they're battling me on Twitter -- twitterDOTcom/SemiAccurate</Msg><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361393482900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:51:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361394288650-58</Id><Topic><Title>another hit piece by SemiAccurate</Title><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361385055261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:30:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Josh, Are you trying to monetize now for SemiAccurate rather than Facebook?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361394288650</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:04:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361394612713-59</Id><Topic><Title>another hit piece by SemiAccurate</Title><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361385055261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:30:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ha maybe i should have linked to my twitter stream instead. i've basically said repeatedly that the free part of the article seemed to confirm news already reported, acknowledges that the GPU and Modem are probably going to perform well, but then didn't suggest there would be anything in the "subscriber" part of the analysis worth paying $50 to read. SA didn't like that.</Msg><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361394612713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:10:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361394779130-60</Id><Topic><Title>another hit piece by SemiAccurate</Title><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361385055261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:30:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've known Charlie for well over 15 years. I can assure you that none of his motivations involve the stock market.</Msg><Username>khuzad</Username><Timestamp>1361394779130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:12:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361395198363-61</Id><Topic><Title>another hit piece by SemiAccurate</Title><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361385055261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:30:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>doesn't matter...just another "journalist" trying to make a living by selling something that is free everywhere else. Ask him what happened with the advertising model next time you see him? LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361395198363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:19:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361395250444-62</Id><Topic><Title>another hit piece by SemiAccurate</Title><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361385055261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:30:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what are his primary motivations in your opinion? the business side of SA certainly seems to rely pretty squarely on professionals operating "in the financial world" that are willing to pay $1000/year or $50/article.</Msg><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361395250444</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:20:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361395387839-63</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think NVDA is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>missionmildred</Username><Timestamp>1360080660065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:11:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just subscribed. I am hoping for the best.</Msg><Username>krigskunstenstrudy</Username><Timestamp>1361395387839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:23:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361397130691-64</Id><Topic><Title>another hit piece by SemiAccurate</Title><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361385055261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:30:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Josh, The internet has killed almost all opportunities for journalists. Only the New York Times, the London Sunday Times, The Financial Times with a few others pay journalists a living wage anymore.Therefore journalists have to find another way to make money off their writing skills. If anyone is worth anything as a stock analyst Wall Street will find them. not the other way around. Plus they can always start up their own financial newsletter....but those have advantages because they track their recommends vs.the S&amp;P 500 or other indices. Semiaccurate is just "Yellow Journalism" playing up sensationalism to sell copies of the evening paper. Randolf Hearst started it I think? I literally pay him and others like that zero attention.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361397130691</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:52:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361400929733-65</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA: Tegra 4i appears to outperform the leading LTE integrated chip significantly, will showcase it at MWC</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361328343278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 21:45:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cannot see any reason Tegra 4i won't be a homerun products. There is one concern needs to be clarified: Anyone know current 28nm i500 modem still has thermal issues as described by Patrick Wang from Evercore Partners in barrons' blogs? blogsDOTbarronsDOTcom/techtraderdaily/2013/02/20/nvidia-rising-bulls-cheer-entry-into-lte-market/?mod=yahoobarrons</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1361400929733</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 17:55:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361403420761-66</Id><Title>SONY introduces PlayStation 4, and AMD dropped a whopping 4.3%</Title><Msg>LOLOL PS: traders and bashers had better understand Wall Street's short-term logic first...</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1361403420761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:37:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361403830989-67</Id><Topic><Title>Folks, Qualcomm has cornered the smartphone market. Its chips are better than Nvidia's</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361345266362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:27:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Qcom may be still the leader at modem in 2013 but they cannot stop losing market share and profit margin with competitions from brcm, samsung, mediatech, intc and nvda.</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1361403830989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:43:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361404063816-68</Id><Title>Relative Costs S800, T4, T4i LTE</Title><Msg>DefectDensity - 0.2 Complexity factor 1 $6,500 per wafer (Using J7's number) for all cases modelled below - S800 120mm2 $29 +$3pkg ~ $32 final yielded tested packaged costs - Barron's S800 ASP $65 so this cost is about right, before including LTE T4i 60mm2 $10 +$2pkg ~ $12 final costs includes LTE T4 80mm2 $15 + $3pkg ~ $18 final costs no LTE S800+LTE ~ $65+$25 =$90 ASP, T4i ~ $25 ASP, T4 + LTE ~ $18 + $20 = $38 = THIS IS UNFAIR COMPETITION - SO EXPECT THE SHRILL MARKETING SCREAMS TO GET LOUDER AND HIGHER PITCHED LIKE THAT OF LITTLE PIGGiES BEFORE THE SLAUGHTER :)</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361404063816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361404327744-69</Id><Topic><Title>Folks, Qualcomm has cornered the smartphone market. Its chips are better than Nvidia's</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361345266362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:27:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Qualcomm is where Apple was last year. LOL</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1361404327744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:52:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361404769593-70</Id><Topic><Title>Relative Costs S800, T4, T4i LTE</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361404063816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction - S800+LTE ~ $65+$25 =$90 ASP, T4i ~ $25 ASP, T4 + LTE ~ $40 + $20 = $60 ASP The whining and the screams from the piglets wil get shriller and louder</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361404769593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:59:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361404958604-71</Id><Topic><Title>Folks, Qualcomm has cornered the smartphone market. Its chips are better than Nvidia's</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361345266362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:27:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you have cornered the market on stupidity.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1361404958604</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:02:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361407182302-72</Id><Topic><Title>Relative Costs S800, T4, T4i LTE</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361404063816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If these numbers are right, this is very encouraging.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1361407182302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:39:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361407993501-73</Id><Topic><Title>Relative Costs S800, T4, T4i LTE</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361404063816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra 4i is perfect for the $200 7 inch tablets. I'm still struck by the 11 inch Tegra 4 reference tablet shown at CES. Is this the new HP Tegra 4 tablet rumored to be in the works. And the 5 inch Tegra 4i reference phone. Is it the new unlocked Nexus 5 for $200. If google got behind a quality $200 unlocked Lte phone it would be came over Apple. Well maybe maybe not...But after all they are just phones!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361407993501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:53:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361409285577-74</Id><Title>One things is for sure, Nvidia will shutdown this tegra nonsense</Title><Msg>in a few months. All the OEMS are mad at Jensun and won't use this tegra stuff. There are many other alternatives, like Mediatek, which sells their chips for real cheap.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361409285577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:14:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361409348987-75</Id><Topic><Title>One things is for sure, Nvidia will shutdown this tegra nonsense</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361409285577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:14:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>STUPID !!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361409348987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:15:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361409670983-76</Id><Title>Sony PS4 obsoletes that Shield stuff that Jensun was touting. LOL.</Title><Msg>Shield -- done before it even gets started.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361409670983</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:21:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361409833897-77</Id><Title>Subject</Title><Msg>STUPID !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361409833897</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:23:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361409864170-78</Id><Topic><Title>Relative Costs S800, T4, T4i LTE</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361404063816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mediatek will have quad-core+LTE chips next year too, and Mediatek is a chinese company, their chips will be cheaper than this Tegra BS.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361409864170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:24:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361409938254-79</Id><Topic><Title>Relative Costs S800, T4, T4i LTE</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361404063816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>provide the pricing of tegra &amp; mediatek... or rather you have NO CLUE.... NONE !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361409938254</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:25:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361411304578-80</Id><Title>No mention of that drop to the right just more BS about up up and away right?</Title><Msg>Keep kidding each other on a message board that Nvidia at $12.38 is wonderful OK? And today was another bank of BS buying back shares OK? lol The same folks called $26 junk and said everyone should hold out for $30, $50 and $100. The $30, $50 and $100 pumpers won't even acknowledge they wrote those words today. They got caught being silly and WALKED AWAY FROM THEIR OWN POST. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361411304578</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:48:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361411648621-81</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia closed at $13.15 BEFORE that SHIELD toy demo and it hasn't seen it since.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1360943893246</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 10:58:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hasn't seen $13.15 since that desperate attempt to find Tegra 4 a home with that SHIELD toy fisaco in Vegas. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361411648621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:54:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361411973987-82</Id><Topic><Title>This BS announcement of Grey, won't be available until next year?</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361303888273</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 14:58:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This BS announcement of Grey, won't be available until next year?" Find a pumpers post about Tegra 4i WITH 2014 IN THE POST? They all cut that part out and put the 2014 bit on ignore. They pretend that Tegra 4i is on sale today even though we all know it ain't. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361411973987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:59:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361412108534-83</Id><Topic><Title>Hold onto your wallet when you read pumping post filled with LIES</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361308539839</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:15:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did I say they make up stuff thinking that will lift Nvidia? Did I say that some here have no problem posting out right LIES thinking that will lift Nvidia? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361412108534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:01:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361412338452-84</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360282938040</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:22:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!" And he is STILL making up stuff. Does he have any shame in posting our right LIES. He has to know now that:Apple has $42.40 Cash Per Share (mrq), Nvidiia has $5.50 Cash Per Share (mrq) Do you see a correction? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361412338452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:05:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361412997095-85</Id><Title>"PlayStation 4: More than just a pixel powerhouse"</Title><Msg>"The Console: The PlayStation 4 will be powered by chips that would make any top-of-the-line PC user drool: A "supercharged" x86 processor, a PC-style graphics processor, and eight gigabytes of RAM. With these guts serving as the PS4's central brain, the console is capable of pushing some truly stunning graphics. It'll likely be ready for the next five to 10 years of living room display technology. "</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361412997095</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:16:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361413024156-86</Id><Title>ZTE, Nvidia team up to launch Tegra 4 handsets in China</Title><Msg>"The Chinese phone manufacturer, ZTE, has teamed up with Nvidia to launch a line of quad-core smartphones slated for midyear or earlier. These handsets will feature the Tegra 4 chipset, which was unveiled last month during CES 2013. Based on ARM Cortex-A15 architecture, Tegra 4 is expected to be much faster and more powerful than its predecessor, which was based on ARM Cortex-A9. Tegra 4 also features six times as many graphics cores (bringing the total to 72) than its predecessor. Along with building these quad-core devices, ZTE announced that it plans on making one phone that will also feature Nvidia's i500 processor, which will enable 4G LTE voice and data capabilities. ZTE already has a few quad-core handsets under its belt (like the Nubia Z5, and the more recent Grand S). And with handsets like the Tegra 3-sporting ZTE Grand Era U985, we know it's no stranger to working with Nvidia. However, many of these quad-core devices rarely make it to the U.S. ZTE was one of the earliest phone manufacturers to officially announce building handsets featuring Tegra 4, and it'd be interesting to see and experience how fast these phones turn out to be. Source: news.cnetDOTcom/8301-1035_3-57570366-94/zte-nvidia-team-up-to-launch-tegra-4-handsets-in-china/ __________________________________________________________________________ Hit It Mr. Intel and XC - Because You know it just ain't true...LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361413024156</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:17:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361413297460-87</Id><Title>Here they come! ZTE, Nvidia team up to launch Tegra 4 handsets in China</Title><Msg>Along with building these quad-core devices, ZTE announced that it plans on making one phone that will also feature Nvidia's i500 processor, which will enable 4G LTE voice and data capabilities</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361413297460</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:21:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361413528314-88</Id><Topic><Title>"PlayStation 4: More than just a pixel powerhouse"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361412997095</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:16:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It'll likely be ready for the next five to 10 years of living room display technology" Does that mean Nvidia is out of its old Playstation job for 5 to 10 years? Now you know what that SHIELD toy is all about right? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361413528314</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:25:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361413587526-89</Id><Topic><Title>Relative Costs S800, T4, T4i LTE</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361404063816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here comes the squealing, the whining and the squalid piggies.</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361413587526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:26:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361413826168-90</Id><Topic><Title>Relative Costs S800, T4, T4i LTE</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361404063816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They should be within 10% to 15%. Variables are 1) actual wafer pricing affecting everybody about equally 2) Defect density of the 28nm process which if it is worse than 0.2 will affect larger die more drastically than smaller ones due the exponential nature 3) a few cents here and there on packaging and testing.</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361413826168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:30:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361414686689-91</Id><Title>"PlayStation 4 Announced: PC-based AMD Hardware Inside"</Title><Msg>"As expected, Sony used its PlayStation 'See the Future' event to show off the next generation of PlayStation, also known as the PlayStation 4. In a radical departure from the rather "unique" system designs that Sony's employed in the past, PS4 seems to be largely designed around existing PC technology. Sony says that the PS4 has been in development for five years, which is a bit surprising as the PS4 is based on x86 architecture with 8 cores, an integrated GPU, and 8GB of shared GDDR5 RAM. Sony used the word APU, which gives us pretty good confirmation that it's AMD inside. The graphical portion of the APU is said to deliver almost 2 TFLOPS of performance. The 8GB of unified memory is shared between the CPU and GPU and supplies over 170GB/s of bandwidth." Source Tom's Hardware</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361414686689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:44:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361415272418-92</Id><Topic><Title>Relative Costs S800, T4, T4i LTE</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361404063816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It seems for their performance other than the t4i, they are over priced Fudzilla Tuesday, 19 February 2013 11:08 Pentium Haswell starts at $64 Written by Fuad Abazovic</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1361415272418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:54:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361415750480-93</Id><Title>Engadget: ZTE to ship the first Tegra 4 superphones by mid-year</Title><Msg>When NVIDIA unveiled the Tegra 4 last month, there were questions as to when it would ship in a phone, or whether it was bound for phones in the first place. ZTE has settled that question with plans to be the first company shipping Tegra 4-packing smartphones. The Chinese phone builder won't spoil the surprise by naming the devices in question, but the first models reach China by mid-2013. An LTE "super phone" is in the pipeline, ZTE says. With that fresh ground broken, we're mostly left wondering how likely it is that these devices will cross the Pacific -- as well as guessing which other companies are lined up for NVIDIA's fourth-generation silicon. SOURCE: engadgetDOTcom/2013/02/20/zte-to-ship-some-of-the-first-tegra-4-phones-by-mid-2013/ ______ Now we know the shipment of Tegra 4 phones is a lot sooner than later.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361415750480</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:02:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361415778596-94</Id><Topic><Title>Relative Costs S800, T4, T4i LTE</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361404063816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra 4i Due out 2014 right? QCOM parts today right? Is that right? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361415778596</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:02:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361415938588-95</Id><Topic><Title>Engadget: ZTE to ship the first Tegra 4 superphones by mid-year</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361415750480</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:02:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra 4 is not for sale today right? So it will be a while before the "first company shipping Tegra 4-packing smartphones" ships anything right? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361415938588</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:05:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361416159854-96</Id><Title>QCOM shipping LTE for products Today right, Tegra 4i due out for 2014 products right?</Title><Msg>Whats the difference between shipping for REVENUE TODAY and NOT SHIPPING UNTIL 2014? Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1361416159854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:09:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361417301395-97</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE, Nvidia team up to launch Tegra 4 handsets in China</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361413024156</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:17:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice job! So do you think we'll see apologies and retractions from the idjits writing articles saying there would be no deals?</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1361417301395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:28:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361417493320-98</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE, Nvidia team up to launch Tegra 4 handsets in China</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361413024156</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:17:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like Nvidia PR is in full swing.. Jensen has been lying all time according to Charlie at Semiaccurate.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361417493320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:31:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361417899329-99</Id><Topic><Title>Relative Costs S800, T4, T4i LTE</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361404063816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haswell $64 and comes free with a space heater :) = Great deal for the clueless</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361417899329</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:38:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361418018089-100</Id><Topic><Title>Relative Costs S800, T4, T4i LTE</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361404063816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have lost the plot! You were against everything Arm etc why are you promoting Mediatek Arn now? iDIOT BOX.</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361418018089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:40:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361418084106-101</Id><Title>Playstation4 will play Android and IOS games. Shield is Jensun jackin off</Title><Msg>for sure. Flush that. LOL.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361418084106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:41:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361418728823-102</Id><Topic><Title>Sizeable volume in $13.50, $14 calls expiring next friday</Title><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1360970457490</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 18:20:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, I just got some time to look at some of these messages because I really did take the weekend off with limited access. And the main reason I'm even responding is because Yahoo sets it up so you know when someone responds. In any case, thanks for all that you shared. I appreciate that. Saying you seem young wasn't really in a pejorative way and the time you took to write this just seems to be way overwrought with proving something you really don't need to prove. Also, I think the way I made that one comment involved none of the assumptions you are making. It was simply pointing out some news about the timeline was better then you seem to anticipate in your previous posts which is better then you thought, hence the 'yes?'. You have been giving a lot of time to your analysis so thanks for the time you are giving; it would make sense IMO that you did put together articles for someone like SA, but that's up to you obviously. And I did mean it when I said take a break for the weekend because you seem to be really driven with the time you have taken on these responses. I do think my responses have been constructive for the most part and that you have been overreaching in your assumptions about what I was doing, ie being patronizing etc. That is I why I tend to think posters who are informative or more constructive in their criticism also tend to take less time to make their points, and/or have less a need to add several posts to one comment which you did at one point with me. That is the perception, obviously you may disagree with it. Anyways, thanks again for the contributions to this board. My time is limited for posting so hopefully this is enough in response to the time you gave to this trail of messages.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1361418728823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:52:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361420770861-103</Id><Title>Head and Shoulders</Title><Msg>Sitting right at support, but see a H&amp;S Pattern forming. Mid December (Left shoulder), Early January (Head), and Mid February (Right Shoulder). Also, the 5-day chart shows a triple top formation, so a drop to $12 in a weak market is a very strong probability. Traders love NVDA because it moves very close to expected Fibonacci ratios. Short term "sell", long term "buy". The high Beta makes NVDA move in an exaggerated fashion.</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1361420770861</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 23:26:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>