<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-28"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372392837695-1</Id><Title>If consoles are dead, why is google developing an android console. LOL.</Title><Msg>Ibex is such an optimist that he has lost sense of reality. Either that or he's a paid pumper.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372392837695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:13:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372393783209-2</Id><Title>Rumor is that shield needs fans... Mechanical issue could be fans don't run</Title><Msg>well, and hence its delayed.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372393783209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:29:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372393856108-3</Id><Topic><Title>If consoles are dead, why is google developing an android console. LOL.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372392837695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a legitimate question that you asked, so I shall accord you with a serious answer. Google's console, if materilized, will be part of EL Goog's ecosystem. This console arguably would not be standing alone, like PS4 or Nintendo Wii U or the likes; rather it will be communicable with other Android devices - phones, tablets and laptops. Apple;s rumored console is reportedly part of the AppleTV also. xBox family of consoles are somewhat in between as MS is far from a media giant, but I think this may be one of its strategic goals. From this perspective the Xbox One is in a stronger position than PS4. Still don't get it? - go find someone who will dumb it down for you. (Suggestion: one of the SA bloggers)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372393856108</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:30:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372395175953-4</Id><Topic><Title>Taken Down a Notch and Marked Down too the Problematic SHIELD is DOA</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372365697193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 16:41:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How long before Nvidia moves SHIELD back to being a Project to end the embarrassment? We now know SHIELD is a very low volume product because their is no way Nvidia can dismantle, repair and test 10s of thousands of units in one month. A few thousand units exist at best. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372395175953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:52:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372395985237-5</Id><Title>Nvidia's story doesn't add up. You can't fix more than a few thousand units in one month.</Title><Msg>Do you think Nvidia can dismantle, repair, re-test and then repackage more that a few thousand SHIELD units in a month? Xbox One and PS4 will take several months to build enough inventory to launch there is no way they could repair and redo that effort in one month. What is Nvidia hiding? How many SHIELD units exist? 100 or 1000? This is looking more like a another GIMMICK or a proof of concept over marketed. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372395985237</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:06:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372396560175-6</Id><Title>Nvidia had to know SHIELD was Broken before Launch Day -1. Why the DELAY?</Title><Msg>Why did Nvidia wait until launch Day -1 to announce SHIELD was BROKEN? QA didn't just find the problem. Were they trying to hide it? Were they coming up with a plan to blame some unnamed 3rd Party? Why not take down the Pre-Orders if they knew it was BROKEN and WOULD NOT SHIP as advertized? Nvidia's story does not add up. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372396560175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:16:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372416943939-7</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: Google is developing Android video game console</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372375022806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 19:17:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Long-term, it's a good news for NVIDIA and Tegra. Short/mid-term, I'm afraid it's just a good news for Qualcomm ...</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1372416943939</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 06:55:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372417656072-8</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: Google is developing Android video game console</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372375022806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 19:17:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the loaded reply ibexx. I still believe that they will pull a rabbit out of the hat and announce that Denver will be available much sooner than scheduled. It will be very interesting to see how how things play-out since the big 3 will need to make some kind of licensing commitment relatively soon if they want top-line performance that IMG can't provide. Paranoia also comes into play as the others don't want to take the risk of having substandard performance.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1372417656072</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 07:07:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372426685508-9</Id><Title>BBRY takes a bath - Shares off 25%</Title><Msg>Blackberry offered few signs of a long-promised turnaround on Friday, with an unexpected quarterly operating loss, few details on sales of its make-or-break new devices and no return to profit in the current quarter. BlackBerry, struggling to compete against Apple Inc's iPhone, Samsung's Galaxy smartphones and other devices powered by Google's Android operating system, reported a net loss of $84 million, or 16 cents a share, in the first quarter ended June 1.</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1372426685508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:38:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372427561518-10</Id><Title>Nvidia CUT IN HALF From $26, back to $13s Again Like old times Nvidia fans? lol</Title><Msg>Enjoy your Marked Down, Recently Repaired and now DOA SHIELD Toy if it ever ships. lol IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372427561518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:52:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372427882677-11</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia CUT IN HALF From $26, back to $13s Again Like old times Nvidia fans? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372427561518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:52:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two years ago Nvidia was $26 and today, just like that SHIELD Toy was marked down, Nvidia has been marked down to $13s. Do you call that winning Nvidia fans? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372427882677</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:58:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372428303379-12</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's story doesn't add up. You can't fix more than a few thousand units in one month.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372395985237</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can there be more than ONE ot TWO thousand SHIELD Units out there if it only takes one month to bring them back in house, dismantle, repair, re-test, repackage and get the truck back to pick up the recently repaired SHIELD Toys? If Nvidia had every employee working overtime on Prject SHIELD Out Until Repaied (SOUR) Lemon they could not pull it off with any HIGH VOLUME product in one month. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372428303379</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:05:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372428466726-13</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia had to know SHIELD was Broken before Launch Day -1. Why the DELAY?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372396560175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:16:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And when July comes don't be surprised if it you hear August? lol SHIELD is nothing more than a Marketing GIMMICK gone bad. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372428466726</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372428811929-14</Id><Title>Unnamed 3rd Party Did it, Nvidia had nothing to do with a BROKEN SHIELD.</Title><Msg>Did anyne get a good look at this "Unnamed 3rd Party" with issues? Would you be able to pick persons "Unnamed" out of a lineup Nvidia ? lmao Round that "Unnamed 3rd Party" up and bring them to justice for DELAYING your Pretend Play Time, right Nvidia fans? IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372428811929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372429302883-15</Id><Topic><Title>Unnamed 3rd Party Did it, Nvidia had nothing to do with a BROKEN SHIELD.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372428811929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:13:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has Nvidia ever taken responsibility for anything? Do you remember how Nvidia blaimed BUMPGATE on TSMC? Nvidia had nothing to do with shipping defective GPUs back then too, right Nvidia fans? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372429302883</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:21:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372430302710-16</Id><Topic><Title>Ouya now #17 on on Amazon from #40 as of yesterday</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372390634850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 23:37:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am hoping that the ouya team can have a quick turn around time for coming out with the second version with a tegra 4 and google play. While it is exciting to see an indie console developer having success, the lack of google play store is a big omission (as having netflix, hulu plus, etc. on this would have been a big selling point). Would having google play access be incompatible with their current business model (all games at least partially free-to-play, ouya store)? If the ouya 2 is not out soon after the madcatz android console (which will likely have tegra 4), then they might be in trouble.</Msg><Username>morrowltd</Username><Timestamp>1372430302710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:38:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372430489294-17</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: Google is developing Android video game console</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372375022806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 19:17:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re. Denver: it would have to be more than one rabbits being pulled out of hats, as Denver's release hinges on the TSMC's process availability/maturity.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372430489294</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372430542870-18</Id><Topic><Title>Ouya now #17 on on Amazon from #40 as of yesterday</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372390634850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 23:37:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And OUYA the "product" is being OUT SOLD by Xbox One or PS4 Pre-Orders. Since neither either one is shipping it proves consumers would rather wait then BUY junk now. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372430542870</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372430660549-19</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: Google is developing Android video game console</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372375022806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 19:17:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is great news. The more support android gaming gets, the better for nvidia. Would tegra have a chance at winning the smart watch?</Msg><Username>morrowltd</Username><Timestamp>1372430660549</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:44:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372430717098-20</Id><Title>Xbox One or PS4 Pre-Orders OUT SELL shipping Ouya, Stop the BS</Title><Msg>That says consumers would rather wait for a quality Game Console then BUY junk now. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372430717098</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:45:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372430986005-21</Id><Topic><Title>Unnamed 3rd Party Did it, Nvidia had nothing to do with a BROKEN SHIELD.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372428811929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:13:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will Nvidia be blaming another Unnamed 3rd Party if SHIELD is a NO SHOW again in July? Or will Nvidia blame the same Unnamed 3rd Party? lol We know Nvidia WILL NOT TAKE Responsibility for anything that goes SOUR imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372430986005</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:49:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372432656336-22</Id><Topic><Title>Wuh oh or Whoopee? Google making game console, watch - report</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1372384607885</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 21:56:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude, make up your mind what side you are on . . you aren't being taken seriously with your flips.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1372432656336</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:17:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372433048096-23</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: Google is developing Android video game console</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372375022806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 19:17:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Qualcomm??? Why would it be Qualcomm? Google showcased Shield at their recent conference and considering that Google plans to release something like that by this Fall (according to CNBC) the shortest path is to clone Shield and put their own stamp on it. Apparently the companies are close and are practically neighbors. Why develop everything from scratch if you have ready reference machine next door and the timing is short?</Msg><Username>jake63634</Username><Timestamp>1372433048096</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:24:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372435856452-24</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ just in: Google is developing Android video game console</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372375022806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 19:17:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As I said before, the long-term winners will be decided on, besides performance factors, who owns the most popularized ecosystem(s) and which players are feeding into it - ie. Google and NVIDIA would be a safe guess. There is more from the above referenced WSJ article: ""Google's head of Android, Sundar Pichai, in May said more than 900 million devices powered by Android had been activated worldwide, up from 400 million a year ago and 100 million two years ago. Jen-Hsun Huang, the chief executive of Nvidia Corp., NVDA +0.43% which makes microchips for devices powered by Android, said in a recent interview that over time there would be three billion people who use Android devices, and that one million programmers globally are already using the software to build applications or devices. He said Android is poised to disrupt the videogame and consumer-electronics industry; computer systems in cars; as well as personal computing, such as desktop computers. He declined to discuss any unreleased products. Think about it....</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372435856452</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:10:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372436087657-25</Id><Title>Embarrassing Week for Nvidia, SHIELD Broken, Stock Traded in the $13s Again.</Title><Msg>And unless Nvidia can close at or above $14.42 today the stock will be down 4 out of the last 5 weeks. The joke on Nvidia investors this week is SHIELD is back to being a Project. Project Shield Out Until Repaired or as its friends call it, Project SOUR Lemon. lol IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372436087657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:14:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372436359849-26</Id><Topic><Title>Wuh oh or Whoopee? Google making game console, watch - report</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1372384607885</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 21:56:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Dude, make up your mind what side you are on " Its not about chosing sides., Its about NOT LOSING YOUR SHIRT betting on junk. As in on the side that wants to continue to be able to buy FOOD. lmao IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372436359849</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:19:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372436467825-27</Id><Title>NVIDIA Tesla GPU Accelerators Power World's Most Energy Efficient Supercomputer</Title><Msg>Latest Green500 Results Establish GPU Accelerator Advantage vs. CPUs, All Other Accelerators for Energy Efficient, High Performance Supercomputing SANTA CLARA, CA -- (Marketwired) -- 06/28/13 -- NVIDIA today announced that NVIDIA® Tesla® GPU accelerators are powering the world's two most energy efficient supercomputers, based on the latest Green500 list published today. The winning system is 'Eurora' at CINECA, Italy's largest supercomputing center, in Casalecchio di Reno. Equipped with NVIDIA Kepler™ architecture-based GPU accelerators -- the highest-performance, most efficient accelerators ever built -- Eurora delivers 3,210 MFlops per watt, making it 2.6 times more energy efficient than the best system using Intel CPUs alone (at Météo France). It also greatly surpasses the most efficient Intel Xeon Phi accelerator-based system, 'Beacon,' at the National Institute for Computational Sciences, at the University of Tennessee. The number-two system on the June 2013 Green500 list is the 'Aurora Tigon' supercomputer at the Selex ES facilities Chieti, Italy. These top two systems are powered by advanced Eurotech high-performance 'Aurora' servers, equipped with NVIDIA Tesla K20 GPU accelerators. More broadly, NVIDIA Kepler GPU accelerator-based systems in the top 100 spots on the Green500 list are 50 percent more energy efficient on average than the latest Intel Xeon Phi-based systems.</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1372436467825</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:21:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372437174766-28</Id><Topic><Title>Xbox One or PS4 Pre-Orders OUT SELL shipping Ouya, Stop the BS</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372430717098</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:45:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If a Pre-Order can OUT SELL any Product ON THE SHELF then that Product must be JUNK. Or that Pre-Order MUST be Really Worth the Wait. Is it sinking in yet Nvidia fans? lol IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372437174766</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372437507985-29</Id><Topic><Title>Embarrassing Week for Nvidia, SHIELD Broken, Stock Traded in the $13s Again.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372436087657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:14:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And meanwhile in Pretend Time Play Land Nvidia fans are STILL singing Nvidia's praises AFTER a week to forget. Stock DOWN, SHIELD DOWN and some "Unnamed 3rd Party" is out breaking Nvidia's Toys? lol MHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372437507985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372438164435-30</Id><Title>Any word on Project SHIELD Out Until Repaired or SOUR Lemon Nvidia fans? lol</Title><Msg>Did they round up that offending unammed 3rd party yet or FIX SHIELD for good? Do you think they'll put the recently repaired SHIELD in new boxes or just re-tape the old boxes? lol I say splurge a little and go with new boxes. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372438164435</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:49:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372438853411-31</Id><Title>Breaking: Intel technology chief Rattner to step down.....</Title><Msg>SOURCE: WSJ One of the most familiar faces at Intel events, Justin Rattner, is giving up the post of chief technology officer at the giant chip maker. Intel said Thursday that Rattner, 65 years old, is hitting the company’s mandatory retirement age for corporate officers. He will depart immediately to attend to what the company called a “pressing family matter,” but will subsequently return to Intel in a post still to be determined, the company said. Rattner also is a vice president and director of Intel Labs, the company’s research arm. Those operations will report to Renee James, Intel’s newly appointed president, until further leadership decisions are made, Intel said. The announcement comes as something of a surprise, as Rattner hosted an Intel research event in San Francisco Tuesday with no mention of any impending changes. Rattner, like James, spent most of his time at Intel’s large operations in Oregon rather than at the corporate headquarters in Santa Clara, Calif. He joined the company in 1973. Unlike many senior technologists at the company, he did not start out in fields such as designing semiconductors or perfecting recipes for how to manufacture them. Rather, Rattner is best known for his expertise in the field of high-performance computing. In the 1980s and 1990s, he helped advance the concepts of “massively parallel” computers, built using hundreds or thousands of standard microprocessor chips rather than a few custom-built calculating engines. Intel at one time sold such systems itself, though later withdrew to focus on supplying chips for them. Rattner was known for his work on a machine called ASCII Red that was built by Intel and installed at Sandia National Laboratories in 1996. The massive machine was credited as the first computer to sustain one trillion scientific calculations per second....</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372438853411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:00:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372438953018-32</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Tesla GPU Accelerators Power World's Most Energy Efficient Supercomputer</Title><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1372436467825</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:21:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very soon, Kepler will be in mobile SoC. According Jenson, Logan will come out end of this year and start shipping early next year.</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1372438953018</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:02:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372441979836-33</Id><Title>Today: last trading day of Q2. Window dressing time</Title><Msg>Funds dumping AMD while adding INTC, NVDA</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372441979836</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:52:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372444110482-34</Id><Title>xc Responsible for 10 of the last 15 Posts</Title><Msg>Obsessive. Get help, man.</Msg><Username>resrij5x</Username><Timestamp>1372444110482</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372448254595-35</Id><Topic><Title>xc Responsible for 10 of the last 15 Posts</Title><Username>resrij5x</Username><Timestamp>1372444110482</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:28:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let XC post what he like, He is wasting his life time on NVDA board .....</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1372448254595</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:37:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372448574658-36</Id><Title>AMD Higher this Week than Last while Nvidia's SHIELD Fell Flat on its .... Yes it did. lol</Title><Msg>Enjoy PICTURES of Project Shield Out Until Reparied or as its firends call it Project SOUR Lemon this weekend Nvidia fans because the actual SHIELD is STILL IN THE SHOP, is it not? lmao IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372448574658</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372449362455-37</Id><Title>AS Q2 Closes AMD Poised to be the TOP S&amp;P GAINER for Q2 2013, AMD UP 60%</Title><Msg>Todays word and the word for all of Q2 is: Performance As in One Solid Q2 Performance AMD. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372449362455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:56:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372449905739-38</Id><Topic><Title>Any word on Project SHIELD Out Until Repaired or SOUR Lemon Nvidia fans? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372438164435</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:49:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is Walmart running a sale on Crazy Glue ? If they are then Jen and company should ship a tubeof crazy glue with every SHIELD that goes out he door, if they ever get one out the door. When they stop by Walmart just mention that Nvidia is a Life Time Member of the Rollback Club for a special discount. lmao IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372449905739</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:05:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372450093284-39</Id><Topic><Title>Embarrassing Week for Nvidia, SHIELD Broken, Stock Traded in the $13s Again.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372436087657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:14:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"And unless Nvidia can close at or above $14.42 today the stock will be down 4 out of the last 5 weeks." Book em Dano. Its in the books, Nvidia DOWN 4 out of the last 5 weeks and SHIELD is STILL Broken. What say you Nvidia fans? IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372450093284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:08:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372450093393-40</Id><Topic><Title>Today: last trading day of Q2. Window dressing time</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372441979836</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try again. Ha!</Msg><Username>e5game</Username><Timestamp>1372450093393</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:08:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372451382261-41</Id><Title>Who's Waiting for a Recently Repaired, Repackaged Open Box, Marked Down POS Toy?</Title><Msg>A Recently Repaired SHIELD Toy that Nvidia is trying to sell as NEW AND IMPROVED? If you find anyone waiting for SHIELD and NOT pumping Nvidia on this board 24/7 then Nvidia may have 3 solid sales leads to work with. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372451382261</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:29:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372451692426-42</Id><Topic><Title>AS Q2 Closes AMD Poised to be the TOP S&amp;P GAINER for Q2 2013, AMD UP 60%</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372449362455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:56:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone wanting to keep up with AMD needs to put up 60% or better on that S&amp;P board for Q2 2013. And you know who won't come anywhere close to posting that kind of "Performance" don't you Nvidia fans? lol IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372451692426</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:34:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372452251700-43</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Higher this Week than Last while Nvidia's SHIELD Fell Flat on its .... Yes it did. lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372448574658</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:42:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whenever Nvidia gets its SHIELD Out Until Repaired (SOUR) Lemon fixed you can let the 2 or 3 Nvidia pumpers on this board that there SOUR Lemon is ready for pick up. You can't SPIN a week that saw Nvidia management embarrassed every time they mentioned SHIELD as good news. lol IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372452251700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:44:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372452954223-44</Id><Topic><Title>Unnamed 3rd Party Did it, Nvidia had nothing to do with a BROKEN SHIELD.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372428811929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:13:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Nvidia fans did Nvidia locate that unnamed 3rd party culprit breaking their SHIELD Toys? Do they have a name now? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372452954223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372457583343-45</Id><Topic><Title>If consoles are dead, why is google developing an android console. LOL.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372392837695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So are consoles dead or not. Stop making up things.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372457583343</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 18:13:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372459538289-46</Id><Topic><Title>If consoles are dead, why is google developing an android console. LOL.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372392837695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Forrest Gump Jr., stop being a mentally challenged D-BAG all your pathetic life. Now go find lieutenant Dan to explain it to you.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1372459538289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 18:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372462275219-47</Id><Topic><Title>If consoles are dead, why is google developing an android console. LOL.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372392837695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No need to be rude. The dude gave you a more thoughtful response than your trite comment deserved. Consoles, as they exist today, are on the way out. Google, with its variety of gadgets and services, can probably use the console concept to be so much more. Microsoft probably can, too. In fact, they seem to want to. They just don't seem to be doing it yet. Sony, well, they probably could, too, but they have nothing like the ecosystem to tie into.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1372462275219</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372464243281-48</Id><Topic><Title>If consoles are dead, why is google developing an android console. LOL.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372392837695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So are CONSOLES dead or not. If they are dead, why is google developing a console for its own Android ecosystem. Let me explain to you, why consoles are not dead. REAL GAMERS need a 50" screen to play REAL GAMES, not your piddly Angry birds toy games on shield with a 7" screen.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372464243281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 20:04:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372464937110-49</Id><Topic><Title>If consoles are dead, why is google developing an android console. LOL.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372392837695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Let me explain to you, why consoles are not dead. REAL GAMERS need a 50" screen to play REAL GAMES, not your piddly Angry birds toy games" That's exactly why Google and Nvidia are making these devices; they want to encourage higher quality third party game development. Unfortunately bringing in gamers is somewhat of a catch 22. Gamers want high quality third party game development; the high quality third party game developers want gamers. Someone has to start somewhere, and Nvidia, Google, and Apple clearly want to get the ball rolling.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1372464937110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 20:15:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372469813061-50</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's story doesn't add up. You can't fix more than a few thousand units in one month.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372395985237</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they include the Temp workers and the lunch room staff then Maybe Nvidia can dismantle, repair, re-test and then repackage approximately 631 SHIELD Toys in one month give or take few according my BROKEN SHIELD iPad App? lmao Which is much more than they will EVER need, right Nvidia fans. Put your hand down, that includes ALL the perma pumpers on this board. Hey that 631 number is as good as the BS Nvidia has been putting out, isn't it? IMHO of course</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372469813061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 21:36:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372470119142-51</Id><Topic><Title>If consoles are dead, why is google developing an android console. LOL.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372392837695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You got a bunch of Nvidia board pumpers talking out of both sides of the mouth at the same time and trying to start a 3rd conversation out of their tail pipe trying to SPIN Google's latest move. lol One word sums up all their gibberish, CLUELESS. IMHO of course</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372470119142</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 21:41:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372470288242-52</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's story doesn't add up. You can't fix more than a few thousand units in one month.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372395985237</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dismantle, repair and repackage would depend entirely on the assembly stage of the defect, and I would probably say the thumbsticks are somewhere towards the end, so that is possible. If Nvidia has known of the issue for some time, they most likely have already developed plan B repair line; the fact that they announced the delay last week probably means that they line wasn't running as fast enough to meet the release date. As for the re-test aspect, have you ever worked in industry? Very rarely is every single product tested; what they will do however is a capability study with a random sampling of the repair line to determine if Shield is meeting the requirements.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1372470288242</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 21:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>