<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-17"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361077759480-1</Id><Topic><Title>Tracking Nvidia's PPS vs. Ashraf's NVDA Articles</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361027499566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 10:11:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks. totally off topic and fairly personal for the board, but i don't really mind answering... part of me does wish i stayed at Facebook, mainly because i would have gotten to continue working on really interesting things, and in hindsight helping to build products was definitely more fulfilling than investing/trading has turned out to be, financial returns aside. i really thought "retiring" at 25 was a dream come true... but in reality i've spent the last ~2.75 years working at approximately the same pace (or harder) and don't have anything substantial that I can point to and say "i helped build that", which it turns out is far more rewarding than i understood at the time.</Msg><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361077759480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 00:09:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361079676555-2</Id><Topic><Title>Tracking Nvidia's PPS vs. Ashraf's NVDA Articles</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361027499566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 10:11:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well Josh, I think you answered what you have to do and wish I was your age so I had the option to do what is obvious. For me....I'm to0 old for for the applying for work. People think I'm not up to snuff on computers or coding or you name it because of my age and experience. Silly but true. My recommendation is get another job, who cares what the salary is and do what you are capable of. Live the dream, build something, and be proud of it! Invest your money wisely of course. I personally, started over 3 times. Once at 30, once at 46, and once at 55. Each time I found more satisfaction in working at something I believed in than all the financial rewards that stock investing can bring you. In other words...apply ant any ole company in silicon valley and be part of the dream. Who cares how it turns out....just be apart of it. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361079676555</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 00:41:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361082198889-3</Id><Topic><Title>Tracking Nvidia's PPS vs. Ashraf's NVDA Articles</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361027499566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 10:11:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Josh, If you are financially OK then look for companies that meet your needs. Needs as defined as " I built that". I have had the luxury of feeling that sense of accomplishment of what you felt at Facebook. It can come again. Research the companies.Look for companies that do not use layoffs to please WS. Once upon they were few, but today they are numerous. My recommendation is to apply to Nvidia. Why......They are old school......They do';t lay-off. Surely you have to do your job or risk being fired. But they do not wholesale cut the workforce because of OPEX is growing too large. Bottom line: Do What You Can and be proud of it. Note: Silicon Valley and a STEM degree allows you the opportunity thtat may in the USA do not have. take advantage of it.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361082198889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 01:23:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361084902747-4</Id><Title>Minimum requirements for Toy Shield to work.</Title><Msg>From the Tom's Hardware article, here are the minimum requirements for the Toy Shield to work. "To stream games directly from a PC to the gadget, customers will need at least, 1) One Nvidia Kepler-based GeForce GTX 650 (Desktop) or GTX 660M (Notebook) GPU, 2) A PC powered by an Intel Core i5 or equivalent CPU, 3) 4 GB of RAM, Windows 7 4) The GeForce Experience app. 5) A dual-band Wireless-N router is also suggested. Not exactly a take-it-out-of-the-box-and-plug-it-in gaming console, right boys? It sure isn't. So, let's have a show of hands. Who has everything they need to make the Toy Shield work today? Hummm? Just as I thought -- a tiny smattering of folks. So while each and every family on the planet could go and buy a new gaming console, and be merrily playing games within an hour -- the market for the Toy Shield is a teeny tiny subset of the total potential gaming market. Those that have the specific combination of required nvidia PC hardware. And accordingly, the Toy Shield will be a scratch.</Msg><Username>best.again</Username><Timestamp>1361084902747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 02:08:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361086808580-5</Id><Topic><Title>Minimum requirements for Toy Shield to work.</Title><Username>best.again</Username><Timestamp>1361084902747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 02:08:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? If the Toy Shield will only work with two (2) specific types of nvidia graphics cards, -- Nvidia Kepler-based GeForce GTX 650 (Desktop) or -- Nvidia GeForce GTX 660M (Notebook) GPU, what happens with all the millions of nvidia customers that own a different brand of graphics card? Up the creek without a shield? And if only those two specific cards -- the 650 and 660M -- will work with the Toy Shield, the maximum market size of the Toy Shield is by definition limited by the population size of those cards, right? For example, let's assume that there are 2 million 650 and 660M cards in existence. And 10% of those owners want to try the Toy Shield. That's a teeny tiny 200k market! It's a scratch.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1361086808580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 02:40:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361087017999-6</Id><Title>Minimum Requirements for Shield, PS Vita, 3DS</Title><Msg>Shield - Any wifi connection to download 500 games and a few pennies to pay for them. PS Vita - A bank to pay for a few games 3DS - A bank to pay for a few animated games</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361087017999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 02:43:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361087417890-7</Id><Topic><Title>Tracking Nvidia's PPS vs. Ashraf's NVDA Articles</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361027499566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 10:11:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"this board is really hard to extract sensible responses from. seems people post incorrect info, not just about the company, but also other commenters, then for some reason unite behind each other to continue making actual info really hard to discern from the typical web forum noise." Many reasons... Paid bashers, starstruck pumpers, competitors' employees... and also that NVidia is a gamers' friend... more youngters than other boards... Ash isn't even out of school yet... and he's telling it like it is to those fools in industry...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361087417890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 02:50:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361093522827-8</Id><Topic><Title>Tracking Nvidia's PPS vs. Ashraf's NVDA Articles</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361027499566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 10:11:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>j7777kxx -- I sincerely appreciate your advice and encouragement. You're either extremely perceptive or I'm being overly transparent about my personal thoughts/feelings on this stock board. Perhaps both. I've definitely debated updating my resume and picking some companies with interesting products to try to go work for/on, and the urge has become notably stronger over the past month or so. I've even considered Nvidia, as you recommend, but haven't yet looked closely at the roles they're looking to fill to see if I might be a good fit for them (and, like you, I'm not particularly passionate about gaming). I may start looking closely in the very near future. For the time being, I'll be around here as an investor but I'll try harder to refrain from revealing too much about myself personally... I'm not sure other posters will be as thoughtful and empathetic as you've been in your last couple of posts to me. Thanks again. I hope your children appreciate having a parent with so much wisdom to share. Again, thank you, and Cheers. Josh</Msg><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361093522827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 04:32:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361093935548-9</Id><Topic><Title>Tracking Nvidia's PPS vs. Ashraf's NVDA Articles</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361027499566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 10:11:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude, j777kxxx is also chief of rumors... undisputed king of conspiracy theory... and be downright wacky when he's pumping...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361093935548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 04:38:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361095274485-10</Id><Topic><Title>Tracking Nvidia's PPS vs. Ashraf's NVDA Articles</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361027499566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 10:11:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe, but none of those seemed to be true in his last two responses to me. he was handing down advice on pursuing happiness outside of investing and it was genuinely appreciated. there didn't seem to be any aspect that was based on rumors, conspiracy theory, or wackiness--just what felt like thoughtful feedback/advice on a personal level that I appreciate him taking the time to share with me.</Msg><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361095274485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 05:01:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361100338522-11</Id><Topic><Title>Minimum requirements for Toy Shield to work.</Title><Username>best.again</Username><Timestamp>1361084902747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 02:08:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the Toy Shield will only work with two (2) specific types of nvidia graphics cards, -- Nvidia Kepler-based GeForce GTX 650 (Desktop) or -- Nvidia GeForce GTX 660M (Notebook) GPU, what happens with all the millions of nvidia customers that own a different model of graphics card? You know. Like a nvidia Ge Force GTX 640 Or Ge Force GTX 630 Or Ge Force GTX 620 Or Ge Force GTX 610 Or Ge Force 210 It's just tough bananas for those nvidia customers, right? "Were sorry that you bought the wrong card for the Toy Shield." And what about the high-end cards? Like the nvidia Ge Force GTX 670 Or Ge Force GTX 680 Or Ge Force GTX 690. Are those folks out-of-luck too, with regards to the Toy Shield? Because they don't own a GTX 650 or 660M card? So many many unanswered questions from nvidia. But what is clear is that Jen's first-ever foray into selling a gaming console device Direct to the consumer, might just pizz-off a lot of his prior indirect graphics card consumers.</Msg><Username>best.again</Username><Timestamp>1361100338522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 06:25:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361102898165-12</Id><Topic><Title>Minimum Requirements for Shield, PS Vita, 3DS</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361087017999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 02:43:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>However, to be fair, Project Shield does need a high-end desktop with GTX 650 (minimum) graphic card, or a laptop with GTX 660M to stream PC games, Steam Library etc, or this feature of PS would be useless. As I posted before, this may post as an initial hold-up to the first adopters who don't already own these gears. However, serious or a good portion of semi-serious gamers should have these gears already.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361102898165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 07:08:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361109854958-13</Id><Topic><Title>Sizeable volume in $13.50, $14 calls expiring next friday</Title><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1360970457490</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 18:20:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would bet we get close to touching $14's this week but close under $13.50</Msg><Username>jojobanks55</Username><Timestamp>1361109854958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 09:04:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361113448947-14</Id><Topic><Title>Minimum requirements for Toy Shield to work.</Title><Username>best.again</Username><Timestamp>1361084902747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 02:08:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting right? It sure is. We've now had six (6) weeks of unbridled carnival barking about the Toy Shield. And only now are the cold, cruel, inconvenient facts about the hardware requirements to make the Toy Shield work are leaking out. I think the whole Toy Shield thing is just more of Jen's fandango to keep the stock price from plunging in the face of nvidia losing all three (3) real gaming consoles, the Sony Playstation, the Nintendo Wii, and the Microsoft Xbox.</Msg><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1361113448947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 10:04:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361117393118-15</Id><Topic><Title>Tracking Nvidia's PPS vs. Ashraf's NVDA Articles</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1361027499566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 10:11:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fair enough.... but do remember j777kxx wears many hats... and has many aliases...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361117393118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 11:09:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361118764388-16</Id><Title>More important than what was said on the conference call is</Title><Msg>what was not said. You did not hear one analyst preface his/her first question with "Congratulations on a great quarter". That says it all. There are no upgrades coming - only downgrades. Stock is not going anywhere near term.</Msg><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1361118764388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 11:32:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361119529794-17</Id><Topic><Title>More important than what was said on the conference call is</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1361118764388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 11:32:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just downgraded you to an imbecile. That says it all.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1361119529794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 11:45:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361120278318-18</Id><Topic><Title>More important than what was said on the conference call is</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1361118764388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 11:32:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>another thing that happened, analysts wouldn't put up with all that delusions Jen was passing about his accessible market share after he's got LTE and pressured him to change his tune. Actually ibbey was the one who's been refuting that all along right here, " LTE is a north american thing". And aapl and samsung totally dominate N. America. So have LTE won't change a thing for nvda. at least till 2015 until people start to put in more LTE outside N. America, what Jen needs are those 'cheap' radios. And since Icera i400 is a total bust, Jen ain't got those 'cheap' radios to get into the bulk of the market for the next 3 years.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1361120278318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 11:57:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361120754773-19</Id><Topic><Title>More important than what was said on the conference call is</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1361118764388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 11:32:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more doom from whosunw...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361120754773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 12:05:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361121141707-20</Id><Title>Best Android phone on AT&amp;T, Verizon, Sprint, T-Mobile</Title><Msg>AT&amp;T: HTC One+ (Tegra 3x) Verizon: HTC DNA (quad-core Snapdragon Pro) Sprint: Google/LG Nexus 4 (quad-core Snapdragon pro) T-Mobile Galaxy 3: Samsung (Quad-core Exynos 4) Source: thewirecutterDOTcom/reviews/best-android-phones-right-now-november-2012/</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361121141707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 12:12:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361134881786-21</Id><Topic><Title>More important than what was said on the conference call is</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1361118764388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 11:32:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whosunw, the icera modems aren't *just* category 3 or 4 LTE... that's just the upper-end of what they're supposedly capable of. Here's a blurb from Anandtech summarizing what they were told by NVDA right after the CES announcements: "Initially i500 will be capable of UE Category 3 LTE (100 Mbps downlink on 20 MHz FDD-LTE) and a later release will enable UE Category 4 LTE, which is one of the nice software upgradeable parts of an SDR architecture. On the WCDMA/HSPA+ side, DC-HSPA+ (42 Mbps downlink) is supported. I'm told that the initial 3GPP release will be 9, and later 10 with LTE Category 4 and carrier aggregation for LTE. i500 at present I'm told includes 3GPP family air interfaces (GSM/EDGE/WCDMA/LTE), no word on CDMA2000 1x/EVDO 3GPP2 suite making it. Voice modes including VoLTE are indeed supported as well." And then you can also look at NVDA's product page that lists the features of the 400 series modems at nvidiaDOTcom/object/nvidia-icera-productsDOThtml For the i450, with the i500 is obviously supposed to support a superset of features, you see: " -HSPA+/3G/2G multimode Multiband HSPA+ Cat 18 (28Mbs) HSUPA Cat 6 (5.7Mbps), Cat 7 (11Mbps) HSUPA upgradable Quad-band GPRS/EDGE -Full 3G and 2G voice -Radio Interface Layer (RIL) for Google's Android™ operating system -MIPI high-speed interface to multiple leading application processors -Major PCB savings due to integrated baseband and integrated RF chips -3GPP Release 7 features inc MIMO and higher order modulation to enhance performance and improve spectral efficiency -IceClear® interference-cancellation technology to improve cell edge performance -Targeted for high-performance HSPA+ Android-based smartphones " So the i500s should be well-suited for working on many of the same bands as the "cheap" radios you point out are necessary for the bulk of the market... they'll just also be capable of faster connections as well, depending on the software loaded on them. And I don't know exactly which QCOM modems they're comparing to when they say they take up just 40% of the size, but it seems reasonable that anywhere near that reduction in size &amp; silicon would make them cheaper to produce and thus more competitive with "cheap" radios built for specific markets. One potentially BIG hole so far is that we don't know about support for the CDMA2000 1x/EVDO suite which could preclude them from some key US carriers, and other key carriers/markets around the world... Wikipedia has a nice list of CDMA2000 markets by country &amp; carrier which you could use to make a more compelling argument about why the i500 might not be as great as NVDA would like to portray... here's the link: enDOTwikipediaDOTorg/wiki/List_of_CDMA2000_networks IMHO if you look at that list, though, there are still many markets &amp; carriers left (with hundreds of millions of phone/tablet buyers each year) that the I500 be able to serve just fine... NVDA would could spend the next year or two just competing in those markets and still do a fantastic job growing the Tegra business. Again, my opinion and of course subject to change if NVDA later reveals the i500s can't actually do all that's been promised so far.</Msg><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361134881786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 16:01:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361137482255-22</Id><Topic><Title>Ouya Game Console - Tegra of Course</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360111355678</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 19:42:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Honestly, I think the perception about NVIDIA stepping on its customers toes here is bit myopic and misread. I agree that it's portability and PC graphics integration are value add features and important points of differentiation there is something to be said, and in many cases missed, about the value of providing multiple HW platforms in several form factors in order to give viability to the SW platform thus making it more appealing to developers. Much like PCs and android devices at large the ubiquity is in the SW alone not the HW or HW/SW tether. This is the antithesis to the current standard for living room or mobile gaming device and, albeit to lesser extent, all of Apple. I think being a ole provider of hardware for this new market actually would make this risk of lack of adoption is higher. No doubt I am grasping at straws here and taking some serious liberties, (may the math gods take mercy upon me) but you could argue this sort of cooperative approach/problem has some lineage and basis in, no other than, John Nash's 'Game' Theory - pun intended. ;) Being alone on an island with an 'open' platform has very seldom yielded great success, right? Does anybody remember the Zodiac (possibly a bad example) or better yet what about Shield 1.0 (minus the streaming) that saw its launch and end with virtually no fan fair or as much as a whisper from the press (taking some literary liberties again here but some might get what I am talking about.)</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1361137482255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 16:44:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361141513863-23</Id><Title>Does Nvidia have any icera modem carrier certified and in use in phones?</Title><Msg>Nvidia has no experience in modems, icera doesn't have any either. Its going to be a disaster.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361141513863</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 17:51:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361142212269-24</Id><Topic><Title>Does Nvidia have any icera modem carrier certified and in use in phones?</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361141513863</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 17:51:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry about your short...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361142212269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 18:03:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361142853510-25</Id><Title>Why Nvidia lost to Qualcomm in the smartphone/tablet market and is destined to scrap</Title><Msg>the tegra. Both manufacture their chips at TSMC, so there is no advantage. Qualcomm has LTE, Nvidia has none (icera is a joke). tegra's are doomed to failure.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361142853510</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 18:14:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361142960116-26</Id><Topic><Title>Minimum Requirements for Shield, PS Vita, 3DS</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361087017999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 02:43:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The point is Shield works just fine with 500 or so Android titles out of th ebox - which is way way more than PS Vita and 3DS combined. The PC GPU streaming is a nice bonus. It's a way better Wikipad with PC GPU Streaming as a bonus.</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361142960116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 18:16:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361143652214-27</Id><Topic><Title>Minimum Requirements for Shield, PS Vita, 3DS</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1361087017999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 02:43:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shield is doomed. Haswell with Kepler 650M graphics Android tablets is it for mobile android games.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361143652214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 18:27:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361144689096-28</Id><Title>Why would anyone buy the shield when Haswell tablets with Kepler 650M graphics</Title><Msg>based Android tablets are available for mobile games... Hellooooo.....</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361144689096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 18:44:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361144782138-29</Id><Title>Nvidia fanbois like to stroke themselves.. But this shield stuff is a little too much.</Title><Msg>Didn't your momma tell you, you could go blind?</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361144782138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 18:46:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361145678671-30</Id><Topic><Title>More important than what was said on the conference call is</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1361118764388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 11:32:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for the clarifications. nvda bought Icera two years ago. 2G/3G biz is booming, for those with or without app processors to go with it. eg. brcm is ramping nothing 3G with single core processors this Q Samsung, and ramping 3G dual cores later this year. What do you think is the reason that nvda is not doing 2G/3G biz bundled with Tegra2? Or even Tegra 1?</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1361145678671</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 19:01:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361146462941-31</Id><Topic><Title>IMPORTANT REPORT ON NVDA (MUST SEE)</Title><Username>jaredmurray772</Username><Timestamp>1360272322771</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:25:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great report.</Msg><Username>smithmike453</Username><Timestamp>1361146462941</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 19:14:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361149459957-32</Id><Topic><Title>Why Shield has an likely opportunity for high volume shipments</Title><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360945027618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 11:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is web security measures as they escape the script characters for input. :-D</Msg><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1361149459957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 20:04:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361149540728-33</Id><Topic><Title>Why Shield has an likely opportunity for high volume shipments</Title><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360945027618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 11:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>going overboard. can definitely sanitize text input without stripping carets.</Msg><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361149540728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 20:05:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361149624036-34</Id><Topic><Title>Why Shield has an likely opportunity for high volume shipments</Title><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1360945027618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 11:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>err, carats.</Msg><Username>joshpritchard</Username><Timestamp>1361149624036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 20:07:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361159707965-35</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia fanbois like to stroke themselves.. But this shield stuff is a little too much.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361144782138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 18:46:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey IDIOTA stroke THIS !!!!</Msg><Username>apoplectichun</Username><Timestamp>1361159707965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 22:55:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361162493765-36</Id><Topic><Title>Does Nvidia have any icera modem carrier certified and in use in phones?</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361141513863</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 17:51:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously you (and a few other bashers such as sunsunw) are ignorant on this subject. The most recent product based on Icera modem bundled with Tegra 3 is ASUS vivo RT tablet running on AT&amp;T network and launched on October 26, 2012 along with Microsoft Surface RT. MS's Surface is WiFi only. Check it out. It's not a big product, but it's a start. There are also a few products released offshore using I410.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1361162493765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 23:41:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>