<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359285998263-1</Id><Topic><Title>Absolutely Nothing In The Tech Press About Nvidia</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359131107764</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:25:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, it's exactly the same concern I expressed right after CES. Tegra 4 might be cool SoC, but there has been no device using it announced. Of course, except NVIDIA's own Shield and some obscure tablet maker. Where is Asus, Acer, LG, Sony, HTC, ...? We got some Nexus rumours last days, but only god knows if those have some merit. HTC M7 was also supposed to have Tegra 4 inside, but recent rumours talk about Snapdragon instead.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1359285998263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 06:26:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359292166880-2</Id><Topic><Title>Absolutely Nothing In The Tech Press About Nvidia</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359131107764</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:25:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The customers decide when any news is divulged. Jen does not care about short term traders in the least bit. Nividia is innovating in many areas and long term investors will be rewarded.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1359292166880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 08:09:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359293698702-3</Id><Topic><Title>Absolutely Nothing In The Tech Press About Nvidia</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359131107764</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:25:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jen is more than a year late in getting his Tegra business profitable.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1359293698702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 08:34:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359294603670-4</Id><Topic><Title>Absolutely Nothing In The Tech Press About Nvidia</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359131107764</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:25:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It does appear that Nvidia is about to double down on Cloud Gaming with Nvidia Grid and Project Shield. But I'm afraid Investors eyes will glaze over. They want sexy new smartphones with LTE powered by Nvidia Tegra processors and Icera modems. The Irony is Nvidia will make very good margins on Gaming....like their discrete GPUs, pro graphics, HPC teslas. Tegra in tablets. Much more so than from Tegra in mobile phones. So we are left with earnings and guidance. Stock buyback or no Stock buyback, and yes we can dream dividend increases....to move the stock. P.S. All the technical traders are foaming at the mouth about a run up into earnings. Above the 50 day SMA already plus the 200 day SMA is near at $12.85. An earnings beat of $0.04 from lower taxes is guaranteed. Now just how are they going to guide? If they are aggressive and say "Yes we can to themselves" and guide above expectations then the stock will pop up above 13 and stay there after earnings, rather than drop back as usual. Don't get me wrong...I like the "No More Hype Nvidia" and we don't talk to the "Tech Press" see you at earning Call!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359294603670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 08:50:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359295943674-5</Id><Topic><Title>Between QCOM, Apple, Samsung the ARM smartphone market is locked up.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359260081600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 23:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boy.. you have really been scared from hitching your post to AMD... like a little school kid in the principal's office telling on the kid that beat you up....</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1359295943674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 09:12:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359296338906-6</Id><Topic><Title>Between QCOM, Apple, Samsung the ARM smartphone market is locked up.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359260081600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 23:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>STUPID !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359296338906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 09:18:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359303080014-7</Id><Topic><Title>Between QCOM, Apple, Samsung the ARM smartphone market is locked up.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359260081600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 23:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is seemingly impossible for you people to display some maturity in corresponding? Your dialogue is painful.</Msg><Username>rlday2010</Username><Timestamp>1359303080014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 11:11:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359304592718-8</Id><Topic><Title>Between QCOM, Apple, Samsung the ARM smartphone market is locked up.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359260081600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 23:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Why is seemingly impossible for you people to display some maturity in corresponding? " 'Why is it... ' Your childish outburst makes you prone to errors...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359304592718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 11:36:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359306773194-9</Id><Topic><Title>Between QCOM, Apple, Samsung the ARM smartphone market is locked up.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359260081600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 23:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Your dialogue is painful." one side dead set on pumping and the other side dead set on bashing, both regardless of nvda's biz realities. Nvda realities in the mobile market (same as txn's realities btw, but then txn has biz managers who would adjust their investments based on biz realities): 1. Tablet - with no access to aap, samsung and amzn dead set on cheap only, nvda won the whole 'non of the above' market last Q and still lost $40M. This Q, after X'mas, winRT launch, losses should go over $100M. And this reality isn't going to change. 2. Phones - again, with no access to aapl and samsung, nvda's accessible market, even assuming they will get Grey a whole year later, is highly limited. No, qcom has not gotten the market locked up - brcm is ramping app processor/radios integrated solutions at samsung like crazy this year. That the diff. between brcm/txn and nvda - one has a real biz plan thought out carefully in advance and will adjst strategies as the biz evolves, the other is just throwing stuff, very expensive R&amp;D stuff, onto a wall to see if it will stick. BTW Denver - that's more $ down the drain. No chance at server, now re-targeting 'hpc market'. There will be 10 elephants all trying to target one tiny phone booth. Even if nvda wins that whole market, it will not pay for the R&amp;D. That's highly unlikely - given that all of nvda's will-be competitors are cpu guys while nvda isn't. Yes, I expect there will be more of those very intelligent, mature 'Stupid' one word responses from both sides on this post.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359306773194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 12:12:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359306989250-10</Id><Title>intc's problem can become nvda's problem too</Title><Msg>Intc, without the push from amd, has not been pushing out faster products at cheaper prices for a while now. There is just no incentive to upgrade anymore. now that amd is pretty much 'amd managed' out to oblivion, if nvda does not keep pushing out new products at lower price points, nvda can face intc's problem too. No competition is not good, not good for consumers, not even good for the guy with the monopoly.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359306989250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 12:16:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359307642557-11</Id><Topic><Title>Between QCOM, Apple, Samsung the ARM smartphone market is locked up.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359260081600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 23:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Your dialogue is painful." Bet your dialogue was far more painful when you ate your crow... btw, did you cook your crow... or took it raw...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359307642557</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 12:27:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359308018921-12</Id><Topic><Title>intc's problem can become nvda's problem too</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359306989250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 12:16:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intc, without the push from amd, has not been pushing out faster products at cheaper prices for a while now. " INtel also dictates what their customers will charge for the customers products... INtel also dictates what size screens their customers would use for ATOM products... INtel wanted to own x86... they own it... pushed ALL other companies to ARM...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359308018921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 12:33:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359311336013-13</Id><Topic><Title>So where's the Tegra #4 orders?</Title><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1359253329238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:22:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the Tegra #4 turns out to be the commercial failure it's shaping up to be, maybe the toy Shield could claim "exclusive" use of the Tegra #4. You know. Like the Genuine Apple iPad claims the A6X chip. Exclusively. Maybe that's why Jen wisely put the Tegra #4 and the toy Shield in the same cost center? The "Consumer Products Business" (CPB) he calls it. To avoid those nasty inter-departmental Bazooka wars. Yes boys, Bazooka wars. Which Always break-out whenever one division uses the parts made by another division. "Inter-company cost transfer" the accountants call. "We've been scre.wed" the losing side of the Bazooka war calls it. Let's take an example, shall we? The toy Shield department will use the Tegra #4 for their processor, right? Just like Jen ordered it would. Now, the toy Shield department 'cuda bought any perfectly good mobile processor -- like from Intel or Samsung or Qualcomm or Broadcom or MediaTech or TI -- on the open market, for like $18 bucks. But instead they must buy the Tegra #4 as Jen ordered. "Take one for the team, boys", Jen probably said. So the toy Shield department is thinking their cost should be around the market price of $18 bucks for the Tegra #4. "Oh no no no." Says the Tegra #4 department. Since we've got Tons and Tons and Tons of Tegra #4 development expenses, -- and no Real customers, other than our sister toy Shield department of course -- our actual cost is $7,846.57 per chip. But we can maybe take 10% off for being our best customer. Here's our bill. Are you starting to see the core problem in the Bazooka war here? So Jen, being a highly experienced, well-versed veteran in the accounting problems created by Failed semiconductor projects, wisely put the Tegra #4 and the toy Shield in the same cost center. And Presto! The shared P&amp;L -- the Consumer Products Business -- for both departments suck. Did I mention? Jen is a highly experienced, well-versed veteran in the accounting problems created by Failed semiconductor projects.</Msg><Username>itsascratch</Username><Timestamp>1359311336013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 13:28:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359315851832-14</Id><Topic><Title>So where's the Tegra #4 orders?</Title><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1359253329238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:22:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mister Best, sir? Is that why Jen's department managers dive under their desks? Everytime they spot Jen walking down the hallway. Because they just Know it's another P&amp;L -- and bonus -- destroying idea on the hoof. From 100 yards away. Coming down the hallway.</Msg><Username>elf.best</Username><Timestamp>1359315851832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 14:44:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359316634331-15</Id><Topic><Title>So where's the Tegra #4 orders?</Title><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1359253329238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:22:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why? What is to become of all this time you waste? Its beyond pathetic</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1359316634331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 14:57:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359324734983-16</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH NVDA Analyst Report !</Title><Username>rodriguezwilliam82</Username><Timestamp>1359123428621</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:17:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>nathanshuler742</Username><Timestamp>1359324734983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 17:12:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359325217533-17</Id><Title>mr.best thinks he is supposed to be privy to Nvidia order pipeline</Title><Msg>he wants to be the first notified by Nvidia sales staff..</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1359325217533</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 17:20:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359335200272-18</Id><Title>Jensen Will Rue The Day He Let All The Cash Pile up!</Title><Msg>He did the dividend or was forced to by the Board. Who Knows? Now he has to deal with all that cash. It just keeps piling up...Intel just cut another $300M check. No stock buyback means over 50% of the share price is Cash. Stupid! 5 Year notes go for less than 1%...ask any large well capitalized S&amp;P 500 company as we enter another M/A period on Wall street as the CEO of GS said last week at Davos. What in the world will Nvidia do?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359335200272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:06:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359335722528-19</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P closes above 1500 for the first time in five years...</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359151436882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:03:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PLEASE;;; PLEASE BY NVIDIA.. &amp; not the S&amp;P500../ if they eeever let me out of this flemish shed;;; i wood buy more nvidia../ much more../ u should 2</Msg><Username>daysinshed30</Username><Timestamp>1359335722528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:15:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359337154546-20</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P closes above 1500 for the first time in five years...</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359151436882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:03:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>daysinshed30, Sorry to hear about those Goldman guys in nice suits. You know. Showing up at your annual release hearing. Again. But maybe next year, right? And yes, I looked into your pre-order for the toy Shield. No, they don't make them yet. But maybe next year, right? Hang in there, okay? Just in case.</Msg><Username>barjonicats</Username><Timestamp>1359337154546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:39:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359337609520-21</Id><Topic><Title>Jensen Will Rue The Day He Let All The Cash Pile up!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359335200272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:06:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you thought through the cash required to build up a pipeline of "Shield" devices in the retail pipeline....how about their "Cloud Gaming Server". $3B of cash seems like it might be barely enough.</Msg><Username>branitt</Username><Timestamp>1359337609520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:46:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359338193733-22</Id><Topic><Title>Jensen Will Rue The Day He Let All The Cash Pile up!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359335200272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:06:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you kidding me??? Fool...</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1359338193733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:56:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359338256261-23</Id><Topic><Title>Jensen Will Rue The Day He Let All The Cash Pile up!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359335200272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:06:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And after this intc payday quarter, there should closer to $4bln</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1359338256261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:57:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359339041291-24</Id><Topic><Title>Jensen Will Rue The Day He Let All The Cash Pile up!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359335200272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:06:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Jen did the dividend or was forced to by the Board. Who Knows?" I know. It was Best that forced Jen to finally pay a cash dividend. After Eighteen (18) years of hoarding cash. Best called Jen out -- right here on this very message board. And shamed Jen into it. You can read and re-read the epic Words of Best, here on Yahoo! Finance. Where is will be carefully preserved for posterity. Just copy into the Search bar at the top : Jeepers Best, Everybody else pays a dividend. Personally, I've made Best's posting about the lack of a dividend into a desktop icon. As well it should be.</Msg><Username>i_know_best</Username><Timestamp>1359339041291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 21:10:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359341816509-25</Id><Topic><Title>intc's problem can become nvda's problem too</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359306989250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 12:16:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you say is fundamentally untrue. Intel's biggest competitor has always been all its old chips which is why it has to spend so much money on producing a brand new design every year and a new smaller process every two years. It gets no money from licensing so it has to sell new products each and every year and has to make the new products attractive enough to make customers want to buy them to replace their older products. It's not subsidized by phone carriers like all the smartphone vendors. It's a never ending semiconductor treadmill and Intel is the best at it.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359341816509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 21:56:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359342136368-26</Id><Topic><Title>intc's problem can become nvda's problem too</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359306989250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 12:16:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'INtel wanted to own x86' Intel invented x86 and I don't see Nvidia giving out its patents for free lol. The only reason AMD and VIA are hanging on like limpets to Intel's x86 is that IBM originally wanted second sources but those IBM PC days are long gone but they managed to wangle legal decisions to keep that original agreement going until the end of time when it is not really relevant now 30 years later. Maybe when Nvidia licenses its gpu technology to *anybody* who wants it you might sound a little less hypocritical ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359342136368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 22:02:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359347198872-27</Id><Topic><Title>intc's problem can become nvda's problem too</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359306989250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 12:16:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fair enough...but I already knew your points... And it does look better for INtel that AMD &amp; VIA are still around otherwise INtel would be sole source of x86... if not becoming already...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359347198872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 23:26:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359348151655-28</Id><Topic><Title>So where's the Tegra #4 orders?</Title><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1359253329238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:22:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The manager of the toy Shield department probably keeps his toy Shield under his desk. Just for such an occasion. "Low profile, low light testing", its called. Don't laugh. The guy has successfully dodged Jen's idea to put the icera modem in the Shield too. So far.</Msg><Username>leftie_the_sockpuppet</Username><Timestamp>1359348151655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 23:42:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>