<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-17"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371464813722-1</Id><Title>And the deals keep coming!!</Title><Msg>Don't look now shorts, wait til its to late. Barcelona taps Tesla and Tegra for next-gen hybrid supercomputer!!! OMG what will they think of next!!!</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1371464813722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 06:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371474219626-2</Id><Title>Nvidia/Mellanox</Title><Msg>I called this one in a piece I wrote about Mellanox...I think that as Nvidia gears up to build its own HPC platform with Denver/Tesla, it will work with Mellanox on the InfiniBand side of things to team up against Intel and its QLogic assets. Should be fun to watch.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1371474219626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 09:03:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371476128941-3</Id><Topic><Title>Re: look for an increase in screwish activity over the next 30-40 days</Title><Username>screwherbes</Username><Timestamp>1369398384547</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 08:26:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I expect the turn big back up to be late Tuesday or early WEdnesday</Msg><Username>screwherbes</Username><Timestamp>1371476128941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 09:35:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371477324794-4</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia/Mellanox</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1371474219626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 09:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LEIPZIG, Germany, Jun 17, 2013 (BUSINESS WIRE) -- Mellanox Technologies, Ltd., a leading supplier of high-performance, end-to-end interconnect solutions for data center servers and storage systems, today announced it will showcase the world's first technology demonstration of ConnectX-3 FDR 56Gb/s InfiniBand solutions running on the SECO ARM development platform featuring NVIDIA Tegra processors. The SECO development platform is powered by an NVIDIA Tegra quad-core ARM processor. The RISC-based ARM architecture is advancing far beyond today's billions of client devices, and is rapidly moving towards the mainstream technical computing and high performance computing (HPC) market segments. Together with NVIDIA, Mellanox will demo the ARM architecture with InfiniBand at the Mellanox exhibit booth #326 during the International Supercomputing Conference (ISC) in Leipzig, Germany from June 17-20. "This particular technology demonstration represents a significant development milestone for adoption of Mellanox's InfiniBand solutions in new CPU platforms such as NVIDIA Tegra-based ARM platforms," said Gilad Shainer, Vice President of Marketing at Mellanox Technologies. "As future generations of 64-bit ARM solutions come on-line, applications will continue to demand ultra-low latency communications and scalability that only Mellanox InfiniBand can provide." "Mellanox and NVIDIA are working together to bring all the benefits of a modern HPC network to ARM-based platforms," said Ian Buck, General Manager of GPU Computing Software at NVIDIA. "This technology demo, coupled with support for ARM platforms in the latest release of the CUDA parallel programming toolkit, provides the foundation for developers to build out the ARM HPC application ecosystem."</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1371477324794</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 09:55:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371477590585-5</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia/Mellanox</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1371474219626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 09:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia ain't shipping Tegra 4 or Tegra 4i and you're talking about a product with what, Denver? lol Todays Riddle Kiddies: If Tegra 4 got pushed out so that Tegra 4i could be pulled in how far did Denver get pushed out to make room for old 4i and then finish Tegra 4? lol Ans: You can start calling Denver Ms California 2020. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371477590585</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 09:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371477692216-6</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia/Mellanox</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1371474219626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 09:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post, thanks!</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1371477692216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371477739934-7</Id><Topic><Title>And the deals keep coming!!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1371464813722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 06:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you read? News been out since June 12th and its a prototype. Do you know what PROTOTYPE means? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371477739934</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:02:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371477898974-8</Id><Title>"AMD could double from entry into 'microserver' market, Barron's says"</Title><Msg>"AMD could double from entry into 'microserver' market, Barron's says" "AMD's acquisition of SeaMicro could drive the stock substantially higher as the "microserver" and tablet market expand, Barron's contends in its Technology Trader column." source: Theflyonthewall</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371477898974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:04:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371478011078-9</Id><Title>"AMD, Netflix lead early tech gains"</Title><Msg>"AMD, Netflix lead early tech gains" "SAN FRANCISCO (MarketWatch) - Technology stocks edged higher Monday, propelled by gains in shares of Advanced Micro Devices and Netflix Inc. AMD AMD +3.81% ganed more than 4% in early trades, leading a chip sector rally that saw the Philadelphia Semiconductor Index SOX +1.79% rise 1.3%. Netflix NFLX +5.66% jumped more than 5% after the digital entertainment company unveiled an original TV deal with DreamWorks Animation DWA +6.75% . Netflix and AMD were the top gainer on the S&amp;P 500 SPX +0.93% which was up about 1%. The Nasdaq Composite Index COMP +1.01% was up 30 points, or 1%, at 3,454. "</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371478011078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:06:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371478139007-10</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia/Mellanox</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1371474219626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 09:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel demos inexpensive 100Gb/sec silicon photonics chip Breakthrough will speed system-to-system data center links By Rik Myslewski in San Francisco, 11th April 2013 Intel has demoed what it says it "believes" is the world's only silicon photonics module that uses a hybrid silicon laser – a breakthrough that should allow such advances as vastly improved system-to-system interconnects in the data center. The demo of the 100Gb/sec module was presented via a video during Intel CTO Justin Rattner's keynote presentation at the Beijing Intel Developer Forum on Thursday. The chip incorporates modulators, detectors, waveguides, and circuitry – and that aforementioned laser – all in garden-variety silicon rather than pricey hand-built, gallium arsenide–based photonics modules such as are currently available. Since integrated silicon photonics modules could be fabbed using existing equipment and tested using a hybrid of conventional and Intel-developed techniques, such speedy modules could be created much more cheaply, and therefore eventually work their way into far more devices and systems [From another interview, The photonics technology was demo’d at IDF Beijing recently, and Rattner says Intel has engineering samples, was building up yields, and “We’ll be in the market within the year.”]</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1371478139007</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:08:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371478152109-11</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia/Mellanox</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1371474219626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 09:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you count to 6 correctly yet? If you had any character you would have corrected your own post and not let that Qulaocomm lie stand. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371478152109</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371478364120-12</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia kicked OUT of Xbox, OUT of PS, OUT of MacBook AIr, OUT of Mac Pro, OUT of Nexus 7.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371386665544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:44:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By all reports Nvidia will be kicked OUT of Microsoft's Surface RT next. The new Surface RT 2 will be sporting a Qualcomm part and you Nvidia fans will be whining not so until it is. lol IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371478364120</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:12:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371478570670-13</Id><Topic><Title>PS4 and Xbox One are ONE and TWO on Amazon's Best Seller List. lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371055117743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:38:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Update for Mnday June 17. 2013 PS4 and Xbox One are STILL ONE and TWO on Amazon's Best Seller List Now let me see you try and bash your favorite pumping list Nvidia fans? lmao IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371478570670</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:16:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371478721304-14</Id><Topic><Title>And the deals keep coming!!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1371464813722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 06:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you ever shut-up? Nobody cares about your silly little opinions you despicable D-bag!</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1371478721304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371479152013-15</Id><Title>Buyers flock to AMD this AM 13 to 1 over Nvidia. Over 13 MILLION shrs in the 1st hour.</Title><Msg>Can you say Nvidia is junk to be avoided. No, you can't if not if you own it right? lol But I can. Nvidia is junk. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371479152013</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371479191826-16</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD, Netflix lead early tech gains"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371478011078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:06:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try and keep up Nvidia fans. lol</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371479191826</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:26:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371479465606-17</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia/Mellanox</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1371474219626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 09:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're welcome, ibexx!</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1371479465606</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:31:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371479977161-18</Id><Title>Why can't you Nvidia fans get it straight or correct your lies when called on it?</Title><Msg>The pattern is put up a LIE and then slink away when called on it. Do you remember this lie: "Nvidia has more cash per share than Apple" Have you seen that liar in a while? lol Now there is the pumper who can't quite count to six (6), he claims Qualcomm was down 7 days in a row going on 8. Did you see him correct his own post or slink away from his own words again? The pattern is put up a LIE and then slink away when called on it. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371479977161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:39:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371480093075-19</Id><Topic><Title>And the deals keep coming!!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1371464813722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 06:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have to forgive him. Ranting mindless poison fulfills his sense of internal balance and meaning of life.</Msg><Username>jtjgmtbt</Username><Timestamp>1371480093075</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371480113169-20</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia/Mellanox</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1371474219626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 09:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is not a motel room? Or a chat line for sweet NOTHINGS boys You can BLOW kisses off line can't you? lmao IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371480113169</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371480932215-21</Id><Topic><Title>And the deals keep coming!!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1371464813722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 06:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that waht it is? I thought I was spreading the truth about Nvidia to a bunch of Nvidia FANatics. Do you see me bashing Apple, AMD, Qualcomm, Sony, Microsoft, Xbox One, PS4 and every tech taking business from Nvidia? I would call bashing all of technology poison. The TRUTH is only poison to the LIE. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371480932215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:55:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371483514107-22</Id><Topic><Title>And the deals keep coming!!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1371464813722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 06:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get a real job you despicable D-BAG! You aren't going to get one by sitting in your darkened parents basement and posting your blather all day.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1371483514107</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 11:38:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371484559517-23</Id><Topic><Title>Why can't you Nvidia fans get it straight or correct your lies when called on it?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371479977161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:39:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nvidia has more cash per share than Apple" Actually "more" was an understatement what that clown really said is: "Nvidia Has Twice The Cash per Share That Apple Has!" For brevity sake I paraphrased and I shouldn't have since it lessened his original lie. Do you see how easy it is to correct your own post Nvidia fans? There is no shame in wanting to get it right. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371484559517</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 11:55:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371485294204-24</Id><Topic><Title>Buyers flock to AMD this AM 13 to 1 over Nvidia. Over 13 MILLION shrs in the 1st hour.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371479152013</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:25:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By midday its only 10 to 1 or 20 Millions shares of AMD traded compared to Nvidia's 2 Million shares Both stock are up but it cost you $14 for 18 cents with Nvidia and only $4 for 15 cents with AMD. Is it sinkng in yet? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371485294204</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 12:08:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371486800633-25</Id><Title>No know-it-all but I know paying $14 for 15 cents is dumb when it can be had for $4?</Title><Msg>Do you know where you could have had 15 cents worth of gains for $4 Nvidia fans? Would you pay $14 for a 15 oz icecream too Nvidia fans when smart shoppers can get the same icecrean for $4? Say you wouldn't do that with icecream just Nvidia. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371486800633</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 12:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371487167292-26</Id><Topic><Title>And the deals keep coming!!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1371464813722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 06:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is interesting news. And it's actually news Six or seven months ago there were a few postings here claiming that Barcelona was switching from the Tegra+GPU design to the Samsung Exynos 5, because the on-die Mali 600 series GPU would potentially use less power than existing CPU + discrete GPU. The reality appears to be that the Exynos 5 couldn't get compute performance out of the Mali 604 GPU. The problem was threefold: memory bandwidth, electrical input power and thermal limitations. You can get brief bursts of good GPU performance, but only if you don't run the CPU. Even then the package thermal limitation precludes sustained performance. The second problem was software support. Even in the famously 'direct to the metal' HPC world, Nvidia is years ahead of other vendors in figuring out the programming model and toolkits. The Exynos 5 has since dropped the Mali 604 GPU, which points out another challenge: long-term consistency. HPC systems are always leading edge technology, but the complexity means that it takes years to get them working correctly.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1371487167292</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 12:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371487495952-27</Id><Topic><Title>And the deals keep coming!!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1371464813722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 06:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This is interesting news. And it's actually news" If it is then its FIVE day old news. That story was out June 12th 2013. Where I'm from they call it current events after a few days and stop calling it new NEWS. lol They olny place they call old NEWS new NEWS is when pumping it on a message board. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371487495952</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 12:44:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371488155966-28</Id><Title>Intel powers the world's fastest supercomputer</Title><Msg>engadget Tianhe-2 supercomputer claims the lead in Top 500 list, thanks its 3.1 million processor cores By Mat Smith posted Jun 17th, 2013 at 10:22 AM As predicted, Chinese supercomputer Tianhe-2 has now been crowned the most powerful supercomputer in the world. Arriving years ahead of schedule, and packing 32,000 Xeon processors alongside 48,000 Xeon Phi accelerator processors, the supercomputer can manage a quadrillion mathematical calculations per second (33.85 petaflops), double that of last year's king (and closest rival), the Titan. In this year's results, 80 percent of the Top 500 used Intel processors, while 67 percent had processors with eight or more cores -- as clock speeds stall, supercomputer development has now focused on processors running in parallel. Top 500 editor Jack Dongarra adds that "most of the features of the [Tianhe-2] system were developed in China, and they are only using Intel for the main compute part," meaning that you can expect to see more Chinese entrants (and possibly champions) over the next few years. For now, however, the US still claims the majority of the Top 500, with 253 top-ranking supercomputers. [ double that of last year's king (and closest rival), the Titan] [are only using Intel for the main compute part] [ In this year's results, 80 percent of the Top 500 used Intel processors]</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1371488155966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 12:55:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371489421020-29</Id><Title>Microsoft’s E3 Xbox One demos ran on Nvidia-powered PCs</Title><Msg>Absolutely hilarious: "It has emerged that Microsoft used Hewlett Packard made PCs equipped with Nvidia GTX 700 series graphics cards to demonstrate Xbox One titles at E3 last week. ... Whether an HP gaming PC running Windows 7 and packing an Nvidia GTX 700 series GPU is comparable to the Xbox One console is debatable. However this use of PCs suggests the Xbox One hardware/software isn’t nearly as ready as the Sony PS4." hexusDOTnet/gaming/news/industry/56841-microsofts-e3-xbox-one-demos-ran-nvidia-powered-pcs/</Msg><Username>torchie4269</Username><Timestamp>1371489421020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 13:17:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371490536836-30</Id><Topic><Title>Intel powers the world's fastest supercomputer</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1371488155966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 12:55:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yawn. Intel CPUs are in nearly every one of the fastest computers in the world. No news here. Except maybe that the Chinese are deploying money for supercomputing at a faster rate than the US.</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1371490536836</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 13:35:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371493886268-31</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia/Mellanox</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1371474219626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 09:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are such a bold person.... anonymous online, message board antagonist..... such power..</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1371493886268</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 14:31:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371497034343-32</Id><Topic><Title>Intel powers the world's fastest supercomputer</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1371488155966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 12:55:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The news you are missing is that the son of Larrabee, Xeon Phi aka 22nm Knights Corner, is the accelerator card for parallel workloads. It's also going to get worse for competitors when the 14nm Knights Landing successor tips up, it can be used as a standalone chip too as well as a PCI-E accelerator giving HPC users more Intel options e.g, Xeons, Xeons and Xeon Phi or just Xeon Phi.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1371497034343</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 15:23:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371498505096-33</Id><Topic><Title>Intel powers the world's fastest supercomputer</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1371488155966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 12:55:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the articles I've seen Nvidia is vastly superior in performance per watt.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1371498505096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 15:48:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371499046738-34</Id><Topic><Title>And the deals keep coming!!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1371464813722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 06:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will be interesting to see what the long term holds for Samsung's chips. Their decision to use INTC for one of their tablets is another data point. Maybe the NVDA salespeople should pay a little more attention to them than we would have though worthwhile a few months ago.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1371499046738</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 15:57:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371501691917-35</Id><Title>"Xbox One Reportedly Netting $3 Billion for AMD"</Title><Msg>"Xbox One Reportedly Netting $3 Billion for AMD" "t turns out that the high-end graphics within the Xbox One cost Microsoft a pretty penny, as GameSpot discovered Monday via an errant detail on a former AMD exec's LinkedIn page. That information revealed that the "custom silicon solution" project for the Xbox One was under a multi-year contract deal valued at more than $3 billion. The project, posted by AMD Director of Business Transformation Ben Allen, came to GameSpot via the profile of Former AMD exec Robert Feldstein, who now works for competitor Nvidia. Similar information was also posted about the Playstation 4, although the terms of the contract for that product weren't in the description. This detail is just another little glimpse into AMD's takeover of console business from Nvidia — which could become very lucrative for the former in the coming months" source: ign</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371501691917</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 16:41:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371502060259-36</Id><Topic><Title>Intel powers the world's fastest supercomputer</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1371488155966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 12:55:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no vastly in it as it only took 110% more power to get 100% more performance than the old Nvidia No.1 'Built for the National Supercomputing Center in Guangzhou China, the "Milky Way 2" system is powered by 32,000 of the upcoming 12-core Intel Xeon processors E5-2600 v2 based on Ivy Bridge architecture, and 48,000 Intel Xeon Phi coprocessors, with a total system power of 17.8 MW. Not only is it the fastest, but also one of the most power-efficient systems on the Top500 list.' HPC though is not the main competitive threat to Nvidia from Xeon Phi, it is to Quadros used as Workstation app accelerators as many more of those are sold than Teslas. Intel is attacking Nvidia's core gpu business from a couple of angles, Haswell and Phi, so you need to get Tegra profitable sooner than later as there may come a time when the core Gpu business profits may not cover the Tegra losses any more.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1371502060259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 16:47:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371502192447-37</Id><Topic><Title>"Xbox One Reportedly Netting $3 Billion for AMD"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371501691917</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 16:41:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Xbox One Reportedly Netting $3 Billion for AMD" That is all an Nvidia fan needs to know about Xbox. You don't need to know how to plug it in, set it up, or turn it on. You don't need to know that Xbox One pre-orders are #2 on Amazon Best Seller list, trailing PS4. lol You don't need to know what games will be available at launch, nope you don't need to know that because Nvidia fanatics ain't spending any money on Xbox One they're just window shiopping in envy. All you need to know is AMD will see $3 Billion and Nvidia won't see a dime. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371502192447</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 16:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371502450831-38</Id><Topic><Title>And the deals keep coming!!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1371464813722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 06:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"And the deals keep coming!!" Deals involve money right? Enlighten us on the money part of this "Deal" sport. And tell us when did a working on a PROTPTYPE become a steady paying job? Can Nvidia hire another Tegra 4 DEBUGGER with PROTOTYPE money? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371502450831</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 16:54:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371503105584-39</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia/Mellanox</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1371474219626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 09:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you try posting something on Nvidia or any technology you think is relevant to this board and save the trash talk for the ball court sport. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371503105584</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 17:05:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371503407254-40</Id><Title>All you need to know about Xbox One is $3 Billion net for AMD and $0 for Nvidia.</Title><Msg>Everything else you've heard about Xbox One does not apply to Nvidai fans, its all irrelevant because an Nvidia fanatic will never own an Xbox One, right?. lol Enjoy your $349 SHIELD purchase Nvidia fans. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371503407254</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 17:10:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371503969605-41</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD could double from entry into 'microserver' market, Barron's says"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371477898974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:04:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"AMD could double from entry into 'microserver' market, Barron's says" Did that Barron's article sufficiently annoy you Nvidia fans? You know they didn't write it just to annoy Nvdia fans, right? No one would write anything just to rub in others new found success right? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371503969605</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 17:19:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371504614737-42</Id><Topic><Title>All you need to know about Xbox One is $3 Billion net for AMD and $0 for Nvidia.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371503407254</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 17:10:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nevermind how much Xbox One cost since you ain't buying. Forget about PS4 competion because regardless of who wins, Xbox One or PS4 Nvidia still won't see a dime. Concentrate on Nvidia's SHIELD toy folly that Nvidia is spending shareholder money on now with little hope of breaking even. SHIELD will be over and done with by Turkey Day. Nvidia would rather not be embarassed by long Xmas shopping lines hoping to snag an Xbox One or PS4. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371504614737</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 17:30:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371505110765-43</Id><Topic><Title>And the deals keep coming!!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1371464813722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 06:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget, too, that dominating the volume of a message board with huge numbers of low-value messages makes you an important person and gives meaning to your life. If you are an AMD employee, it also somehow helps your financially struggling employer to do better. Well, at least judging from poor XC,'s behavior it must somehow. I have suggested that he find some kind of community outreach organization, but to no avail. He would be happier and healthier if he did.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1371505110765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 17:38:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371506776423-44</Id><Topic><Title>And the deals keep coming!!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1371464813722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 06:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If you are an AMD employee, it also somehow helps your financially struggling employer to do better" You see its that sort of BS that makes you look like a complete fool and a total Nvidai fanatic? It may be difficult but THINK about the BS you're tossing up. Would Nvida allow an Nvidia employee to post on the AMD board? Would Nvidia even allow an Nvidia employes to post on the Nvidia board? Are you really so ignorant to think AMD would allow an employee to post on this message board. Do you see me calling Nvidia fans Nvidia employees or paid pumpers? Why does everyone who disagrees with you have to be paid or employed by a competitor? Speak of what you actually know and stop making up BS and you won't look so CLUELESS. iimho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371506776423</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 18:06:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371507453773-45</Id><Topic><Title>Why can't you Nvidia fans get it straight or correct your lies when called on it?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371479977161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:39:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've only seen one poster admit they can be wrong about anything. From $26 down to $14 everyone here was right, right? lol "Looks like I was wrong regarding PS4 pricing" is the only post I remember where the poster cared about getting it right? Anyone else here ever admit your post was wrong? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371507453773</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 18:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371508004951-46</Id><Title>More about the new Top500 supercomputer list: NVIDIA's special-purpose chips are used more widely</Title><Msg>On the Top500 list, 39 use Nvidia chips, 11 use Xeon Phi, and three use ATI Radeon chips. The top machine uses Xeon Phi, the No. 2 uses Nvidia chips, and Tianhe-1A, now bumped down to No. 10, uses Nvidia chips. SOURCE: CNET</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1371508004951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 18:26:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371508156363-47</Id><Topic><Title>More about the new Top500 supercomputer list: NVIDIA's special-purpose chips are used more widely</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1371508004951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 18:26:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The heat is on...Intel and Nvidia, the two heavyweights in the HPC market. Should be very fun to see them race to outdo each other :)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1371508156363</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 18:29:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371509859544-48</Id><Title>One thing Nvidia is good at is renaming their chips from 6xx to 7xx. Rebranding</Title><Msg>they call it.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1371509859544</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 18:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371520356847-49</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia/Mellanox</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1371474219626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 09:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Says the biggest #$%$ douce bag loser...</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1371520356847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 21:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371520930161-50</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia kicked OUT of Xbox, OUT of PS, OUT of MacBook AIr, OUT of Mac Pro, OUT of Nexus 7.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371386665544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:44:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nvidia is not in the Xbox One, PS4, NEW MacBook Air, NEW Mac Pro Desktop and the Next Nexus 7 because Microsoft, Sony, Apple and Google didn't want Nvidia in those products" Now say it ain't so Nvidia fans. Tell us that Nvidia is the DECIDER of what goes in these products. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371520930161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 22:02:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371521344580-51</Id><Title>SHIELD must be an acronym for SHIp to ELDerly only cuz kids won't play with Junk. lol</Title><Msg>How cool would it be for some kid to walk around with a Toy the size of a wooden shoe in his pocket? Hey, if they list SHIELD in an encyclopedia do you know where you' ll find it next to? SHI..., SHIPS right? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371521344580</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 22:09:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>