<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-25"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366863244001-1</Id><Title>The perfect contrarian indicators</Title><Msg>NVDA bashers and SA bloggers seem to possess an uncanny sense of contrarian timing. As soon as blogger #2 exit NVDA and bought into Qualcomm, QCOM tanked big time. So much for their swing trading skills. Take a look at the "disclaimer" section: seekingalphaDOTcom/article/1368901-qualcomm-what-the-heck-happened #2 even outdid #1 in his contrarian accuracy. Amazing.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366863244001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:14:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366863891797-2</Id><Topic><Title>The perfect contrarian indicators</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366863244001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seeking Alpha is garbage. They are right sometimes and wrong sometimes like a broken clock.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366863891797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:24:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366864215704-3</Id><Topic><Title>The perfect contrarian indicators</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366863244001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For once, I will agree with you.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366864215704</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:30:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366864916496-4</Id><Topic><Title>The perfect contrarian indicators</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366863244001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure who is who on the SA bloggers you are citing, but I don't see a problem with owning both companies' stocks. I owned Intel at own point along with Nvidia. It's possible and not really betraying anything. I don't think these bloggers are just swing traders, one of them at least. Anyways, we'll what happens. I'm glad that any disappointment in Qualcomm's outlook can be a good bump for Nvidia and help us gain traction before the real news for Nvidia starts coming week to week . . guessing as early as mid-May, right after our ER and into the summer. Even Goldman Sachs is saying this year is unique for the market and one shouldn't 'sell in May and go away' this time. Whatever the motivation of the MMs now, it seems to bode well for us.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366864916496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:41:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366865191733-5</Id><Topic><Title>The perfect contrarian indicators</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366863244001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are like forumers 50-50 chance. Oh motley fools too. In fact, often the odds are worse then 50-50.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366865191733</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:46:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366865321718-6</Id><Topic><Title>Why Why Why the recent upsurge.</Title><Username>rounhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366831619436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 15:26:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This I agree with. Nvidia has a solid profitable business, large cash reserves, and is the leader in their primary business of GPUs. I think that Shield and Nvidia Grid each have a modest chance of being wildly, profitably successful, and the Tegra 4i looks like it's good enough and early enough to start taking smartphone market share. But all of those positive fundamentals were ignored or punished by the market. The recent upward price movement doesn't reflect any of those products gaining market traction. It's entirely big players making money from their ability to move the stock price. The price will drop just as suddenly when momentum investors start going long.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1366865321718</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:48:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366868336547-7</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra could be taking marketshare from QCOM. Thats why its down AH.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366854071660</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 21:41:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra is a family of chips, not just one. We are now on the 4th generation part named Logan, and Logan's successor Parker has been demonstrated in a real time video. Do you bashers think Qualcomm can match this pace? Logan will have Kepler GPU with unified shaders and Parker will have stacked dram - you may want to read up on these features.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366868336547</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 01:38:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366868447719-8</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra could be taking marketshare from QCOM. Thats why its down AH.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366854071660</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 21:41:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In addition to the fact that Parker SoC will incorporate Denver CPU which supports 64 bit memory interface.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366868447719</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 01:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366868822463-9</Id><Topic><Title>The perfect contrarian indicators</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366863244001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I still own Nvidia.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1366868822463</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 01:47:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366869103693-10</Id><Topic><Title>The perfect contrarian indicators</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366863244001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also, bought into $QCOM into the AH sessions, so not quite "buy then tank". You'd better learn how to BS better, ibexx. Claiming I sold my NVDA position is pretty low, especially considering that I'm quite bullish on the company's long term future and have made it quite clear that I'm long the stock. The reason that I don't disclose a long position in Nvidia in the Qualcomm article is - gasp! - I don't mention Nvidia and therefore am not asked to disclose my position. Anyway, continue on spending your day on these boards making up lies, while I continue to happily hold my NVDA shares.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1366869103693</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 01:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366870134936-11</Id><Topic><Title>since besides me, ibey is so interested in brcm too: brcm up 7% now:</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1366826224647</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 13:57:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Broadcom is a great company. But so is Nvidia.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1366870134936</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 02:08:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366878175848-12</Id><Title>Where is xc?</Title><Msg>$13.36 closed Did you cover your short call?</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1366878175848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 04:22:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366879626773-13</Id><Title>Cant stand the arrogant bulls after just a few days of rally!</Title><Msg>This POS is only around 10% above its several years lows and the bulls are being arrogant. Be humble about your gains. If Nvidia can clear $16, can stay above it, followed by continuous 52 wks high, then be arrogant. Eg. If your stock behaves like ARMH after it has dropped followed by strong rallies, then u start to ridicule bashers. This is still a POS til proven otherwise. Hence acknowledge that there's a rally. Be humble and say this is a good start. That it could lead to a major rally so that when it happens, the bashers are dammneddd wrong. But dun count your chickens before the eggs are hatched yet.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366879626773</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 04:47:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366879906113-14</Id><Topic><Title>Cant stand the arrogant bulls after just a few days of rally!</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366879626773</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 04:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish this stock can turnaround to $30 or more. And I am sure to be on board. Cos I am around to invest and make money. I am not around to bash. But neither am I willing to be an ostrich to say this is a good stock when all it could do is rally 10% of lows while others double, triple or quadruple!</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366879906113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 04:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366896527722-15</Id><Topic><Title>since besides me, ibey is so interested in brcm too: brcm up 7% now:</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1366826224647</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 13:57:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>brcm's mobile strategy is based on two thing: 1. first and foremost, there's no value added in just linking ARM cores (forget nvda,s graphic hypes, Tegra graphic has always lagged, still are not on unified cores whereas blah blah blah...). 2. brcm gets their added values through integrating their cheap radios for an integrated solution that lowers BOM costs and drastically speeds up the time to market. Point #1 has proven to be very true - anybody everybody making linking ARM cores, especially the leading two names in mobile. This is the undoing of the whole Tegra program. The market to high end bleeding edge ARM cores does not exist. As for point #2, the lower cost smart phone market is just opening up while the bleeding edge smart phone market is at best standing still. Hence aapl's woes. nvda's high end strategy's days came and gone without them getting a toehold in the market they targeted. And nvda does not have enough cheap radios for the huge, very huge lower priced smart phone markets. My guess is brcm is right and that in a year, when low priced smart phones are all the talk of the market, brcm will be shown a clear winner, spoken in the same breadth as qcom. brcm,s rise yesterday was really due to ramping their multiple wins 3G integrated solutions at Samsung. That is just a taste of things to come in about one year+. In a year, Jen will be extorting T5, T6 or whatever to an empty hall at wmc, barcellona, analysts day etc. etc., just like this year.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1366896527722</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:28:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366896700265-16</Id><Title>Yesterday's action and looking forward at today.</Title><Msg>Well, no one could be disappointed with yesterday's action unless he/she were short or calling for a "rangebound stock price". As I had mentioned, numerous times on this board, we would come in one day and the stock would jump and NOT retreat. Although the Bears DID try, several times, to sell into the rally, each time that selling was met with more buying. They did press harder in the last 1/2 hour, but I'm pretty sure most of them were frustrated that the stock closed at 6 month high on 40%+ higher than normal volume. One thing I found interesting was that there was not a large amount of volume in the options. But, with a 2 day move of over 6%, and no "news" that we've seen/heard, I'm thinking that someone either got inside info on when the Project Shield "coming out party" is going to happen, and/or the price of the device. Or, they knew that QCOM was going to lower guidance due to "competition" and when that word is used in that context, it says to me that people are now anticipating that Tegra 4i is about to be announced in several products, since the LTE modem is the place where QCOM has had NO competition up to his point. On that subject, Ibexx has already posted stories about several Chinese companies that are reportedly going to release phones with Tegra 4i in them, and maybe the market is wising-up to the reality of how big a market there is for NVDA to grow into. In any case, today will be truly interesting to see if the stock can continue this break out. I would expect to see SOME effort made by The Bears to break the stock back down, but looking at the charts, this is a CLEAR Break out, and the scrambling to cover those May 13s, 14s and maybe 15s (and those strikes in June, Sept, etc) will start in earnest IF the stock clears 13 1/2 with good volume and doesn't back off. One last thing directed at young Ashraf. I have to tell you I'm disappointed that you haven't acknowledged that "NEVER" came pretty darn quickly, and ARMH already won me my nickel.</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366896700265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:31:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366897127372-17</Id><Topic><Title>Why Why Why the recent upsurge.</Title><Username>rounhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366831619436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 15:26:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My bet is on MOMO trading. The other reasons don't seem logical or reasonable.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_cc</Username><Timestamp>1366897127372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:38:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366899398166-18</Id><Title>Too bad Nvidia must report to the shareholders every quarter, look at QCOM</Title><Msg>If QCOM took Nvidia's Google Nexus JOB and beat earnings estimates and is down what does that mean for Nvidia, who lost their Google Nexus JOB? lol Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366899398166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:16:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366899571241-19</Id><Title>Nvidia is HOLDING the door open with that CASH FOR CLUNKERS PROGRAM again</Title><Msg>$13s is the BEST thing you under water Nvidia fans have seen in a long time. I know its not $16 BUT who told you to PAY OVER $16 and brag about it on a message board? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366899571241</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:19:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366899900874-20</Id><Title>Who PAID OVER $16, bragged about it here and is SO HAPPY to be holding $13 Nvidia now? lol</Title><Msg>CLUELESS Nvidia fans who LIVE on a message board professing their LOVE for Jen, that's who paid over $16 and bragged about it here . Its $16 who now, right? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366899900874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:25:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366900041654-21</Id><Topic><Title>HUG $15 and Love it cause $15 loves you Nvidia fans</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1309452698000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2011-06-30 12:51:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"HUG $15 and Love it cause $15 loves you Nvidia fans" When Nvidia WAS $15 Nvidia fans called this post BASHING. Now Nvidia is $13s and they are SO HAPPY they're calling $13s the BEST THING to happen to Nvidia. You tell me who is bashing? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366900041654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:27:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366900343988-22</Id><Topic><Title>Who PAID OVER $16, bragged about it here and is SO HAPPY to be holding $13 Nvidia now? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366899900874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:25:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$13? How about $20 plus,,,,,"Nvda was going to $80" the pundits said, while they unloaded on the public.</Msg><Username>ruounhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366900343988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:32:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366900345522-23</Id><Topic><Title>Too bad Nvidia must report to the shareholders every quarter, look at QCOM</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366899398166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:16:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that product even shipping yet? I don't think that will show up with quarter.</Msg><Username>manski14</Username><Timestamp>1366900345522</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:32:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366900615367-24</Id><Title>Didn't Nvidia TRADE OVER $26 a Share at One Time? Is $13 half of $26? lol</Title><Msg>How soon Nvidia fans FORGET ALL THEIR OWN BS about $30, $50 and the silly $100. Nvidia has been punched for so long and so hard that if the pounding stops for just a bit Nvidia fans think they''re winning the fight. Nvidia is STILL sitting on the canvas groupies. Duh. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366900615367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:36:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366900835184-25</Id><Topic><Title>Too bad Nvidia must report to the shareholders every quarter, look at QCOM</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366899398166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:16:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No the NEW Nexus is not shipping yet BUT wouldn't Google need to order the NEW QCOM SoC to replace the OLD Nvidia part before they ship the NEW Nexus? Are the parts for the NEW Nexus free? Just a thought. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366900835184</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:40:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366901032966-26</Id><Title>Nice run is over?</Title><Msg>Momo dead?</Msg><Username>poundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366901032966</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:43:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366901075411-27</Id><Topic><Title>Who PAID OVER $16, bragged about it here and is SO HAPPY to be holding $13 Nvidia now? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366899900874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:25:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How about $20 plus" Most of the so called longs who SHOW UP HERE EVERYDAY HOPING TO BREAK EVEN are too embarassed to even admit what they PAID to hold $13 Nvidia today. And each and everyone of them know it. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366901075411</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366901240052-28</Id><Topic><Title>Little guys selling....</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1272554019000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2010-04-29 11:13:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I had an order in at open for mid-xxxx shares at $16.01." Is your Nvidia holdings STILL Underwater or what? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366901240052</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:47:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366901454523-29</Id><Title>Did anyone notice, Apple and AMD are having a better day? No one notices on UP days right?</Title><Msg>Is that why no bashing Apple and AMD today or what? lol hmm? How much is Nvidia up today? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366901454523</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:50:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366901833536-30</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is HOLDING the door open with that CASH FOR CLUNKERS PROGRAM again</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366899571241</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:19:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And just like $15 and over, $13 isn't good enough right? lol When will we see that $30, $50 and Silly $100 a share NONSENSE again? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366901833536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:57:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366902616469-31</Id><Topic><Title>Nice run is over?</Title><Username>poundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366901032966</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:43:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The creativity in using my id to copycat is waning . .</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366902616469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:10:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366902762370-32</Id><Title>Sadly, xc is right. Thats why i said, bulls should be humble.</Title><Msg>This POS stock is still pos til proven otherwise. If it rallies like ARMH and clears $16, clears $20, then u all ridicule XC and bashers, u be fine. And he will then deserves to be laughed at. But u guys declare victory over mini gains, u ask for it. Bulls, be humble and quietly make money, dun lose money loudly !</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366902762370</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366902993155-33</Id><Title>If a 10 cent UP day makes you feel like a WINNER then you may be an Nvidia head case</Title><Msg>If all it takes is a 10 cent up day to bring out the trash talking pumping Nvidia fans from their hiding hole then you know Nvidia has been beaten DOWN TO JUNK. It WAS $26 Nvidia fans, WAS, I said WAS. lol When you can ignore $26 to $12 but get all HOT AND STEAMY from $12s to $13 you' must love hugging JUNK. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366902993155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366903311816-34</Id><Topic><Title>Sadly, xc is right. Thats why i said, bulls should be humble.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366902762370</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:12:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its not about being right, its about being honest and puting things in perspective. $13s is NOT what these PUMPING Nvidia fans BRAGGED about paying and some times they NEED to be reminded that they are STILL UNDER WATER. No matter how much they HIGH FIVE on a message board, Nvidia HAS BEEN A LOUSY INVESTMENT all the way DOWN from $26 to today. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366903311816</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:21:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366904212708-35</Id><Topic><Title>Sadly, xc is right. Thats why i said, bulls should be humble.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366902762370</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:12:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing your profound and most informative posts with the board. I dun know what I would have dun without u? I dun know why everybody here thinks u r a POS?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1366904212708</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366904775752-36</Id><Title>Watch for a BIG "BLOCK" at 13.50</Title><Msg>So far, the Bears have not been able to muster any kind of real profit-taking. We did hit 13.50, earlier, and have made a few more attempts at 13.48-9, and now there's been a modest attempt to knock us back down. However, the volume is still pretty strong, and each time they knock it down another buyer steps in. This is a "tell", and the bigger one will be what happens if/when we get back to 13.49 bid. I would "guess" that there will be a BIG BLOCK, maybe 150-250k shares trying to keep the stock from going beyond that point. So, that is the next "battleground" area, and then somewhere in the 13.62-68 area, which was the intraday high area in October. Clearing that would open the path to a test of 14, and if we get another 10mm+ share day, I won't be surprised if we see that happen. The market is going MUCH higher than most people think, and with many of the semis, along with MSFT breaking out (the SMH hit another new high both yesterday and today) and the QQQs are almost there, too, we should clear 1600 in the S&amp;P in the VERY near future. I tried to warn people that they should cover any calls from the 13 strike and above for May and beyond. I do hope a few of them took that suggestion. As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. Max</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366904775752</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:46:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366905501268-37</Id><Topic><Title>Sadly, xc is right. Thats why i said, bulls should be humble.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366902762370</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:12:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sigh. I know truth hurts. U make childish sweeping statements. Everybody here thinks... Since when u represent everybody. Anyways, have been enjoying my days trades with DDD and RAX etc. They make intraday 5% moves. Just hope this Nvidia can stop being a POS and move well too. I believe the time is close . Hopefully I can profit well from it to make back some losts money that I stupidly bought around $18. Should have cut when made small losses. Unfortunately, I read too much into this boards stupid bullishness and SA's. Now I only trust price actions. Cos only price pays.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366905501268</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:58:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366905944918-38</Id><Title>Apple ADDING $4.00 while AMD ADDS 4%, what's Nvidia doing TODAY? lol</Title><Msg>Come on, let me see you Nvidia groupies bash UP $4 or UP 4%. Can you say Nvidia is JUNK? I bet you can if you take your head out from between your back pockets groupies. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366905944918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:05:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366905969584-39</Id><Topic><Title>The perfect contrarian indicators</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366863244001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very smart (not!) to catch a fallen knife which is still falling And to exit a stock (NVDA) whose long-waited breakout was just confirmed.. Retail traders are meat for the lion - big boys will always get you.</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1366905969584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:06:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366906053266-40</Id><Topic><Title>Sadly, xc is right. Thats why i said, bulls should be humble.</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366902762370</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:12:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I dun know what u r talking bout? I dun know what I was thinking, I should have said most everybody here thinks u r a POS. I dun know Y I find your posts entertaining and informative cus</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1366906053266</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:07:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366906456301-41</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is HOLDING the door open with that CASH FOR CLUNKERS PROGRAM again</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366899571241</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:19:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does Nvidia call its CASH FOR CLUNKERS PROGRAM, a STOCK BUY BACK PROGRAM? Now that Nvidia Management is buying distressed Nvidia shares no one seems to mind that is was Management that distressed those shares in the first place. Its like Nvidia driving a dump truck into your new car and then offering you the going rate for WRECKS to make it right. Don't you feel special with half what you paid GONE. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366906456301</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:14:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366906959865-42</Id><Topic><Title>Too bad Nvidia must report to the shareholders every quarter, look at QCOM</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366899398166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:16:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many time has Nvidia reported and then TANKED? Take all the cheap shots you want at Apple or QCOM or Intel BUT Nvidia will get its turn to report and then lets see if the old saying: "BUY the RUMOR and SELL the NEWS" works for Nvidia just like everyone else OK? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366906959865</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:22:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366907288488-43</Id><Topic><Title>Apple ADDING $4.00 while AMD ADDS 4%, what's Nvidia doing TODAY? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366905944918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>XC, you are an idiot, so you assume other investors are also your kind. Why did you use $$ for AAPL and % figures for AMD? LOL</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1366907288488</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366907590830-44</Id><Topic><Title>Didn't Nvidia TRADE OVER $26 a Share at One Time? Is $13 half of $26? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366900615367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:36:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pick pocket these Nvidia fans and TAKE HALF THEIR MONEY and they'll say THANKS every time if you put back a half empty wallet. Take $14 OUT from $26 and give back $1 and its all good right Nvidia fans? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366907590830</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:33:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366908164723-45</Id><Topic><Title>The perfect contrarian indicators</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366863244001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you mentally incompetent or do you choose not to read? I still own Nvidia.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1366908164723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366908861514-46</Id><Topic><Title>The perfect contrarian indicators</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366863244001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Getting huffy, eh? Because you are EXPOSED? Your NVDA ownership is not mentioned in your latest disclaimer - btw, your disclaimer statement were different with respect to different stock commentary. Does SA editors know about this? Oh yeah, they don't pay you so they don't care...</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1366908861514</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:54:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366909878265-47</Id><Topic><Title>The perfect contrarian indicators</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366863244001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The disclosure only asks for disclosures related to stocks that were mentioned in the article. Nvidia was not mentioned, therefore no disclosure.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1366909878265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:11:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366909947585-48</Id><Topic><Title>Apple ADDING $4.00 while AMD ADDS 4%, what's Nvidia doing TODAY? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366905944918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What the matter Nvidia fans? AMD 4% is better than your .6% TODAY? Or is Apple's $4 better than Nvidia's 8 cent TODAY? No matter how you TRY to spin it Apple and AMD are having a better day. lol Now say it ain't so. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366909947585</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:12:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366910039960-49</Id><Topic><Title>The perfect contrarian indicators</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366863244001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I also own Cisco and IBM but didn't disclose those either. Jeez, I wonder why. Right...because the article didn't mention them. The disclaimers are different in different articles because different articles mention different stocks. SA doesn't ask authors to disclose positions in stocks that were not mentioned.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1366910039960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366910334095-50</Id><Topic><Title>If a 10 cent UP day makes you feel like a WINNER then you may be an Nvidia head case</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366902993155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:16:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know YOU Nvidia fans were all ready to declare Nvidia is on its way to $30, $50 and that $100 BS again, right? UP 10 cents can do that to you if you happen to be an Nvidia head case. Tell me does 8 cents have the same effect on YOU? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366910334095</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:18:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366910588030-51</Id><Topic><Title>Did anyone notice, Apple and AMD are having a better day? No one notices on UP days right?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366901454523</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:50:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clowns made a lot of noise about Apple dropping below $400 BUT NOT ONE WORD about Apple moving back OVER $400 AFTER REPORTING EARNINGS. AFTER Reporting Earnings, Nvidia fans, AFTER. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366910588030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:23:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366910631626-52</Id><Topic><Title>If a 10 cent UP day makes you feel like a WINNER then you may be an Nvidia head case</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366902993155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:16:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm pretty happy about it. You don't seem to be though</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1366910631626</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:23:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366910724982-53</Id><Topic><Title>If a 10 cent UP day makes you feel like a WINNER then you may be an Nvidia head case</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366902993155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:16:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am even happier than you are to see you JUMP FOR JOY FOR A DIME. lmao Really I am happy to see you enjoy that DIME because I remember when it was $26, do you? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366910724982</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:25:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366910784353-54</Id><Topic><Title>If a 10 cent UP day makes you feel like a WINNER then you may be an Nvidia head case</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366902993155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:16:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I remember when it was 11.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1366910784353</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366911090242-55</Id><Topic><Title>If a 10 cent UP day makes you feel like a WINNER then you may be an Nvidia head case</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366902993155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:16:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I remember when it was 11." I know you do, just like I know you forgot on purpose that it WAS $26 too right? lol Because you're so Happy its HALF what is once WAS right? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366911090242</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:31:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366911154838-56</Id><Topic><Title>If a 10 cent UP day makes you feel like a WINNER then you may be an Nvidia head case</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366902993155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:16:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Past performance is no indicator of future results" I'll be happy as long as I am gaining value.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1366911154838</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:32:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366911505602-57</Id><Topic><Title>If a 10 cent UP day makes you feel like a WINNER then you may be an Nvidia head case</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366902993155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:16:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" I'll be happy as long as I am gaining value." And when you are NOT gaining value do you go back to being UPSET with the world because Nvidia is HALF what it was and still JUNK? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366911505602</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:38:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366911878268-58</Id><Title>Appke and AMD REPORTED and moved HIGHER lets see Nvidia TRY that Trick.</Title><Msg>When does Nvidia come clean with the sharehoders aboit losing the Google Nexus JOB? lol Can you imagine that conf call? Yes, what is your question Mr Analyst Wipe? #$%$ Happen with that Google Nexus JOB cool breeze and if I may follow up, how much time did the barber get who messed up your head Jen? lmao imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366911878268</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366912232856-59</Id><Topic><Title>Apple ADDING $4.00 while AMD ADDS 4%, what's Nvidia doing TODAY? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366905944918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD is still down heavily from 2011/2012.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1366912232856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:50:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366912514693-60</Id><Topic><Title>Apple ADDING $4.00 while AMD ADDS 4%, what's Nvidia doing TODAY? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366905944918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"AMD is still down heavily from 2011/2012." That's nice and HOW DOES THAT HELP YOU? Quiz time sport: Is $13 STILL HALF of $26 even if AMD, or Apple or QCOM is DOWN? You may use a calculator but remember to show all work. Pencils down when the bell rings sport. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366912514693</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:55:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366914752467-61</Id><Topic><Title>Apple ADDING $4.00 while AMD ADDS 4%, what's Nvidia doing TODAY? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366905944918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because that would show that AAPL $4 or + .85% move is close to NVDA's +.75%. haha</Msg><Username>manski14</Username><Timestamp>1366914752467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366915001890-62</Id><Topic><Title>Apple ADDING $4.00 while AMD ADDS 4%, what's Nvidia doing TODAY? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366905944918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia is up about 8% since the announcement of the BB program when it was trading around 12.40. If your going to bash Nvidia for falling from $26 to $12, you might want to pick a stock that didn't fall from $700 to $390 to make a comparison</Msg><Username>manski14</Username><Timestamp>1366915001890</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:36:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366915783405-63</Id><Topic><Title>Apple ADDING $4.00 while AMD ADDS 4%, what's Nvidia doing TODAY? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366905944918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>turtle defender</Msg><Username>kharies99</Username><Timestamp>1366915783405</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:49:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366917225746-64</Id><Title>Has NVDA new "price channel" $13 to $14?</Title><Msg>Maybe too early, but it looks like Nvda will be in the channel tween $13 and $14 for the next year or so.</Msg><Username>siwttle</Username><Timestamp>1366917225746</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:13:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366917356469-65</Id><Topic><Title>Apple ADDING $4.00 while AMD ADDS 4%, what's Nvidia doing TODAY? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366905944918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If your going to bash Nvidia for falling from $26 to $12, you might want to pick a stock that didn't fall from $700 to $390 to make a comparison" A $700 Envy there little fella? Those riding the Apple bus were'nt posting BS about holding for $1000 or $5000 like the Nvidia fans who were posting $30, $50 and one silly clown with $100. Apple may be $400 NOW but Apple made its shareholders RICH many times over unless they fell asleep on a message board the past few years like YOU. lol Nvidia was $26 for all of 30 minutes, which was JUST ENOUGH TIME TO WASTE ON A MESSAGE BOARD POSTING BS and then it was slapped right back DOWN.. Apple shareholders had OVER A YEAR TO GET PAID AT OVER $600 AND MANY DID. Did you get PAID? lol So yeah $13 is STILL HALF of $26 and NO WHERE $700. A $50 to $700 run in any stock is an opportunity of a LIFETIME and YOU BLEW IT posting BS about Nvidia on a message board. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366917356469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366917714161-66</Id><Title>You also put Nvidia going from $26 to $12 on IGNORE, how's that working sport?</Title><Msg>lmao</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366917714161</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:21:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366917795608-67</Id><Topic><Title>You also put Nvidia going from $26 to $12 on IGNORE, how's that working sport?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366917714161</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:21:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many times wil the SAME clowns claim to put you on ignore? lol Anyone here have a clue? lmao</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366917795608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:23:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366917964185-68</Id><Topic><Title>Has NVDA new "price channel" $13 to $14?</Title><Username>siwttle</Username><Timestamp>1366917225746</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:13:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Maybe too early, but it looks like Nvda will be in the channel tween $13 and $14 for the next year or so." And you know this because it was up 2 days in a row so YOU can now predict the next 365 days right? And you wonder why they call it CLUELESS PUMPING, do you? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366917964185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:26:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366918544424-69</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is HOLDING the door open with that CASH FOR CLUNKERS PROGRAM again</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366899571241</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:19:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many Nvidia fans are taking this $13 GIFT to sneak out the back door and HIGH FIVEhere like they're still holding shares? Come on Mr "Took My Profits" fess up, we know there are many Nvidia shareholders who took Nvidia up on that CASH FOR CLUNKERS PROGRAM and are driving a NEW QCOM coupe now right?. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366918544424</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:35:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366919477469-70</Id><Title>They STILL don't get it. A $50 to $700 run was the OPPORTUNITY OF YOUR GENERATION.</Title><Msg>You BLEW the best investing Opportunity OF A LIFETIME posting NONSENSE about Nvidia on a message board because you can't stand being wrong. Apple was a company once marked for dead and then rose to be the MOST VALUABLE COMPANY on Earth and YOU still don't get it. RAGS to RICHEST is a story that RARELY happens. And no souped up Nvidia fan, high on a $12 to $13 run can changes that. Sure Apple is NOT $700 now but Apple FLEW and made many RICH for LIFE. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366919477469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:51:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366920007931-71</Id><Topic><Title>You also put Nvidia going from $26 to $12 on IGNORE, how's that working sport?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366917714161</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:21:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOU CREATED A NEW ID today just to post BS and call names? I post with ONE ID sport, I don't hide behind fly by night IDs. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366920007931</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:00:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366920071473-72</Id><Topic><Title>Apple ADDING $4.00 while AMD ADDS 4%, what's Nvidia doing TODAY? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366905944918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My cost basis on Nvidia is just a tad over $12, so at the very least I'm not deeply underwater. I also get a dividend from the PROFITS that Nvidia produces ;)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1366920071473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:01:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366920094312-73</Id><Topic><Title>They STILL don't get it. A $50 to $700 run was the OPPORTUNITY OF YOUR GENERATION.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366919477469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:51:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your PHONY ID CREATED TODAY is a give away for someone who wants to HIDE and then POST BS. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366920094312</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:01:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366920204596-74</Id><Topic><Title>Did anyone notice, Apple and AMD are having a better day? No one notices on UP days right?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366901454523</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:50:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Settled, APPLE and AMD HAD the Better day. Now say it ain't so. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366920204596</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:03:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366920436534-75</Id><Topic><Title>I put xc on ignore</Title><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1366917445238</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be SURE to leave me on YOUR IGNORE list this time OK? So you don't have to waste your time postingf BS again OK sport? lol</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366920436534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:07:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366925628670-76</Id><Topic><Title>Did anyone notice, Apple and AMD are having a better day? No one notices on UP days right?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366901454523</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:50:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're worse than Jehovah's witness. Sorry, but I have to put you on ignore to avoid your message board flooding attacks.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1366925628670</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366925740009-77</Id><Topic><Title>Yesterday's action and looking forward at today.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366896700265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:31:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Max, Nice summary thanks. I thought this was interesting from QCOM's report: "Revenues - Quarterly total revenue of $6,124 million was up 23.9% year over year. Segment wise, Qualcomm CDMA Technologies businesses contributed $3,916 million of revenues in the second quarter, up 28% over the prior-year quarter. Qualcomm Technology Licensing generated $2,057 million in revenues, up 19% year over year." Licensing is basically $0 cost, right? I mean there are some administrative costs, but those have to be close to zero I'd think. Then you get to the interesting part of the report: "Net Income - On a GAAP basis, quarterly net income from continuing operations was $1,866 million. . ." Licensing, a business with no costs, generated 2.05B for the Q. Yet the net for the entire business was 1.86B. In other words, every other business QCOM is in is under water. Everything else constant, licensing costs $190M than they brought in. Sounds to me like they are giving away their hardware. Not what I'd call a good long term business model.</Msg><Username>schmenkle321</Username><Timestamp>1366925740009</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:35:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366926953039-78</Id><Topic><Title>Yesterday's action and looking forward at today.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366896700265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:31:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, Schmenkle... I was wondering about that myself, too. When companies have a near monopoly, as INTC almost has and QCOM has had in these arenas, they will often sell things BELOW cost to keep their market-share high. That's one of the issues that got INTC into anti-trust problems and court cases with AMD, and to some extent, NVDA. I do think that QCOM is doing just that, and once Tegra 4i is certified and starts showing up in products, QCOM's margins are going to be seriously pressured. Perhaps that's why the stock got hit so hard, today, while NVDA continued its 3 day climb to another new 6 month high. Volume was quite low in NVDA, today, but in QCOM it was 5 1/2 TIMES normal, and somehow the Bulls got it to close ONE PENNY above the 200DMA. It broke below EVERY major MA, and even with the last minute "buying" that got it back over that 200DMA, that may not keep it from going into a Bear Market. While anything can happen, and surely will, I do believe that the "tells" or signposts that I had seen developing a month or two ago, have come to pass and NVDA has finally broken out of its own long Bear Market and is headed MUCH higher. (And, YES, there WILL BE DOWN DAYS.) Whatever has precipitated this change in the "tenor" of how the stock is trading is open to debate, but from a "technical" standpoint, it's all systems go. I have no inside info, so I don't know if my speculation that someone has gotten wind of a release date party for Project Shield (and the price) is the catalyst or not. Or, perhaps it's just the technicals getting much better, or someone knows about some real design wins for Tegra 4i (as Ibexx has "reported" for some in China). Whatever the "reasons", I'm happy with the change we've seen and believe this stock will easily double, or more, over the next 1-3 years. And, as I said earlier, I'm a little stunned that young Ashraf has not admitted that "NEVER" came pretty darn quickly in ARMH. As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. Best, Max</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366926953039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366927962775-79</Id><Topic><Title>Yesterday's action and looking forward at today.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366896700265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:31:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One thing that has really stuck me lately is that I am now seeing Snapdragon advertisements when going to the movies... I have never seen a QCOM advertisement before.</Msg><Username>sasquatchlicious</Username><Timestamp>1366927962775</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366931287348-80</Id><Topic><Title>Where is xc?</Title><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1366878175848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 04:22:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Went to buy a tube of Preparation H.</Msg><Username>izeippol</Username><Timestamp>1366931287348</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366932124155-81</Id><Topic><Title>Yesterday's action and looking forward at today.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366896700265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:31:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Despite of Qualcomm's financial muscle, the company still isn't a household name, and reportedly this has troubled QC's senior management not insignificantly. QC is now in the process or buying Sacramento Kings basketball franchise, as part of an orchestrated effort to enhance its consumer image/awareness.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366932124155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:22:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366933857377-82</Id><Title>Shield price is set at $350.</Title><Msg>Recently while flying from vacation I saw a Shield commercial in a magazine. It had a price tag - $350. I took that magazine with me and have it as a proof.</Msg><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366933857377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:50:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366934235846-83</Id><Topic><Title>Shield price is set at $350.</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366933857377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no need to post anything we all believe you. Nobody lies on the internet. I'm a french model. Bon jour!</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1366934235846</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:57:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366934514361-84</Id><Topic><Title>Shield price is set at $350.</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366933857377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can post pictures but yahoo would not let me attach them. Do you know of any way to do it without revealing identity?</Msg><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366934514361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366934874709-85</Id><Topic><Title>Shield price is set at $350.</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366933857377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you remember the name of the magazine? Of course not.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1366934874709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:07:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366936408044-86</Id><Topic><Title>Yesterday's action and looking forward at today.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366896700265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:31:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Losing the Nexus 7 to QCOM could have been a result of what you just stated. QCOM giving their stuff away much cheaper than they would like just to keep anyone from an easy entrance into the market. QCOM may have given google an offer they couldn't refuse. However, with the resources and cash balance at Nvidia, QCOM would destroy their margins trying to do that forever imo. With Tegra 5 and 6 already in the works, it seems like Nvidia is more than persistant enough to break through such a barrier and enter this market with some staying power.</Msg><Username>manski14</Username><Timestamp>1366936408044</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366937267732-87</Id><Topic><Title>Shield price is set at $350.</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366933857377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know why yahoo deleted my 2 latest replies. One with a link to picture. Once more it was April's issue of Hemispheres.</Msg><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366937267732</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:47:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366938960069-88</Id><Topic><Title>Shield price is set at $350.</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366933857377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I checked it out page 90 hemisphere inflight magazine small article of sheild price of 350 . Maybe thats what caused the move up?</Msg><Username>sashafido</Username><Timestamp>1366938960069</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 21:16:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366939431162-89</Id><Topic><Title>Shield price is set at $350.</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366933857377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for confirming it. I don't like to be called a liar. I just wonder why they did it so silently without press release.</Msg><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366939431162</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 21:23:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366940629342-90</Id><Topic><Title>Shield price is set at $350.</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366933857377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surprised me that there hasn't been discussion of this price on the web....usually the web chatters get their heads up before anybody else....but $350 is a reasonable price point for it offers. That's where I would place it. Thanks for sharing this information. (Still looking for a verifiable link)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366940629342</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 21:43:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366941499853-91</Id><Topic><Title>Shield price is set at $350.</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366933857377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm kinda glad there is no way to attach pictures :).</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366941499853</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 21:58:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366942337569-92</Id><Topic><Title>Shield price is set at $350.</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366933857377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just searched for Hemispheres Magazine, and then again for NVIDIA Shield on the site. It's on page 6 of Geared Up, but it is notated as "not yet priced"</Msg><Username>sasquatchlicious</Username><Timestamp>1366942337569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:12:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366942469910-93</Id><Topic><Title>Shield price is set at $350.</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366933857377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy subscription on-line and take a look for yourself or just wait until it is officially announced. You have rights to be ignorant, But based on latest stock price move I am not the only one who saw that magazine. I can't help you. I uploaded the picture at photobucket and tried to post a link 2 times. Both did not show up.</Msg><Username>adikdrun</Username><Timestamp>1366942469910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:14:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366942518886-94</Id><Title>Been Reading The Nvidia Proxy Statement!</Title><Msg>It seems someone in management made a Foo Pah and stated the request for additional shares for employee options and RSUs wrong last year. Alas they have to do it again this year for management to get their ginormous compensation. It's proposal 2 and I just voted NO on a whole bunch of shares. Note: Options are OK in my book, but these ZERO basis RSUs are definitedly not shareholder friendly. In the proxy statement they promise to only issue 30 million new shares to employees in the next two years. Perhaps that is why they are buying back 60 to 70 million shares this fiscal year. Perfect timing. Read the proxy on Nvidia's website.....some of those numerous Senior VP's option are seriously underwater, and apparently becoming unhappy..</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1366942518886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:15:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366943190079-95</Id><Title>QCOM's margin pressure</Title><Msg>QCOM's margin pressure ocurred 3-to-6 month earlier than I expected. If this started so early, it's gonna get worse at faster pace, as Tegra 4 and Tegra 4i ships commercially. Don't forget Tegra 5 is about 6 months away. Good luck to SA bloggers, who's article have been a clear trading signal in the opposite direction.</Msg><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1366943190079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:26:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366943743760-96</Id><Topic><Title>Shield price is set at $350.</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366933857377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK guys I found a way how to see that commercial. Go to hemispheresmagazine then click on "Subscribe" and then on April issue and go to page 90. They did not ask me to pay. The commercial is right there with a price.</Msg><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366943743760</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:35:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366943781031-97</Id><Topic><Title>Shield price is set at $350.</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366933857377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey will_sell_nvda_at_100, Just sell 4 share of Nvidia and you should be all set to be the first Nvidia sucker to blow $350 on a SHIELD toy. Earth to all space invader game players, The SHIELD toy like Tegra 4 is DOA but no matter since Nvidia is no where near $100 either, is it? lol Enjoy your Nvidia purchase imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366943781031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:36:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366944008302-98</Id><Topic><Title>QCOM's margin pressure</Title><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1366943190079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:26:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trending is not in Qualcomm's favor. Three things (at least 4) are going against QC's margins. --The deterioration of 3G connectivity chip (overtaken by MediaTek and some by Broadcom) --The steadily lowering average sales price of all its parts --The steadily lowering royalty rate --Competition catching up, and fast, in key areas. Qualcomm's recent "breakthrough" in LTE, claimed to overcome global geographical difference in spectrum requirements, really have no bearing on NVDIA's software defined Icera LTE radios.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366944008302</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:40:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366944251769-99</Id><Topic><Title>Shield price is set at $350.</Title><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366933857377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wwwDOTink-liveDOTcom/emagazines/hemispheres-united-airlines/1337/april-2013/#/90/zoomed</Msg><Username>will_sell_nvda_at_100</Username><Timestamp>1366944251769</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:44:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366944328672-100</Id><Title>QCOM has a market Cap of 107 BILLION while Nvidia is at 8.3 BILLION. Nvidia is out of its league</Title><Msg>From all the talk on this message board you would think Nvidia competes with QCOM but Nvidia can't carry QCOMs water. Score is QCOM at 107 BILLION vs Nvidia at 8.3 BILLION, now you tell me who WON this game. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366944328672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:45:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366944664270-101</Id><Title>A $35 SHIELD Toy is would be DOA just like Tegra 4.</Title><Msg>Nvidia is playing games but NOT on a SHIELD toy The game Nvidia is playing is called PRETEND TIME, acting like SHIELD has a chance. lol Sony, MSFT and Nintendo will eat Nvidia's lunch if QCOM leaves anything. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366944664270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:51:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366944976737-102</Id><Topic><Title>QCOM's margin pressure</Title><Username>findingnemoyes</Username><Timestamp>1366943190079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:26:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ship Tegra 4 where? What design wins are you talkin bout? lol Tegra is moving backwards, QCOM TOOK Nvidia's Google Nexus JOB, which accounted for 60% of Tegra sales. Tegra is DONE. Tegra 4, Tegra 4i, 4j, 4k, ... is ALL DOA. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1366944976737</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:56:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366946223206-103</Id><Topic><Title>Where is xc?</Title><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1366878175848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 04:22:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U fool. Xc has been calling this a POS since higher then $16, now this POS rallied a few days at near to years lows and u wanna be arrogant. Learn to acknowledge a loss and dun pretend to be a winner</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1366946223206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 23:17:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>