<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-15"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373869272070-1</Id><Title>JUST IN: ZTE Geek U988S outed as world's first Tegra 4 phone, headed to China Mobile Mobile</Title><Msg>SOURCE: Engadget July 15 China's TENAA certification database is notorious for leaking mobile devices, but this time ZTE's learned that if you can't beat it, then just play along with it. After this U988S was leaked by TENAA recently, ZTE decided to share some product shots on a forum and Sina Weibo ahead of time. What's more, the company confirmed that this red device is actually the China Mobile version of the Geek, but the Intel chip has been replaced by NVIDIA's upcoming Tegra 4. As teased before, this will likely make the new Geek the world's first phone to pack this quad-core chip, which will be clocked at 1.8GHz and will have 2GB of RAM, according to the TENAA filing. Other changes include the 5-inch LCD upgrade from 1,280 x 720 to 1,920 x 1,080 resolution, plus the front-facing camera is now at 2 megapixels instead of just 1. On the other hand, the old 8-megapixel main camera is here to stay. Sadly, this particular device will only work on China Mobile's TD-SCDMA network, meaning the rest of the world will have to stay tuned for a global version. Let's hope that this wouldn't take too long. ______ PS: ZTE previously announced that the ZTE Geek would be powered by Clovertrail, but now the Intel chip has been replaced by Tegra 4. ZTE probably found out the truth the hard way before the recent benchmark scandal broke out - the Intel part simply did not perform to snuff. lol, I bet JH is now LHAO.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373869272070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 02:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373870768393-2</Id><Topic><Title>JUST IN: ZTE Geek U988S outed as world's first Tegra 4 phone, headed to China Mobile Mobile</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373869272070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 02:21:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Intel got kicked out of the ZTE Geek, chances are it may happen again with Samsung's Galaxy Tab 3 which reportedly will deploy Intel ATOM Z2560. Now the whole world knows that Emperor Intel has no clothes on, except for Marsavian and Ashraf E. Lovely!</Msg><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1373870768393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 02:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373872870823-3</Id><Topic><Title>JUST IN: ZTE Geek U988S outed as world's first Tegra 4 phone, headed to China Mobile Mobile</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373869272070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 02:21:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'but now the Intel chip has been replaced by Tegra 4.' More made up BS by the chief nvidia clown here notebookcheckDOTnet/ZTE-Geek-smartphone-launches-in-China-ZTE-Grand-X2-In-to-launch-in-Europe.97417.0.html 'The ZTE Geek will be available in China on July 25th. Prices start at ¥1888 (US$307).'</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1373872870823</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 03:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373873001641-4</Id><Topic><Title>JUST IN: ZTE Geek U988S outed as world's first Tegra 4 phone, headed to China Mobile Mobile</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373869272070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 02:21:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dream on fantasists, Tegra 4 is too expensive to replace Clovertrail+.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1373873001641</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 03:23:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373876397378-5</Id><Topic><Title>Nexus 7 2 with S4 Pro heading to trouble</Title><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1373569421806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think that Qualcomm could offer a great deal to Google just to kick Tegra out of this flagship.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1373876397378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 04:19:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373891797887-6</Id><Title>Ouya is IN STOCK and holding down #74 on Amazon's Best Seller List</Title><Msg>Ouya is off that #95 spot but is still being out sold by a Nintendo DS Wall Charger. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373891797887</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 08:36:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373892557772-7</Id><Title>This just in July 15 POS SHIELD is Still Broken and Who Cares?</Title><Msg>Pull that plug on that Broken POS SHIELD Nvidia and end the embarrassment. Take that Microssoft and Sony Game Console REJECTION like a big boy and stop throwing a SHIELD HISSY FIT Jen. SHIELD will be buried in an eBay grave shortly after it ships IF IT EVER SHIPS. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373892557772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 08:49:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373893492166-8</Id><Title>HEADCASE thinks this board is for Bashing INTC, AMD, QCOM, AAPL, MSFT, SNE and GOOG</Title><Msg>HEADCASE is Bashing Google now for going with Qualcomm for the Next Nexus 7 and Microsoft for for going with AMD for the Xbox One. Hey HEADCASE without Google's Android or Microsoft Windows and RT there is no reason for Nvidia to exist. lol Nvidia selling into the Androd and Windows ecosystem accounts for almost ALL of Nvidia's sales. Does Nvidia have an Operating System to offer anyone? IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373893492166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 09:04:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373894505005-9</Id><Topic><Title>HEADCASE thinks this board is for Bashing INTC, AMD, QCOM, AAPL, MSFT, SNE and GOOG</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373893492166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 09:04:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HEADCASE Nvidia and fans are out talking up Games on PCs now after being REJECTED by ALL 3 Game Consoles and BASHING Intel and Microsoft And those PCs that HEADCASE Nvidia and fans are pumping for games are running on what? Intel CPUs and Microsoft Windows. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373894505005</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 09:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373896155223-10</Id><Topic><Title>EETimes: ARM beats Intel in revised Antutu benchmark (newest article published July 12)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373677580233</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel Cheating with Benchmarks. How exactly is the new news.</Msg><Username>salemthecat100</Username><Timestamp>1373896155223</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 09:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373896244757-11</Id><Topic><Title>Processor Testing Fudged to Give Intel Advantage</Title><Username>hendar00</Username><Timestamp>1373676310390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 20:45:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better title would be "Intel Cheats on Benchmarks - AGAIN"</Msg><Username>salemthecat100</Username><Timestamp>1373896244757</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 09:50:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373897806696-12</Id><Title>Seems like the only way to make money on Nvidia recently</Title><Msg>Is to wait for a bottom near $14 then buy CALL Options with strike price of $14 two months out then wait for the stock to peak (like last Friday) and sell those CALLs for pretty decent profits. Then wait for the next cycle (which looks to be starting today).</Msg><Username>salemthecat100</Username><Timestamp>1373897806696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 10:16:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373901624639-13</Id><Title>An excellent summary for the ZTE Geek U998S powered by Tegra 4</Title><Msg>SOURCE: Mobile Witch, July 15 The ZTE Geek U988S is the first mobile phone powered by the quad-core Tegra 4 and has just been announced by Chinese manufacturer ZTE. The phone was initially expected to feature an Intel processor inside, but instead it will be powered by the NVIDIA produced chip. The Tegra 4 will be clocked at 1.8GHz and will be backed up by 2GB of RAM onboard. There are also other changes brought to the device and they include an improvement in the screen's resolution from the initial 720 x 1280 to the actual 1080 x 1920, and the sensor on the front-facing snapper being doubled to 2-megapixels from the original 1-megapixels. The camera on back will remain at 8-megapixels, however. With all the updated specs that ZTE has decided to launch the phone, it is a real shame that this model will only be released in China for China Mobile, currently the largest mobile operator in the world. In case you have forgotten, we can tell you that the original ZTE Geek was introduced on April 10th and was initially supposed to launch in this year’s third quarter. There is no available information on whether the phone will keep that launch date time period or not, but we’ll let you know as soon as more news surfaces. ..... _______ 3 upgrades for the ZTE Geek from the original concept phone announced in April: ---Processor changed from Intel Clovertrail to Tegra 4 (probably based on performance alone, having nothing to do with the recent scandal of Intel CHEATING AGAIN. --Screen upgraded due to T4 capability --Front upgraded due to T4 capability Original article can be found by googling, "Tegra 4-powered ZTE Geek U988S coming to China Mobile" on Witch Mobile</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373901624639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373901844109-14</Id><Topic><Title>An excellent summary for the ZTE Geek U998S powered by Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373901624639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The above message was posted for those in denial. They have a hard time accepting that Tegra 4 has replaced Clovertrail in a major win, let alone the Intel cheating (again!) scandal. Because of the processor upgrade, ZTE Geek will have a higher-resolution screen and support a better front camera because of the more powerful SoC.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373901844109</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:24:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373902821586-15</Id><Title>"China to lift 13-year ban on video game consoles"</Title><Msg>"China to lift 13-year ban on video game consoles" "Video games are coming out of the shadows in China. China is expected to lift a 13-year ban on the sale of video game consoles, as long as they are manufactured within Shanghai's new free trade zone, the South China Morning Post is reporting. Consoles have been available on the black market in China, but video game manufacturers, such as Nintendo, Sony (SNE), and Microsoft (MSFT, Fortune 500), have not been able to sell their products legally there since 2000 -- even if the consoles were manufactured in the country. Nintendo's Wii, Microsoft's Xbox and Sony's Playstation have been manufactured in China, according the the newspaper. The change is part of a broader policy supported by Premier Li Keqiang, aimed at opening up the Chinese economy. The government is also expected to allow foreign banks to set up subsidiaries in the new Shanghai free trade zone, as well as allow foreign firms to participate in commodities exchanges there. Beijing approved a plan to launch the Shanghai zone on July 3, the report said. Although the new rules have not yet been made public, they are widely expected to allow the sale of gaming consoles once the Ministry of Culture approves them. That ministry spearheaded the ban on the sale of consoles more than a decade ago, citing concern about the content of video games." source: cnn</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373902821586</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373903825699-16</Id><Topic><Title>This just in July 15 POS SHIELD is Still Broken and Who Cares?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373892557772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 08:49:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like they should have marketed it with a free Avenger's game or something. But I doubt that'd help it. Why does Nvda always try to break into a market that's already saturated instead of creating a new market? That's why this POS never goes anywhere. It's one shining moment was Tegra which turned out to be the worst disaster as it dropped 150% from it's high.</Msg><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1373903825699</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:57:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373905792811-17</Id><Topic><Title>This just in July 15 POS SHIELD is Still Broken and Who Cares?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373892557772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 08:49:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jen keeps losing credibility Q to Q, sequentially. No one believes him and NVDA stock suffers.</Msg><Username>dubmeok</Username><Timestamp>1373905792811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 12:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373908827469-18</Id><Topic><Title>This just in July 15 POS SHIELD is Still Broken and Who Cares?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373892557772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 08:49:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IWATCH? Or is it already too late?</Msg><Username>fkdorfi</Username><Timestamp>1373908827469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 13:20:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373911992822-19</Id><Topic><Title>An excellent summary for the ZTE Geek U998S powered by Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373901624639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'because of the more powerful SoC' BS. The Intel powered K900 has the same screen size and resolution.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1373911992822</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:13:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373912109445-20</Id><Topic><Title>An excellent summary for the ZTE Geek U998S powered by Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373901624639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Using the best most efficient compiler in the world is not cheating but best practice which you would know if you knew anything about computing but sadly you are just a cut n paste man no more no less.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1373912109445</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:15:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373912256968-21</Id><Topic><Title>An excellent summary for the ZTE Geek U998S powered by Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373901624639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>google 'Intel-powered ZTE Geek lands on market' which just shows how stupid your DD truly is.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1373912256968</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:17:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373912303415-22</Id><Topic><Title>An excellent summary for the ZTE Geek U998S powered by Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373901624639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>usa chinadaily dotcom dotcn /business/2013-07/12/content_16768600.htm</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1373912303415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:18:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373914455167-23</Id><Title>Qualcomm downgraded by Lazard Capital Markets from BUY to NEUTRAL</Title><Msg>""The firm downgraded QCOM from “Buy” to “Neutral,” noting its flagship smartphones solution advantages are likely to weaken."" SOURCES: WSJ, Streetinsider, DIVIDEND etc QC's high-end smartphone advantages have been weakening.....not just "likely to" NVIDIA Tegra 4 has replaced Snapdragon in the much coveted design win in Xiaomi Mi3 and ZTE's new flagship phone, the Geek.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373914455167</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:54:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373914773347-24</Id><Topic><Title>This just in July 15 POS SHIELD is Still Broken and Who Cares?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373892557772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 08:49:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I might be wrong, but those watch gadgets are a bad idea. Look at calculator watches. They were fun.. for about six months and then nobody wanted them anymore.</Msg><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1373914773347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:59:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373916655759-25</Id><Title>Where are all those tegras anyway. Anyone see one in the wild?</Title><Msg>Are they delayed or something?</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1373916655759</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 15:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373917316005-26</Id><Topic><Title>An excellent summary for the ZTE Geek U998S powered by Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373901624639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Marsavian, You are ignored</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1373917316005</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 15:41:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373917454108-27</Id><Topic><Title>An excellent summary for the ZTE Geek U998S powered by Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373901624639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's your reaction and/or excuse to the latest manipulation of the by Intel to misinform the world once again? I thought they were going to do it the legitimate way this time?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1373917454108</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 15:44:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373918438267-28</Id><Topic><Title>An excellent summary for the ZTE Geek U998S powered by Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373901624639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My reaction ? Good on Intel for making #$%$ code faster and more of it !!</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1373918438267</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 16:00:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373918476411-29</Id><Topic><Title>An excellent summary for the ZTE Geek U998S powered by Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373901624639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and #$%$ are you ?!</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1373918476411</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 16:01:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373919681351-30</Id><Title>AMD closed at NEW DAY HIGH, Intel closed GREEN and Nvidia CLOSED DOWN</Title><Msg>And a Broken POS SHIELD is DOA if Nvidia ever gets the ARRIVAL part done. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373919681351</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 16:21:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373920323504-31</Id><Title>Where's the Cut-N-Paste HEADCASE Bashing AMD at today?</Title><Msg>Is he off looking for Ouya to top a best seller list in Mongolia or Uzbekistan today? Any of you Nvidia fans pumping Tegra 4 own anything with Tegra 4 inside? lol Tegra 4 is DOA and anything using Tegra 4 is DOA POS. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373920323504</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 16:32:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373920599052-32</Id><Topic><Title>"China to lift 13-year ban on video game consoles"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373902821586</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:40:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"China to lift 13-year ban on video game consoles" To bad Nvidia has been REJECTED by ALL 3 Major Game Consoles right Nvidia fans? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373920599052</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 16:36:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373922988539-33</Id><Title>Analysts downgraded 3 big tech stocks: FB, IBM, QCOM</Title><Msg>SOURCE: Schaeffers Research, July 15 FB - Off roughly 16% on a year-over-year basis, FB saw its price target lowered to $33 from $36 at Pivotal Research in pre-market activity. However, the sentiment scales among the analyst crowd remain bullishly tipped toward Facebook Inc. The stock boasts 21 "strong buys" and two "buy" endorsements, versus four "holds" and not a single "sell" suggestion. Furthermore, the equity's consensus 12-month price target of $32.36 reflects expected upside of nearly 25% from Friday's closing price of $25.91. This leaves the door wide open for further downgrades and/or price-target cuts, which could exacerbate the security's technical troubles. IBM - which has tacked on just 0.3% so far this year to linger in the $192.07 neighborhood -- was slapped with a pair of price-target cuts at Jefferies (to $210 from $225) and BMO (to $215 from $220) today. Nevertheless, International Business Machines Corp. -- which is due to report quarterly earnings after this Wednesday's close -- remains popular with near-term call players. The stock's Schaeffer's put/call open interest ratio (SOIR) sits at 0.90, with calls outweighing puts among the front three-months' series of options. QCOM - was downgraded to "neutral" from "buy" at Lazard today, which could chip away at the stock's year-to-date advance of just 0.3%. QUALCOMM, Inc. -- currently priced at $62.02 -- has also trailed the broader S&amp;P 500 Index (SPX) by close to 11 percentage points during the past three months, yet bullish bettors remain undaunted. In fact, the security's 20-day International Securities Exchange (ISE), Chicago Board Options Exchange (CBOE), and NASDAQ OMX PHLX (PHLX) call/put volume ratio of 1.94 confirms calls bought to open have almost doubled puts during the past month. This bevy of bullish bets -- particularly within the August series of calls -- could end up translating into options-related resistance down the road.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373922988539</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 17:16:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373929090697-34</Id><Title>Techradar comments on the new ZTE U998S Geek vs the old one</Title><Msg>SOURCE: Techradar dotUK ""The ZTE Geek looks likely to be the world's first Tegra 4 handset, as ZTE confirms that one Chinese variant at least will come rocking Nvidia's Tegra 4 chip. The Geek, which has to be the worst handset name since HTC went with ChaCha, was originally announced back in April, and was the ZTE to rock an Intel processor. But it's so long farewell to that Intel Atom Z2580 on the upcoming edition known as the ZTE Geek U988S."" _____ SO LONG FAREWELL, Clover!</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373929090697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:58:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373929494730-35</Id><Topic><Title>Techradar comments on the new ZTE U998S Geek vs the old one</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373929090697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:58:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you and all the braindead idiot sites you are quoting fail to realize is that it is not being replaced. The Clvovertrail+ ZTE Geek is being sold worldwide now while your Tegra4 is appearing in some extra limited edition Chinese variant which will probably burn the hands of its users whenever it has to do any serious work lol !!</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1373929494730</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 19:04:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373930653315-36</Id><Topic><Title>Techradar comments on the new ZTE U998S Geek vs the old one</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373929090697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:58:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Clovertrail version of ZTE Geek has NOT been released to any market worldwide, and there is a good chance it will not be. Many analysts think that's why ZTE hurried out the new version powered by Tegra 4, in the aftermath of Intel cheating scandal and ZTE's internal testing results. Again, ZTE Geek based on Clovertrail was only announced, but not SHIPPED. Let alone being sold.....that's a stretch.</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1373930653315</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 19:24:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373930973291-37</Id><Topic><Title>Techradar comments on the new ZTE U998S Geek vs the old one</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373929090697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:58:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Meanwhile back in the real world ... 'Chinese handset maker ZTE and Intel on Thursday jointly announced that ZTE smartphone Geek, powered by a 2Ghz Intel Atom Z2580 Clover Trail+ processor, is landing on the market, c114.net reported. The minimum selling price of Geek is 1,888 yuan, and can go up to 2,288 yuan. Consumers can buy the smartphone from e-commerce suppliers such as jd.com. He Shiyou, executive vice president of ZTE, said he hopes ZTE's cooperation with Intel can make a difference and provide consumers with more powerful smartphones. President of Intel China Yang Xu said that Intel thinks highly of the strategic cooperation with ZTE, which could help Intel improve its market position in the mobile communication area. According to insiders, both ZTE and Intel are at a crucial stage in their development. The most important work at the moment is to improve their brand values. While ZTE needs to shift its strategic focus to mid- and high-end products to win both market share and profits, Intel has to enhance its market position in the mobile area.'</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1373930973291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 19:29:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373931102141-38</Id><Topic><Title>Techradar comments on the new ZTE U998S Geek vs the old one</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373929090697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:58:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why ? Do all those braindead idiot websites have feelings ? LOL</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1373931102141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 19:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373933763498-39</Id><Topic><Title>Techradar comments on the new ZTE U998S Geek vs the old one</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373929090697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:58:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are not helping your own cause with the careless writing/spelling in your posts. Just give it a rest . . there are better things to do, unless you really NEED to be here for some reason. Caio.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1373933763498</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 20:16:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373938374476-40</Id><Topic><Title>Techradar comments on the new ZTE U998S Geek vs the old one</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373929090697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:58:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Why ? Do all those braindead idiot websites have feelings ? LOL" I guess cutting-n-pasting doesn't require reading.comprehension or he has a problem with you having an opinion on the "braindead idiot websites" he quotes. lmao imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373938374476</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 21:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373938839793-41</Id><Topic><Title>Where's the Cut-N-Paste HEADCASE Bashing AMD at today?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373920323504</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 16:32:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that HEADCASE spending his time looking for DOWNGRADES for the companies he bashes while making it a point to IGNORE UPGRADES? lol Didn't a GPU outfit and Nvidia competitor get a couple of upgrades last week that moved the stock UP? Did HEADCASE mention the upgrades that other GPU outfit earned ? His BS game only involves posting downgrades right? IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373938839793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 21:40:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373939269692-42</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcomm downgraded by Lazard Capital Markets from BUY to NEUTRAL</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373914455167</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:54:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ah ibey, yap yap yap all day long, pumping nvda and bashing all other friends and foes alike. Guess telling lies is all in a day's work as long, pathetic. For those who really want to know the real reason for the qcom downgrade, which has nothing to do with nvda, just google 'QCOM: Lazard Cuts to Hold on Low-Cost Smartphone ‘Downshift’'</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1373939269692</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 21:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373939410938-43</Id><Title>"ZTE Geek could be the world’s first NVIDIA Tegra 4 smartphone"</Title><Msg>"ZTE Geek could be the world’s first NVIDIA Tegra 4 smartphone" "There’s no question NVIDIA has been fighting an uphill battle when it come to adoption of their Nvidia Tegra 4 mobile processor. Aside from the NVIDIA’s own SHIELD portable gaming handheld, there just aren’t too many smartphone vendors jumping at the opportunity to feature NVIDIA’s Tegra 4 SoC in their devices. In a market largely dominated by chipset maker Qualcomm, it seems NVIDIA has made a believer out ZTE who is rumored to be introducing the world’s first Tegra 4 smartphone, a newly leaked version of the ZTE GEEK (US988S). Apparently 2 versions of this device will arrive this year (which looks awfully similar to the HTC First). The international model, announced back in April, will be powered by an Intel Atom processor, while this latest version seems to be headed for China Mobile housing an NVIDIA Tegra 4 processor. Obligatory specs for the ZTE Geek show a 5-inch 1080p display, 2GB of RAM, 8MP/2MP cameras, along with Android 4.2.2. No word on if we’ll see this device outside its homeland of China, but with ZTE’s new focus on high-end devices for the US, it’s possible we could see a carrier branded version of this device in the near future." source: phandroid</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1373939410938</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 21:50:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>