<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364098763980-1</Id><Topic><Title>I did warn some of the folks....</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364094935180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 23:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For ibexx, on one of your posts, did you mean March 19th, instead of May 19th? I didn't expect financial numbers myself, but I was glad for all the partnerships and major players cited involved with GRID VCA. Again, I'm not getting the comments about the expectations for Tegra as if it's done for the year. Jen has said several times to expect Tegra wins to be made for the 2nd half of the year, not at this time. I get the impression on any day you have a very light trading day and not see a bump, you get every anxious investor (or trader) posting like it's a total disappointment and the game is essentially lost. I do think we will be seeing behavior that is less volatile and maybe a pop with any news forthcoming on a tablet or phone getting a T4 or T4i. IMO, a lot of the trading the last few weeks has been accumulation, including shares in buyback. Also, it seems like we are overlooking a major difference between Qualcomm and Nvidia at this point. Qualcomm has an advantage due to their royalties as well. It's been a cushion for them for a while, and that's changing as soon as 2014. I think Qualcomm loses it's shine by the end of the year, partly because they also will have some risk in a way that Nvidia has had with their dGPUs &amp; PCs. You may have analysts looking for a new angle and start pointing to Qualcomm as being in trouble by the fourth quarter because of some item like Verizon moving away from CDMA. We'll see.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1364098763980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:19:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364099862690-2</Id><Topic><Title>I did warn some of the folks....</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364094935180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 23:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for your correction, roundhouse. I did mean March 19th. I should be more careful proofreading. Also, Y! didn't let me respond directly to your post, so I found a "reply" button that could be activated...</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364099862690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364101686701-3</Id><Topic><Title>I did warn some of the folks....</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364094935180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 23:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This post is in response to roundhouse. I agree it is grossly unfair to compare QC with NV at this stage of game. --First of one, QC has been working in the mobile space (baseband + app processors) for 30-35 years and , and NV is a newcomer, only having started in the year of 2008. It's fair to say that that NV, with its strong background in PC. graphics, and platforms, has caught up with QC in the pure app space; connectivity on the other hand will take a couple of more years barring no unforeseen event. My observation is that many tech pundits (majority of them, I would say) commented that NV has done an amazing job of re-tooling itself in a brand new technology and marketing area after being squeezed out by Intel. PC Mag mentioned a few days ago that I-500 is the only non-Qualcomm LTE modem that has been certified by ATT. Next in-line will be ther certification of Tegra 4I, hopefully in Q2. I have no idea why some had said that NV was not executing. By what criteria can one say this? --Secondly, as you pointed out, QC has a Licensing/intellectual property business that has a profit margin as high as software - almost 100% - and it has an extremely long product cycle, unlike mobile hardware that needs to be refreshed once a year or less. --QC is a pure mobile play, unlike NV which is still (unfortunately) exposed to the PC market (about 30-40%) which is entirely out of control of NVIDIA. People seem to be ambivalent about Jen Hsun: you get 50% of folks criticizing him as promising too much and delivering little, yet another 50% would accuse him of being coy, like some posters on this board I think his tune was entirely appropriate at both the HTC keynote presentation as well as in the analysts call afterwards. I would be sweating if he had promised the sun to the naive (clueless is the word) analysts.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364101686701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 01:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364111254059-4</Id><Title>Zacks: NVIDIA Offers Visual Computing Product</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-offers-visual-computing-product-214330518.html</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1364111254059</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 03:47:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364129614704-5</Id><Topic><Title>I did warn some of the folks....</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364094935180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 23:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Ibexx, JH revealed Tegra yearly income target last year at this time and QCOM had their competing product out at exactly at the same time. What's changed? Note: 2014 could be a banner year with Nvidia finally getting a presence in phones with Tegra 4i and tegra division could breakeven. Other stuff looks great. But in the meantime What do you think of writing June 13 Calls for 0.49 each?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364129614704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 08:53:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364134472157-6</Id><Topic><Title>I did warn some of the folks....</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364094935180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 23:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>roflol - wrote 20 pages trying to say Tegra isn't a bust.... roflol 5+ years of year after year bigger and bigger pies in the sky, end result loses are bigger and bigger, to the point of struggling to control it to less than $100M/Q.... and you are trying to say 'Just wait till next year, again....." this one has no clothes.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1364134472157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:14:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364138514508-7</Id><Topic><Title>I did warn some of the folks....</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364094935180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 23:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>c'mon whosunw... how do you get that -$100M/Q you sure do hide when asked about it... till your next dodge...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1364138514508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:21:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364138635792-8</Id><Topic><Title>I did warn some of the folks....</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364094935180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 23:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Why is the double standard being practiced here?" Because QCOM has never had troubles gaining design wins with their Snapdragon chips. On the other hand, Nvidia has a lot to prove with Tegra ...</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1364138635792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:23:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364141878497-9</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia: The Buzz Is Gone</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364052070621</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 11:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CUDA on ARM probably doesn't represent revenue. It signals that Nvidia will be trying to change the competition points in the mobile space. Combine it with the HDR demo and the Chimera computational photography system (another talk at GTC), and it looks like mobile processors are moving into a space where Nvidia excels: complex GPU software. It takes years to develop that expertise.</Msg><Username>eastportsail</Username><Timestamp>1364141878497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:17:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364144309076-10</Id><Topic><Title>Nvda stock BETA is 1.63</Title><Username>chazkdbel</Username><Timestamp>1364141633948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:13:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suggest you don't just look up the "beta" off of Yahoo when you analyze investments and calculate your own, with your own sampling period. I am guessing you don't now how to seeing as how you can't see a correlation between Nvidia's price action and its beta.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1364144309076</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:58:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364145731659-11</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia: The Buzz Is Gone</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364052070621</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 11:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You snooze, you loose" you missed the explanation, now you are on your own. Perahps o-investor might explain that one to you as he did the exact same calculations from the 10Q. Word of caution, I was being kind to nvda in my margin assumptions, so my numbers 'only' show $100M/Q. o-investor's numbers are hasher.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1364145731659</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364149883592-12</Id><Topic><Title>Nvda stock BETA is 1.63</Title><Username>chazkdbel</Username><Timestamp>1364141633948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:13:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo takes beta over a larger period of time than 1 year... It has had a number of spikes and drops over the past 5 years, contributing to its beta. Also do not try to measure beta off of long term gains, for example, although Nvidia is down 15% for the year, and the SandP is up 10%, this does not make the beta of the Nvidia -1.5. Beta is sampled over a variety of lengths of time, as well as periods, eg weekly, daily, even hourly gains if you have the data. Yahoo is using a standard for all stocks, and clearly is using a greater length of time than one year, and I believe this is because it is focused on long term investors, who invest for more than 1 year. I am not really sure what you are trying to accomplish here, if you think this is an incorrect beta, go ahead and complain to yahoo. They will tell you how it works much better than I can.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1364149883592</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:31:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364159420243-13</Id><Title>“Cloud gaming” has a future—just maybe not in the cloud</Title><Msg>arstechnicaDOTcom/gaming/2013/03/cloud-gaming-has-a-future-just-maybe-not-in-the-cloud/</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1364159420243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 17:10:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364163034534-14</Id><Topic><Title>“Cloud gaming” has a future—just maybe not in the cloud</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1364159420243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 17:10:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is really interesting about Project Shield is no one can realistically say whether 100,000 units or 1,000,000 units will be sold. But it certainly will be discussed once the media can get their hands on one. They all are angling for that free demo unit. The same can be said about cloud gaming...who knows what will happen but the concept is pretty cool but that's next year. Question Getanid - What did you think of the another two years for Project Denver? Makes sense to me because of timing with ARM 64 bit instruction set release.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364163034534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 18:10:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364164141201-15</Id><Topic><Title>“Cloud gaming” has a future—just maybe not in the cloud</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1364159420243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 17:10:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Question Getanid - What did you think of the another two years for Project Denver?" Still wondering if it is two years ?? We know that the Tegra with PD cores will be 2 yrs away... but still find myself entirely unsure if there will another PD product before that... Jensen also said before that Stark would be first Tegra device to get PD cores... Now that's changed to Parker... Or the Tegra line will increase in options from mobile SOC to larger desktop &amp; server versions... Tegra has already split into two lines of targeting tablets/notebooks vs phones... We should expect more of this as Tegra targets more mkts... "Makes sense to me because of timing with ARM 64 bit instruction set release." IF that's the case... then NVidia, AMCC. and others will have the time to tune it for the release...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1364164141201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 18:29:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364165369661-16</Id><Topic><Title>“Cloud gaming” has a future—just maybe not in the cloud</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1364159420243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 17:10:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Still wondering if it is two years ?? We know that the Tegra with PD cores will be 2 yrs away... but still find myself entirely unsure if there will another PD product before that.." Who knows? I suspect Nvidia just ran out of engineers to do all the things on their plate and had to make choices as to what order to do things to make the most money in 2013 and 2014. They certainly got two large and credible companies competing with them in Smartphones and PC like devices. A little forking in the road makes sense. I really don't expect anything earlier related to 64 Bit ARM and glad that Jensen moved it off to a more realistic time frame. Of course no one else is standing still. And then there is Samsung - It looks like they are very intent in gobbling up every cell phone order in the world and using their own internal parts throughout the BOM. I suspect eventually Sammie will kick Qualcomm to the curb just like they did Nvidia in 2011. It's hard to remember but Tegra 2 was in 6 or 7 Samsung phones worldwide that year and Nvidia really did have a $500M order from them. But Sammie canceled when they got their own application processor going.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364165369661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 18:49:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364168849125-17</Id><Title>Could Intel become irrelevant?</Title><Msg>They had their chance to buy nvidia. And just for fun, the GE tech also specced out how he would go about building supercomputers using Nvidia's future hybrid CPU-GPU chips based on the "Project Denver" cores that Nvidia has been working on for the past several years.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1364168849125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 19:47:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364171536684-18</Id><Topic><Title>Could Intel become irrelevant?</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1364168849125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 19:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EETIMES Slideshow: Intel rising in embedded systems Rick Merritt 3/20/2013 4:01 PM EDT Intel is on the rise and DSPs are on their way out while graphics and ARM chips are just getting started in embedded systems, based on a recent round of interviews. LONG BEACH, Calif. – Intel is in and DSPs are history when it comes to single-board computers and embedded systems, according to vendors at the recent Embedded Tech Trends 2013 show here. Most of the dozens of vendors who spoke to EE Times were longtime PowerPC and Freescale customers. Most were increasingly adopting the x86 while rolling out their first products with ARM and Atom cores. Most saw a rise in the need for communications in embedded markets, but generally at data rates of a gigabit/second. A handful of vendors are pushing into Ethernet and Infinband at 40 Gbit/s rates. These board makers were also driving into high performance apps using general-purpose graphics processors (GPGPUs) from AMD and Nvidia. Some are even starting to talk about a new category of embedded supercomputers. Meanwhile DSPs have been on their way out of embedded boards. Increasingly they are being replaced by FPGAs at the high end and x86 chips with their latest SIMD instructions in other markets. All took with a grain of salt budget cuts under the U.S. sequestration. Their highly fragmented markets and programs will help shield them from at least some of those cuts--they hope. From Power PC to x86 GE Intelligent Platforms is one of a handful of big dogs in this market (see chart below). Its products are a 60/40 mix of Intel and Freescale boards including a lot of legacy PowerPC-based designs. “Historically we’ve been an Intel and Freescale house, but the design wins now are going for Intel,” said David K. Pepper, a technologist in the mil/aero group of GE’s embedded group. Intel refreshes its products about every 15 months so “it’s a better tech play, Freescale is struggling to catch up,” he said.</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1364171536684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:32:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364173866588-19</Id><Title>I Hope Mitt Romney Doesn't Have His Money In Cyprus</Title><Msg>What's this world coming to when offshore Tax haven's aren't safe?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1364173866588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 21:11:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364176568885-20</Id><Title>Are people writing 2013 off?</Title><Msg>Nvidia could still have some good growth it seems, especially with Shield &amp; Grid expected to contribute to results during the second half of the year. I guess Tegra 4 is the wild card, but maybe the company will finally give a bit more guidance at its analyst day next month... Plus, 2014 seems like it could be a great year, with all growth engines starting to fire. I would imagine the stock will eventually move up in anticipation of that... Still think high teens is very possible by the end of 2013...</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1364176568885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 21:56:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364177635462-21</Id><Title>Tegra4 will capture significant mobile marketshare</Title><Msg>Why the heck not.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1364177635462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 22:13:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364178580082-22</Id><Topic><Title>Could Intel become irrelevant?</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1364168849125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 19:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From my experience x86 for true embedded applications is absolutely absurd. It can almost compete in more complex dedicated systems like media devices but even then it falls behind in hurry. We all but ruled out x86 cores as their cost, thermal profiles, and performance all lag behind many arm offerings. Unless you need to run windows embedded there really is little benefit to x86. The system we are aiming to replace right now was built on single core atom and costs close to $1k to produce. During our evaluation process we benchmarked graphics and computing performance of some of the more readily availble x86 cores and compared the results to several ARM chips that cost half as much and we found that not only did ARM crush x86 in the thermal profile and compute per watt but in raw peerformance both graphic and computational. We had to move up to laptop class processors before we saw x86 outperform the ARM cores we tested. However, those types of cores can't even masquerade as dedicated/embedded system class proc - at a cost at 5x and a thermal profile categorically unsuitable for an embedded/dedicated device. So, it's possible that GE and companies alike are moving to x86 in devices like image scanners, large dedicated security devices and things like that where a few hundred if not more doesn't affect your margins all that much but with larger quantity smaller devices x86 simply isn't economical for a lot of dedicated/embedded devices.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1364178580082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 22:29:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364180709731-23</Id><Title>BrreakingNews: EU ministers agree to a bailout package for Cyprus</Title><Msg>BREAKING NEWS Sunday, March 24, 2013 10:34 PM EDT E.U. Ministers Agree on Bailout Package for Cyprus European Union leaders agreed on a bailout package intended to keep Cyprus in the euro zone and rebuild its devastated economy. The deal, struck after hours of meetings, was approved by the finance ministers from the euro zone, the 17 countries that use the common currency. It would drastically prune the size of Cyprus’s oversized banking sector and scrap the highly controversial idea of a tax on bank deposits, although it would still require forced losses for depositors and bondholders. SOURCE: New York Times alert</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364180709731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 23:05:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364182138627-24</Id><Topic><Title>BrreakingNews: EU ministers agree to a bailout package for Cyprus</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364180709731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 23:05:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barring unforeseen factors, market should respond to the news positively.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364182138627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 23:28:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>