<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367380821959-1</Id><Topic><Title>It really wasn't THAT long ago..</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1367377000335</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 22:56:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think WS was stunned by the early signs of deterioration revealed at QC earnings cc. Not only that, I also read an article stating that NV's upcoming Tegra 4i, whose end devices are to be sold at prices below $200, could cut into QC's royalty income stream (mostly on CDMA/3G communication chips). I have no way to ascertain the degree of damage quantitative, but certainly can appreciate the point on a qualitative basis. So... --LTE: Competition catching up (NVDA, BRCM) --CDMA/3G: royalty income stream steadily declining... And QC is not battle trained as NV is....</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367380821959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 00:00:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367381950584-2</Id><Topic><Title>It really wasn't THAT long ago..</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1367377000335</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 22:56:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia ex cash is a cheap company with 10% of qcom valuation. They are supposed to be an ok competition to qcom. Just taking some market shares from qcom could skyrocket nvda share. But really wondering why it takes them so long to do a good job? And the integration of LTE chips. I thought tegra 4 would do it. Why not? And When will it be ready? Anyway, with a decent technical chart set up and with semis showing bullishness, Nvidia better not screw up this time round.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367381950584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 00:19:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367382809570-3</Id><Topic><Title>Blooody XC, whosnw &amp; chrisssy is super hated!</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367372596855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 21:43:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude, if u buy around $12ish u are fine. I am referring to all those ostriches who bought from $26, 24, $20, $16 etc and there are lots of them. They should learn going forward. And if u long at $12, same thing applies. Dun be cocky. Anything can happen in stock market. Have a sell discipline. Who knows Nvidia breaks support and plunged below $10??? And for those idiots, I am not saying it will. Also, if broad market is rallying and a stock can only stay in a small range, that stock is also is also a POS. Cos it wastes your time and $. Anyway, may Nvidia rally from here, makes 52 wk highs, take out $20 and head for $30 soon.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367382809570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 00:33:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367382953029-4</Id><Topic><Title>"Nvidia shakes up Tegra leadership team"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367378173968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 23:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow interesting perspective. Seems like good truth to it. Just like msft rt guy. Got booted shortly after launched. Lol</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367382953029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 00:35:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367389923077-5</Id><Title>Max</Title><Msg>1. Sorry to hear about your mom, best of luck there. I know that's hard, lost my dad two summers ago. 2. Ashraf - Pretty much MIA, just so you know. Maybe he was shamed away. 3. As always, appreciate your insights. You are one of the few longs to really put your trading strategy out there. While I don't "trade" per se, it's welcome to see your option ideas. You call it like you see it, and I for one am tickled you are making substantial money in a short time. And who knows, with another replay of the last few weeks in store, maybe I'll toe the options waters a bit. 4. Your run/streak/predictions of trading opportunities are impressive with this stock, going back years. My biggest "tell" for an up move with NVDA is when you show up and start participating here again :) best</Msg><Username>schmenkle321</Username><Timestamp>1367389923077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 02:32:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367390572766-6</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra poised for growth - organization changes announced today</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367360960062</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the post Ibexx. Jensen continues to make the right moves to grow this business. Phil is a good guy and I'm sure will be successful in what he does next, but Deepu has the experience and relationships to take Tegra to the next level.</Msg><Username>schmenkle321</Username><Timestamp>1367390572766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 02:42:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367391960695-7</Id><Topic><Title>Max</Title><Username>schmenkle321</Username><Timestamp>1367389923077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 02:32:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope I don't come across as an SA fan or someone that sponsors Ashraf here, because I'm neither, but I don't get the need to dwell so much on Ashraf or for that matter other posters who have come and gone (and come back) that imo have plenty of input and information to share whether you agree with them or not. We all trade or invest in several companies' stocks I would imagine, maybe not within one industry per se, so I just don't see how it is good to basically insult someone that seems mostly competent in their comments and respectful. Sure, they may be wrong or take an angle we may think is not totally honest but if their information is solid or at least shows some research, why be so insulting or condescending at times? I admit, I'm insulting and condescending at times, but it's usually in response to someone's own bashing and immature statements. I'm pretty sure Ashraf, from his last responses that I've read, is not shamed at all but more insulted, and doesn't see the point in responding at this point. Anyways, I really do appreciate max's comments (as well as ibexx and others for the most part on this board) and hope he gets all the time with his family that he needs. I lost my mother late in 2011 and it was not an easy time for me either. Regards . .</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1367391960695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 03:06:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367400579620-8</Id><Topic><Title>Max</Title><Username>schmenkle321</Username><Timestamp>1367389923077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 02:32:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rh; was only responding to an earlier post that max had put ashraf on ignore and so he may not know if he was here posting or not cheers</Msg><Username>schmenkle321</Username><Timestamp>1367400579620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 05:29:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367405098284-9</Id><Topic><Title>Blooody XC, whosnw &amp; chrisssy is super hated!</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367372596855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 21:43:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we buy stocks based on potential. but one has to keep not just an open mind, but set up signposts that the company needs to hit on its way of realizing the potential. These signposts cannot be this chip or that. Or this design win or that. These signposts must be market penetration and sales because the end user market is the one who does the final judging. This way one can remain objective. Take brcm and nvda. Brcm's mobile strategy of fully integrated solutions is almost hitting the signposts. Late, but very encouraging. Their 3G chips are in Samsung phones and have been adopted in India. The share price pop after earnings was due to that. I hope they can get into China too. This will prove that their strategy has merit and is worth waiting around for. Nvda, on the other hand, has missed all the signposts. Nvda chased the high end and totally flopped: the high end tablet market has segmented into something that will not support any other 3rd party silicon. The high end phone market is mature and saturated, all without nvda being able to get a toehold. If nvda tries to swim downstream, like with the T3i, there is only so much space to go before they run into brcm's targeted space. Icera is a huge success, but you won't hear Jen talk about it. nvda is calling modem sales 'Tegra sales' and hoping nobody can see through that. Losing Nexus 7 is huge. That is the one and only Tegra device selling that has any kind of run rates. And longs here say it does not matter? You can't expect yourself to be taken seriously if you spout stuff like that. "How do you model Tegra sales?"</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1367405098284</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 06:44:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367416196192-10</Id><Topic><Title>"Nvidia shakes up Tegra leadership team"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367378173968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 23:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Wow interesting perspective. Seems like good truth to it. Just like msft rt guy. Got booted shortly after launched. Lol" Yoiu know it had to happen. They talked up Tegra in the beginning year but didn't ship anything. They pitched Tegra to Google and BLEW the Nexus deal and with it 60% of Tegra sales WALKED. HEADS HAD TO ROLL at the Nvidia HEADQUARTERS for ONE BIG Tegra 4 "Mess" UP. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367416196192</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 09:49:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367416349398-11</Id><Topic><Title>If Tegra was so hot the Tegra Unit Head wouldn't be WALKING AWAY.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367379713523</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 23:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When they lost the Google DEAL his days were numbered. Google accounted for 60% of Tegra sales according to a Digitimes article. Good riddens is what you Nvidia fans should be saying because Tegra 4 is LATE and no where in sight. Tegra 4 is DOA imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367416349398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 09:52:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367416868267-12</Id><Topic><Title>If Tegra was so hot the Tegra Unit Head wouldn't be WALKING AWAY.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367379713523</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 23:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many times do you plan on repeating your same worn out Tegra 4 propaganda today? Give it a rest already.</Msg><Username>fairbanksmorse1</Username><Timestamp>1367416868267</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:01:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367417944241-13</Id><Title>Strategy Analytics: 2012 baseband market</Title><Msg>Qualcomm, MediaTek and Intel Together Held Three-Fourths of Cellular Baseband Revenue Share in 1H 2012 interest read</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1367417944241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:19:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367418208570-14</Id><Title>Nvidia, keep up tis good work</Title><Msg>Stay resilient, time for u to show your haydays strength. Show that its pos that calls u pos! Lol</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367418208570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367419227504-15</Id><Topic><Title>Max</Title><Username>schmenkle321</Username><Timestamp>1367389923077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 02:32:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some people can spot a phony miles away, but you don't seem to have that kind of talent. Instead, you are a compulsive enforcer totally misdirected at times. I will show you some real targets for your obsessive urge to control: XC Whosunw Followon Chrisssable etc etc This list will keep you busy for a while. Frankly, your self-righteousness makes me ill.</Msg><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1367419227504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:40:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367420211535-16</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia, keep up tis good work</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367418208570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey chrisssey, this has to be your most incoherent post yet. Can you please apply your mentally challenged mind and try to explain in a way that people will understand what you were trying to say?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1367420211535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:56:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367420784949-17</Id><Topic><Title>Max</Title><Username>schmenkle321</Username><Timestamp>1367389923077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 02:32:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, those folks are on my ignore list. So how am I self-righteous again? This weird response to someone that is tired of putting half (or more) on ignore . . did you ever think that my comments are a response to the self-righteousness of many that are 'authentic' on this board? I'm sorry that you feel sick about my comments really. It seems very weird to me to call my comments self-righteous given the comments of those calling me self-righteous. But best of luck in your investing really, I do mean that.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1367420784949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:06:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367420988872-18</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia, keep up tis good work</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367418208570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are u the stupidiest guy on earth? I have said before, I long this POS recently again, and even thou I long, I still think it is a POS. Unless it proves me otherwise. More days like this will do so. And fool, no stocks stay good forever, and no pos stays forever. Adjust and trade. The wise said, there is no bull or bear market, there is only the right side of the market. And if people call me pos, I am fine as long as I am a rich pos. Its better to be a rich pos than a poor loyalist.</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367420988872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:09:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367421107042-19</Id><Topic><Title>Max</Title><Username>schmenkle321</Username><Timestamp>1367389923077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 02:32:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for being civil in your response to me. I probably should have responded direct to 'max' . . thought I had. I guess in the midst of a nice uptick, that seems to have legs, we all start showing our warts so to speak.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1367421107042</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:11:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367422274188-20</Id><Title>POS nvidia</Title><Msg>Last few days I traded this POS, I bought, made some $ , I sold cos I still regard this a POS. The few times I sell, it either rally, or goes down a bit and? Well rally again. Fed up, I bought more and stop selling pos. Wow, today showed surprising strength. Semis showing strength too. Wish this semis sector convincingly break out of its multi year range. Cos when semis rally, they rally real hard . Fundamentally, wonder what could be the catalyst for semis? Are they gonna sell lots of pcs or laptops? Hmmmmm</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367422274188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367423844710-21</Id><Topic><Title>POS nvidia</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367422274188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Short term, some phone and tablet wins are what NVDA needs to really progress. I wouldn't expect really notable wins for a few more months based on the T4i schedule, so I expect range-bound performance. On the other hand, some of the T4 sightings and previews are starting to look good. Much as the expected Nexus 7 loss is unfortunate, the Nexus line has shown weakness. The Nexus 10, for example, is rarely seen compared to the Asus 10" table which sports a T3. So, there is definitely life outside of Nexus. I hold INTC, NVDA, and will likely pick up AMD soon. All for very different reasons. MHO.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1367423844710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:57:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367423981684-22</Id><Topic><Title>Max</Title><Username>schmenkle321</Username><Timestamp>1367389923077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 02:32:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Schmenkle- Thanks. My mother is suffering more pain than anyone should and I'm hoping she finds some peace in the near future. I watched my dad die 8 years ago, and was there at the end, as I likely will be with my mom. And, thanks for the kind words. I'd rather be lucky than "smart" but I'll take it! I do think something VERY good is coming in the VERY near future. As for Ashraf...sorry to have ruffled some feathers about him, but I expected more maturity and class from a young person just starting out in the market, when all I had tried to do was help him understand some things about the market...like NEVER say "Never"....I've tried to share my experience with everyone here, and he seems like a bright young man, so I was disappointed to say the least that he didn't acknowledge his losing a nickel, CASH, to me on the bet we made about ARMH. Oh well. Best, Max</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1367423981684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:59:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367424423130-23</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia, keep up tis good work</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367418208570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think it's getting close to your regular afternoon nap and medication.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1367424423130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:07:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367425493948-24</Id><Topic><Title>POS nvidia</Title><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367422274188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If smh rally big, u will be a richer guy !</Msg><Username>chrisssable</Username><Timestamp>1367425493948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:24:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367427091955-25</Id><Title>Latest rumor about Google X phone - Tegra 4i in it</Title><Msg>""Google X-Phone Finally, the Motorola acquisition starts to make sense. Or does it? It is rumored that the X-Phone is set for release this year. The device will supposedly have a 4.7-inch Full HD display, and will get the power from an Nvidia Tegra 4i multi-core processor clocked at 2.3 GHz, and a 16MP camera. It is believed that this will be first new phone with the Android Key Lime Pie OS version, but we will take that, like all rumours with a pinch of salt – mostly because, the Nexus 5 is also being talked about quite a bit."" SOURCE: thinkdigitDOTcom/Mobiles-PDAs/Forward-Looking-Gadgets-to-look-out-for_14476.html</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367427091955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:51:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367427898813-26</Id><Title>ARMH: processor share and royalty rate to rise, says analyst</Title><Msg>SOURCE: Barrons just in "By Tiernan Ray Shares of Canaccord Genuity’s Matthew Ramsay this morning reiterates a Buy rating on shares of chip intellectual property licensor ARM Holdings (ARMH), and a $52 price target, writing that his recent meetings with investors regarding the stock in Milwaukee, Chicago, Kansas City, and Denver were “upbeat,” and that he maintains a view the company is “is well positioned to hold dominant processor market share within the growing smartphone and tablet markets while benefitting from royalty rate expansion due to increased Cortex-A penetration, Mali graphics attach rates, and secular trends toward chipset integration.” Ramsay sees ARM increasing its share of microprocessors by the end of this decade to more than 50% from 32% at present, and he sees the company’s royalty rate will rise to 1.5% next year from 1.3% last year, on average, and may approach 2% at the end of the decade. ARM shares today are up $1.03, or 2.2%, at $47.78. _______ Posting this as general information, as well as for our "esteemed" SA blogger who is heavily short ARMH by his own account. So far, unfortunately, Blogger #2 has been deadly wrong on several accounts (QCOM, ARMH most notably). Er....well, as long as the SA folks aren't aware of it....</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367427898813</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:04:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367433365920-27</Id><Topic><Title>Latest rumor about Google X phone - Tegra 4i in it</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367427091955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:51:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look who is reduced to spreading RUMORS. Buying Nvidia at OVER $16 can cause some to do all sorts of things trying to break even? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367433365920</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:36:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367433556398-28</Id><Title>Apple had antena gate now Nvidia has Tegra 4 gate. In both cases HEADS ROLLED</Title><Msg>Tegra UNIT HEAD GONE and not a day too soon because that Google Nexus money is also GONE and way to early right Nvidia fans? lol Tegra 4 is DOA imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367433556398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:39:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367433864711-29</Id><Topic><Title>If Tegra was so hot the Tegra Unit Head wouldn't be WALKING AWAY.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367379713523</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 23:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How many times do you plan on repeating your same worn out Tegra 4 propaganda today?" Nvidia put the story out that the Tegra 4 UNIT HEAD is GONE. Did you call it "propaganda" when Nvidia put out that "cover its rear" PR? lol Tegra 4 is DOA. Now you can count that "Tegra 4 is DOA" too and keep a running tally to report to the board sport. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367433864711</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:44:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367434314147-30</Id><Title>AMD ADDING OVER 13% Today Following Yesterdays 5% GAIN while Nvidia is DOWN again.</Title><Msg>Which GPU outfit is having a good day? Hint: Not the one you Nvidia fans bet your saving on, nope, not that one. lol On a seriuos note what's UP with AMD? Anyone here have a clue? IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367434314147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:51:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367434351387-31</Id><Topic><Title>Latest rumor about Google X phone - Tegra 4i in it</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367427091955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:51:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's interesting to note that at the Google developer conference scheduled for may 14-16 that they have separated the keynote address into mobile &amp; Android, and the other for Chrome and desktop. Perhaps this is where the HP 21" desktop will be released, among other Tegra devices?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1367434351387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:52:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367434548871-32</Id><Topic><Title>Latest rumor about Google X phone - Tegra 4i in it</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367427091955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:51:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is every Nvidia fan going to sign on to this rumor spreading nonsense now? lol Has it come to that? How low can will you go trying to break even? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367434548871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:55:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367434667121-33</Id><Title>"AMD Spikes 13% on Heavy Volume"</Title><Msg>"AMD Spikes 13% on Heavy Volume" "Shares of Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) just had a big pop in heavy volume, lifting off of earlier gains and rising 36 cents, or over 12%, to $3.17, and as high as $3.27 just before that. There’s not a lot of news flow today to which to peg the sudden rise." Source: Barrons</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367434667121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367434830736-34</Id><Title>"AMD reveals potent parallel processing breakthrough"</Title><Msg>"AMD reveals potent parallel processing breakthrough" "AMD has released details on its implementation of The Next Big Thing in processor evolution, and in the process has unleashed the TNBT of acronyms: the AMD APU (CPU+GPU) HSA hUMA." Source: TheRegister</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367434830736</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:00:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367435151837-35</Id><Topic><Title>"Nvidia shakes up Tegra leadership team"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367378173968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 23:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zdnet go it right. PROBLEMS led to a shake up at the top. Nvidia is having problems BIG TIME getting the next Tegra out the door IMHO. Which is why Google ran into the ARMS of QCOM. Pun intended Nvidia fans. lol Tegra 4 is DOA. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367435151837</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:05:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367435395250-36</Id><Title>What is going on? AMD UP OVER 15% and CLIMBING!!!</Title><Msg>Forget FALLING Nvidia Today. Today is all about AMD PERIOD Anyone here have a clue why AMD is UP BIG TIME and Nvidia is DOWN? IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367435395250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:09:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367435426717-37</Id><Title>AMD introduced new processors, dropped prices across the board (significantly)</Title><Msg>On its website, AMD has made pricing changes for various performance desktop offerings including A-Series, FX-Series, and Phenom chips. The changes include: A6-3600 (2.1/2.4GHz QC 4M) from $95 to $77; A8-3800 (2.4/2.7GHz QC 4M) from $105 to $91; A8-3820 (2.5GHz QC 4M) from $115 to $101; A6-5400K (3.6GHz DC 1M) from $67 to $57; A8-5500 (3.2GHz QC 4M) from $101 to $91; A8-5600K (3.6GHz QC 4M) from $101 to $91; FX-4300 (4.0GHz, 4C, 1MB L2, 4MB L3) from $122 to $108; FX-6300 (4.1GHz, 6C, 1MB L2, 8MB L3) from $132 to $112; FX-8320 (4.0GHz, 8C, 1MB L2, 8MB L3) from $169 to $153 ; Phenom II X4 965 BE(3.4GHz QC 8M) from $91 to $81... SOURCE: Wells Fargo analyst David Wong OY!</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367435426717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367435738428-38</Id><Topic><Title>AMD introduced new processors, dropped prices across the board (significantly)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367435426717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As usual YOU ARE CLUELESS A Price Cut, which happens all the time, WOULD NOT CASUE AMD TO BE UP OVER 15%. TODAY. How is Nvidia doing? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367435738428</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:15:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367435906521-39</Id><Title>Somebody has AMD ENVY Today and we all know who? lmao</Title><Msg>Where is your 15% UP day Nvidia fans? lol You get the Tegra 4 UNIT HEAD Walking Away from Tegra. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367435906521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:18:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367436315458-40</Id><Topic><Title>AMD ADDING OVER 13% Today Following Yesterdays 5% GAIN while Nvidia is DOWN again.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367434314147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:51:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Heavy Volume both days. Hmm? What about your Nvidia? How you doing Today Nvidia fans? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367436315458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:25:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367436719689-41</Id><Topic><Title>Apple had antena gate now Nvidia has Tegra 4 gate. In both cases HEADS ROLLED</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367433556398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know its TRUE Nvidia fans. The Tegra 4 roll out is a MESS, so someone had to go over at headquarters and who better than the Tegra UNIT HEAD. Tegra UNIT HEAD departs HEADQUARTERS as Tegra 4 faces HEAD WINDS. That sounds right doesn't it? A QCOM storm is approaching fast Nvidia fans. Ask Google why they ran into the ARMS of QCOM OK? lol Tegra 4 is DOA imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367436719689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367436931293-42</Id><Title>To Add Insult to Injury, AMD is UP BIG TIME while Nvidia is Tanking?</Title><Msg>AMD UP BIG TIME and Nvidia is DOWN some real change today. Now say it ain't so. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367436931293</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:35:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367437344457-43</Id><Topic><Title>Where did you Nvidia fans buy your Tegra 4 tablet? Because NO ONE ELSE can find Tegra 4.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367335560231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 11:26:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did anyone find a Tegra 4 tablet for sale today Nvidia fans? Same as yesterday right, you can't buy aTegra 4 tablet anywhere TODAY. Hmm, do you think that is why the Tegra UNIT HEAD is walking away from Tegra? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367437344457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367437874676-44</Id><Topic><Title>AMD introduced new processors, dropped prices across the board (significantly)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367435426717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whoever designed the amd model #s should be taken out and be shot. totally confusing as with the Acura rebranding/model change. At least Acura had the guts now to admit their model naming system's wrong. guess bad companies don't get to be bad for nothing. they make bad moves.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1367437874676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367438062614-45</Id><Topic><Title>AMD introduced new processors, dropped prices across the board (significantly)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367435426717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take that WHINE to the Acura board or the AMD Naming Suggestion Box sport. AMD UP OVER 13% IS THE NEWS TODAY Not your WHINING Tegra 4 is DOA imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367438062614</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:54:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367438374564-46</Id><Topic><Title>AMD introduced new processors, dropped prices across the board (significantly)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367435426717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good news, XC. Now you only need another 80% or so to catch up with NVDA for TTM performance. Bought AMD today. Feeling pretty good so far. Oh yes... this isn't 2002. NVDA and AMD (or should I say ATI) are not opposites anymore.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1367438374564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367438583564-47</Id><Title>AMD UP Over 13%, 82 MILLION Shares and you want to talk about CPU NAMES and PRICES? lol</Title><Msg>GET REAL, AMD UP BIG TIME IS THE ONLY AMD NEWS TODAY. When was the last time Nvidia added 5% on Tues followed by 13% on Wed? Somebody get out an iPad and ADD 5% PLUS 13%? Did you get ONE GREAT DAY FOR AMD? lmao imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367438583564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:03:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367438730731-48</Id><Topic><Title>AMD introduced new processors, dropped prices across the board (significantly)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367435426717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Bought AMD today. Feeling pretty good so far. " Are you claiming you bought AMD TODAY? Only Today right? lmao Do you know what a fair weather friend is? Got a mirror? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367438730731</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:05:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367438943527-49</Id><Topic><Title>To Add Insult to Injury, AMD is UP BIG TIME while Nvidia is Tanking?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367436931293</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:35:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Give me back my 12 cents?" I hear you Nvidia fans BUT I don't care. lol Tegra 4 is DOA. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367438943527</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367439867707-50</Id><Title>As the Tegra 4 UNIT HEAD departs HQ the Smart Money is Fitting Tegra 4 for a PINE BOX</Title><Msg>When the UNIT HEAD walked the blame game is on and Tegra 4 is DOA. Smart money saw it coming when QCOM took Tegra's job at Google. How long have I been saying, Tegra 4 is DOA. Anyone here have a clue. Ask the old Tegra UNIT HEAD how successful Tegra 4 was as he collects his belonging, cleans out his office and hands in his badge. lmao imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367439867707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:24:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367440062360-51</Id><Title>XC wins April's most prolific &amp; annoying poster honor!</Title><Msg>Congrats to XC for 40+ redundant &amp; annoying posts for April. It appears that XC is trying to beat the all-time record held by dumbest and his many aliases. The other run-away winner is Chrisssey for using "POS" the most. If there was a category for not making much sense chrisssey would have won that also. They both have won 3 free sessions with a psychologist of their choice.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1367440062360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:27:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367440292870-52</Id><Topic><Title>XC wins April's most prolific &amp; annoying poster honor!</Title><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1367440062360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:27:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: The 40+ designation was in regards for annoying posts for today only.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1367440292870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:31:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367440654537-53</Id><Title>"AMD surges as Intel, XBox talk surfaces: report"</Title><Msg>"AMD surges as Intel, XBox talk surfaces: report" "As U.S. stocks tumbled Wednesday on fears the economy is stalling again, and at the start of the traditional “sell-in-May” season, Advanced Micro Devices bucked the trend noticeably. AMD stock AMD +0.31% rose 14.2% to close at $3.22 a share, its highest close since Oct. 9. The percentage gain was AMD’s biggest since July 22, 2011, when it jumped 19.2%. Barron’s Tech Trader Daily noted the resurgence of speculation that Intel could move to buy AMD, noting that anti-trust issues are less of a concern than in earlier years because the personal computing space is broader than it was when WinTel dominated technology. Other speculation has centered on new game console from Microsoft MSFT 0.00% due to be announced later this month that could use AMD chips. There’s also substantial short interest in AMD, about 20%, Tech Trader Daily noted. AMD reported a narrower first-quarter loss on April 18, and forecast second-quarter revenue would range from a 5% gain to a 1% loss, vs. the first quarter." Source: Marketwatch</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367440654537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:37:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367440794314-54</Id><Topic><Title>XC wins April's most prolific &amp; annoying poster honor!</Title><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1367440062360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:27:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHINE all you want sport its good practice for anyone HOLDING Nvidia paper. Now don't forget to count this post. lol Tegra 4 is DOA. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367440794314</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:39:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367441220681-55</Id><Topic><Title>XC wins April's most prolific &amp; annoying poster honor!</Title><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1367440062360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:27:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>40+ posts buy a lot of hamburgers.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367441220681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:47:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367441248883-56</Id><Topic><Title>XC wins April's most prolific &amp; annoying poster honor!</Title><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1367440062360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:27:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not whining, but telling it the way it is by your prolific and annoying posts. Now make sure you alert the board another 40 times today about how Tegra 4 is DOA.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1367441248883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:47:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367441300538-57</Id><Topic><Title>XC wins April's most prolific &amp; annoying poster honor!</Title><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1367440062360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:27:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, XC is the last poster on all but a couple of the last few dozen threads.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1367441300538</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367443066539-58</Id><Topic><Title>AMD introduced new processors, dropped prices across the board (significantly)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367435426717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fair weather friend? This isn't about friendship, it's about money. Stocks are not your friend. In the past, I have traded INTC, AMD, and NVDA. Years ago I did really well trading ATYT and NVDA back and forth. AMD was generous enough to cash me out of ATYT. Am I a fair weather friend? If stocks were your friends, then sure. They aren't, though. They are investments and you pick the winners. Do you work for AMD? If so, then that's different. I don't work or do business with any of the above, so I am free to pick winners.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1367443066539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367443250391-59</Id><Topic><Title>To Add Insult to Injury, AMD is UP BIG TIME while Nvidia is Tanking?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367436931293</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:35:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wouldnt be surprised because AMD chips are going to be in all the new gaming consoles this winter....</Msg><Username>real_estate_bobby</Username><Timestamp>1367443250391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:20:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367445642894-60</Id><Topic><Title>To Add Insult to Injury, AMD is UP BIG TIME while Nvidia is Tanking?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367436931293</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:35:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Consoles are trash, they won't compete with mobile, the picture for them is only getting weaker as more people who had a generational tie to consoles fade away.</Msg><Username>manski14</Username><Timestamp>1367445642894</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:00:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367448282179-61</Id><Topic><Title>To Add Insult to Injury, AMD is UP BIG TIME while Nvidia is Tanking?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367436931293</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:35:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the picture for them is only getting weaker " YES, and AMD was weaker by a whopping 14% UP today right? And now back to the Nvidia story, Nvidia was DOWN AGAIN TODAY but Nvidai is still BIG STRONG MAN right? lol BIG STRONG MAN Nvidia just fall down thats all, right? Take your weakness BS and wallpaper the stall you came up with that junk, OK? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367448282179</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367448674362-62</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD surges as Intel, XBox talk surfaces: report"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367440654537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:37:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Barron’s Tech Trader Daily noted the resurgence of speculation that Intel could move to buy AMD, " An Intel AMD Love-In would be BAD NEWS for you know who IMHO. BTW, How long would it take to put a stop payment on a royalty check? Just curiuos? lol Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367448674362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367451185243-63</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD surges as Intel, XBox talk surfaces: report"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367440654537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:37:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The royalty check is required by the legal settlement; think of it as NVDA's pay-off to be shut out of the x86 chipset market a few years ago and not to yell "anti-trust" too loudly. Read the details before you invest anything based on the idea that it would go away. An AMD buy-out would likely accelerate the collapse of the discrete video card market for all but the high-end. That is already happening and NVDA is working to develop other opportunities, but it would push the collapse forward enough that NVDA would be challenged to be ready. What do you guess, 18 months to see ATI graphics make their way into INTC processors, if a deal happened? On the other hand, it wouldn't really change anything about Tegra or supercomputers. I know, you don't believe Tegra is real. LOL. AMD is struggling for relevancy in both those markets. IMO, it would speed up a transition that is happening anyway. Anyone investing in NVDA based on the future of discrete graphics was on the wrong track anyway.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1367451185243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 19:33:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367462405772-64</Id><Title>Heads of Icera and Tegra were out and a copycat of the "OMAP roadmap" is taking shape</Title><Msg>They - who did the real work- did not get 15% based wage increases. They should have been the CEO &amp; COO should the mobile business were spun off, and let the rest of them stay with the server/GPU/high performance computing business. The reorganized Nvidia mobile business roadmap is the OMAP roadmap! The Tegra head will be a CEO of Nvidia ?PARTNER? - wait &amp; see if it would be it would be a friend of foe - the future competitior. Cheers!</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1367462405772</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 22:40:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367463003713-65</Id><Title>How to distribute reserve cash to insiders</Title><Msg>Stock buyback ...... stock dilution and unload them. BTW, it is legal since investors like Ibexx approved it. Do not have to be a mathematician to figure it out. Cheers!</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1367463003713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 22:50:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367463027597-66</Id><Topic><Title>Somebody has AMD ENVY Today and we all know who? lmao</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1367435906521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:18:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why you own both...</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367463027597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 22:50:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367463235790-67</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH: processor share and royalty rate to rise, says analyst</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1367427898813</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:04:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's funny...as an Nvidia bull you should be thinking, "Gee, but if Tegra takes significant market share, then ARM doesn't get Mali royalties, undermining a portion of this thesis!" Further, do you actually think that it's a good thing for Nvidia that royalty rates will get ridiculous, especially as wafer cost increases are NOT offset by the traditional scaling benefits in the 20nm generation and, more markedly in the "16nm" generation? For a guy who likes to talk trash, you sure have your head where the sun don't shine. I like Nvidia, but it's funny how you're taking out the pain you feel from xc's attacks on me ;)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367463235790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 22:53:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367466448971-68</Id><Title>New Tegra head -- think Kindle Fire 3</Title><Msg>love to speculate on this. lol</Msg><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1367466448971</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 23:47:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>