<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358064861798-1</Id><Topic><Title>Why NVIDIA's Shield struck hardest at CES 2013?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358058964148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 01:36:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's this? Hummm? Cheap, tawdry, wretched and too easy imitation journalism. From hackster Chris Burns of slashgear. "NVIDIA’s Tegra Zone will surely be the place where you’ll find the best of the best." Despicable, cheap, tawdry, wretched imitation journalism, from slashgear's Mr. Burns. Attempting to take a lame, kitten-like slash at the Genuine Best. It's sleazy and oh so, well, plebeian. Yes boys, plebeian. Take note Mr. Burns of slashgear: “By three methods we may learn genuine Wisdom. First, by reflection, which is noblest; Second, by imitation, which is cheap, tawdry, wretched and easiest; and Third, by experience, which is the most bitter.” -- Confucius quotes (China's most famous teacher and philosopher, 551-479 BC)</Msg><Username>genuine.best</Username><Timestamp>1358064861798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 03:14:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358065390859-2</Id><Topic><Title>Why NVIDIA's Shield struck hardest at CES 2013?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358058964148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 01:36:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? Don't the Real journalists -- the true Craftsmen of the Word -- get paid for what they do. Unlike the Imitation journalists, that just slash and burn the best stuff from other folks.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1358065390859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 03:23:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358066273753-3</Id><Topic><Title>Why NVIDIA's Shield struck hardest at CES 2013?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358058964148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 01:36:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Craftsman Best, It's a shame really. There's only three or four Real journalists in the semiconductor space today. The rest are just cheap, clueless Imitation journalists. Trying to eek out a living -- stealing from the best. C|B</Msg><Username>charlie_best_here</Username><Timestamp>1358066273753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 03:37:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358066490550-4</Id><Topic><Title>Why NVIDIA's Shield struck hardest at CES 2013?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358058964148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 01:36:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed Charlie. And you BE DA MAN !!!!</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1358066490550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 03:41:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358077068399-5</Id><Topic><Title>Hardware specs comparison: Project Shield vs competing devices</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358051173266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:26:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Sony PS Vita's 400 MHz PowerVR SGX543MP4+ is in the same performance league as the Tegra 4 gpu.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358077068399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 06:37:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358079854547-6</Id><Topic><Title>Hardware specs comparison: Project Shield vs competing devices</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358051173266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:26:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So where is the Tegra4 GPU benchmarks?</Msg><Username>razorgarf</Username><Timestamp>1358079854547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 07:24:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358086927077-7</Id><Topic><Title>Why NVIDIA's Shield struck hardest at CES 2013?</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358058964148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 01:36:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for posting all the information ibexx. It seems you have best the pest all flustered with all the impressive information that he replied 4 times with his usual blather.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1358086927077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 09:22:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358088820939-8</Id><Topic><Title>Hardware specs comparison: Project Shield vs competing devices</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358051173266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:26:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In one of the many Youtube articles one of the Nvidia guys said the Project Shield he was holding had 32GB storage plus a micro SD slot. Like the Micro SD slot because most of these games ported over to Tegra PC require a lot of storage. For example Harwken requires 1.5GB.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358088820939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 09:53:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358094239756-9</Id><Title>The Media thinks they are the CEO of Nvidia</Title><Msg>yes, the media made apple great, google great, right?</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1358094239756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:23:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358094914880-10</Id><Topic><Title>Hardware specs comparison: Project Shield vs competing devices</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358051173266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:26:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So here's an idea, boys. Since Jen says he's all about "intellectual honesty" and this and that. And the readers here are clamoring insistently about benchmarks for the toy Shield. Yes, clamoring insistently. And we all know that at least one toy Shield exists. 'Cause Jen waived it in the air at the CES. So here's the idea. Jen has his driver take the toy Shield over to Anandtech. THE gold standard on the planet for benchmarking electronic devices, right? Can you think of another one? Hummm? I didn't think so. So as I was proposing, Jen has his driver take the toy Shield over to Anandtech, and has Mister Anand Lal Shimpi -- the veritable Founder of Anandtech, not a one-of-three co-founders kind of guy, nope, THE Founder himself, -- personally benchmark the toy Shield himself. Versus the reigning heavyweight champion of the world, THE Sony PS Vita 400 MHz PowerVR SGX543MP4+ Mister Anand Lal Shimpi, the veritable Founder of Anandtech, does really quick work too -- kind of like a Hong Kong laundry. In by 9:00 am, out by 2:00 pm. Satisfaction guaranteed. So Jen doesn't need to worry about his only toy Shield missing the next show. Whataya think, boys? Yet Another Great Idea From Best, right? It sure is. An intellectually honest way to End all of this insistent clamoring about what the toy Shield's benchmarks might be. "Just do it." Unless of course, Jen is a chicken. And is cowering because he doesn't want the world to know how the toy Shield stacks-up versus THE Sony PS Vita 400 MHz PowerVR SGX543MP4+ Bwark! bwark! bwark! bwark! bwark!</Msg><Username>bests.idea</Username><Timestamp>1358094914880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:35:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358095705141-11</Id><Title>Value Uncovered1.</Title><Msg>I've been searching for another tech titan to invest in. I've found it with NVDA. They have over $5/share in cash on the books, no debt, increasing revenues and earnings, a plethora of strong products to offer. Additionally, NVDA is oversold. I like what I see, and will be investing Monday morning. I recently liquidated my FLEX positioon in in the 5s, out at 6.50 Friday, and ACTS, in at 1.65, out at 1.82 Thursday. FCEL, in at 1.03, out at 1.26. NVDA is one of those stocks that has been oversold due to a glitch with a tradeshow presentation. Most investors are so ignorant about how to invest. Investors' penchant to react negatively to every bump in the road will be my gain. Jobe</Msg><Username>jobe1098</Username><Timestamp>1358095705141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:48:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358096331084-12</Id><Topic><Title>Value Uncovered1.</Title><Username>jobe1098</Username><Timestamp>1358095705141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:48:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10 percent profit, what an "investor"!</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1358096331084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:58:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358096332104-13</Id><Topic><Title>Value Uncovered1.</Title><Username>jobe1098</Username><Timestamp>1358095705141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:48:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10 percent profit, what an "investor"!</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1358096332104</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:58:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358098512783-14</Id><Title>Nvidia is taking big risks moving into game hardware. Is it crazy or genius?</Title><Msg>venturebeatDOTcom/2013/01/11/the-deanbeat-nvidia-takes-big-risks-moving-into-game-hardware-is-it-crazy-or-genius/</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358098512783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 12:35:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>28</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358099932748-15</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is taking big risks moving into game hardware. Is it crazy or genius?</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358098512783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 12:35:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>btw, the author is kinda clueless how the industry works... but posted anyway...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358099932748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 12:58:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358101515066-16</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is taking big risks moving into game hardware. Is it crazy or genius?</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358098512783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 12:35:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's take a look at that fine news article, shall we? In excerpts. "Nvidia grabbed a lot of the coveted media attention this week at the Consumer Electronics Show in Las Vegas. The [last remaining] world’s biggest standalone graphics-chips company announced it would make Project Shield, a portable game system that can run Android and Steam PC games on a 5-inch screen or via an HDMI cable on a television screen. Nvidia will make and sell this system itself, turning its traditional partners into competitors. It’s a bold move — the kind that Microsoft made when it decided to move beyond software into hardware. It happens when a company has either been disrupted or plans to disrupt others. The pros in this case outweigh the cons, but Nvidia will have to make a lot of trade-offs as it enters this market. The $60 console-game companies haven’t embraced free to play or cloud technology in a big way. Nvidia needs more exclusive content to launch its machine successfully. Android and Steam games alone may not be big sellers. Deciding to move into integrated hardware is not something that a component maker does lightly. Nvidia will be competing with companies that are or could be its potential customers or partners, like Sony, Nintendo, and Microsoft. Those customers won’t be happy. It’s not the kind of move you want to make out of weakness. Microsoft has tried to move into tablets for years, and it finally made its own Microsoft Surface tablets with the debut of Windows 8. But that move seems defensive — made out of weakness in the face of competition against Apple. Nvidia has pretty much lost out to Advanced Micro Devices in the race to supply chips to next-generation consoles. In that respect, Nvidia has made this business decision from a weak position, too, but it also has nothing to lose. Nvidia has probably lost some trust among its partners and customers. How do they know that Nvidia won’t compete head-on with them? The tough challenge for Nvidia will be marketing since it has very little elbow room in a crowded market. Rivals such as PowerA (the maker of the Moga controller) and Green Throttle Games (the creator of an upcoming Android game controller) will be selling their products for a lot less. How will Nvidia convince customers to pay a lot more for its device? JJ Richards, the head of marketing on PowerA’s Moga mobile-gaming controller marketing team, doesn’t think adding the screen to a controller will add much value, and he notes that it entails a lot of cost. The challenge is that Nvidia is going into areas where it has little experience, such as mass-market customer support and heavy-duty marketing. Nvidia also lacks the kind of design expertise that makes consumers lust after a new tech product. Some observers have reacted with disdain to the system’s design and wondered why it has a tablet that can’t be detached. If Nvidia gets one aspect of the design wrong, you can bet a competitor will get it right. One of the key features of Tegra 4 is its support for 4K video and 4K games. But there is very little 4K content out there. This feature adds costs, but it may not gain any new customers for Nvidia. Anand Shimpi, the head of tech analysis site Anandtech, said... he isn’t so sure that Android developers are up to the challenge of producing mobile games that people really want to play on a TV. And if there is no killer content for Nvidia, then the Project Shield system will fail. And what about the fact that the system can play titles from Valve’s Steam digital distribution service? Valve itself is expected to launch its own Linux-based open game console, dubbed the Steam Box. If that box takes off... at some point, Valve’s success means Nvidia’s failure. What we still need to know. ■ If Nvidia has to price the machine higher because of the high costs of components such as the Tegra 4, will it be trampled by other general-purpose mobile devices, such as those that Google and Apple are making? ■ Will Nvidia have to subsidize hardware costs by pricing the machine low?" Jen's toy Shield sounds like a scratch, boys. An expensive, desperate, egotistical attempt by Jen to purport that nvidia is still IN the gaming console business. When they're not. Having lost the Sony PlayStation®, the Nintendo Wii U®, and Microsoft's Xbox® to AMD's superior graphics processors.</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1358101515066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 13:25:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>27</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358102406745-17</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is taking big risks moving into game hardware. Is it crazy or genius?</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358098512783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 12:35:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This article gets a number of things wrong. " Agree...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358102406745</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 13:40:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358102582578-18</Id><Title>NVIDIA Project SHIELD extended talk with Nick Stam</Title><Msg>Less than 4 minute video on youtube that shows what Project Shield is all about You can skip the add in front. youtubeDOTcom/watch?v=Dbj0TYhSYWQ</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358102582578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 13:43:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358104054597-19</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is taking big risks moving into game hardware. Is it crazy or genius?</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358098512783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 12:35:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? Jen lost 100% of the next generation gaming consoles, right? He lost the next generation Sony PlayStation® He lost the next generation Nintendo Wii U® He lost the next generation Microsoft's Xbox® And there aren't any more to lose. Because that's 100% of the global gaming console industry. And the gaming console industry has sailed without nvidia graphics on board. So Best? Will nvidia shareholders be left stranded on their tiny little island? With nobody to talk to but Wilson the volleyball. Well that, and read ibbey's little fluff pieces about nvidia every day. Making nvidia sound like some Tahiti vacation spot or something. When it clearly isn't. Oh no no no. The folks stuck on nvidia know the Truth. Nvidia. It's a sad little desert island. Without any game consoles.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1358104054597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 14:07:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358105122992-20</Id><Topic><Title>Value Uncovered1.</Title><Username>jobe1098</Username><Timestamp>1358095705141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:48:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what's wrong with 10% profit ?</Msg><Username>mapp78</Username><Timestamp>1358105122992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 14:25:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358106784843-21</Id><Title>The market voted on that SHIELD toy announcement, results to the right in that weekly chart</Title><Msg>Can you read a chart? What does the weekly chart for Nvidia say after that SHIELD toy show and tell in Vegas? You can't spin the markets ugly reaction to that SHIELD toy on a message board. Nvidia's SHIELD toy did not impress the street no matter how much phony praise you pile on a CES show and tell for an unfinished developement project. Who wants to walk around with a smart phone (which can play games), a tablet (which can play games), an Ultrathin notebook (which can play games) and some dedicated toy gadget in your pocket which just plays games and is NOT posting Nvidia love notes on this board by the pound everyday? lol Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358106784843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 14:53:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358107326040-22</Id><Topic><Title>Value Uncovered1.</Title><Username>jobe1098</Username><Timestamp>1358095705141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:48:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try 30%, 10%, and 20%, all in an average of 3 months hold. Works out to be 20% on average in 3 months. That's an annualized 80% gain. Scowl all you want, but it works for me. With NVDA, I see it retracing to the low to mid 13s based on technicals alone. Any good news will only add to that gain. The downside, about .75/share. The risk reward, from the metrics I run, are about 3.5 to 1 over a 2 to 3 month hold period. Jobe</Msg><Username>jobe1098</Username><Timestamp>1358107326040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 15:02:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358110263924-23</Id><Topic><Title>The market voted on that SHIELD toy announcement, results to the right in that weekly chart</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358106784843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 14:53:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Geez Best, You mean that toy Shield doesn't even have a phone in it? Just a tiny 5" screen for playing games. Why, that's ridiculous. Yes boys, Ridiculous. EVERY phone on the planet can play games today. It's like standard, right? It sure is. On each and every Genuine Apple iPhone -- or even those android knock-off phones. Yet ET can't call home on his toy Shield? Jen's phoneless toy Shield -- It will be a Fail of Epic Proportions.</Msg><Username>geez.best</Username><Timestamp>1358110263924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 15:51:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358110992411-24</Id><Topic><Title>Vegas was Expensive, boys. NVDA leaves town (-$581 million) Poorer.</Title><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1357962660131</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 22:51:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Vegas was Expensive, boys. NVDA leaves town (-$581 million) Poorer." Is that it? Nvidia fans know exactly what happeed last week and now all attention is on this week? Is "(-$581 million)" all this markets wants back from Nvidia for that SHIELD show and tell fiasco in Vegas? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358110992411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:03:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358112405669-25</Id><Title>It certainly is a new way to play games with shareholder money?</Title><Msg>Are Nvidia shareholders taking all he risk while Nvidia management is coming up with new ways to play games with investors money? lol Isn't that what SHIELD is, a new way to play games? And who's paying to bring this new gadget to market? Did you ever think, that when Nvidia management poured over all the ways to increase revenue and grow the business that they'd go with a suggestion often found in suggestions boxes at companies around the globe. "More vcacation time", "An extra hour for lunch", "Play games at work", Free candy and soda machines And the winner is? lol Enjoy your Nvidia purchase. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358112405669</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:26:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358112831321-26</Id><Topic><Title>It certainly is a new way to play games with shareholder money?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358112405669</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:26:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone know how they'll test a new game console to make sure all the games play properly? It must take a long time and be really hard work if they're still testing it right? It's a tough job but someone has to do it. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358112831321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:33:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358113088367-27</Id><Topic><Title>It certainly is a new way to play games with shareholder money?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358112405669</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:26:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>May I say your posts are extra stupid today.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1358113088367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:38:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358113135825-28</Id><Topic><Title>It certainly is a new way to play games with shareholder money?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358112405669</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:26:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>times for you medicine and afternoon nap.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1358113135825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:38:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358113221880-29</Id><Topic><Title>The market voted on that SHIELD toy announcement, results to the right in that weekly chart</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358106784843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 14:53:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another bash-boy stuck on stupid today!</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1358113221880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:40:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358114026969-30</Id><Topic><Title>Hardware specs comparison: Project Shield vs competing devices</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358051173266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:26:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good one!</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1358114026969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:53:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358114134959-31</Id><Topic><Title>Value Uncovered1.</Title><Username>jobe1098</Username><Timestamp>1358095705141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:48:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please, don't use a word "invest" for your week long trades.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1358114134959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:55:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358118896956-32</Id><Title>Just in boys. Next generation iPads and IPad Minis coming in March.</Title><Msg>Rumor: Fifth-gen iPad, second-gen iPad mini to debut in March Apple Insider | Friday, January 11, 2013, 10:13 am By Neil Hughes Apple's iPad lineup is now on a twice-a-year refresh cycle, according to a new rumor, which pegs both the full-size iPad and iPad mini as due for updates in March. Brian White of Topeka Capital Markets said his checks with industry sources at this week's CES event in Las Vegas, Nev., indicated both the fifth-generation iPad and second-generation iPad mini will debut this March, just five months after the last update was announced. White was told that the new "iPad 5" will be lighter and thinner than the fourth-generation model Apple released late last year. The updated model features a new A6X processor and Apple's smaller Lightning chip but maintained the same design as the third-generation iPad released last March. As for the iPad mini, White said the second-generation device is expected to have the same form factor. A new model would likely just have upgraded components, such as a faster chip. No mention was made of a potential high-resolution Retina display in a new iPad mini. One report from last month claimed Apple was focused on boosting the resolution of the next-generation iPad mini. Though many industry insiders attend CES, Apple does not have an official presence at the annual event. White did not indicate the source of his information aside from unnamed "checks" at the show. White also reported last week that Apple is expected to debut new iPhones this summer in more sizes and colors, expanding the lineup from the current black and white options. He expects the new iPhones to debut in the May-June timeframe, which would be earlier than the last two years. " Looks like those android sales will hit another vacuumn here shortly, boys. As folks anxiously wait to check out all the cool new Apple stuff. Be sure to let the analysts know about the coming vacuumn in android sales, okay? Those guys with the folding pocket hatchets. Did I mention? The new generation Apple iPads and iPad Minis make their debut in March, boys. Like six (6) short weeks from now.</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1358118896956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 18:14:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358119883679-33</Id><Topic><Title>Just in boys. Next generation iPads and IPad Minis coming in March.</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1358118896956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 18:14:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jeepers Best, Twice a year (2X) Upgrades to the Genuine Apple iPad and IPad Minis. Looks like what Jen said about Apple is correct. "Apple does what Apple does and nobody else is going to compete with them." -- Current nvidia CEO Jen Hsun Huang, MobileBeat, March 4, 2011.</Msg><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1358119883679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 18:31:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358123091902-34</Id><Title>Nvidia Retains Lead In Non-Ipad Tablet Application Processor Sales with 1/3rd share</Title><Msg>Global tablet applications processor market showed a robust 77 percent year-on-year growth in Q3 2012 to reach $0.9 billion, according to the Strategy Analytics Handset Component Technologies service report, “Tablet Apps Processor Market Share Q3 2012: NVIDIA Retains Lead in Non-iPad Tablets with One-Third Share.” Based on Strategy Analytics estimates, Apple maintained its lead in the tablet applications processor market with 53 percent revenue share in Q3 2012. NVIDIA, Texas Instruments, Qualcomm and Samsung made up the rest of the top-five vendors. According to Sravan Kundojjala, Senior Analyst, “NVIDIA led the non-iPad tablet market with one-third unit shipment share in Q3 2012 with the help of its Google Nexus 7 and Microsoft Surface RT design-wins. During the quarter, NVIDIA registered its highest quarterly Tegra tablet processor shipments since the introduction of the Tegra product. Strategy Analytics believes that NVIDIA is well-positioned to maintain its share in non-iPad tablets in the next few quarters.” According to Stuart Robinson, Director of the Strategy Analytics Handset Component Technologies service, “Strategy Analytics estimates that stand-alone applications processors represented about 99 percent of all tablet applications processors shipped in Q3 2012. Baseband-integrated processors have had limited traction so far in tablets and this has affected shipments of integrated vendors such as Qualcomm, Broadcom and MediaTek.” ____________________________________________________________________________________ And This was before Tegra 4! In this context I see where Nvidia is going with Project Shield. Games just look better with Nvidia Geforce GPUs and Tegra processors. Think of it as a Killer App. By the way one of the Game developers that will release a Tegra 4 optimized game with the launch of Project Shield will also launch the game on IOS for Apple. At a higher price Apple than Google Play and without the Physics visual effects because they only work on Nvidia processors. Can't wait for the side by side youtube video comparision. Just about the same time people will be quoting GLbenchmarks...LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358123091902</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 19:24:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358125686631-35</Id><Topic><Title>The market voted on that SHIELD toy announcement, results to the right in that weekly chart</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358106784843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 14:53:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clearly not you...</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358125686631</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:08:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358134135104-36</Id><Topic><Title>Value Uncovered1.</Title><Username>jobe1098</Username><Timestamp>1358095705141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:48:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Generally 2 to 3 months, and it is investing. Really depends on one's perspective. Jobe</Msg><Username>jobe1098</Username><Timestamp>1358134135104</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 22:28:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>