<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-02"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359781963980-1</Id><Title>WSJ: Coping with souring Apple shares....</Title><Msg>As the U.S. stock market flirts with record highs, investors who hold big stakes in Apple Inc. AAPL -0.41% are taking a beating. Since peaking at $705.07 during the day on Sept. 21, Apple shares have fallen 36% to close at $453.62, erasing more than $236 billion in market value—a figure equal to about 35 times the current value of BlackBerry RIM. maker Research In Motion Ltd. The pain has been widespread. About 60% of actively managed U.S. stock mutual funds that invest in big companies owned at least some Apple shares at the end of the year, according to investment-research firm Morningstar Inc. Ninety funds had 10% or more of their portfolios in the stock. But Apple's plunge is affecting investors in different ways. While some are getting out for good, others are staying put or even buying more. And some are glad they avoided the stock altogether. Most mutual funds disclose their holdings quarterly, but the 145 actively managed U.S. stock funds that hold Apple and reported monthly results sold a net 223,402 shares, or 3% of their Apple holdings, in December, according to Morningstar, a time when the stock was between 16% and 28% off its peak. Sixty-one funds sold shares, while 45 funds bought. ..... Here are some examples of how professional money managers and small investors have reacted: • Bailing out. Some investors, feeling burned by the steep drop, are selling their stakes. Frank Sansone, a retired college professor in Pensacola, Fla., bought 40 Apple shares during the first half of last year. As its stock price breached $700 in September, Mr. Sansone said he intended to sell but missed his chance while on vacation. As Apple's stock dropped, he sold most of the shares in November and December, locking in losses of about $2,800. "I left it alone, and it turned out to be a bigger mistake than I ever expected," he said. Among mutual-fund managers, one of the biggest sellers was the $857 million Brandywine Fund, which last quarter dumped its entire Apple stake of more than 143,000 shares, according to Morningstar. In a year-end note to investors, fund manager Bill D'Alonzo cited tightening profit margins, among other worries, as reasons for selling. A spokesman for Friess Associates, which manages the fund, declined to comment. • Staying the course. The $406 million Matthew 25 Fund landed in the top 2% of funds that invest in large, growth companies for each of the past three years, largely because of its huge stake in Apple. As of September, when the fund last disclosed its holdings, Apple comprised 15% of its portfolio. That has come back to bite manager Mark Mulholland. The fund has had a total return of 4.5% this year through Thursday, 0.7 percentage point less than the S&amp;P 500 and in the bottom 41% of its peers, according to Morningstar. "It's been a headache, but not a cancer," Mr. Mulholland said, noting that since November he has fielded a handful of emails and phone calls from investors asking about his Apple stake. • Seeing a cheap stock. John Barr, portfolio manager of the $67 million Needham Aggressive Growth Fund, last quarter bought 100 shares, increasing his stake to 5,350 shares, even though the fund invests mostly in small-capitalization stocks. At the end of the year, Apple was Mr. Barr's fifth-largest holding, with 4.3% of the fund. Mr. Barr said he still believes the stock is cheap and that the company might see hot earnings growth as it introduces new products, such as a rumored cheaper iPhone or television set. Apple's price/earnings multiple based on expected earnings over the next 12 months is eight, compared with 13 for the S&amp;P 500, according to Morningstar. "It's an inexpensive stock that is growing much faster than the market as a whole," he said. "We're happy to own something at a reasonable price." Needham Aggressive Growth, which first bought Apple shares in 2006, has never sold shares, Mr. Barr said. Bob Turner, manager of the $223 million Turner Large Growth fund, said that his firm "would be more buyers than sellers" of Apple; it had about 13% of its portfolio in the stock at the end of 2012, according to Morningstar. Through Thursday, the fund has had a return of 3%, about 2.2 percentage points below that of the S&amp;P 500, according to Morningstar. Given how widely owned the stock is, Mr. Turner, whose fund first bought shares in 2004, said he thinks Apple simply ran out of investors looking to add shares at its peak in September. "What's always befuddled me is valuation," he said, adding "You can be right with your thesis all day, but it doesn't stop you from losing money." • Sitting out. Apple's drop provides some vindication for the few money managers who didn't hold Apple during its bull run and saw their portfolios trail because of it. Robert Zagunis, who co-manages the $4.3 billion Jensen Quality Growth fund, has never owned Apple shares. The fund invests only in companies with a decadelong history of high returns on equity, a test Apple doesn't meet yet. In the last three years through Thursday, the fund has had an average annual return of 12%, 2.5 percentage points lower than the S&amp;P 500, according to Morningstar. Last summer, Mr. Zagunis devoted a note to investors explaining why he didn't hold Apple. "We had times when [much] of the underperformance was due to one stock that we didn't hold," he said in an interview. But when Mr. Zagunis was recently a guest speaker at an investment class at a university, he said, the students showed him a chart of their portfolio, which has performed poorly this year. "They said—it was almost apologetic—'We owned Apple.'"</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359781963980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 00:12:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359782482041-2</Id><Topic><Title>Hope this is true - Tegra 4 in HTC flagship phone M7</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359775628647</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 22:27:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This would be great. However, it is understood that the Tegra 4 chip is just now starting to ramp up production. I'm not sure how any phone launched in March can house the chip. Obviously, if enough of the chips were ready for this launch and HTC was one of the reasons they ramped up the production and R&amp;D costs last quarter, that would bode very well for what's ahead as the new chip gets into full production. All the more reason an article like the one from Digitimes is premature which allows some of the clowns that post on this board to make their predictable &amp; annoying put-downs and gripes.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1359782482041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 00:21:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359784778862-3</Id><Topic><Title>Just correcting the record.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1280115788000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2010-07-25 23:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if they eeever;;; let me out of this ƒlemish shed.., i plan ( √ ) to get drunk ignorantly drunk _Ÿ_ and pretend to bee a goldman analyst again.,/</Msg><Username>daysinshed30</Username><Timestamp>1359784778862</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 00:59:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359803501668-4</Id><Topic><Title>Why Nvidia pushing tablets while QCOM is pushing Nvidia out of Surface? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359772129472</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:28:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think everybody would rather laugh at you.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1359803501668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 06:11:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359806677479-5</Id><Topic><Title>Just correcting the record.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1280115788000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2010-07-25 23:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you correct your spelling while you are at it numb-nuts.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1359806677479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:04:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359816594251-6</Id><Topic><Title>IDC just released Q4 tablet shipment data: total shipment 52.5 million units, 75% y/y increase, 74% q/q increase</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359684675590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 21:11:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow, full 70% of the tablet market is not accessible to Tegra.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359816594251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:49:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359816835843-7</Id><Topic><Title>ASUS and Google working on next-gen Nexus 7 (Key Lime Pie and Tegra 4 on board?)</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359589011660</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:36:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>qcom accidentally showed off a road map with key lime pie and krait. you can take this one, and not digitime, to the bank. no nexus 7, longs care to predict the size of the tegra quarterly loses? pls?</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359816835843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:53:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359817129611-8</Id><Title>aapl to stop making processors</Title><Msg>seekingalpha if some nothing tech writer is predicting aapl will stop making processors because they don't have enough cheap radios to integrate with, how long do you think the sell side will start demanding the same for nvda to get out of Tegra?</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359817129611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:58:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359823559266-9</Id><Title>Robeco Investment Management, Inc. Must Like The Dividend - Adds 6 million shares</Title><Msg>Institutional Value Management added 6,139,523 shares in 4Q. Now 8,041,269 shares. And we all know Blackrock doubled it's stake in Nvidia to 32M+ shares in Q4 for 5.15% stake in the company. Source: NasdaqDotcom</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359823559266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 11:45:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359828181466-10</Id><Topic><Title>aapl to stop making processors</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359817129611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:58:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMG !!!!!!!!!! "some nothing tech writer is predicting" too much crow has gone to your head...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359828181466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:03:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359829049006-11</Id><Title>NVDA to 20/-</Title><Msg>Believe it or not Nvda will be $20/- end of this year. Good luck longs</Msg><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1359829049006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:17:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359829089495-12</Id><Topic><Title>Do you think Sony already ended its PS3 GPU orders from Nvidia to ready PS4?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359755047850</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:44:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. The new order will be with AMD. This is a huge loss for NVDA.</Msg><Username>yuorbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1359829089495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:18:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359829174491-13</Id><Topic><Title>Why no game console business for Tegra 4 if its so good at playing games?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359739773522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:29:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because AMD can do it better, faster and cheaper. A huge loss of Nvidia</Msg><Username>yuorbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1359829174491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:19:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359829228385-14</Id><Topic><Title>Sony to unveil PS3 successor amidst video industry slump and concern about AMD chip compatibility</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359751159315</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:39:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A huge blow to Nvidia.</Msg><Username>yuorbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1359829228385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:20:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359829324979-15</Id><Title>Look for Nvidia to miss estimates.</Title><Msg>Larger losses than expected is coming.</Msg><Username>yuorbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1359829324979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:22:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359829453480-16</Id><Title>Look for a strong turn south come earnings.</Title><Msg>The market is due for a pull back about the same time NVDA will be reporting. The market will drop about 5% and then NVDA will have a poor report and slide further south. NVDA will get hit twice as hard.</Msg><Username>yuorbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1359829453480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:24:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359830897387-17</Id><Title>Must be why analysts are raising estimates</Title><Msg>in the last 7 days/yahoo</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1359830897387</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:48:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359831010841-18</Id><Title>NVDA Q4 earrings release date Feb 13</Title><Msg>Why did nvidia moved its Q4 earnings release date from 2/14 to 2/13? Ominous sign to competitors or to investors?</Msg><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1359831010841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:50:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359831505136-19</Id><Topic><Title>IDC just released Q4 tablet shipment data: total shipment 52.5 million units, 75% y/y increase, 74% q/q increase</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359684675590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 21:11:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A year ago, 90% of the tablet market was not accessible by NVIDIA....so there's been big progresss. For your education, a separate study reported that NVIDIA had 19% of tablet market. 19-20% percent of a big pie is a big slice for a median-size company like NVIDIA. Where is the BRCM in this? Hmmm? Cheap quality/cheap price didn't help much, did they? As for you: cheap talk and cheap shots didn't get you very far, did they?</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359831505136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:58:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359833308293-20</Id><Title>AMD Top End Gamer Card Is Almost Free--$157.00. Nvidia Top Card Still $499.99</Title><Msg>XFX Radeon HD 7970 3GB DDR5 Video Card and SLEEPING DOGS/HITMAN/FAR CRY 3 and 20 % Off MEDAL OF HONOR COUPON BundleItem#: P450-7976 GAME4 | Model#: FX797ATDFC Bundle ADD EXTRA PROTECTION with SquareTrade Warranty Learn More SquareTrade 2-Year Electronics Warranty $34.98 SquareTrade 3-Year Electronics Warranty $53.98 List Price: $429.99 Instant Savings: - $50.00 (12%) Price: $379.99 Less Rebate: - $30.00 Final Price - $349.99 Ends 02/15/2013. See Terms. Restrictions Apply. NOTICE: Limit (2) TWO rebates per person, billing address, company, or household _____________________________________________________________________________ OK let's do the math - 3 free $60 Games, + 20% of 1 $60 Game AMD 7979 Price $349.00 - $192.00 = $157.00 Same site Nvidia GTX 680 Goes for $499.00 with no game bundle How can they sell their GPUs at 1/3rd the price of Nvidia cards when their die size is 20% larger than Nvidia's? CONCLUSION - AMD IS EXITING THE GAMER GPU BUSINESS FOR SURE! Source: TigerDirect</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359833308293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 14:28:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359836886625-21</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Top End Gamer Card Is Almost Free--$157.00. Nvidia Top Card Still $499.99</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359833308293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 14:28:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"OK let's do the math - 3 free $60 Games, + 20% of 1 $60 Game AMD 7979 Price $349.00 - $192.00 = $157.00" You can't stop making up NONSENSE can you? The card list for $429.99 and if you place it in your cart you can't check out until they charge you credit card $379.99 PLUS shipping. $379.99 PLUS shipping to your dump is what they'll charge your credit card NOT $179.99. That offer is ONLY good until 2/15/13 and $379.99 out of your pocket ain't "Almost Free" BTW the same site list the GTX 680 for $424.99 or $5 less than the 7970 card you listed if you bothered to look. "EVGA GeForce GTX 680 FTW LE 2GB GDDR5 Video Card $424.99*" One of many 7970 cards on that site is running a special. Conclusion CLUELESS giberish again. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359836886625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 15:28:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359837304381-22</Id><Topic><Title>Took My Profits</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1311623376000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-07-25 15:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Took My Profits" "Could be wrong but don't like it when 5 figure profits evaporate. Happened too many times before." Looks like he want out again. Posting all sorts of pumping NONSENSE so he can dump. Did you see his post begging Jen to buy his shares and take Nvidia private and begging Jen for a dividend increase? Someone is restless holding junk going nowhere and wants a qucik pay day so he can post another "Took My Profits" gem. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359837304381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 15:35:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359838350402-23</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Top End Gamer Card Is Almost Free--$157.00. Nvidia Top Card Still $499.99</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359833308293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 14:28:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>XC, I know your a AMD Fanboi from way back when and frankly those prices for AMD gamer cards are phenomenal, but I recommend you buy the 3rd party warranty when buying. We just finished the Fall, and then the Winter AMD layoffs but rumor has the Spring layoffs will hit the discrete Gamer GPU cards very hard. Something about minimum cash...I couldn't quite understand Rory when he talking. LOL I'm thinking this might be the end of life sale for ATI so you want the 3rd party warranty for sure. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359838350402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 15:52:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359838822607-24</Id><Topic><Title>Little guys selling....</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1272554019000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2010-04-29 11:13:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I had an order in at open for mid-xxxx shares at $16.01. Amazingly! When the confirmations came in, there were nearly ALL 100 share trades and some 50 shares trades too - so there were over 40 conformations. Never seen anything like this. Retail shorts are playing with their lunch money. Either that or the big shorts tried to walk down the tick with zillions of small trades. WS professionals always regard retail sell as one of the most reliable bullish signs." If you PAY over $16 you too could end up pumping Nvidia on a message EVERYDAY trying to break even. BTW Nvidia dropped to $8s within a few months after he paid over $16 so he could have had twice and many shares for what he paid. Little guy got the better of that deal. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359838822607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:00:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359839355672-25</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Top End Gamer Card Is Almost Free--$157.00. Nvidia Top Card Still $499.99</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359833308293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 14:28:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you try buying one for $157.00? Stop the NONSENSE. the 7970 can't be had for $157.00 . BTW TigerDirect is selling the XFX card not AMD. The $429.99 less $50 instant rebate is between TigerDirect and the $379.99 charge on anyones credit card that wants one. AMD already SOLD XFX a GPU chip. XFX and TigerDirect can sell the card for whatever and with any software they want. You seem confused about who is selling what? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359839355672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:09:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359840112478-26</Id><Topic><Title>Little guys selling....</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1272554019000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2010-04-29 11:13:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was just visiting this message board for a bit and was curious who would bother to post anything here at this point, and of course it would be one of the posters, xc3155, that seems to base everything he says on a long held grudge against Nvidia for what they did to AMD. Really, you need to post here and cling onto some thread that is WAY past any relevance to the current state of Nvidia (and AMD as well actually)? How sad is it that you are like one of maybe a few posters even bothering to write anything on this thread, desperate for attention. Back to the ignore list you go . . no need to reply, but I'm sure you will.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1359840112478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:21:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359841536044-27</Id><Topic><Title>Check Out Dell - Jensen Take us Private!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359727148564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:59:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Jensen Take us Private!" How many times are you going to beg Jen to get you out of your Nvidia shares? What happen to all that nonsense you've been posting about Nvidia going higher? If Jen did what you keep begging him to do it wouldn't even trade. I guess you don't believe your own pumping gerberish, do you? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359841536044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:45:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359841940226-28</Id><Title>any chance project denver might show up in the new playstation?</Title><Msg>i wouldn't be totally stunned if sony went with an amd gpu for the next playstation. I would be shocked and awed, however, if the cpu were amd's or anything close to an x86 chip. it would seem to me to make absolutely no sense whatsoever for sony to take its playstation line down that road, which leads me to the question of what is actually in there. sony has cozied up to android with its playstation certified program, and its vita handheld is an ARM variant. wouldn't it make a heap more sense to go with something like project denver as a cpu than really anything else rumored or currently out there?</Msg><Username>hydroponic_tomatoes</Username><Timestamp>1359841940226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:52:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359842110525-29</Id><Topic><Title>Jews, they create problems, then drag you into them.</Title><Username>dean_martin_17</Username><Timestamp>1359696104732</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 00:21:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you find it necessary to make such obnoxious and stupid comments?</Msg><Username>rlday2010</Username><Timestamp>1359842110525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:55:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359842866477-30</Id><Title>Nvidia has to have its own phone, tablet, game tablet.. No one else</Title><Msg>has any use for the power hog tegra4.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359842866477</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:07:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359842937915-31</Id><Title>Has AMD started a price war with Nvidia on high end graphics cards?</Title><Msg>If so, Nvidia is in deep doo doo.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359842937915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:08:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359843968345-32</Id><Topic><Title>Has AMD started a price war with Nvidia on high end graphics cards?</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359842937915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:08:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's all AMD has left to do... DESPERATE !!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359843968345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:26:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359844082794-33</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia has to have its own phone, tablet, game tablet.. No one else</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359842866477</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:07:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much power does Tegra 4 use ?? Or you have NO CLUE... NONE !!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359844082794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:28:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359844379604-34</Id><Topic><Title>any chance project denver might show up in the new playstation?</Title><Username>hydroponic_tomatoes</Username><Timestamp>1359841940226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:52:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>probably not...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359844379604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:32:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359844659923-35</Id><Topic><Title>any chance project denver might show up in the new playstation?</Title><Username>hydroponic_tomatoes</Username><Timestamp>1359841940226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:52:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"any chance project denver might show up in the new playstation?" No. That's why its called "project denver". Its a project today not a product. Google the aritcle title below and catch up on current events "Sony sparks expectation of PS4 launch on February 20" imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359844659923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:37:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359845399708-36</Id><Title>Does AMD Have A Take It Or Pay Agreement With TSMC</Title><Msg>If so that would explain why they are selling off their discrete GPU inventory almost free prices. Too bad they won't work with Project Shield.They are so cheap even I would buy one Now. 3 games and 20% off on another for mid $350's when they came out at $549 with no games bundled. Oh if only they had shrunk the die...352 sq. mm vs. 294 for Nvidia's GTX 680. By way Nvidia is still holding to their introductory price of $499 from a year ago. Rory said they would raise cash. Apparently selling their buildings wan't enough. Now they are selling off their channel inventory at pennies on the dollar. LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359845399708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:49:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359846063802-37</Id><Topic><Title>Took My Profits</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1311623376000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-07-25 15:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"In Nvidia, AMD, and Intc. Just don't like this ballyhoo in Washington right now. See you next week. Could be wrong but don't like it when 5 figure profits evaporate. Happened too many times before." Why are you working so hard throwing up bashing NONSENSE about QCOM, TSMC, AMD, Apple and Intel while begging Jen for dividend increases and a buyout? How much is your Nvidia under water? No "Took My Profits" post this time around, hmm? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359846063802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 18:01:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359846342420-38</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Top End Gamer Card Is Almost Free--$157.00. Nvidia Top Card Still $499.99</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359833308293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 14:28:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Did you try buying one for $157.00? Stop the NONSENSE. the 7970 can't be had for $157.00 . BTW TigerDirect is selling the XFX card not AMD. The $429.99 less $50 instant rebate is between TigerDirect and the $379.99 charge on anyones credit card that wants one." Catch you MAKING UP STUFF and off to a new thread right? lol Come on, you know that no one is paying $157.00 for an XFX 7970 card at TigerDirect, you just like making up NONSENSE, right? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359846342420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 18:05:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359846674364-39</Id><Topic><Title>Does AMD Have A Take It Or Pay Agreement With TSMC</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359845399708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:49:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Almost free is good, but who will provide driver updates on the almost free AMD gamer cards if in fact Rory is leaving the business? I'm not knocking what Rory is doing downsizing to embedded and semi custom only semiconductors. It's the only thing they can do to stay in business. Sans another 5000 employees in the spring. Fitch did downgrade their Debt to Junk one step above Default Friday. Nvidia is wise to not match AMD in prices as they spiral towards Default. Let Intel do it....they have destroyed whatever CPU and APU sales AMD could hope to get. Only $400M left in cash before default XC.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359846674364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 18:11:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359851892584-40</Id><Title>Why China Allowing Gaming Consoles Won't Help Game Makers</Title><Msg>What's that you say? A completely untapped gaming market! A billion people? Do you think anyone would...? Seems Jen may have the pulse of the world.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1359851892584</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 19:38:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359854969512-41</Id><Topic><Title>Why China Allowing Gaming Consoles Won't Help Game Makers</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1359851892584</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 19:38:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice flip there . . . or bait and switch I s'pose.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1359854969512</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 20:29:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359856327267-42</Id><Title>SONY fighting the relevancy of the console?</Title><Msg>Is this because of NVDA?</Msg><Username>steelingmoney</Username><Timestamp>1359856327267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 20:52:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359858084804-43</Id><Topic><Title>(((AMD lands the new Wii, SP4 &amp; Xbox)))</Title><Username>keeperoftheq</Username><Timestamp>1357148663090</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:44:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"That does not look good for NVDA." So what does Nvidia do to save face? Errect a SHIELD toy to block out the fact that their high profile Play Station job is gone. And the market promptly took Nvidia's stock down from $13.15 after that SHIELD show and tell fiasco in Vegas. SHIELD is one dumb idea, watch as it fades away like all dumb ideas. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359858084804</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 21:21:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359858799320-44</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia struggles to convince vendors to adopt Tegra 4</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359741312994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:55:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Consumers will not see a lot of Nvidia Tegra 4-based smartphones and tablets in the later part of 2013, according to reports out of Taiwan." ... "Toshiba is the only vendor, thus far, to confirm the launch of Tegra 4-based tablets some time in mid-2013." Just one "thus far"? But whos counting right? lol</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359858799320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 21:33:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359864931823-45</Id><Title>Toms hardware: "Toshiba Currently the Only One to Adopt Tegra 4?"</Title><Msg>"Sources seem to be jumping the gun a bit, saying Tegra 4 is slow to attract tablet and smartphone makers. The usual suspects cited by the oh-so-spotty DigiTimes report that Toshiba is currently the only tablet and smartphone vendor to sign up for Nvidia's Tegra 4 SoC. Of course, the chip was only revealed less than a month ago at CES 2013, and it won't officially launch until June 2013, so there's still time for device makers to jump on the Tegra 4 bandwagon. But sources appear to think the seemingly slow adoption rate has something to do with competing quad-core platforms developed by Qualcomm, MediaTek and China-based IC design houses. Sources plead their case by pointing to Asus and Acer which have thus far been aggressive in the tablet sector. Both have reportedly not yet decided whether to place Tegra 4 orders with Nvidia due to a possible shift in focus from 10-inch form factors and above to the cheaper, seemingly more popular 7-inch entry-level market. On the smartphone front, Qualcomm's close ties with Asus will likely prevent the latter company from choosing Team Nvidia. Sources said Asus will continue steering on the same lucrative Qualcomm-tainted path while setting Tegra 4 aside as a backup solution. Sources added that in order to regain its momentum, Nvidia may reduce the price of its current Tegra 3 chip to attract entry-level orders from brand vendors. But even with a reduced price, Tegra 3 may not be able to compete in price with solutions from MediaTek and China-based IC design houses, they said."</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359864931823</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:15:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359866488121-46</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Q4 earrings release date Feb 13</Title><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1359831010841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:50:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All three models, covering high end, mid range, low end, are reportedly carrying Snapdragons. tech2.inDOTcom/news/smartphones/htc-m7-shown-off-by-ceo-peter-chou-details-of-m4-and-g2-leaked/733522</Msg><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1359866488121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:41:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359866940171-47</Id><Title>HTC M7 shown off by CEO, Details of M4 and G2 leaked</Title><Msg>tech2.inDOTcom/news/smartphones/htc-m7-shown-off-by-ceo-peter-chou-details-of-m4-and-g2-leaked/733522 All three devices are reportedly sporting snapdragon processors.</Msg><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1359866940171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:49:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359867161010-48</Id><Topic><Title>HTC M7 shown off by CEO, Details of M4 and G2 leaked</Title><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1359866940171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:49:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NVIDIA needs white label phones badly!</Msg><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1359867161010</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:52:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>