<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365943456933-1</Id><Topic><Title>loss of nexus overblown</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1365908733890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 23:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As long as Tim Cook is at the helm, it would be a bad idea for NVIDIA to be acquired or merged with Apple. I wouldn't want to see it happen I could see worse matchups. Coming to find Jen may have the vision Cook may not have. Good time in Apples stock valuation to be bought out. We don't need it though and I agree we have a brighter future going alone.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1365943456933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 08:44:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365945499038-2</Id><Topic><Title>Apple should buy nvidia</Title><Username>njrocker26</Username><Timestamp>1365875815693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:56:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's highly unlikely that Nvidia would be acquired or merged with Apple for various reasons. Apple using Tegra in the future is likely and would be a very welcome and substantial contributor to the bottom line. Being long-term in Nvidia the future has never looked more promising.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1365945499038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 09:18:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365949631518-3</Id><Title>IMO, it seems that xc3155 and ibexx are paid bashers or large shorts. Must be paid by the negative posts they can put out.</Title><Msg>They simply work to hard to be ordinary disappointed investors. JMHO</Msg><Username>dyk742000</Username><Timestamp>1365949631518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 10:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365950406037-4</Id><Topic><Title>IMO, it seems that xc3155 and ibexx are paid bashers or large shorts. Must be paid by the negative posts they can put out.</Title><Username>dyk742000</Username><Timestamp>1365949631518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 10:27:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just reported you to Yahoo police for abuse and personal harassment. Your stupidity is self evident by calling me a NVIDIA basher! The regular board attendees are gonna have the biggest laugh of their lives! No more words needed.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365950406037</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 10:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365951897102-5</Id><Topic><Title>loss of nexus overblown</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1365908733890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 23:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These product cycles are short, and fierce. Missing one design isn't going to kill you :)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1365951897102</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 11:04:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365953006692-6</Id><Topic><Title>loss of nexus overblown</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1365908733890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 23:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nope, not overblown at all, after all, that is the only 1 design that is of has any run rate to speak off. Losing the socket that accounted for what 50% ti 60% of last year's sales? Nope, nothing to it at all. Top 2 names of mobile totally out of reach. #3 is cheap only. #4 is into spreading the wealth. The high end app market is really no high end app proc market - the market nvda targeted. A non existing market. Good luck and god bless, you'll need a whole lot more than that. How do you model the Tegras?</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1365953006692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 11:23:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365957131923-7</Id><Topic><Title>loss of nexus overblown</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1365908733890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 23:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How do you model the Tegras?" About flat Y/Y, as per analyst day.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1365957131923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 12:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365967637346-8</Id><Topic><Title>Any rumor who will roll out gadgets w/ T4i this summer</Title><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1365870059897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 12:20:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the info out, it has undergone certification for AT&amp;T’s, and NVDA is working to certify this with other LTE carriers.</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1365967637346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 15:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365974278758-9</Id><Topic><Title>Who is killing the PC? Blame the cloud,,</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365828292436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:44:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry. i can't blame the cloud for this. all those tablets that have made surfing the web, checking email, staying in touch with friends/family, etc. are the main culprits here. the fact that they can use the cloud in certain applications helps, but it's that touch screen user interface that's simple enough a monkey can use it, that's killing the pc. on top of that, microsoft's rolling out a bizarro, sesame street inspired live tile driven, craptastic operating system windows 8 is the straw that finally breaks the camel's back, or in this case, what makes most ppl buy smartphone or tablet instead of a pc. this, however, is just one man's opinion.</Msg><Username>hydroponic_tomatoes</Username><Timestamp>1365974278758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 17:17:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365978776625-10</Id><Title>Has Jensen seen the light and is killing off tegra? With competition like Rockchip</Title><Msg>mediatek and Allwinner selling $10 chips, tegra just can't compete. Flat sales, in an fast growing market for tegra means its dead.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1365978776625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 18:32:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365995238411-11</Id><Title>xbitlabs: Kepler and Maxwell graphics architecture will change the game on the mobile market</Title><Msg>Nvidia Expects GPGPU Capabilities to Substantially Alter Landscape of Mobile SoC Market [04/14/2013 02:34 PM] by Anton Shilov Nvidia Corp. expects a revolution to happen on the market of mobile devices once it launches its application processors with Kepler and Maxwell graphics cores. The latter are designed both for graphics processing and computing in general. Nvidia believes that GPGPU capabilities will help its Tegra series of chips to change the game on the mobile market. “Not only then will you see this first Logan being the first case of an integrated Kepler in a mobile device, allowing you to do what you saw on the Kayla system earlier, […] but you will see a whole family of products over time. This will allow us to take our advantage of GPUs across the entire spectrum. […] Being able to take that [GPGPU] competitiveness and have this weapon of the visual computing that comes from our GeForce, Kepler GPU and just follow on Maxwell is key to our ability to really change the game for people,” said Philip J. Carmack, senior vice president of mobile business unit at Nvidia, at Nvidia’s annual investor day conference, reports Seeking Alpha web-site. Nvidia’s next-gen Tegra 5, code-named Logan and due in 2014, will feature ARM Cortex general-purpose processing units as well as Kepler graphics processing unit with support for GPU computing, Direct3D, OpenGL 4.3 and so on. With a graphics processor capable of general-purpose processing on GPU, Nvidia will offer a breakthrough in performance and capabilities. (to be continued)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365995238411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 23:07:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>