<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359179302598-1</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P closes above 1500 for the first time in five years...</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359151436882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:03:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point, Best. Let's say that the S&amp;P 500 was just one stock. Rather than the average of 500 different Good Stocks. With the S&amp;P 500 hitting a new Five (5) year high, by definition, there are no bagholders. Nope. None. It would be a bagholder-free stock. 'Cause EVERYBODY that bought the stock in the past 5 years would be in-the-money. And EVERYBODY could freely -- and profitably -- sell anytime they wanted. Anytime. Compare that to nvidia, which is now selling for Less than Half of it's Five (5) year high of $26.85 So many many bagholders here who would like to unload their nvidia -- but just can't afford to take the Loss. So many many bagholders. All those folks that bought nvidia at, $26.00 $25.00 $24.00 $23.00 $22.00 $21.00 $20.00 $19.00 $18.00 $17.00 Mister $16.01 with xx,xxx nvidia shares. $15.00 $14.00 $13.00 None of those folks have the Freedom to sell their nvidia at any time they want, without taking a BIG LOSS. And they don't like it. Nope. Not one damn bit. So the only thing they can do is come to the Yahoo! Finance nvda message board, and try their hand at talkin' the stock back to close to where they overpaid for it. Which explains why this board has so many desperate posters. Well, okay. One particularly desperate bagholder here also posts over on the seeking.alpha board. But the message is always the same. "PLEASE PLEASE BUY NVIDIA" -- so they can finally unload their bad stock on you.</Msg><Username>good_point_best</Username><Timestamp>1359179302598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 00:48:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359208976502-2</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P closes above 1500 for the first time in five years...</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359151436882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:03:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"So while the S&amp;P 500 Index is setting new Five (5) Year highs, your precious nvidia is trading at Less than Half of it's comparable high. There are so many many bagholders here who would like to unload their nvidia -- but just can't afford to take the Loss." Buying nvidia stock is like Hotel California, right? "We are programmed to receive. You can check-in any time you like, But you can never leave! " "We are all just prisoners here, of our own bad choice"</Msg><Username>truly.best</Username><Timestamp>1359208976502</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:02:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359219644643-3</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P closes above 1500 for the first time in five years...</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359151436882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:03:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>amazing... another best alias made it past my IGNORE filter... on IGNORE you go !!!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359219644643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 12:00:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359225743999-4</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcomm job postings: 64-bit ARMv8 designers wanted</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359159381452</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 19:16:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>xbitlabs has this to say about QC entering the ARM servers race: ""ARMv8 is ARM’s 64-bit architecture with special tweaks made for server-class hardware, including ECC (error-correcting code, i think), extended reliability and scalability features for high-performance enterprise applications. The family of ARMv8-compatible cores includes Cortex-A53 designed for low-power use cases and Cortex-A57 designed for performance-hungry applications. Qualcomm is at least the eighth company now known to be working on ARM server SoCs. Others with announced or known plans include AMD, Applied Micro, Cavium, Calxeda, Marvell, Nvidia and Samsung. It is expected that the first generation of 64-bit chips with ARMv8 architecture for serverswill emerge in 2014.""</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359225743999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 13:42:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359229747071-5</Id><Title>If ARM cannot design a chip thats lower power than Intel, what good are their</Title><Msg>server chips with less performance than ATOM. Intel already sells an ATOM server chip for $50. ARM servers are just hype.. No backward compatibility, no power advantage, no price advantage, lower performing. It will an even worse failure than Surface RT, because Server sales are not to people at Best buy.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359229747071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 14:49:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359233843480-6</Id><Topic><Title>If ARM cannot design a chip thats lower power than Intel, what good are their</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359229747071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 14:49:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does intc sell cbips for $15?? Vendors are tired of being bullied by intc after all these years.. gonna have to do alot better than ARM</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1359233843480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 15:57:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359235487927-7</Id><Topic><Title>If ARM cannot design a chip thats lower power than Intel, what good are their</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359229747071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 14:49:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NVIDIA's Project Boulder will run on ARLMv8 instruction set + CUDA cores. It will be a high-performance, low-power SoC (plus SECRET SAUCE) intended for the server market. xbitlab and other reviews say that, even though details are unrevealed as yet, it looks like NV's entry will have significant advantages over the others. Google the subject and read xbitlabs articles. (This website is historically more supportive of AMD products, not NV's, in my years of observation).</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359235487927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 16:24:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359236312809-8</Id><Topic><Title>If ARM cannot design a chip thats lower power than Intel, what good are their</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359229747071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 14:49:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typo correction: should read "ARMv8, not ARLMv8..."</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359236312809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 16:38:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359238092369-9</Id><Topic><Title>If ARM cannot design a chip thats lower power than Intel, what good are their</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359229747071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 14:49:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even though details are unrevealed... LOL. Nvidia's project's are #$%$, like tegra... consumes too much power and runs slow.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359238092369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 17:08:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359239513438-10</Id><Topic><Title>If ARM cannot design a chip thats lower power than Intel, what good are their</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359229747071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 14:49:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The conceptual framework/architectural features are announced. You are on ignore - not worthy of my time or a serious discussion. Bye!</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359239513438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 17:31:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359240495782-11</Id><Topic><Title>If ARM cannot design a chip thats lower power than Intel, what good are their</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359229747071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 14:49:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool... One less idiot to reply to.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359240495782</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 17:48:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359244277706-12</Id><Topic><Title>If ARM cannot design a chip thats lower power than Intel, what good are their</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359229747071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 14:49:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please enlighten the board of all the ultra mobile devices Intel is in? I didn't think so.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1359244277706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 18:51:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359245530677-13</Id><Topic><Title>If ARM cannot design a chip thats lower power than Intel, what good are their</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359229747071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 14:49:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>must be why ARMH is at a 52-week high and INTC is at a 52-week low...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359245530677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:12:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359247447569-14</Id><Title>Boy Nvidia Has Sure Changed!</Title><Msg>Nivida has really changed in the 6 to 9 months. Once it was all about new products, guesses about new products, and articles in the "Tech Press" about the same looking for those ever elusive clicks. Today, NADA absolutely nothing leaking. At CES Nvidia announces a gaming console or portable gaming thing...take your pick and nary a leak appears in the "Tech Press". What has happened? This is serious for those that make their living off Google Adsense. Plus AMD appears to have gone to the mattresses and no new generation GPU cards to write about while we eagerly wait for Nvidia's response...you remember don't you about all the one hand but on the other hand articles. Commentators bitxxxxx about what the gamers have to pay Nvidia and why doesn't Nvidia make Physics open source...etc. etc. Now those same gamers are on the Android gamer websites...still saying the same thing about Nvidia but in a slightly different tone. I'll never pay $400 for the shield and why don't they open it up for those of us that own AMD cards...etc. etc. It's so bad that Charlie on SemiAccurate had to go on a subscription basis to make any money...LOL So what caused this... I can only guess, but Nvidia said what the heck. I'm tired of this Crxx and we'll just talk to people at the appropriate venue's..i.e. CES, MWC, GTC, E3 gamer, etc. But where are we going to get the nect rumor about a smart phone with Tegra 4? How are we going to get the volatility back in this stock, so we can write call and sell put options to make a living. I know, perhaps we can make a product placement with those BOZO's on CNBC. We got to get the volatility back!!!! In the meantime all we got is the old fashioned way.....Earnings and guidance. Good luck all longs. I for one am supremely confident that earnings will beat substantially and guidance will be decent.Of course "decent is in the eye of the beholder of course". Watch those analyst earnings estimates...they are rising...check yahoo finance. Love the Dividend....Don"t you?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359247447569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:44:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359247607917-15</Id><Topic><Title>Boy Nvidia Has Sure Changed!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359247447569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:44:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you actually nailed it yrs ago... NVidia is top heavy... especially on the Tegra team !!! Vice-President is an entry level position on the Tegra team...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359247607917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:46:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359250120218-16</Id><Topic><Title>Boy Nvidia Has Sure Changed!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359247447569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:44:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you actually nailed it yrs ago... "NVidia is top heavy... especially on the Tegra team !!! Vice-President is an entry level position on the Tegra team..." You have heard of grade inflation I'm sure. Well the same thing happened in the Semiconductor industry. Started in the 90's. There are only so many qualified semiconductor people to go around, so companies came up with the idea when recruiting to ask just what title you would like to have. No more responsibility of course or for that matter money, but it does really look good on the resume you know. Well once at a company that I know, the Chief Technical Officer became so incensed about it what was happening during a massive expansion that he went and screamed to high heaven to HR. True story....HR tried to placate by explaining to him the reasoning and how it didn't cost the company anymore money and how helped morale. Well this guy wouldn't have any of it and threatened to quit if the policy wasn't changed. Quickly the CEO was brought into the discussion because this guy was really extremely valuable...much more so than any new hire. The CEO said "OK what can we do to make this right?" The Chief Technical Officer said "If the company is making people Directors when they don't have any people working for them and the company is making people Vice Presidents when they don't have any profit and loss then GDdXXX it I want my title changed to drumroll please.... "Emperor of the Universe". Long story short the company made the change and he proudly walked around and gave everyone he could his fancy business card saying he was "Emperor of The Universe" ________ Corporation at the next company TGIF as he and the CEO got wasted laughing continuously about it.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359250120218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 20:28:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359253329238-17</Id><Title>So where's the Tegra #4 orders?</Title><Msg>It's been a month already. Since Jen launched the non-integrated LTE Tegra #4. And Still no decent orders. None. Even Asus took a pass on the Tegra #4, and will bring their newest Asus Transformer Pad TF300TL 10.1" tablet with the old Tegra #3. Tegra #4 : It's looking like a scratch, boys. A very very Expensive scratch.</Msg><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1359253329238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:22:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359253728904-18</Id><Topic><Title>So where's the Tegra #4 orders?</Title><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1359253329238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:22:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Master? If the Tegra #4 turns out to be the commercial failure it's shaping up to be, maybe the toy Shield could claim "exclusive" use of the Tegra #4. You know. Like the Genuine Apple iPad claims the A6X chip. Exclusively.</Msg><Username>best.clone185</Username><Timestamp>1359253728904</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:28:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359254334116-19</Id><Topic><Title>So where's the Tegra #4 orders?</Title><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1359253329238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:22:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>God bless you .. for all that you are.. you are the BEST.. i mean that</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1359254334116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:38:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359259870454-20</Id><Topic><Title>So where's the Tegra #4 orders?</Title><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1359253329238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:22:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is tegra4 anyway.. Has anyone seen one in the wild?</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359259870454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 23:11:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359260081600-21</Id><Title>Between QCOM, Apple, Samsung the ARM smartphone market is locked up.</Title><Msg>With Microsoft dumping tegra in surface, and many other OEM's like lenovo dumping tegra.. Nvidia is finished in tablets. Hence the SHIELD fiasco. LOL.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359260081600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 23:14:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359261412452-22</Id><Topic><Title>Boy Nvidia Has Sure Changed!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359247447569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:44:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is very surprising how much has changed. Tegra 4 info leaked less than a month before CES, and a major new product, Shield, was launched with no leak. Not a hint. This might signal a new era at Nvidia. Now that they know it's possible, they might do it more often.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1359261412452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 23:36:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359262056229-23</Id><Topic><Title>Absolutely Nothing In The Tech Press About Nvidia</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359131107764</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:25:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm in the same boat. Sux. What I've noticed lately is it appears NVDA is somewhat - unloved in media. When there is the least bit of 'fresh' news on amd - someone really pumps it. qcom is almost always getting good press; even intel - in its doldrums - receives more positives than nvda. and on bloomberg tv - on the tape that loops on the bottom - where the chip names are - nvda isn't. coincidence?? doubt it. So, I wait; impatiently; to sell this to someone for $16. don't hold your breath...........</Msg><Username>tippytappy</Username><Timestamp>1359262056229</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 23:47:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>