<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-09"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370792005500-1</Id><Title>Galaxy S4 (SHV-E330S) Pops up on AnTuTu with a Snapdragon 800</Title><Msg>"" There’s a new version of the Galaxy s4 making the rounds on AnTuTu today. This one has the model number SHV-E330S, and is running Android 4.2.2 like the others, but it’s said to be running the Snapdragon 800 processor and is also said to support LTE-Advanced, according rbmen. Of course the device is not official, and these benchmarks are easily faked, but it’s still interesting nonetheless. The screenshot above shows that the processor is clocked at 2265MHz which is equivalent to 2.3GHz. Keep in mind that the Snapdragon 800 maxes out at 2.3GHz. What is interesting here is that the Snapdragon 800 did not pass the Snapdragon 600 or Exynos 5 Octa Galaxy S4 on the benchmark. In fact it scored lower than both of them."" androidheadlinesDOTcom/2013/06/galaxy-s4-shv-e330s-pops-up-on-antutu-with-a-snapdragon-800.html PS: Tegra 4 scores 36500 consistently in the hands of third party testers as well as NV itself, in public as well as in private.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370792005500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 11:33:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370795119244-2</Id><Topic><Title>Galaxy S4 (SHV-E330S) Pops up on AnTuTu with a Snapdragon 800</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370792005500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 11:33:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gizmodoDOTcoDOTuk/2013/06/hands-on-with-toshibas-new-android-tablets-stunning-specs-but-shocking-design/ Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets: Stunning Specs But Shocking Design June 4, 2013 - 12:30pm Chris Mills "Toshiba’s just launched a trio of new Android Excite tablets, and on paper they look pretty sweet: a budget £250 machine, and a more interesting pair of Tegra 4-powered tablets that are gunning after the high-end Android tablet market, all powered by sweet sweet stock ‘Droid. In the flesh, though, they don’t exactly live up to their promise. In fact, they’re all-round a little disappointing." ...."Battery life is promised at 9.5 hours on all the tablets, though obviously we didn’t have time to verify that. What we can say, though, is that the Tegra 4-packing tablets get uncomfortably hot when you start pushing them, far more so than any other tablet we’ve played with before. All the machines will be available in the UK in Q3, being initially retailed through PC World. To be brutally honest, none of the tablets are really worth the money."</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1370795119244</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:25:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370796106125-3</Id><Topic><Title>Galaxy S4 (SHV-E330S) Pops up on AnTuTu with a Snapdragon 800</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370792005500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 11:33:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There are other rumored devices to be sporting the Snapdragon 800 like the Sony Xperia ZU, Galaxy Note 3, Optimus G2, and the HTC One Max. Since the Snapdragon 800 went into mass production in late May, we should start seeing it in the second half of this year." humm... different corporate goals. nvda goes for the buzz while qcom goes for sales and profits.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1370796106125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:41:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370809707844-4</Id><Title>NBC News: Why Qualcomm lagged this week?</Title><Msg>""Disappointing unit sales (of Galaxy S4) would translate into the sale of fewer Snapdragons, while reducing selling prices of Samsungs would result in lower royalties to Qualcomm. In the meantime, it may be another few months until Apple ramps up new iPhone models carrying Qualcomm baseband modems. Topeka Capital markets also expressed some neutral sentiment, starting coverage on Qualcomm with a "hold" rating and a $65 price target. Topeka analyst Suji De Silva believes Qualcomm has a strong position to capitalize on smartphone trends but that those opportunities are already priced in at current levels. Qualcomm faces competitive risks that could put pressure on margins as smartphone sales progress to emerging markets. Qualcomm has underperformed the market year to date and currently trades at just 17.4 times earnings. ... SOURCE: nbcnewsDOTcom/id/52148227/ns/business-motley_fool/#DOTUbTgVRxbOh8</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370809707844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:28:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370809905822-5</Id><Topic><Title>NBC News: Why Qualcomm lagged this week?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370809707844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:28:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hate to say "I told you so"- bad manners, I know - BUT I DID TELL YOU SO before the web pundits did. Bashers and swing traders (who switched out of NVDA and into QCOM) need not thank me, for I know, in some cases, the inflated ego is proportionally to the dimension of their stupidity.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370809905822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:31:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370810850239-6</Id><Topic><Title>Galaxy S4 (SHV-E330S) Pops up on AnTuTu with a Snapdragon 800</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370792005500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 11:33:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Tegra 4 scores 36500 consistently in the hands of third party testers as well as NV itself, in public as well as in private." We still don't have results in power constrained conditions. I suspect they will still be good, but not 36500 good.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1370810850239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:47:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370811233109-7</Id><Topic><Title>Galaxy S4 (SHV-E330S) Pops up on AnTuTu with a Snapdragon 800</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370792005500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 11:33:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fair enough, Ashraf. When Shield is officially released, the third=parties can test it at 1.9GHz and find out the difference, Needless to say that other factors such as resolution, screen size etc would also come into play.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370811233109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:53:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370815818133-8</Id><Topic><Title>Galaxy S4 (SHV-E330S) Pops up on AnTuTu with a Snapdragon 800</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370792005500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 11:33:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ibexx, I think that the SHIELD will be a very interesting application of a full-tilt Tegra 4, and for an Android device that can use active cooling/large heatsink (All in one desktops, notebooks, and handheld gaming devices), Tegra 4 may just be the "best" chip for the job. For higher end tablets, too, T4 should be a solid performer, although I really hope we see a T4 in a 7" tablet!</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1370815818133</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:10:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370828317937-9</Id><Title>How many discrete nvidia chips can beat the Haswell 5200, and what are their prices.</Title><Msg>Most of Nvidia's product portfolio is obsoleted by Haswell.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370828317937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:38:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>