<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365327802222-1</Id><Topic><Title>Seems like Tegra4 wins are coming soon</Title><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1365189086286</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 15:11:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, and a thought you had something material to say.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1365327802222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 05:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365347642487-2</Id><Title>who's got what in LTE</Title><Msg>barrons QCOM: Competitors Won’t Easily Take LTE Share, Says Raymond James just watch ibey is going to throw one of his usual fits.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1365347642487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 11:14:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365348036269-3</Id><Title>This Week's Big Potential Winner</Title><Msg>It was just announced that there were 45 million online streams of the NCAA March Madness Basketball Tournament games so far this year, up 158% from last year, with 60% of them over mobile devices! Concurrent (CCUR) is an undiscovered and extremely undervalued low float stock that will capitalize most on this! CCUR's MediaHawk multi-screen technology can deliver any format of video, to any screen/device, at any time, over any network. CCUR was the first company to introduce video on demand (VOD) technology over a decade ago and today they hold a 30% market share of the VOD space with 212 VOD deployments across 4 continents and a reach of 50mm VOD homes. CCUR's clients include Time Warner Cable, Cox, Charter, and Bright House. CCUR ran from $7 to over $200 during the original VOD boom and now we are about to experience a boom of pay-TV companies rushing to upgrade their VOD infrastructure to support multi-screen video delivery to tablets and smartphones. CCUR just signed Virgin Media (VMED) the largest cable TV company in the UK with 3.8mm subscribers. CCUR will be powering VMED's brand new Virgin TV Anywhere service that allows their subscribers to watch content over their tablets and smartphones. CCUR has also signed a huge multi-screen deal with the largest cable TV company in Japan. CCUR closed last week at $7.24 per share with only 9.2mm shares outstanding and a market cap of $66.6mm with $24.6mm in cash, no debt, and an enterprise value of only $42mm or just 0.67X its revenue of $62.59mm! CCUR's EPS has been ramping up big on a quarter-to-quarter basis from $0.02 to $0.04 and to $0.08. Their main competitor Seachange (SEAC) is losing money, yet it's trading with an enterprise value/revenue ratio of 1.81, which would value CCUR at $15. CCUR's gross margins of 58.81% exceed SEAC's gross margins of 50.18% CCUR has potential to at least double this month.</Msg><Username>rblatuis</Username><Timestamp>1365348036269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 11:20:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365348110749-4</Id><Topic><Title>who's got what in LTE</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1365347642487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 11:14:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>barrons also say winRT is on last gasp of air. now ibey throws double fit.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1365348110749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 11:21:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365350088773-5</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's buyback is working</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1365195078539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:51:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, while the stock WAS higher at 3:30, the volume and price movement the last 1/2 hour was MUCH more significant than up to that point. At 3:30, the stock was 12.34-5 and 8.188mm shares had traded, and at 4PM it was 1% higher and volume had increased by almost 50%. If you add the block of 1.41mm shares at 4:18, total volume was 13.75mm vs. the 8.188 at 3:30. In fact, at 3:50, the volume was still only 9.66mm and the stock was 12.39-40, so we had 4mm more shares trade after that time. I would call that "significant", wouldn't you? M</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1365350088773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 11:54:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365353027865-6</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's buyback is working</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1365195078539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:51:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll calling that p-ing into the wind. the more bullish engulfing something or whatever breakout, the lower the stock goes. the only thing left that can make the stock jump is a buyout. And i doubt anybody wants to put with with Jen, who couldn't read the market he spent $1B attacking worth a darn. "How do you model the Tegras?"</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1365353027865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 12:43:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365362073370-7</Id><Title>Last week's losses &amp; Next week's</Title><Msg>It's pretty illustrative to look at last week's losses compared to the losses in other techs and semis, since so many uninformed folks post on this board, without putting things into context. Here's a list of many of the stocks that so many of the bashers favor over NVDA and how they did in comparison. NVDA--Down 2.88% INTC--Down 4.1% AAPL--Down4.4% AMD--Down 10.19% QCOM--Down--2.7% BRCM--Down-4.68% HPQ-Down 7.8% GOOG-Down1.4% TXN--Down3.6% CRUS-Down 5.4% SWKS-Down 5,08% MU-Down 6.7% I think that "should" help elucidate a few of the myopic folks who come here to bash, and even a few of the fatigued longs. NVDA has NOT been "alone" in its suffering, and, in fact, outperformed most of its peers/competitors. Also, keep in mind that CRUS hit a NEW 52 week low, SWKS came with 3-4%, AAPL came within 4 TENTHS of 1% of a new low, and closed only 1% above it. Even INTC is closer to its low than NVDA (8.89% vs. 11.74%). Of course, I don't expect this to change anyone's mind about which stock they favor. It's simply a way to look at the entire spectrum of names and see how they fared on a comparative basis. Also worth noting is the Annual Investor Day, next Thursday. I'm certainly hoping that that will provide the "venue" for one or more announcements that could prove to be the catalysts for a move above 13. I don't and won't respond to any of the regular bashers, so save your venom for someone who will. I have most of you on ignore, so I won't even know you posted. (I'm sure you know who you are.) As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. Max</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1365362073370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 15:14:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365362168622-8</Id><Topic><Title>Last week's losses &amp; Next week's</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1365362073370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 15:14:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for your views, kvimax1. Always enjoy your posts.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1365362168622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 15:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365370243381-9</Id><Topic><Title>Last week's losses &amp; Next week's</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1365362073370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 15:14:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Max, totally agreed. The ones who whined abut NVDA's recent performance (ie, 1 week or 1 day) are simply not paying attention. Below is a simple graph to further help them comprehend the picture. I didn't include the loser loser AMD for fear of distorting the charts too much: financeDOTyahooDOTcom/q/bc?s=NVDA&amp;t=5d&amp;l=on&amp;z=l&amp;q=l&amp;c=qcom%2Cintc%2Cbrcm PS: I am as intrigued as you are re. QCOM's recent weakness vs. NVDA's relative strength (especially toward close, indicating institutional activity. After extensive reading and "soul searching", I've come to the following reasons to possibly explain this: --QCOM is obviously being dragged down by Apple's lackluster prospects in near term, as BRCM is to a lessr extent, despite the numerous design wins for S600/S800. Without a doubt the Apple effect seems overly done, as the big fruit constitutes only a minor fraction of Qualcomm total revenues, but the investors' perception of the negative effect persists....no surprise here as market always has a ST knee-jerk motion. It will correct itself in due course, I am sure. --The second factor - here I am going out on a limb - is the possibility that there may be something brewing about a Intel-NVIDIA merger with JH Huang at the helm - at least variations of such rumors are fermenting on the web ever since January. The ones helped spreading it include some serious websites for the 1st time that I am aware of. My speculation is that some factions of the Wall Street community may begin to see this as a possibility; this scenario would then lend appeal to INTC in addition to NVDA. Following the same reasoning, major losers from this "union" would be AMD, QCOM, BRCM - in the same order as last weeks' price performances would show. Additional support is provided by TSMC, which fabricate NV's chips, also declined about 3%. Just throwing out the above as food for thought. I have no more grounds for speculation than what's available in the public domain...Y's cutting me off</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365370243381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:30:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365375794751-10</Id><Topic><Title>Last week's losses &amp; Next week's</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1365362073370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 15:14:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks, Ibexx. While INTC "should" have bought NVDA quite some time ago, the animosity between the companies might have been a roadblock until the announcement of Ottelini's retirement. And, I concur that such a merger would be good for BOTH companies, and would be viewed as a major positive for INTC going forward, since JHH is the kind of "visionary" that INTC has been lacking for so long. While I did think that QCOM would have already made a move for AMD, it's also possible that they could get in a bidding war with INTC for NVDA, although if JHH was offered the CEO position of the combined INTC/NVDA, I think investors would side with that combination. The new company would be a difficult entity for QCOM to compete with, and for anyone else, as i mentioned. Even if INTC had to "pay" 25 for NVDA (twice present value), they'd really only be paying 19, due to NVDA's cash horde. So, 11 Billion would be the actual "price", net of cash, which would be an easy thing for INTC to accomplish, given their cash and ability to raise money through a bond offering. With INTC's manufacturing prowess (they're 1 or 2 generations ahead of the competition), and NVDA's vision, patents, and leadership in the graphics arena, i think INTC's stock would soar on the news. And, don't forget, a "combined" entity could EASILY bring back the "chipsets" (or some offshoot of same) that NVDA had been working on before INTC refused to "license" them anymore. THAT would be huge. Of course, at this moment there would still be possible anti-trust issues, but with QCOM now being BIGGER (at least in market cap) than INTC, perhaps it wouldn't have as difficult a time of being done, especially since I believe The Street would applaud the idea. Thanks for that chart, too. I do hope the whining stops, but it will probably take the break out over 13 for that to happen. As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. Best, Max</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1365375794751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 19:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365378821454-11</Id><Topic><Title>Last week's losses &amp; Next week's</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1365362073370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 15:14:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, that's what I was pondering, would the SEC allow the sale to Intc. With AMD all but finished, the SEC may consider INTC having a monopoly in graphics acquiring NVDA.</Msg><Username>bigonnvda</Username><Timestamp>1365378821454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 19:53:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365380902404-12</Id><Topic><Title>Last week's losses &amp; Next week's</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1365362073370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 15:14:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bigonnvda, I think the privilege of being #2, not #1, does give Intel a bit more freedom, as Max astutely pointed out.. I bet that, now, Intel is less in the cross hairs of regulatory authorities as before. The SEC only goes after top guns like MSFT, INTC, GOOG, AAPL etc, very seldom they would waste time on the second tier companies,which Intel now belongs to. However, there are also the EU agencies that the hypothetical merger would have to deal with. Another thought is that, apparently, the mobile market and its technologies are now getting most of the spotlight, not the traditional PC market. Thus, a "merger" of Intel and NVIDIA could revive the latter and do wonders for the US economy. We all realize that all regulatory decisions should be above real-world politics, but they rarely were 100%. If JH is indeed talking to Intel, then he must have a good feel that the "climate" has changed.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1365380902404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 20:28:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>