<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-05"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370406642877-1</Id><Title>One year ago... QC Readies Snapdragon for RT</Title><Msg>That's right, folks. One year ago, QC claimed that snapdragons were ready for Windows RT. Qualcomm Readies Snapdragon Line for Windows RT pcmagDOTcom/article2/0,2817,2405353,00.asp</Msg><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1370406642877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 00:30:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370407362957-2</Id><Title>BreakingNews: ITC rules for Samsung, bans iphone 4 (and other parts) import</Title><Msg>sfgateDOTcom/business/technology/article/ITC-rules-for-Samsung-bans-iPhone-4-imports-4576769.php This could hurt Apple badly, as Apple draws 50% of its phone revenues from older iphones.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370407362957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 00:42:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370407543026-3</Id><Topic><Title>One year ago... QC Readies Snapdragon for RT</Title><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1370406642877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 00:30:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, they did show up for WinRT...you know, late, and nobody bought them. lol</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1370407543026</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 00:45:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370411509957-4</Id><Topic><Title>One year ago... QC Readies Snapdragon for RT</Title><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1370406642877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 00:30:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>S800 WinRT ready in 2015 - they announced early to give their engineers plenty of time to hit the 2015 date :)</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1370411509957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 01:51:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370414530948-5</Id><Title>A new interview with Jen Hsun Huang</Title><Msg>Source: HardwareLUXX Title: "Computex 2013: talking with NVIDIA" An excellent read, but Y! wouldn't let me post the link information. Just google the subject title and website.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370414530948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 02:42:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370433183024-6</Id><Title>Outlook comes to RT The power of Huang!</Title><Msg>Who could possibly replace Balmer?</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1370433183024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 07:53:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370436795851-7</Id><Topic><Title>Will that SHIELD toy come 3 to a box with perforated packaging + AWARD sticker?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370374041823</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:27:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Will that SHIELD toy come 3 to a box with perforated packaging + AWARD sticker?" With a name like SHIELD that junk ought to be priced at $3.49 a box. Isn't that right Nvidia fans? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370436795851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:53:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370437058171-8</Id><Title>"AMD fires back at Intel's Haswell with its A-Series desktop processors"</Title><Msg>" On Saturday, Intel fired a salvo of ”Haswell” microprocessors across AMD’s bow. Now, Intel’s chief rival has responded in kind, with five new desktop processors that combine midrange microprocessor power with AMD’s powerful graphics technology. AMD’s A team is the A-series: the A10, A8, and A6 chips, aimed at Intel’s Core i3 and Core i5 microprocessors. Although AMD calls the chips its flagship offering, the A-series chips concede the high end of the market to Intel’s Core i7. On the other hand, they’re priced accordingly: AMD sells the low-end A6-6400K for $77, on up to the $149 A10-6800K. Overall, AMD says Richland will yield 21 percent more graphics performance (using the 3DMark “Fire Strike” benchmark) versus the previous generation, dubbed “Trinity,” as well as 8 percent more performance using the more generic PCMark 7 benchmark. That’s because the Richland chips include Radeon HD 8000-quality graphics. All of the Richland APUs are part of what AMD calls its “Elite A-Series” platform, and will be built into PCs from Acer and Hewlett-Packard."</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370437058171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:57:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370437277918-9</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD fires back at Intel's Haswell with its A-Series desktop processors"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370437058171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:57:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The article was from: PCWorld Take notes Nvidia fans this is a product launch. If you can read then you will see Prices, Specs, Benchmarks and OEMs selling products based on the NEW A-Series processors. You won't see any of that for Tegra 4 Today, will you? lmao imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370437277918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:01:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370437440274-10</Id><Title>"AMD Touts Big Leap in Graphics Performance With New Richland APUs"</Title><Msg>"AMD Touts Big Leap in Graphics Performance With New Richland APUs" "Advanced Micro Devices on Wednesday launched a new desktop APU code named Richland which combines CPU and GPU performance in a single package that the chip maker said at the Computex show in Taiwan will hands-down beat rival Intel's offerings in the mainstream market. Richland is the next stage in AMD's A-Series APU lineup, which kicked off with Llano-class chips in 2011 and was followed up with Trinity last year. The chip maker said its Richland series boosts its 3DMark Fire Strike benchmarking score by 21 percent from the Trinity generation and has scored double-digit performance increases in other key benchmarking tests as compared with the preceding generation. AMD's Richland, utilizing the chip maker's Radeon 8000 series graphics, provides 779 GFLOPs of GPU compute performance to supplement a quad-core x86-based central processor capable of up to 4.4GHz clock speeds out of the box." Source: PCMag</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370437440274</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:04:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370437713237-11</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD Touts Big Leap in Graphics Performance With New Richland APUs"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370437440274</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:04:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I put this up to show you Nvidia fans what a REAL Product Launch looks like. If you can read you might even see the word "LAUNCH" in the PC Magazine article. lol Take note Nvidia fans and remember if you can't buy a Tegra 4 product is all BS and not a launch. No matter how many times you Cut-N-Paste a design sighting, its still BS if it ain't for sale today. IMHO of course</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370437713237</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370440505260-12</Id><Title>"Why Qualcomm is likely to power Microsoft’s next Surface RT"</Title><Msg>"Why Qualcomm is likely to power Microsoft’s next Surface RT" ... "Qualcomm announced its support for Microsoft Windows 8.1 on Tuesday, which by itself is no big surprise. Here’s an interested bit from the press release, however: “At Computex Taipei 2013, Qualcomm Technologies is building on this innovation and collaboration with Microsoft by showing Qualcomm Snapdragon 800 processors running on an early version of Windows RT 8.1.” Again, this isn’t a huge surprise either but I haven’t seen any news of Nvidia showing off Windows RT 8.1. It could well be doing so — I’m not at the show — but there’s no press release to indicate any effort. For Nvidia, Computex seems to be an Android event. Sometimes words can be louder than actions Here’s another interesting angle: Which company has publicly supported Microsoft’s Windows RT effort? Both of course, but Nvidia has commented negatively about Windows RT sales. In March, Nvidia CEO Jen-Hsun Huang told developers that “Windows RT is disappointing to us because we expected to have sold more than we did.” While the sales disappointment is pretty obvious, some things are better left unsaid; especially when you’re a key Microsoft partner and supplying chips to the flagship device for the Windows RT platform." source: gigaom</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370440505260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:55:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370441424534-13</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD Touts Big Leap in Graphics Performance With New Richland APUs"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370437440274</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:04:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone must be paying you a lot of money for your willingness to answer your own notes.</Msg><Username>jtjgmtbt</Username><Timestamp>1370441424534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370442049124-14</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD Touts Big Leap in Graphics Performance With New Richland APUs"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370437440274</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:04:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Someone must be paying you a lot of money for your willingness to answer your own notes." No more than you for posting absolute worthless BS with no value to anyone. Did you just want to see if you could still talk out of your back pockets? Well you can. Now read your own BS and rate its worth to this board. IMHO of course</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370442049124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:20:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370442143312-15</Id><Topic><Title>Outlook comes to RT The power of Huang!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1370433183024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 07:53:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a very big deal, one that Jen Hsun had been advocating for months. Apparently the MS email system has enjoyed extremely wide popularity among users. Porting to RT will likely bring a lot of folowers.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370442143312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370442474762-16</Id><Topic><Title>"Why Qualcomm is likely to power Microsoft’s next Surface RT"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370440505260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:55:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it typical for Jen to bad mouh his "partners" when trying to cover his rear? Tegra sales fell off a cliff when Nvidia last reported and Jen blamed weak Surface sales on who, Microsoft? Well it looks like Microsoft is going to fix those weak Surface sales with a Qualcomm upgrade, hmm? lmao imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370442474762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:27:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370443305006-17</Id><Topic><Title>Outlook comes to RT The power of Huang!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1370433183024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 07:53:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is huge, and takes away the single largest reason that I would not consider RT up until now. Legacy support for desktop programs is a minor issue, since I am not and most people are not looking to run high-power desktop programs on a tablet. Connectivity with Outlook is big.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1370443305006</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:41:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370443852230-18</Id><Title>Are the Tech Rags wrong about Qualcomm TAKING Surface RT and Nexus from Nvidia?</Title><Msg>Did all the Tech Rags reporting about Qualcomm having a ball taking business away from Nvidia get it wrong? Do you think Nvidia is actually shipping Tegra 4 parts to Google for the Next Nexus and to Microsoft for the New Surface RT? Wouldn't there be one tech rag reporting that? Wouldn't there be one pumping post about the Next Nexus and New Surface RT to go with all the other design sightings posted here? lol Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370443852230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:50:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370443955991-19</Id><Topic><Title>Outlook comes to RT The power of Huang!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1370433183024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 07:53:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"That is huge, and takes away the single largest reason that I would not consider RT" Will you still love Surface RT if its running on a Qualcomm part? lol</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370443955991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:52:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370444251282-20</Id><Topic><Title>Outlook comes to RT The power of Huang!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1370433183024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 07:53:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now why would anyone buy a Intel based tablet? That's going to hurt them. A lot.</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370444251282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370444612215-21</Id><Title>Bloomberg credits Jen Hsun Huang for advocacy of porting Outlook to Win RT</Title><Msg>""At least one Microsoft partner also asked the company to reconsider. Nvidia Corp. (NVDA) Chief Executive Officer Jen-Hsun Huang has said he wants Microsoft to include a version of Outlook that works on RT. “Give me Outlook and I’ll use it every day,” Huang, whose company makes chips used in Microsoft’s Surface RT and other devices based on the software, said in May. The executive said in March that he was disappointed with sales of RT-based tablets."" bloombergDOTcom/news/2013-06-05/microsoft-to-add-outlook-to-windows-rt-update-after-complaints.html Ballmer apparently didn't know how to run his business - it was up to a visionary leader like JH to tell him jow to fix it.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370444612215</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:03:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370444920266-22</Id><Topic><Title>Outlook comes to RT The power of Huang!</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1370433183024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 07:53:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Now why would anyone buy a Intel based tablet? That's going to hurt them. A lot." Yup, no reason in the world to buy an Intel tablet now. Do you want to tell Intel to seize their tablet efforts and give up to Nvidia or should Jen? lol When silly roams wild this is what happens? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370444920266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:08:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370445314208-23</Id><Title>If Surface RT is a Qualcomm win will you still Love RT Tomorrow?</Title><Msg>The Shirelles Will You Still Love Me Tomorrow? wwwDOTyoutubeDOTcom/watch?v=cbxxkwBQk_o lmao</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370445314208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370446063699-24</Id><Topic><Title>Are the Tech Rags wrong about Qualcomm TAKING Surface RT and Nexus from Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370443852230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:50:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All that RT love here is good. But will Microsoft return the love when they announce who the New Surface RT SoC winner is? What happens to all that Surface RT love if it ain't Nvidia? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370446063699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370449129963-25</Id><Title>HEADED BACK TO $13?</Title><Msg>SURE LOOKS LIKE NVDA JUMPED THE SHARK!</Msg><Username>flyinwsquirl</Username><Timestamp>1370449129963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:18:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370449599801-26</Id><Topic><Title>Passed on selling 8 cyl turbo charged engines for a Porche like outfit out of my garage because its TOO EXPENSIVE</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363370010802</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:53:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Too Expensive" to rake in the now estimated $9 BILLION while they delay Tegra 4 and play games on a condom sounding SHIELD toy right? That Nvidia excuse for losing out on Game Consoleswas funny then and its funnier now after we saw how they used their time. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370449599801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:26:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370449989049-27</Id><Title>Is that talking head at Nvidia still busy after claiming Nvidia was Too Busy to make money?</Title><Msg>If Nvidia paid a talking head to talk to the press and his excuse for losing out on Game Consoles was a 7th grade cop out of "Too busy" then Nvidia should have shown us just how busy they were right? Does delaying Tegra 4 and playing games on a SHEILD Toy sound busy to you Nvidia fans? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370449989049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370451242117-28</Id><Topic><Title>"Why Qualcomm is likely to power Microsoft’s next Surface RT"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370440505260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:55:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is the author of this article CLUELESS? Does Qualcomm even have the slightest chance of TAKING Nvidia's Surface RT job? Surface RT is Nvidia's job to lose right? Lets see how it plays out, Microsoft will eventually announce what part is in the New Surface RT. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370451242117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370451278964-29</Id><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablets Crashing and Overheating</Title><Msg>Reviewer finds these crashing overheating Tegra 4 tablets will be lucky to sell at $100 to $150 rather than $400 to $600.</Msg><Username>techvest21</Username><Timestamp>1370451278964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:54:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370451735008-30</Id><Title>Outlook gods speak: Outlook 2013 returning to Win RT</Title><Msg>This is NVIDIA's version: :) Earlier this year, our CEO Jen-Hsun Huang urged the Outlook gods to add Outlook to Windows RT. Apparently they listened. Microsoft announced at the Computex trade show in Taiwan that Outlook 2013 RT will be coming to Windows RT tablets later this year with the release of Windows 8.1. This is an exciting development that we believe will deliver a much more robust and full-featured experience to Windows RT users, including those with the Microsoft Surface RT, Lenovo Yoga 11, and ASUS VivoTab RT, which are all powered by NVIDIA Tegra 3. As Microsoft noted, consumers and business users alike have asked for Outlook for Windows RT, and we are thrilled that it will join the rest of the Office apps, Word, Excel, PowerPoint and OneNote, that are already available on Windows RT devices when the free update to Windows is available later this year in the Windows Store. We agree with Microsoft that the addition of Outlook on Windows RT, along with the announcements Microsoft made this week at TechEd on security, manageability and networking capabilities coming with Windows RT 8.1, makes Windows on ARM even more compelling for enterprises users. (from NVIDIA website)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370451735008</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:02:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370451866113-31</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablets Crashing and Overheating</Title><Username>techvest21</Username><Timestamp>1370451278964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sheer fabrication. Shame on you!</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370451866113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:04:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370452947559-32</Id><Topic><Title>Is this the Hate SNE, MSFT, AAPL, AMD, INTC and QCOM Board because Nvidia sucks? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1369654274819</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 07:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are all waiting to find out who Google and Mircorsoft select as the Next Nexus and New Surface RT supplier to see if Microsoft, Google, RT and Android make the Nvidia fan club "hate it" list? Nvidia fans you are running out of companies and stuff to hate and you may find yourself in a room alone hugging a condom sounding SHIELD toy. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370452947559</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:22:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370453104418-33</Id><Title>Intel Haswell "hotter and slower than expected"</Title><Msg>Retail versions of Intel Haswell processors are hotter and more power-hungry than pre-production chips, and can’t be overclocked to the same speeds, British PC manufacturers have told PC Pro. Wasn't haswell going to save the (Intel's) world?</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370453104418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370454589276-34</Id><Title>Trefis: NVIDIA has huge potential in the mid-range smartphone market</Title><Msg>SOURCE: trefisDOTcom/stock/nvda/articles/190058/nvidia-has-huge-potential-in-the-mid-range-smartphone-market/2013-06-05 Quick Take Nvidia has decided to primarily focus on the mid-range smartphone market for now, competing directly with Qualcomm’s Snapdragon 400 chip. Qualcomm has been the leader in mobile chip market for many years while Nvidia is a relatively new player. Nvidia claims that its first fully integrated 4G LTE mobile processor – Tegra 4i – delivers almost three times higher performance than Qualcomm’s S400 solutions. LTE capability and competitive processor prices will increase Nvidia’s competitiveness in the smartphone market. With an estimated 487 million devices, the mid-range mobile market is projected to exceed the number of premium smartphones and tablets by 2015. The mobile device market and the LTE market are expanding at a rapid pace, and we believe that there is plenty of room for both Nvidia and Qualcomm to sell a higher number of processors in the future.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370454589276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:49:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370454742429-35</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Haswell "hotter and slower than expected"</Title><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370453104418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:25:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel's wind got taken out of its overblown sails, now that reports are rampant about Haswell being "hot and slow" lol</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370454742429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:52:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370456299912-36</Id><Topic><Title>"Why Qualcomm is likely to power Microsoft’s next Surface RT"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370440505260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:55:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nvidia has commented negatively about Windows RT sales. In March, Nvidia CEO Jen-Hsun Huang told developers that “Windows RT is disappointing to us because we expected to have sold more than we did.”" Would Jen be bad mouthing Microsoft if Nvidia was in the running for the New Surface RT tablet? lol The author didn't think so, do you? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370456299912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:18:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370456491629-37</Id><Topic><Title>Are the Tech Rags wrong about Qualcomm TAKING Surface RT and Nexus from Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370443852230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:50:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Digitimes claimed 60% of Tegra sales would walk with the loss of the Next Nexus tablet to Qualcomm. Does 60% matter Nvidia fans? When Tegra 4 is DOA anyway? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370456491629</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:21:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370456724032-38</Id><Topic><Title>Re: look for an increase in screwish activity over the next 30-40 days</Title><Username>screwherbes</Username><Timestamp>1369398384547</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 08:26:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good thing we knew NYC screw boy was going into mass manipulation mode back then when I first posted the warning...</Msg><Username>screwherbes</Username><Timestamp>1370456724032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:25:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370456760733-39</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Haswell "hotter and slower than expected"</Title><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370453104418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:25:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could that be why Mars isn't posting his usual blather about the apocalyptic end for ARM today?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1370456760733</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:26:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370457018637-40</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Haswell "hotter and slower than expected"</Title><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370453104418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:25:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At last sighting, the infected avian had his head buried between his hind legs.</Msg><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1370457018637</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:30:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370457196075-41</Id><Title>Without Intel Nvidia would be out of business, so why bash Intel?</Title><Msg>70% if Nvidia's revenue is from GPU sales. But GPU sales for what? GPU sales for Intel based systems for the most part. Which means Nvidia makes its living following Intel around and begging the Intel x86 OEMs to add an Nvidia discrete GPU. Do you thnk AMD APUs and CPUs need an Nvidia GPU? Without Intel servers, desktops and notebooks there is no reason for Nvidia to exist and Nvidia fans spend their silly time bashing Intel? lmao Even Jen said Nvidia GPU share is tied to Intel since AMD systems have little need for Nvidia. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370457196075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:33:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370457704273-42</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Haswell "hotter and slower than expected"</Title><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370453104418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:25:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tom's Hardware has a good review of the i7-4770K. Users are going to want the graphics to run at 1080P or higher (MacBook retina is 1600) and this chip cannot play games higher than 720p. Even if the Iris Pro is 50% faster it is still not enough for anything over 1080P with decent levels of detail and you pay the huge ultrabook tax. So Intel is really only competing with itself as notebooks for gaming will still require dedicated gpu. And this fall DX11 and OpenGL 4.X become the standard for game engines so Intel graphics will lose more ground. Great CPU if you transcode video, gaming not so much.</Msg><Username>flstf_97</Username><Timestamp>1370457704273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370457859953-43</Id><Topic><Title>Without Intel Nvidia would be out of business, so why bash Intel?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370457196075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:33:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra is a money losing experiment. GPU sales to Intel x86 OEMs, including Apple, pays the bills. Have you Nvidia fans ever heard the phrase: "Don't bite the hand that feeds you?" lmao You Nvidia fans must think that food just falls off trees into your lap right? FACT: The Intel ecosystem is the hand that has been feeding Nvidia its entire life. Nvidia is an Intel suckling. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370457859953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370457871990-44</Id><Title>Intel's ATOM is on a collision course with Core - and everybody loses</Title><Msg>SOURCE: PC World pcworldDOTcom/article/2040752/intels-atom-is-on-a-collision-course-with-core-and-everybody-loses.html Intel has made it clear that its fourth-generation Core or “Haswell” processors will power future PCs. But at the low end of the notebook market, the company's branding strategy will be far muddier—and that's bad for Intel, considering it needs to tell consumers exactly what to buy. On one hand, Intel needs to present a clear alternative to ARM, whose tablet partners dominate the mobile space and threaten traditional PCs. From a technical standpoint, Intel seems well on its way to solving that problem. Intel’s Haswell chip will eventually migrate to as little as 6 watts, Intel said Tuesday, meaning that its Core chips could eventually power tablets, too. But in the meantime, Intel's upcoming “Bay Trail” Atom chips are waiting in the wings—and could offer the performance buyers want at a fraction of the price. This fall, buyers looking to pick up an inexpensive Windows convertible or notebook may have to sort through several processor brands, including Atom, Core, Pentium, and Celeron. And that’s without even factoring in the code names: Bay Trail, Silvermont, and Haswell, among others. Intel may have the right chip at the right price, but because its processor line-up is so crowded, it's in real danger of screwing the whole thing up .......</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370457871990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:44:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370458032014-45</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Haswell "hotter and slower than expected"</Title><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370453104418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:25:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, some overclockers are complaining they can't get 4.5 GHz out of a chip rated only for 3.5-3.9 GHz and you idiots think Haswell is slow lol. Well duh, overclocking is called that for a reason LOL.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370458032014</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:47:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370458458779-46</Id><Topic><Title>Without Intel Nvidia would be out of business, so why bash Intel?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370457196075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:33:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am glad you pointed out to these idiots that without x86 cpus Nvidia is one dead company, it's been leeching off the x86 cpu ecosystem for decades.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370458458779</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370458486700-47</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Haswell "hotter and slower than expected"</Title><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370453104418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:25:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, just hot. Again, the performance doesn't match the mighty Intel marketing hype that naive idiots like you always drool over.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1370458486700</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:54:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370458694286-48</Id><Title>Intel is trying to WEAN Nvidia off with Haswell and Nvidia fans are upset?</Title><Msg>Nvidia is an Intel ecosystem SUCKLING. And Nvidia fans wants to keep sucking what mommy Intel provides. You need Intel x86 CPU going out into the world for Nvidia to follow behind like any SUCKLING. Without Intel what would Nvidia do? Tegra loses money. GPUs sales to Intel x86 OEMs accounts for ALL the profits. Telsa needs an x86 system or its useless. GeForce needs an x86 system or its useless. And those 2 parts pay all the bills. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370458694286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:58:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370458942082-49</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Haswell "hotter and slower than expected"</Title><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370453104418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:25:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Newegg is giving away free copies of Dirt 2 with the 4770K. That was the only game playable at 1080P according to the Tom's Hardware review. At least the 'PR' (aka FUD) team is in high gear.</Msg><Username>flstf_97</Username><Timestamp>1370458942082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:02:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370459139396-50</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's ATOM is on a collision course with Core - and everybody loses</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370457871990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:44:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like I said in a prior post, what is lacking here is a clearly articulated (new) vision.....that's what happens when you promote an operational manager to the top and expect him/her to lead the company into the future. Just look at Apple's Tim Cook disaster, and you will know what I mean.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370459139396</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:05:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370459738178-51</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is trying to WEAN Nvidia off with Haswell and Nvidia fans are upset?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370458694286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:58:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD fans can bash Intel. AMD is not an intel ecosystem SUCKLING but a competitor. Without Intel AMD would have a ball in the market place. Without Intel Nvidia would close the doors and fold because why buy a GPU card if you don't have an Intel x86 computer? lol Why bite the hand that feeds you Nvidia fans? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370459738178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:15:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370459763964-52</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Haswell "hotter and slower than expected"</Title><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370453104418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:25:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rubbish ! The performance jump from Ivy Bridge to Haswell is greater than the performance jump from Sandy Bridge to Ivy Bridge even though the former does not involve a silicon process shrink and the latter does ! You will also be pleased to know that includes non-gpu limited gaming fps so once again another opportunity to leech off another great Intel chip, sheesh you guys should learn to say thank you when you are being helped but you are not bright enough to see cause and effect here lol. hardocpDOTcom/article/2013/06/01/intel_haswell_i74770k_ipc_overclocking_review/4 hardocpDOTcom/article/2013/06/01/intel_haswell_i74770k_ipc_overclocking_review/5</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370459763964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:16:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370460254931-53</Id><Title>BARRONS just in: Bernstein, JPMorgan, Morgan Stanley press downside thesis</Title><Msg>Part 1: "Intel (INTC) has enjoyed a relatively healthy rate of endorsements from the Street of late, with the unveiling two weeks ago of its “Silvermont” CPU for mobile devices, and the formal unveiling yesterday at the Computex conference of its “Haswell” processor architecture for everything from servers to low-power mobile devices. The announcement Monday morning by Samsung Electronics (005930KS) that the South Korean giant will use Intel’s “Clover Trail+” processor in its next “Galaxy Tab 10” tablet computer also heartened those with a bullish view of the stock, as it seems a major breakthrough in Intel’s attempts to crack a table market that’s been dominated by chips from competitors such as Nvidia (NVDA) and Qualcomm (QCOM). The latest victory was Monday’s upgrade to Outperform from Market Perform by FBR Capital‘s Christopher Rolland, who wrote that the company has “added enough new avenues of growth to replace lost PC units.” My colleague Jack Hough wrote an endorsement of Intel in this week’s Barron’s print magazine. However, it was the bears’ turn today to offer up what they see as the downside for the company and the stock. Stacy Rasgon of Bernstein Research reiterated an Underperform rating on the shares and an $18 price target, writing that “more than 100% of the stock’s performance year-to-date has been driven by multiple expansion (both from the market, and on a relative basis),” by which he means that the expansion of the stock market’s multiple, measured by the S&amp;P 500, to 14.8 times at present, from 13 times forwarding earnings back in December, has been accompanied by an expansion of Intel’s relative stock multiple, from 0.83 the S&amp;P multiple back in December to 0.91 at present. (To be continued)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370460254931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:24:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370460271276-54</Id><Title>Intel gave you an ALLOWANCE before WEANING you off with Haswell right? lol</Title><Msg>Why all the WHINING now. You knew the day would come when you would have to STAND ON YOUR OWN Nvidia is a teenage Intel ecosystem SUCKLING who refuses to get out of the house. lmao You won't be able to follow Intel around forever hoping to attach to an Intel x86 account and suck it dry for GPU pocket money. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370460271276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:24:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370460431824-55</Id><Topic><Title>BARRONS just in: Bernstein, JPMorgan, Morgan Stanley press downside thesis</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370460254931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:24:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Part 2: "But Rasgon thinks the stock is mainly benefiting from very low expectations: PC expectations have been extremely poor; the expectation now is that actual results will be merely bad, instead of truly abysmal. Secondly, Intel’s mobile product roadmap (as we have said for some time) appears very competitive; new BayTrail products for tablets appear compelling on power and performance vs. prior Atom generations [...] And thirdly, the company is in the beginning of a product cycle, with all attendant hype (exacerbated by Computex). Additionally they will be building product – fabs will be full, and gross margin outlook will (for now) climb upward as fab utilizations recover. Rasgon advises “not pressing the short here, but rather to use upside into the back half to short the stock,” and in addition to long-term structural challenges for Intel, such as the PC market not being a growth market, he sees some immediate reasons why the stock could face a tougher second half: Rolling out seasonality (given where numbers came in Q1) would suggest overall PC units down 5-10%. Intel, however, still believes computing units for them will grow, and is planning capacity build-out and loadings accordingly [...] 2014 unit expectations appear even more aggressive to us. Our analysis indicates that the company is implicitly suggesting fab output will increase in the high double digits YoY in 2014 [...] Additionally, given somewhat weak Data Center results in Q1, it is likely that the back half will need to be up more than 20% YoY in order to high company guidance for “double-digit” increases in the business. Currently the year appears to be setting up similarly to 2012, where Intel continued to build product on the hope of the Ivy Bridge refresh through the first three quarters, and was consequently forced to cut loadings and inventories at the end of the year. We model a repeat of last year’s events – namely an inventory flush and gross margin hit, starting in Q114.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370460431824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370460506543-56</Id><Topic><Title>BARRONS just in: Bernstein, JPMorgan, Morgan Stanley press downside thesis</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370460254931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:24:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Part 3 Morgan Stanley’s Joseph Moore, meanwhile, also reiterates an Underweight rating, and a $22 price target, writing that “Intel has already proven us wrong on Android,” where he had doubted the ability to Intel to win customers. However, “We are encouraged by these shifts, but still don’t like the stock.” Moore had written only two weeks ago that “We think Intel’s traction in the Android tablet market will remain fairly limited, given compatibility issues,” with developers on Android unwilling to move the most demanding applications to the Java or ”Dalvik” runtime environments. The Samsung win is “a key milestone” for Intel, he writes, and “the endorsement of Samsung could go a long way towards solving this chicken and egg problem” with developers. However, Moore thinks Intel “priced aggressively” to win the deal “both the CPU and the modem, which made the decision easier,” citing unnamed sources. He thinks the Samsung contract may boost Intel market share in tablets but may not help financial results much: Our prior assumption of 7.5% share of Android tablets will likely prove conservative given the Samsung announcement. But if Intel achieves 30% share of Android, it impacts our prior 2015 EPS estimate by just $0.04 as the opportunity is still relatively small compared to Intel’s total earnings stream. And lastly J.P. Morgan‘s Christopher Danely, who has a Neutral rating on Intel stock, and a $19 price target, writes that his visits in Asia this week with personal computer component suppliers suggest Q2 sales of PCs are trending below even reduced expectations. Danely thinks Haswell is not yet prompting “incremental demand” (though given the processor is new to market, it may be too soon to judge):</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370460506543</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:28:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370460629805-57</Id><Topic><Title>BARRONS just in: Bernstein, JPMorgan, Morgan Stanley press downside thesis</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370460254931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:24:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Part 4: Demand from the PC end market remains soft as Intel’s new Haswell processor is not driving incremental demand, touch-enabled PCs are still too expensive, and tablets and smartphones continue to cannibalize PC demand. Many companies we met with in the PC food chain stated 2Q13 is tracking towards the low end of guidance. We believe this is negative for Intel and Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) as both are over 85% exposed to the PC end market and guided 2Q13 and 2H13 to be in line with normal seasonal growth [...] Although Intel’s new Haswell microprocessor enables higher performance at lower power, none of the companies we met with indicated PC demand is improving. We do not expect Haswell to drive incremental PC demand as new processor launches have not historically resulted in higher PC demand. Like Moore, Danely is unimpressed with the financial prospects of Intel’s improved profile in tablet computers: Although Intel appears to be gaining tablet share at Samsung, Lenovo, and Acer, we believe the content and expected unit shipments are too small to offset declining demand in notebooks. We note the ASP of an Atom tablet processor is roughly $25-$30, well below Intel’s notebook microprocessor ASP of $110. Danely is modeling Intel revenue this quarter at $12.9 billion, the mid-point of Intel’s forecast, $12.9 billion, but for the full year he sees revenue of $53 billion, which is below the company’s forecast for revenue to rise in the “low single digits” on a percentage basis, and below Street consensus of $53.5 billion. blogsDOTbarronsDOTcom/techtraderdaily/2013/06/05/intel-bernstein-j-p-morgan-morgan-stanley-press-downside-thesis/</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370460629805</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:30:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370461284743-58</Id><Title>Qualcomm to Intel: "Bring on your best game!"</Title><Msg>Paul Jacobs and gang are ready for battle. zdnetDOTcom/qualcomm-to-intel-bring-on-your-best-mobile-game-7000016398/</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370461284743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:41:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370462407235-59</Id><Title>Rob Enderle says thisL "The doors of heaven open, angels are singing, Outlook is arriving on Windows RT""</Title><Msg>suliaDOTcom/channel/all-tech-science/f/de60cb2d-6de6-4f17-a870-db71e22092b1/?source=twitter ""Watching Microsoft repeat the mistake that IBM made with the PC Jr. back in the ‘80s with Windows RT has been painful. Crippling a product to assure a more expensive version has never ended well and leaving out both Outlook and Domain Join on Windows RT made it function like a crippled product. With this latest announcement Outlook will be added to Windows RT and while it still won’t get domain join, no other tablet will either, and there are a number of good work alternatives. I loved Windows RT’s battery life, price and weight but the lack of Outlook made it hard to use without screaming. With Outlook I’m having a religious moment. ""</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370462407235</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 16:00:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370462769267-60</Id><Topic><Title>Are the Tech Rags wrong about Qualcomm TAKING Surface RT and Nexus from Nvidia?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370443852230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:50:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you think Microsoft and Google chose the now DOA Tegra 4 for their new products raise your lying hand. lol Can you read the writing on the wall? lol Tegra 4 is DOA. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370462769267</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 16:06:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370462830516-61</Id><Topic><Title>"Why Qualcomm is likely to power Microsoft’s next Surface RT"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370440505260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:55:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who will be cuddling up to RT when Qualcomm wins the day? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370462830516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 16:07:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370463039365-62</Id><Topic><Title>If Surface RT is a Qualcomm win will you still Love RT Tomorrow?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370445314208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:15:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm betting Nvidia fans will through RT under the bus before Qualcomm cashes the first Microsoft pay check for what use to be Nvidia work? Did the tech rags get it all wrong or is Nvidia on the way out at Microsoft? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370463039365</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 16:10:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370463217632-63</Id><Topic><Title>Someone who bought in at $16.01 is PUMPING hard trying to break even Today. lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368207526854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"He may be off posting more LIES and calling anyone who disagrees with his $100 target for Nvidia a PAID basher. BUT he is not bragging about paying $16.01 for Nvidia weeks before Nvidia dropped to he $8s." Has he mentioned $16.01 since? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370463217632</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 16:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370463492176-64</Id><Topic><Title>Is this the Hate SNE, MSFT, AAPL, AMD, INTC and QCOM Board because Nvidia sucks? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1369654274819</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 07:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"SNE, MSFT, AAPL, AMD, INTC and QCOM" Bashing every stock on that list didn't help Nvidia today did it? lol Intel this and Qualcomm that but no mention of that fact that Nvidia was DOWN over 2% today, right? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370463492176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 16:18:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370463992329-65</Id><Topic><Title>BARRONS just in: Bernstein, JPMorgan, Morgan Stanley press downside thesis</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370460254931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:24:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ibexx, do you think that Samsung's decision to use the Clover Trail+ in the Galaxy Tab 10 is just temporary until they get their chip problem fixed? It sounds like Intel gave them a price they couldn't refuse?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1370463992329</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 16:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370465618720-66</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcomm to Intel: "Bring on your best game!"</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370461284743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:41:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a pretty misleading title. The better quote from the article might be the following: "I watch Intel and I worry about them a lot," Jacobs said. "We will have to wait and see what develops there."</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1370465618720</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 16:53:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370466220638-67</Id><Topic><Title>BARRONS just in: Bernstein, JPMorgan, Morgan Stanley press downside thesis</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370460254931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:24:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung doesn't have permanent bedfellows. They are looking for parts that are cheap, reasonably good performance, volume availability and, most importantly, requiring minimum development time. (ie. LTE bundled, or parts allowing turn-key like operations). Even with Samsung's immense marketing prowess, not all of its products are a HIT - case in point is Nexus 10 which, by the standard set with Nexus 7, is almost a FLOP. When Tegra 4i hits the ground, Sammie will come courting....and same with Logan next year for tablets, chromebooks or notebooks.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370466220638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:03:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370466751495-68</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcomm to Intel: "Bring on your best game!"</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370461284743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:41:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Qualcomm is at a big disadvantage. They depend on TSMC for their chips and everyone knows TSMC is unreliable.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370466751495</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370467330482-69</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcomm to Intel: "Bring on your best game!"</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370461284743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:41:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's developing is a good old fashion backside kicking</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1370467330482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:22:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370470019568-70</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcomm to Intel: "Bring on your best game!"</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370461284743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:41:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD doesn't have its own fabs either. Funny how you NEVER mention this being a big disadvantage of AMDs. LOL</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370470019568</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 18:06:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370471073557-71</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablets Crashing and Overheating</Title><Username>techvest21</Username><Timestamp>1370451278964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you have any link? Or have you made it up?</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1370471073557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 18:24:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370472688931-72</Id><Topic><Title>HERE IS WHY BUY BACK HAS BE ANNOUNCED: FREE LOOT WITH ZERO COST LOOT DUMP..ONLY IN USA FRAUD STREET CASINO</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369167839935</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 16:23:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This buy back really exposed insider agenda and long term sealed fate to single digits here</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1370472688931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 18:51:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370474012625-73</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablets Crashing and Overheating</Title><Username>techvest21</Username><Timestamp>1370451278964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Link, or...are you FOS?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1370474012625</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370474734297-74</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablets Crashing and Overheating</Title><Username>techvest21</Username><Timestamp>1370451278964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are reports that GAMES running on the pre-production sample at DID CRASH A FAIR BIT Its no BS And everything tablet running on Tegra 4 is pre-production since Tegra 4 is pre-production. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370474734297</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:25:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370475216738-75</Id><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablet "crashed a fair bit" running games report says</Title><Msg>And if you Nvidia fans didn't burry your heads in the sand you wouldn't be calling out the poster who brought the Tegra 4 crashing problem to your attention. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370475216738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:33:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370475904522-76</Id><Title>What's so hard to find, just google "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" lmao</Title><Msg>If you can't find an article searching with "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" then you don't want to find it. lol Why it crashed - don't care. How it crashed - don't care. Don't even care that it crashed Do care how you Nvidia fans are so quick to call some one names for pointing it out. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370475904522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:45:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370475991494-77</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablet "crashed a fair bit" running games report says</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370475216738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now you are in a paradox. You have repeated dismissed any rumors, previews, and pre-announcements about the T4 as groundless pumping, but suddenly you believe unsubstantiated T4 crash rumors without link or reference? I know that you see this as part of your job, but really, how do you sleep at night? I take back what I said about applying to NVDA. You are just lucky to have survived the layoffs at AMD. Don't rock the boat.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1370475991494</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:46:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370476265536-78</Id><Topic><Title>What's so hard to find, just google "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" lmao</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370475904522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:45:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice, you don't have a link so you send people off, hoping that they might stumble on something. Classy.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1370476265536</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370476376943-79</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablet "crashed a fair bit" running games report says</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370475216738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its not a rumor so stop acting like a fool and READ the article first. Then you can apologize for your acusing BS. imho of course</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370476376943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:52:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370476518409-80</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablet "crashed a fair bit" running games report says</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370475216738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. You mean the article that you have no link to? Speaking of apologizing, when do you apologize for reacting to unsubstantiated T4 rumors. Remember that you don't believe anything about products that aren't currently available for sale? Does that sound familiar? Remember your willful ignorance of the T4 product previews? No?</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1370476518409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:55:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370476522524-81</Id><Topic><Title>What's so hard to find, just google "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" lmao</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370475904522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:45:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, I do have a link but I don't care if Tegra 4 crashes, do you? Anyone with enough brains to type "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" will find it. Were you able to find it? lmao imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370476522524</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:55:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370476821548-82</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablet "crashed a fair bit" running games report says</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370475216738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"LOL. You mean the article that you have no link to? " If you want to keep your head in up between your back pockets after you were told how to find it then have at it. Enjoy the ignorance that comes from not knowing because you prefer to not read. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370476821548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:00:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370477171279-83</Id><Title>Shining a light on Intel silvermont claims</Title><Msg>""ARM hit back at Intel this week at Computex, asserting that its Cortex CPU cores that ship today both outperform and run at lower power than Intel’s future next-gen mobile processor, Silvermont. Cores from the UK-based semiconductor IP group are known for their low-power capabilities and run a vast proportion of the world’s mobile devices. And they’re starting to get known for high performance, as well, such as with the quad Cortex-A15 CPUs built into Tegra 4, the world’s fastest mobile processor. But Intel has recently been claiming that Silvermont is 1.6 times faster and 2.4 times more power efficient than Cortex. ARM dismissed those charges at its event here in Taipei. It showed data with the accompanying chart that compares Cortex against Intel’s Silvermont claims. Based on actual measurements of Intel Atom chips shipping today and Intel’s own claims of future performance, today’s current performance of Cortex-A15 processors are 30% more efficient than Intel’s future Silvermont chip. ARM also noted that Intel’s x86 processors create compatibility issues on Android systems, which require them to “emulate” an ARM processor for apps to run properly. That’s no small issue, as fully 84% of the top games and 64% of top apps use native ARM code. Emulation, unfortunately, has several side effects. For starters, it doesn’t always work. And, when it does work, it degrades performance and burns more energy. That’s because the x86 processor is “emulating” the intended processor’s instruction set, which requires a lot of heavy lifting. In any event, neither option is helpful for a mobile device. There’s a rich tradition from the PC era of opposing architectures failing due to poor emulation results. SPARC, Transmeta and MIPS, among them. The moral of the story is there’s really no need to rely on emulation when so many great ARM-based solutions are already available. blogsDOTnvidiaDOTcom/2013/06/shining-a-light-on-intels-silvermont-mobile-processor-claims/</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370477171279</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:06:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370477319421-84</Id><Topic><Title>What's so hard to find, just google "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" lmao</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370475904522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:45:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good try. You don't have a link, but you don't care... so the truth is no real issue for you. Glad to see you finally admit that. I did see pricing announced for a very nice Toshiba T4 tablet. Pricing. So, is this when you apologize?</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1370477319421</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:08:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370477799108-85</Id><Topic><Title>What's so hard to find, just google "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" lmao</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370475904522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:45:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you really that SLOW? The article's title says something about: "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" Dated June 4th 2013 12:30 PM Search under Google News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" anyone woth a brain should be able to find it now right? lmao Does that sound like a rumor? Or do you need to apologize for your acusing BS? IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370477799108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:16:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370477832189-86</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablet "crashed a fair bit" running games report says</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370475216738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really, I am disappointed. You spin stuff and distort stuff all the time, but making up linkless rumors and bashing people who can't Google stuff that exists mainly in your own. Sad. Well, I guess these is one other option. You don't know that other people can't Google things that exist in your head? Right?</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1370477832189</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:17:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370478036345-87</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablet "crashed a fair bit" running games report says</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370475216738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"this being a pre-production sample, the games we were playing with crashed a fair bit–that’s to be expected"</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1370478036345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:20:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370478054081-88</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablet "crashed a fair bit" running games report says</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370475216738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"bashing people who can't Google" Are you saying you don't know how to use google or yahoo search? Who are you saying can't use google? Can you read? Can you type? If yes to both then what is your problem? Really? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478054081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:20:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370478376398-89</Id><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Msg>And then some of you Nvidia fans can apologize for CALLING NAMES BEFORE READING THE FACTS. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370478418282-90</Id><Topic><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Calm down. No need for 4 posts revolving around the same subject. I understand your hurt.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1370478418282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370478474214-91</Id><Topic><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*you're</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1370478474214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:27:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370478770293-92</Id><Topic><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not my issue. I don't care about Tegra 4 crashing. I'll go out on a limb even further, I don't care about Tegra 4 at all since Tegra 4 is DOA. I didn't point out Tegra 4 crashing but if Nvidia fans want to call names then maybe an Nvidia fans with access to the internet should check the story out first hmm? lol IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478770293</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:32:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370479125500-93</Id><Topic><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next time don't post about the same thing techvest21 did 7 hours ago. Also don't proceed to create two more threads regarding exactly the same thing, with one of them asking for an apology. People on this board don't like you because you spam the hell out of the same information over and over again, and this is a perfect case. This time you actually managed to post something relevant, but you missed the full quote. "this being a pre-production sample, the games we were playing with crashed a fair bit–that’s to be expected"</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1370479125500</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:38:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370479564478-94</Id><Topic><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Next time don't post about the same thing techvest21 did 7 hours ago. Also don't proceed to create two more threads regarding exactly the same thing, with one of them asking for an apology" I am not here running for Ms Congeniality And when I see Nvidia fans jumping all over someone for TELLING THE TRUTH I will point it out as many times as needed to let them know it was wrong. And if that bothers you and the name calling did not then I rubbed the right noses in their own BS. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370479564478</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370479904038-95</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablets Crashing and Overheating</Title><Username>techvest21</Username><Timestamp>1370451278964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forwarded to the company for possible action.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1370479904038</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:51:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370480089044-96</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablets Crashing and Overheating</Title><Username>techvest21</Username><Timestamp>1370451278964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Forwarded to the company for possible action." Did you forward the article or the message board post about the problem in the article? Do you think they'll will fix it before it gones on sale? lmao imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370480089044</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:54:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370480521236-97</Id><Topic><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I will point it out as many times as needed to let them know it was wrong." Clearly this is not your end goal. If that were the case you would just post the link, proving you were right. Instead you make three threads about it, never actually posting the link, and ask for an apology when people get upset at you for it.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1370480521236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 21:02:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370481051663-98</Id><Topic><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Clearly this is not your end goal. If that were the case you would just post the link" Links are not allowed. I do sight sources whne posting an article I quote. But more importantly I DON'T CARE TO HELP YOU DO YOUR HOMEWORK. Yes I created a post to answer EVERY DUMB ACUSING POST I got about claiming it was a rumor, lie or they can't find it. READ all the "I can' t find it" and "Its a rumor" BS. Dod you see your BS there too? And it looks like there should be anoither post for those who WIHINE ABOUT THEY DON'T WANT TO SEE IT. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370481051663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 21:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370481291426-99</Id><Topic><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only post I made was a quote from the article, about how the reviewer stated it was to be expected. "Yes I created a post" *Three posts. Not to mention the countless number of console threads you have made stating the exact same info. At least just bump the same thread, instead of making a new one every week.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1370481291426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 21:14:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370481598514-100</Id><Topic><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The only post I made was a quote from the article, about how the reviewer stated it was to be expected." First Nvidia fans said it didn't happen right? Now you claim "it was to be expected" to happen right? So does that mean it did crash? And why is a tablet running on a Tegra 4 SoC expected to crash ? Sound like PR BS to me. If you show it and let others test it then you don't expect it to crash. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370481598514</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 21:19:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370481644977-101</Id><Topic><Title>Trefis: NVIDIA has huge potential in the mid-range smartphone market</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370454589276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:49:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The CEO conceded Nvidia can not penetrate the smartphone &amp; tablet markets. The smartphone and particularly the tablet market were at the infant stages when you &amp; JJH were hyping Tegra I. EU cited Chinese Huawei and ZTE for violating anti-dumping and anti-subsidy. EU got the Chinese for dumping solar. EU is also looking into steel dumping. US slapped Chinese with solar tariffs and still ongoing for Yuan manipulation. Cheers!</Msg><Username>followon</Username><Timestamp>1370481644977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 21:20:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370481998703-102</Id><Topic><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If you show it and let others test it then you don't expect it to crash." These are questions for Toshiba and the reviewers. It could have been a results of anything in the tablet, hardware or even software. They didn't elaborate, but they certainly didn't seem concerned. "Now you claim "it was to be expected" to happen right?" I don't claim anything by the way, I quoted the article. I never denied this article, I managed to find it, but it is the only review with this crash issue I have found.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1370481998703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 21:26:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370482539420-103</Id><Topic><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"These are questions for Toshiba and the reviewers." And not Nvidia? lol So why are Nvidia fans concerned? Just forget about it then. And from the article since you only quote the article right, did they say if it crashed just one time or was it something like "a fair bit"? Because you keep talking about "a" crash right? lol Does "fair bit" mean "a" crash? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370482539420</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 21:35:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370483465296-104</Id><Topic><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where have I ever said "a crash"? I suggest you actually read my posts. Obviously this is something to think about, and I am not arguing against that, even though this is the only Excite Pro review that has run into this issue that I can find. "And from the article since you only quote the article right, did they say if it crashed just one time or was it something like "a fair bit"?" A fair bit could be due to them running attempting to repeatedly run the same game, which could be a software issue or software/hardware issue. The fact of the matter is that because the reviewers didn't specify the game/games we don't know; once again a question for the reviewers.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1370483465296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 21:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370484185615-105</Id><Topic><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A fair bit could be due to them running attempting to repeatedly run the same game" Whoa, You have me confused with someone who cares why a Tegra 4 tablet would crash. I said I don't care why it crashed or how it crashed only that Nvidia fans called the original post a "rumor" or lie. So I googled "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" and found that article just to check out that post. Just to check, that's all I did. Sounds like some Nvidia fans who own Nvidia should do more checking FIRST and drop the name calling. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370484185615</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 22:03:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370484954073-106</Id><Topic><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good! Mix the honest title in with your fabrication and hope no one will notice the switch. Sad.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1370484954073</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 22:15:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370485548132-107</Id><Topic><Title>Search News for "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash" or "Hands-On With Toshiba’s New Android Tablets:" lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370478376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Good! Mix the honest title in with your fabrication and hope no one will notice the switch. Sad." I found that article using Google search with the key words "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash". So why couldn't you? I DID NOT HAVE THE TITLE BEFORE I FOUND THE ARTICLE. I told YOU here how I found it and how YOU cound find right? Go to google news and see what happens if your enter "Toshiba Tegra 4 Crash". Did google return that article and only that article or is it a "fabrication"? lol I KNOW YOU ARE SLOW BUT PLEASE STOP MAKING A FOOL OF YOURSELF. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370485548132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 22:25:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370488829774-108</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablets Crashing and Overheating</Title><Username>techvest21</Username><Timestamp>1370451278964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone should bring this NEWS up with Nvidia marketing and have them sue this guy or his organization for defamation and false advertisement - take him to the cleaners!</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1370488829774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370489352381-109</Id><Title>If anyone actually READS "Hands-On With Toshiba Tegra 4 Androids Tablets:" its funny</Title><Msg>First Paragraph on the Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablet: : "Toshiba’s just launched a trio of new Android Excite tablets, and on paper they look pretty sweet: a budget £250 machine, and a more interesting pair of Tegra 4-powered tablets that are gunning after the high-end Android tablet market, all powered by sweet sweet stock ‘Droid. In the flesh, though, they don’t exactly live up to their promise. In fact, they’re all-round a little disappointing." Somewhere in here it "crashed a fair bit" playing games Last Paragraph on the Toshiba Tegra 4 Tablet: "All the machines will be available in the UK in Q3, being initially retailed through PC World. To be brutally honest, none of the tablets are really worth the money. The Excite series can certainly play with the best of the current generation of tablets, but with new stuff like the Galaxy Tab 3 and the HP Slatebook X2 coming out in the next few months, I suspect the Excite range will be dead on arrival." Source: Gizmodo Did he say "I suspect the Excite range will be dead on arrival.""? Now where have I heard "dead on arrival" before? lmao imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370489352381</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:29:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370490061089-110</Id><Topic><Title>If anyone actually READS "Hands-On With Toshiba Tegra 4 Androids Tablets:" its funny</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370489352381</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For completeness sake: "Tegra 4-packing tablets get uncomfortably hot when you start pushing them, far more so than any other tablet we’ve played with before." The article also backs up the claim about heat, So the original post said crashing and overheating and there is an article that seems to says both. Is is still a rumor if they had access to the tablets and tested them and published the results with pitcures? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1370490061089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370491191363-111</Id><Topic><Title>Shining a light on Intel silvermont claims</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1370477171279</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:06:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM people talk a lot. Don't see any A15's around except Samsungs Octa which is #$%$. Tegra4 tabets are still not available.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370491191363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:59:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>