<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359090428582-1</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft to launch WP8 reference design -- WITHOUT nvidia,</Title><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1359088245735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 23:30:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You do a good job of re-affirming your ignorance with every post you composed. Qualcomm always had the WP business from the very start, and QC went from 100% to much less, having to giving up some to others like BRCM and MediaTek. You can almost draw an analogy that, one of these days, QC will be just like Apple today, having no where to go but DOWN. And you need a better script to type from - or a new brain if medical advances are made fast enough.</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1359090428582</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 00:07:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359092039006-2</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft to launch WP8 reference design -- WITHOUT nvidia,</Title><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1359088245735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 23:30:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stings like a beach, right? I bet it does. LOSING that new Microsoft Windows Phone 8 reference design. To QUALCOMM and MediaTek. And How many potential Windows 8 phone buyers are there in China?</Msg><Username>dr.bester</Username><Timestamp>1359092039006</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 00:33:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359093598203-3</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft to launch WP8 reference design -- WITHOUT nvidia,</Title><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1359088245735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 23:30:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Microsoft reportedly is cooperating with chipset supplier QUALCOMM on development of Windows Phone 8 reference design aiming to attract more smartphone makers in China to enter production of WP8 phones for the entry-level and midrange smartphone segments in China and other emerging markets, according to industry sources. Microsoft is expected to release the WP8 reference design in mid-2013, with smartphone models built on the reference design to hit the market in the second half of the year, the sources indicated." Sounds like an excellent plan by the Microsoft/QUALCOMM Team. You know -- to capture the Enormous China cellphone market in 2013. A Very Very Good Plan.</Msg><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1359093598203</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 00:59:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359110287122-4</Id><Topic><Title>Limited payments after Blue Monday?!</Title><Username>shaffer.shad</Username><Timestamp>1359052005415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 13:26:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DANGEROUS SCAM VIRUS REPORTED !</Msg><Username>alphonite</Username><Timestamp>1359110287122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 05:38:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359121117143-5</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL sell-off deepening, down 12% and heading lower</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1359054472350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:07:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Will continue to slide until $420 and pause briefly....and decide what to do.' What analysis makes you think that ?</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359121117143</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 08:38:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359121412079-6</Id><Title>U.S. Homeland Chief : Cyber 9/11 could happen "imminently"</Title><Msg>U.S. Homeland Chief : Cyber 9/11 could happen "imminently" Reuters – 15 hrs ago. WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Homeland Security Secretary Janet Napolitano warned on Thursday that a major cyber attack is a looming threat and could have the same sort of impact as last year's Superstorm Sandy, which knocked out electricity in a large swathe of the Northeast. Napolitano said a "cyber 9/11" could happen "imminently" and that critical infrastructure - including water, electricity and gas - was very vulnerable to such a strike. "We shouldn't wait until there is a 9/11 in the cyber world. There are things we can and should be doing right now that, if not prevent, would mitigate the extent of damage," said Napolitano, speaking at the Wilson Center think tank in Washington and referring to the September 11, 2001, attacks. Napolitano runs the sprawling Homeland Security Department that was created 10 years ago in the aftermath of September 11 and charged with preventing another such event. She urged Congress to pass legislation governing cyber security so the government could share information with the private sector to prevent an attack on infrastructure, much of which is privately owned. A cyber security bill failed in Congress last year after business and privacy groups opposed it. The measure would have increased information-sharing between private companies and U.S. intelligence agencies and established voluntary standards for businesses that control power grids or water treatment plants. Business groups said the legislation was government overreach. Privacy groups feared it might lead to Internet eavesdropping. New cyber legislation is being considered, but it is unclear whether it will get through the gridlocked Congress. President Barack Obama is expected to soon issue an executive order that would set up a voluntary system to help protect some critical infrastructure and offer incentives to companies that participate. But without a new law, companies cannot be granted any kind of legal immunity for sharing information with the government and within the industry about potential threats. Officials have pointed to recent hacking attacks on U.S. banks as a sign that the cyber threat is real and growing. "The clarion call is here and we need to be dealing with this very urgently," said Napolitano. "Attacks are coming all the time. They are coming from different sources, they take different forms. But they are increasing in seriousness and sophistication." My my my. The U.S. Homeland Security Department is apparently concerned about "recent hacking attempts" by cyber-dreamer, mister ashraf.eassa "They are coming from different sources, they take different forms, and we need to be dealing with this very urgently," said Napolitano. As was suggested here last week by the Mayor of Bestville (pop. 719), the Feds need to put that ashraf.eassa guy on the B.S. Don't Fly List. Otherwise folks might wake up one morning and say, "What the Heck Happened to the value of my trading account?"</Msg><Username>bnh.police</Username><Timestamp>1359121412079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 08:43:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359122037525-7</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft to launch WP8 reference design -- WITHOUT nvidia,</Title><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1359088245735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 23:30:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post...However QCOM has declined with increased volume in 4 out of the last 10 trading days and is now below its 50 day MA. Now compare that to NVDA which has increased volume on the up days and is over its 50 day MA. (Oh, by the wasy NVDA is up over 1% in premarket). So I guess we will be reading posts from "Broke.Best" and "Crying in my beer.Best" and "I should have Listen to the Long NVDA.Best."in the coming days...</Msg><Username>cobrafish1723</Username><Timestamp>1359122037525</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 08:53:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359122330015-8</Id><Title>bears hearts are about to break..............................</Title><Msg>poor shorty........................</Msg><Username>netttrunner</Username><Timestamp>1359122330015</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 08:58:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359124561485-9</Id><Title>what intel is doing with hpc, nvda dream on with omlette Denver</Title><Msg>google seekingAlpha and mlxn: During the September 11-13th Intel Developer Forum, Intel officially announced its intention to integrate its next-generation CPU with an interconnect device, theoretically cutting out the need for a third-party interconnect provider like Mellanox. Intel's intent was mentioned by multiple press sources and presentations from Intel's technical sessions on the topic are available online. By assembling interconnect technologies and engineering teams from Cray, QLogic, and Fulcrum, Intel should be well positioned to complete its task. But even if Intel doesn't meet its timeline goals, the chipmaker controls the CPU design, allowing it to build a design that only functions optimally with an Intel's interconnect. This integration could potentially provide power and performance synergies as well as cost savings for the end-users. It would also completely box Mellanox out of the high-end HPC (high-performance computing) market. Forget 'cheap' radios, you need interconnect to play the hpc game before long. And nvda ain't got no 'cheap' interconnect. Denver is best served as an omlette.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359124561485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:36:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359124604599-10</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL sell-off deepening, down 12% and heading lower</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1359054472350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:07:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I say 300's before eoy, growth has stopped</Msg><Username>daysofshred30000000000</Username><Timestamp>1359124604599</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:36:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359124793025-11</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Homeland Chief : Cyber 9/11 could happen "imminently"</Title><Username>bnh.police</Username><Timestamp>1359121412079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 08:43:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They won't even bother to try hacking nvda, it's already on its way out.</Msg><Username>amdshortsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1359124793025</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:39:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359125284840-12</Id><Title>AAPL near 52 weeks low, GOOG near 52 weeks high...</Title><Msg>hehe, I can draw a picture for those who are in da nile...no links however :) "trend"lol</Msg><Username>daysofshred30000000000</Username><Timestamp>1359125284840</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:48:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359125396258-13</Id><Topic><Title>time to take some profits</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1359043427121</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 11:03:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As posted earlier...Rookie Mistake, since NVDA has broken through the $12.30 range...on to $13.00</Msg><Username>cobrafish1723</Username><Timestamp>1359125396258</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:49:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359125454797-14</Id><Topic><Title>what intel is doing with hpc, nvda dream on with omlette Denver</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359124561485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:36:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Chipmaker Intel controls the CPU design, allowing it to build a design that only functions optimally with an Intel's interconnect." Oh my! My my my. It looks like a Disconnect coming for those Tesla GPGPU's from nvidia.</Msg><Username>perceptive.best</Username><Timestamp>1359125454797</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:50:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359126919757-15</Id><Topic><Title>what intel is doing with hpc, nvda dream on with omlette Denver</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359124561485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:36:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess we'll all have to wait and see how long this will take to get to market? I think they will be extremely late just as they are low power chips for the ultra mobile market where they still have no design wins. Perhaps they will have some kind of breakthrough around the time the 1.5 billion licensing agreement with Nvidia expires?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1359126919757</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 10:15:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359127027289-16</Id><Topic><Title>what intel is doing with hpc, nvda dream on with omlette Denver</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359124561485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:36:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So here's an idea for Intel's next-generation CPU. "The Intel Defender® CPU". It has a little pass-code, right? And when you try to connect something to it, it asks for the pass-code. So for example, if you connect a Genuine Intel Xeon Pro Graphics Accelerator, the next-generation Intel GPU asks, "Are you friend or foe?" And or course the Genuine Intel Xeon Pro Graphics Accelerator says, "I am a friend -- just from a different Intel profit center." And the next-generation Intel GPU says, "Okay then. You are my friend." But, if you try to connect one of those nvidia Tesla graphics cards, it says, "Hit the curb pal. You are not worthy of connecting." And the next-generation Intel GPU admisisters a one million volt cattle prod to the $2,500 nvidia Tesla graphics cards -- rendering it smoldering junk. Hence the name, "The Intel Defender® GPU".</Msg><Username>bests.idea</Username><Timestamp>1359127027289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 10:17:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359127620939-17</Id><Title>Dear Best...</Title><Msg>See what QLogic Is Doing Today? A Cash Rich, Significantly Undervalued Company That squire ashraf.eassa told the world about And that he is also up ~40% on Guess which company's likely to be next? Nvidia, the Way It's Meant To Be Squeezed</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359127620939</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 10:27:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359127627559-18</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA is looking really delicious. Don't miss out on why!</Title><Username>robertsykes76</Username><Timestamp>1359119815154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 08:16:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks legit</Msg><Username>haydenjeremy942</Username><Timestamp>1359127627559</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 10:27:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359128047984-19</Id><Topic><Title>Dear Best...</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359127620939</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 10:27:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes yes yes. Squire ashraf.eassa's rent is due the first of the month. And the guy has to keep blogging for cash. He's become like a paid hampster on the seekingalpha wheel, u know.</Msg><Username>it_is_best</Username><Timestamp>1359128047984</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 10:34:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359129460898-20</Id><Topic><Title>Dear Best...</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359127620939</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 10:27:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it_is_best, What is your cost basis on your short position?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359129460898</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 10:57:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359129934282-21</Id><Title>weird, I mean weird behavior here...background checks needed</Title><Msg>childish and weird and strange</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1359129934282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:05:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359130405521-22</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH NVDA Analyst Report !</Title><Username>rodriguezwilliam82</Username><Timestamp>1359123428621</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:17:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report , thanks !</Msg><Username>april_simpson</Username><Timestamp>1359130405521</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:13:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359131107764-23</Id><Title>Absolutely Nothing In The Tech Press About Nvidia</Title><Msg>I've been following Nvidia for 3+ years and I have never seen such a quiet period in the Tech Press about Nvidia. Frankly, I don't know what this means. At the Raymond James Tech conference Nvidia's presenter said before beginning his presentation; "I know when I talk about Gaming People's eye's will glaze over" and then proceeded to talk about Gaming and almost nothing about mobile. At CES Jensen appears to be doubling down on Gaming with the Project Shield and Nvidia Grid. Again nothing on mobile design wins. All the traders are breathlessly waiting for news about mobile, but nothing so far. Surely it will come...but trader and option players live for volatility....Too bad I say! I am of the camp that Nvidia's earnings and revenue will improve because of Nvidia's refocus on it's core Gaming. Mobile for Nvidia is looking like a back half 2013 and 2014 story. In the meantime I expect they will manage the mobile division on expenses and run the mobile division as a business I would be tickled pink if I could get $15-$16 for my shares in a year or so. In the meantime dividend is nice and the lack of volatility is even better. Of course Nvidia could actually be buying back shares to the tune of 100 million. But that is so out of character for Nvidia. Besides, most companies initiate buying back shares when the stock is high, not at a low. But Nvidia completely surprised me with the dividend so just perhaps they are buying shares down at these prices, and I won't have to wait a year or so for $15 to $16. Won't hurt my feelings at all if Jensen fools me again!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359131107764</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:25:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359132978404-24</Id><Topic><Title>Absolutely Nothing In The Tech Press About Nvidia</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359131107764</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:25:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with you 100%. I am stuck with $15 and wiating to hit $15 to cover my losses and time I wasted. I should had made way more money playing some other stock. Again I hope to get to $15 soon.</Msg><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1359132978404</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:56:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359133241771-25</Id><Topic><Title>what intel is doing with hpc, nvda dream on with omlette Denver</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359124561485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:36:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would there be a antitrust lawsuit against Intel,if that happens,that can put lots of company out of business and that will create a monopoly. JIMO.</Msg><Username>jin_18do8</Username><Timestamp>1359133241771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:00:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359133616598-26</Id><Title>Up a cent, pretty soon a RED candle</Title><Msg>POS. Got no legs, an empty suit. Get a new CEO, this stock headed for new low.</Msg><Username>dastelryd</Username><Timestamp>1359133616598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:06:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359133833405-27</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA is looking really delicious. Don't miss out on why!</Title><Username>robertsykes76</Username><Timestamp>1359119815154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 08:16:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow great stuff cant wait</Msg><Username>jayvogt</Username><Timestamp>1359133833405</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:10:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359133836674-28</Id><Topic><Title>Absolutely Nothing In The Tech Press About Nvidia</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359131107764</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:25:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bought at $11.50 and came back only because Nvidia announced a dividend. Before when trading Nvidia you could play the "Tech Press" articles and swing trade reliably knowing that the hype would not live up to the billing, but your amount of sleep might be affected. Who will ever forget the run-up 2 years ago. New Product companies live by the buzz and die by not continuing to introduce more buzz and fall drastically when the buzz stops.....ala Apple! It just appears to me that Jensen has been chastised enough by the hype and buzz to just concentrate on making profits and growing the business steadily. IMHO, the pieces are in place for Nvidia to be a very reliable growth and income stock allowing one to buy for the long term...or at least the semiconductor cycle. If CNBC fast money boys start talking about Nvidia again.....then get ready to pull the trigger and get out. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359133836674</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:10:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359134780640-29</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA is looking really delicious. Don't miss out on why!</Title><Username>robertsykes76</Username><Timestamp>1359119815154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 08:16:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great strategy imo</Msg><Username>francisco.wright</Username><Timestamp>1359134780640</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:26:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359134951678-30</Id><Topic><Title>what intel is doing with hpc, nvda dream on with omlette Denver</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359124561485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:36:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whosunw, tell us a shred of info about Denver &amp; interconnect... btw, did you cook your crow... or took it raw...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359134951678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:29:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359136130523-31</Id><Topic><Title>Up a cent, pretty soon a RED candle</Title><Username>dastelryd</Username><Timestamp>1359133616598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:06:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least you make it easy to put you on ignore. Bye bye.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1359136130523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:48:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359137132666-32</Id><Title>The Best!!</Title><Msg>Good news to come!!!</Msg><Username>justsemi</Username><Timestamp>1359137132666</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:05:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359137195113-33</Id><Title>Apple market capitalization falls below Exxon's today</Title><Msg>Exactly a year after AAPL took the top spot. Analysts say that margin calls will fuel further decline. AAPL will test the $400 - $410 area.</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1359137195113</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:06:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359137897322-34</Id><Topic><Title>what intel is doing with hpc, nvda dream on with omlette Denver</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359124561485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:36:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Question to Best... Which one is going to hit $20.00 price per share first INTC or NVDA?</Msg><Username>cobrafish1723</Username><Timestamp>1359137897322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:18:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359137995178-35</Id><Title>MSFT SHOULD BUY NVDA</Title><Msg>They need "hardware" end of the mobile market.</Msg><Username>bootis0</Username><Timestamp>1359137995178</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:19:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359138241635-36</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT SHOULD BUY NVDA</Title><Username>bootis0</Username><Timestamp>1359137995178</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish, at $21/- . what price you think, MSFT should but at. Thanks.</Msg><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1359138241635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:24:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359138574428-37</Id><Title>Lord Please Let Nvidia Never Be Discussed On CNBC</Title><Msg>CNBC has turned into a Reality TV show work NYC hedge funds. Pathetic and Disgusting! Stay Away from these Bozos Jensen. Keep quiet and run the business in the businesses you know how to run better than anyone. JMHO Love the Dividend....Don't you?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359138574428</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:29:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359139764753-38</Id><Topic><Title>time to take some profits</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1359043427121</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 11:03:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"sold half - NVDA will either announce earnings date today or, pre-announce earnings." this stock just ain't for you...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359139764753</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:49:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359140462137-39</Id><Topic><Title>time to take some profits</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1359043427121</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 11:03:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold all - out of NVDA, revisit after earnings. smartphone/tablet party is getting stale. NVDA is looking like value trap - no eps growth.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1359140462137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 14:01:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359140553597-40</Id><Title>aapl can't develope cpu/gpu efficiently anymore, serves them right</Title><Msg>for not using nvidia to do the job..... apple wanted the whole pie, they became pigs...</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1359140553597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 14:02:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359141980316-41</Id><Title>O.Investor do you think we should go long</Title><Msg>Just like the long one that will be stuck up your S when your boyfriend finds out you sold too soon</Msg><Username>galondan</Username><Timestamp>1359141980316</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 14:26:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359143655722-42</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT SHOULD BUY NVDA</Title><Username>bootis0</Username><Timestamp>1359137995178</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of all the improbable buyout rumors involving nVidia, I think MSFT would have a slight better than zero chance of acquiring nVidia - a better chance than Google - but still improbable. Intel has almost ZERO chance of being an acquirer in this case. JMHO.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359143655722</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 14:54:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359144538814-43</Id><Topic><Title>aapl can't develope cpu/gpu efficiently anymore, serves them right</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1359140553597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 14:02:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>where did you find this?</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1359144538814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 15:08:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359144945292-44</Id><Topic><Title>aapl can't develope cpu/gpu efficiently anymore, serves them right</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1359140553597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 14:02:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>conjecture, of course apple will not publish their own shortcomings...aapl gross profit margins on the decline.... their own in house cpu/gpu design teams cannot compete dollar for dollar with Nvidia.... Jen knows this as well and I am sure nvidia is making the sales call..</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1359144945292</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 15:15:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359146384092-45</Id><Title>Jeepers Best. She's up $.22 -- Just $2.44 short of last year.</Title><Msg>It's fun to watch the pumper boyz cheer wildly. Oh so wildly. On the one-in-ten days that nvidia actually goes up. Like right now -- nvidia is currently up $.22 But it's Friday afternoon, and we All know what happens to nvidia on Friday afternoons. Yes we do. Anyway, nvidia still has a loooong ways to go. For the folks that bought a year ago to break even. When nvidia was at $14.85. On January 25, 2012. The good 'ole days, right boys? Ha ha ha ha!</Msg><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1359146384092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 15:39:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359147269613-46</Id><Topic><Title>Jeepers Best. She's up $.22 -- Just $2.44 short of last year.</Title><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1359146384092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 15:39:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today's $12.41 might look like Good Money a month from now, boys. After the Mobile World Congress in Barcelona, February 25-28, 2013. The CES in Las Vegas chopped (-7.5%) off of nvda, right? It sure did. So Another (-7.5%) off is Eleven and a half bucks -- after the equally disasterous MWC. Did I mention? Today's $12.41 might look like Good Money a month from now.</Msg><Username>perceptive.best</Username><Timestamp>1359147269613</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 15:54:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359148285942-47</Id><Title>mr best is a pure taunter. strange dude</Title><Msg>he is what is wrong with america</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1359148285942</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 16:11:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359149002715-48</Id><Topic><Title>mr best is a pure taunter. strange dude</Title><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1359148285942</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 16:11:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm still trying to figure out why they let him post from a computer at the sanitarium?</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1359149002715</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 16:23:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359149242218-49</Id><Topic><Title>Dear Best...</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359127620939</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 10:27:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What is your cost basis on your short position?" You must be new to this investing business, right squire ashraf.eassa? There is no cost basis, since it cost Best zero to short nvidia. Not a bent Canadian penny. Zilch, nada, goose egg. In fact, selling nvidia short creates a Huge Credit Balance in your account. Without spending any money. In Best's case, he just called-up the polite folks at Fidelity's High Net Worth Client group and said, "I understand you boys have a Lot of nvda to lend out." "Yes" they whispered, sheepishly. "I would like to borrow as much of your nvda as you would like to lend me" said Best, profitably. "Yes Mister Best." And the next thing you know, Best has a Huge Credit Balance in his account. Yards and yards of Cash. That just keeps growing and growing and growing. An INFINITE Cash-on-Cash Return it's called. Since it never cost you even a penny.</Msg><Username>best.short</Username><Timestamp>1359149242218</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 16:27:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359151242605-50</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Homeland Chief : Cyber 9/11 could happen "imminently"</Title><Username>bnh.police</Username><Timestamp>1359121412079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 08:43:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amd shorts are fools?.. worthless worthless worthless... both you and your account</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1359151242605</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:00:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359151436882-51</Id><Title>S&amp;P closes above 1500 for the first time in five years...</Title><Msg>Shorts need to pay attention....bulls are running in your path.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359151436882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:03:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359151636554-52</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P closes above 1500 for the first time in five years...</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359151436882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:03:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Per WSJ: S&amp;P 500 Closes Above 1500 for First Time in Five Years The S&amp;P 500 closed above 1500 for the first time in five years on Friday, capping its longest streak of daily gains since 2004. The Standard &amp; Poor's 500-stock index tacked on 8.14 points, or 0.5%, to 1502.96, its highest close since Dec. 10, 2007. The index rose for an eighth session in a row, the longest such streak since a nine-day run ended in November 2004. The Dow Jones Industrial Average advanced 70.65 points, or 0.5%, to 13895.98. The Nasdaq Composite Index gained 19.33 points, or 0.6%, to 3149.71.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359151636554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:07:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359153214590-53</Id><Topic><Title>Lord Please Let Nvidia Never Be Discussed On CNBC</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359138574428</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:29:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you saw what the NYC CNBC Bozo's did to Apple stock in the last 2 seconds. Made a fortune I'm sure on the weekly options. Is there anyway a company can have their stock delisted from weekly options?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359153214590</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:33:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359153776063-54</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P closes above 1500 for the first time in five years...</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359151436882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:03:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"S&amp;P 500 Closes Above 1,500 for First Time in Five Years." That's really Good News for the S&amp;P 500 Index, right boys? It sure is. But that's Not what you invested in here. Oh no no no. You unfortunately bought nvda -- Not the S&amp;P 500. For comparison purposes, do you know that the Five (5) Year closing high for nvidia is? Hummm? $26.85 On February 13, 2008 So while the S&amp;P 500 Index is setting new Five (5) Year highs, your precious nvidia is trading at Less than half of it's comparable high. Do try to pick a better stock for the next five years, boys.</Msg><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1359153776063</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:42:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359154429491-55</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P closes above 1500 for the first time in five years...</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359151436882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:03:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"S&amp;P 500 Closes Above 1,500 for First Time in Five Years." That's really Good News for the S&amp;P 500 Index, right boys? It sure is. But that's Not what you invested in here. Oh no no no. You unfortunately bought nvda -- Not the S&amp;P 500. For comparison purposes, do you know what the Five (5) Year closing high for nvidia is? Hummm? $26.85 On February 13, 2008 So while the S&amp;P 500 Index is setting new Five (5) Year highs, your precious nvidia is trading at Less than half of it's comparable high. So Master? Is that why we never see anybody hyping the S&amp;P 500 Index of Good Stocks? Like never. 'Cause the Good Stocks do good on their own. It's the really dog stocks -- like nvidia -- that are always being hyped. You know. By their current bagholders.</Msg><Username>best.clone185</Username><Timestamp>1359154429491</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:53:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359154594967-56</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH NVDA Analyst Report !</Title><Username>rodriguezwilliam82</Username><Timestamp>1359123428621</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:17:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful info, thanks</Msg><Username>georgethompson382</Username><Timestamp>1359154594967</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:56:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359159381452-57</Id><Title>Qualcomm job postings: 64-bit ARMv8 designers wanted</Title><Msg>Fudzilla: Qualcomm is advertising at least three software engineering positions that seem to indicate it is gearing up to enter the ARM server market. According to EE Times, the chipmaker is looking for designers who know their way around ARMv8-based server SoC ASICs and can deal with development, porting and integration of server platform management software and firmware. In plain English, Qualcomm is apparently working on 64-bit server SoCs. Although the company is the clear market leader in the ARM space, it never really focused on server parts. Other players, including AMD, Marvell, Samsung and Nvidia have also announced plans to enter the ARM server market. The first shipments of 64-bit server SoCs are expected next year, but Calxeda and Marvell are already shipping 32-bit SoCs for servers, but in limited numbers. ____ If the Q guys just started this, they may be playing catching up. as NVIDIA Project Boulder is well underway....</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359159381452</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 19:16:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359161283971-58</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT SHOULD BUY NVDA</Title><Username>bootis0</Username><Timestamp>1359137995178</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$18 now, in 6 months $23.</Msg><Username>koaylaber</Username><Timestamp>1359161283971</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 19:48:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359162072749-59</Id><Title>AAPL: "flash dump" closes stock at $439.88 - not the doing of retail investors or talk show</Title><Msg>SOURCE: Barrons Apple (AAPL) shares closed down $10.62, or 2.4%, at $439.88 this afternoon. ZeroHedge’s Tyler Durden points us to what appears to have been a “flash dump” in the closing moments of the market, noting a large block of $350 million worth of stock in the waning minutes of the session: Unlike traditional flash crashes where the trade is an HFT error, or a few shares traded through the entire bid or offer stack, in this case it looks like a very premeditated unloading of some 800K shares (some $350 million worth) of AAPL in the last second, with the full knowledge it was shake the market. Why anyone would want (or wait until the very last second) to do that, while covering the offsetting ES short in the pair trade, to ramp the market into the close, is anyone’s guess. .......</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359162072749</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 20:01:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359166002218-60</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL: "flash dump" closes stock at $439.88 - not the doing of retail investors or talk show</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359162072749</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 20:01:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the point is?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359166002218</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 21:06:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359172303499-61</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT SHOULD BUY NVDA</Title><Username>bootis0</Username><Timestamp>1359137995178</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish, Thanks</Msg><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1359172303499</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:51:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>