<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-17"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366173717785-1</Id><Topic><Title>Are there any phones with Icera around? Or is it just Jensen's BS.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366162591263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 21:36:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NVIDIA sold 20 million units of Icera I4100 units which is certified by ATT LTE network. You obviously didn't do your homework before coming out here bashing. The number came from last week;s investors presentation by NVIDIA executives. Several ASUS tablets (at least two) use this radio. One is a ASUS TF transformer and the other is ASUS' Win RT model. Can't hurt for you to be just a tad smarter - you might even get a raise from your hedge employer.</Msg><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1366173717785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 00:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366177529449-2</Id><Topic><Title>new iphones delayed 1 Q</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1366157979609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:19:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whosunw, I will give you a few points to practice thinking with, since you are notoriously known as not having a thinking process in place. iPhone delay will hurt BRCM the most outside of Apple itself. Broadcom has been used increasingly as a supplier by Apple, from the original iphone to iphone 2,3,4, 5 and the ipads. Without income stream from Apple, BRCM will lose a big chunk of its revenue. Qualcomm is more broadly based; it will get hurt a lot less. Secondly, have you heard - iPhone is no longer COOL. One piece of evidence is that the iphones are now being sold at Walmart. Many of the fanboys get so turned off by Apple's desperate move to go lower in its marketing stretch. Several recent Apple commercial are still trying to make the point that the iGears are so oh so cool, but you know what, to paraphrase Margaret Thatcher who used to say: "Being powerful is like being a lady, if you have to tell people you are, then you aren't". Apple will be on a sustained decline as long as Tim Cook is the boss who is incapable of coming up with any innovative ideas. Broadcom had better look for an alternative customer before it's too late.</Msg><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1366177529449</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 01:45:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366180930900-3</Id><Topic><Title>new iphones delayed 1 Q</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1366157979609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:19:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whosunw, Why do you troll these boards? I ask this legitimately and would like a straight answer.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1366180930900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 02:42:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366197487520-4</Id><Topic><Title>new iphones delayed 1 Q</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1366157979609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:19:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is this the nvda board or is this the whosunw board? do you care about the business prospects of nvda or do you care about my wellbeing? I ask these questions legitimately.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1366197487520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 07:18:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366203831509-5</Id><Title>Today should be interesting</Title><Msg>Given INTC's earnings "miss" and guidance being lowered, it will be quite interesting to see how its stock and others like NVDA fare, today. INTC was initially a lot higher, right after the release, then sold off and was down 1+% at one point in AH trading. However, so far in the pre-market, it's holding at a loss of less than 1% and we'll see whether or not the "PC is dying" trade has already pretty much played out, or whether the Bears can muster one more downdraft based on a story that is NOT "news". With the overall market looking to open down 3/4-1%, there will certainly be an attempt to hit the semis, once again. CRUS is getting CRUShsed, in the pre-market, based on their earnings, and TXN was down last night by 2% on no news. IF these stocks do NOT get hit real hard, I would venture a guess that that will prove that this is now old news and already in the stocks, and therefore we could actually see them rally, later, unless we get another 150-250 point drop overall. Also of interest, especially to Ashraf I'd think, is that ARMH is actually UP 1.75% in the pre-market, and whether it's just as an "anti-INTC" trade OR because of the announcement of the extension of their partnership with Arteris, I would suggest that ARMH at anything under 40 is a buy. It has been pushed below 40 at least 3 or 4 times the last few weeks, and each time it has bounced right back. My take is that regardless of its "valuation", the stock is headed to 45-50 in the not too distant future. NVDA is likely to be tested, once again, but as long as we don't break back down under 12.50 on huge volume, any downdraft is just "noise". And, if we DON'T stay down for more than an hour or two (or less), and if INTC actually turns higher (which I think is likely), then NVDA should resume its climb and get back over 13 and grind higher. A move above 13.23-25 will constitute a further break out and we will be setting up for some fireworks for the end of the week OpEx. AAWKITFOT Max</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366203831509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:03:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366209354263-6</Id><Topic><Title>Today should be interesting</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366203831509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:03:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bingo! GREAT action, and really good volume, too, and we are now down 3 cents. INTC had tried to recover, but fell back a little bit. But, ALL the other semis are down MUCH more, and NVDA should be the one to turn first and lead us higher. With 3mm shares in the first hour, I think today IS going to be a good one. I don't care WHO is buying, whether it be the company or the shorts, but it's pretty clear that the "floor" under this stock is rising and just watch what happens when/if we get back over 13 and then 13.23-25. As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. Max</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366209354263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:35:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366209431974-7</Id><Topic><Title>Today should be interesting</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366203831509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:03:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with your opinion. I am very happy to see how NVDA is trading today. it augurs something very positive. of course, it's just a feeling that the selling interest is minimal at this juncture.</Msg><Username>jtjgmtbt</Username><Timestamp>1366209431974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:37:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366210102426-8</Id><Title>AAPL made a new 52 wk low today, all food chain stocks (BRCM, QCOM) tank big time</Title><Msg>AAPL: down 4.87% BRCM: down 3.53% QCOM: down 1.76% INTC: down 0.98% NVDA: down 0.25%</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366210102426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366211375850-9</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL made a new 52 wk low today, all food chain stocks (BRCM, QCOM) tank big time</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366210102426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reason for Apple's (and food chain stocks) steep drop is that Cirrus Logic warned significant rev shortfalls for CY Q1 and Q2 and AAPL is CRUS's largest audio chip supplier. Analysts figure that this could translate into a 10% drop in iPhone shipments annually, from 60 million units down to 55 millions or lower. Separately, Digitimes reported this morning that iPAD mini will see reduced shipments by 20-30% as consumers awaiting the next refresh.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366211375850</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 11:09:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366214225607-10</Id><Topic><Title>Today should be interesting</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366203831509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:03:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kvimax1, Always love your posts, but I respectfully disagree on ARMH. It will never see $45 again. This is similar to AAPL at $650 or CRUS at $37. Overhyped and will soon disappoint. You really think ARMH is worth $20B? This thing needs to be at more like $15 - $20 to be anything close to sensibly valued ;) Nvidia is a deep value play, and I think it is easily worth $20/share...probably more. Intel didn't guide down - their guidance for the year was reaffirmed and Q2 guide was better than the street - so I'm pretty sure this marks the beginning of the end of the funk surrounding PC levered names. Intel's higher end "Core" business is still doing fine, and HPC is doing great, so this means good things for Nvidia's PC GPU + Tesla business.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1366214225607</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 11:57:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366214862180-11</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL made a new 52 wk low today, all food chain stocks (BRCM, QCOM) tank big time</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366210102426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AAPL heading for UNDER $400!</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366214862180</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 12:07:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366215553848-12</Id><Topic><Title>Today should be interesting</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366203831509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:03:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf....I'll bet you a nickel, CASH...NO IOU...that ARMH does hit 45. And, NVDA is much more than a deep value play. It's a major growth story and people are beginning to realize that the new TAM is so much bigger than they ever dreamed it would or could be, and it is surely worth 20 or more, NOW, but it will take us a little longer to get there. If you're holding a true short (rather than puts) on ARMH, I seriously "suggest" you take advantage of getting it below 40 and cover, and you can then, of course, short it from a higher level when it gets there...;) It is in no way like AAPL nor CRUS, in my opinion. Shorting based on "valuation" is NOT a winning strategy. As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. Max</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366215553848</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 12:19:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366215920958-13</Id><Topic><Title>Today should be interesting</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366203831509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:03:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kvimax1 (&amp; ashraf) I think the general market is getting spooked by all the news regarding the boston bombings and now these letters to leaders in Washington DC. I'm encouraged that Nvidia is holding up and like what you guys are saying, but I'm just wondering how these other news items are making the price action too unpredictable at the moment to know what is happening short-term. The sooner we have news of some group or individual found responsible for the bombings and now these letters the better for the markets. I'd like to think the market will be less volatile after OpEx week but I'm not so sure now.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1366215920958</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 12:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366216333478-14</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL made a new 52 wk low today, all food chain stocks (BRCM, QCOM) tank big time</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366210102426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The Decline of the Apple Empire" by Gibbon, Jr. :) AAPL down 5.8% BRCM down 4.1% QCOM down 2.3% INTC down 1.2% NVDA down 0.7%</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366216333478</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 12:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366216890754-15</Id><Topic><Title>Today should be interesting</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366203831509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:03:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RH_C...Yes, the market IS spooked, and the Bears have been SO beat up, they're taking this "news" as a major opportunity to try to get a Big "C" going...(sorry, the word represented by the "C" is one of the most insulting terms used by Wall St. and I won't say it out loud). My belief is that even this kind of news will NOT succeed in getting them what they want/need, but sure, we could have a sell off or profit-taking that takes the general market down 2, 3, 5%, but I doubt much more than that. I'm one of the few who believe we've already entered a "New Secular Bull Market", and given that view, any lower prices are great buying opps. As for NVDA, as I said, this is GREAT action, and the volume is terrific, but it's clear to ME, at least, that the "tenor" of how this stock trades DID change, last week, and it is the only one of its peers, other than ARMH, that has been green, today....well, NOK, but I'm talking semis. I still expect NVDA to close higher, and with volume already 1 hour ahead of yesterday, I think we'll see 12-15mm and a close over 13. The question is how high. But it is showing AMAZING relative strength, here, and it just doesn't matter WHO the buyer is...it's NOT going to go down in a major way...not at this point, unless the entire market goes down MUCH more...250-350 points. One last thing for our friend, Ashraf. I do think it might be helpful for you to consider ARMH to be much more akin to AMZN or CRM, which have looked like great short candidates for how many years now, and ALL the shorts have been carried out on their cardboard boxes...;) Just trying to help. As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. Max</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366216890754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 12:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366221539187-16</Id><Topic><Title>Today should be interesting</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366203831509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:03:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Max, I think the quality of NVDA ownership has improved steadily. Many hedge funds left, and so did a bunch of retail traders at the stock's recent trough - around the week of March 25. Those who remained are likely long-term holders and believers of JH's vision. PS: still waiting for the news that you would play Zero's role in Fiddler on the Roof on Broadway. :)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366221539187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 13:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366221717554-17</Id><Title>Just inLaw enforcement officers believe a suspect in Boston explosion has been identified</Title><Msg>Source: Reuters</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1366221717554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366222026085-18</Id><Topic><Title>Today should be interesting</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366203831509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:03:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>:) Well, not likely Broadway, but a good chance I'll be doing it here, in Woodstock, next year...I'll let you know when it's "official". Yes, that is my point...they've "changed partners", which is VERY positive..INTC now higher, and NVDA should follow soon. M</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366222026085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:07:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366224434894-19</Id><Topic><Title>Today should be interesting</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366203831509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:03:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorting based on "valuation" is NOT a winning strategy. Shorting because everyone is drunk off their #$%$ thinking that ARM vendors will take any meaningful server share is a winning strategy. Nailed Applied Micro short at ~$9 after it got hyped up for these reasons, and I believe the October run for ARMH was heavily influenced by the ARMv8 hype. Also, as much as I love Nvidia, Windows RT and Warren East's PC domination dreams are not going to come to fruition. That's why I am happy that Jen Hsun has been pushing Android...the volume is there and it is not at a disadvantage. As you say, we will know in the fullness of time. While we wait, I look forward to more of your posts, as you always have something interesting and insightful to say. Regards, Ashraf</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1366224434894</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366224981707-20</Id><Topic><Title>Today should be interesting</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366203831509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:03:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess that means we don't have a bet? While my experience surely doesn't make me "right" all the time, I HAVE been doing this for much longer than you've been alive. I'm trying to help you NOT make some of the mistakes I made when I was younger. Please, please, please NEVER say "NEVER" when it comes to the stock market. And, what I was saying was don't short SOLELY based on "valuation", as both AMZN and CRM are great cases in point. CRM is probably THE MOST overvalued stock of the last 10 years, but for the most part, the shorts that have used valuation as the metric for their decision to short it have been crushed. ARMH will go higher, regardless, and I do hope you understand that taking the attitude that it will "never see 45" is a youthful way to look at it and could very well be very painful, too. I wish you well, either way, and still will be happy to bet that nickel, CASH... As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. M</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366224981707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366234031960-21</Id><Topic><Title>Today should be interesting</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1366203831509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:03:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kvimax1, I'll bet you the nickel :) Every bubble needs a catalyst. My view is that by the end of the year, the myth that Intel can't compete in mobile will be busted, and along with it the ARMH bubble. I don't know what it would take the pop the AMZN/CM bubbles. ARM may see $45 again, but in my view, it will go much lower before we see that again. And of course I wish you well. You are a credit to this board, and a really sharp guy. Regards, Ashraf</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1366234031960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 17:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366245635935-22</Id><Title>Stock buybacks</Title><Msg>Last quarter Nvidia gave their investment banker instructions to buyback $100M. When settled they got 8.3M shares for an average price of $11.94. At the investment day presentation, Nvidia management said they were going to buy back $100M this quarter and $600M spread over Q2, Q3, and Q4. I've seen lots of Accelerated stock buybacks in Semi's, but this one is strange. It's so piece mill, usually companies jump the shark and do it quickly...not spread over 5 quarters. This begs the question......Are they trying to play the summer slowdown and get a better price or is Nvidia thinking that their investment banker being in the market opportunistically puts a floor on the price per share. And if so, why not buy at the cheapest price. Have no idea, what do you think?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1366245635935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 20:40:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>