<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363937836066-1</Id><Topic><Title>ARM to help second-tier IC designers to catch up, DigiTimes reports</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1363921666940</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:07:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"ARM Holdings (ARMH) is considering plans to provide complete platform solutions to help second-tier IC design houses catchup with Qualcom (QCOM) and Nvidia (NVDA) in 2013" Really now... "The only way Arm can compete with Intel is to try to reduce cost." yet ARM keeps growing... and INtel hit with another PC declining forecast... " How cheap can Nvidia make a Tegra?" Tegra is 80 sq mm... so cheaper than anyone...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363937836066</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 03:37:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363948463090-2</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agee, its going to June or perhaps as long as late August before lift off but after that its all systems go. We need a few high profile T4 wins on smartphone and tablet wins to shake the doubters. the Grid play is incredible, and will pay off in calendar 2014</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1363948463090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 06:34:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363951149538-3</Id><Topic><Title>Jensen On Nvidia Grid and Project Shield Revenue and Profitability</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363919568340</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 22:32:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"As previously reported, Project Shield will be available in 2Q13. It sports a quad-core Tegra 4 SoC, a 5-inch capacitive multi-touch screen, and Google's full-blown Android "Jelly Bean" OS. There are also two built-in speakers, Wireless-N connectivity, HDMI output, a microUSB port, a microSD card slot, 32 GB of internal storage and 2 GB of RAM." Good article from Hands on Test of project Shield From Tom's Hardware tomshardwareDOTcom/news/Project-Shield-Tegra-4-Hands-On-Pricing-Jelly-Bean,21649.html</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363951149538</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 07:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363957656115-4</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just subscribed. I am hoping for the best.</Msg><Username>phraseursvicky</Username><Timestamp>1363957656115</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 09:07:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363959644390-5</Id><Title>Looks Set to Double in Value Next Week - Must Read!</Title><Msg>Concurrent (CCUR) looks ready to double in value next week currently $7.76 only has 9.2mm o/s with $24.6mm in cash no debt enterprise value of only $46.79mm or 0.75x revenue of $62.59mm. CCUR has the lowest multiple in the industry when its gross margins of 58% are the second highest. Seachange (SEAC) along with CCUR are the two leading video on demand (VOD) companies and together they control the global VOD market with a combined market share of over 50%. SEAC has lower gross margins of 50% yet it's trading with enterprise value/revenue ratio of 1.9, which would value CCUR at $15.60 per share. SEAC is a money losing company while CCUR's net income has been exploding! CCUR's EPS last quarter was double the quarter before and quadruple two quarters ago. Virgin Media (VMED) just chose CCUR's multi-screen video delivery platform MediaHawk over SEAC's platform. SEAC was providing traditional VOD services to VMED so for VMED to choose CCUR for their new Virgin TV Anywhere platform is HUGE. There is a good chance CCUR will replace SEAC's software for traditional VOD at VMED before long as well! VMED is the #1 largest cable TV company in the UK with 3.8 million subscribers! CCUR also just announced the signing of an undisclosed Top 5 North American pay-TV company! Together these two major new clients could potentially allow CCUR's EPS to once again double, triple, or quadruple over the next 2-3 quarters! Major consolidation is taking place in this space and CCUR and SEAC have been rumored takeover targets, Google it to see for yourself! If neither of them get boughtout, SEAC has enough cash to acquire CCUR for a huge premium of $12 per share and it would still be very accretive to their earnings! CCUR has the best looking chart in the market today and looks ready to absolutely explode today!</Msg><Username>frankf4u489</Username><Timestamp>1363959644390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 09:40:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363959708659-6</Id><Title>DOA NVDA</Title><Msg>This stock is so dead in the water. Say buh bye To most of their main revenue sources and hello To inability to generate new ones</Msg><Username>mdlugolecki</Username><Timestamp>1363959708659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 09:41:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363961107345-7</Id><Topic><Title>DOA NVDA</Title><Username>mdlugolecki</Username><Timestamp>1363959708659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 09:41:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a strong short, eh? put your money up big boy</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1363961107345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 10:05:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363961443495-8</Id><Title>Guesses on Q4 sales?</Title><Msg>Wonder what the revenue run rate will look like by the fourth quarter? I still can't get my mind around this valuation. The market just isn't giving Nvidia credit for any of its new initiatives, even though the company has lots of cash and is still highly profitable. Jen is clearly under pressure to get the stock price up. I wonder what else he can do...</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363961443495</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 10:10:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363962584557-9</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job. Informational article.</Msg><Username>licnobiomae</Username><Timestamp>1363962584557</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 10:29:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363963118973-10</Id><Topic><Title>Guesses on Q4 sales?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363961443495</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 10:10:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New initiatives affect price as sales materialize. Investment in Grid has been going on for over a year. Servers from IBM, HP, and Dell hitting the market now. VCA next quarter. Love the reoccuring revenue stream from each Grid GPU every year. And of course --- Share buybacks and they are happening. Shouldn't take too long to buyback back 75M to 100M shares at these prices. $100M last quarter..done ..$300M this quarter? $300M next quarter? Gotta get the share share count down to where it was 3 years ago before the revenue and earnings rise. Most companies buy at the top with a few exception....Nvidia is buying at the bottom Then some Tegra 4 action sometime in couple of months, and the big question mark "Project Shield". The Tech Press will have a field day but Nvidia will make money on each and every one. Nvidia is paying us a dividend to wait....Enjoy the Dividend. Sells some calls if you like. Spring is here.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363963118973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 10:38:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363963494325-11</Id><Topic><Title>DOA NVDA</Title><Username>mdlugolecki</Username><Timestamp>1363959708659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 09:41:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just another drive-by idiot.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363963494325</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 10:44:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363964860345-12</Id><Topic><Title>DOA NVDA</Title><Username>mdlugolecki</Username><Timestamp>1363959708659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 09:41:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1 post | Last Activity: 1 hour 24 minutes ago Member since: Mar 22, 2013. A reincarnated short at that...LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363964860345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:07:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363965219852-13</Id><Topic><Title>DOA NVDA</Title><Username>mdlugolecki</Username><Timestamp>1363959708659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 09:41:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even though Nvidia's performance on a yearly basis is slightly higher than I expected, there was a decrease of 8% in quarterly performance, which was due to weaker Tegra sales (even though there was a transition from Tegra 3 to Tegra 4) and a drop in desktop GPU sales. Additionally, increases in operating expenses have outnumbered the revenue. This trend isn't expected to reverse in near future. In comparison to competitors QCOM (NASDAQ: QCOM) and AMD (NYSE: AMD) Nvidia's performance is not up to the mark. Its lack of smartphone penetration isn't going to pick up in the coming future as Tegra 4 faces intense competition, and vertical integration by OEM handsets will further worsen the situation. Hence, future revenue, which is primarily based on Tegra, may not increase as expected. High dependence on HTC, which itself is losing market share, adds additional negativity to Nvidia's performance. Recently, Nvidia's loss of the Google nexus platform to QCOM, plus poor performance of Microsoft Surface tablet sales, makes Nvidia a less lucrative stock. I expect that economic scenario will further worsen, making competition more aggressive. If the economic scenario deteriorates, this will further reduce consumer demand for PCs. The PC market generates about 80% of Nvidia’s revenue. This high dependence on a particular segment, i.e. PC sales, will make Nvidia a highly volatile stock. There are greener pastures elsewhere. This is a deadman walking stock.</Msg><Username>pcofcakmunch</Username><Timestamp>1363965219852</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:13:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363967312866-14</Id><Topic><Title>DOA NVDA</Title><Username>mdlugolecki</Username><Timestamp>1363959708659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 09:41:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting spin... " weaker Tegra sales (even though there was a transition from Tegra 3 to Tegra 4)" what transition ?? where is it ?? "lack of smartphone penetration isn't going to pick up" NVidia just announced their first part targeted at smartphones... you know that, but are too busy spinning... " increases in operating expenses have outnumbered the revenue." you're too busy spinning to notice all the new products... but even you will see obvious with the transition from Tegra 3 to Tegra 4 "Nvidia a highly volatile stock." Really... stock hasn't moved much... "There are greener pastures elsewhere." How much did you short ??</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363967312866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:48:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363967316952-15</Id><Title>Could the volume be any lighter?</Title><Msg>Doubts about Tegra 4 really seem to be hurting us. Maybe Nvidia will finally give some Tegra revenue guidance at its annual investor day in April? Wall Street just isn't buying the whole Tegra story right now...</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363967316952</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:48:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363967952726-16</Id><Topic><Title>Come ON......up 2 stink'n cents</Title><Username>vineswoinger</Username><Timestamp>1363967443896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just another drive-by Bozo!</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363967952726</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:59:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363968251719-17</Id><Topic><Title>Come ON......up 2 stink'n cents</Title><Username>vineswoinger</Username><Timestamp>1363967443896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They always seem to come by on a quiet day like this . .</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1363968251719</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 12:04:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363969812934-18</Id><Topic><Title>Come ON......up 2 stink'n cents</Title><Username>vineswoinger</Username><Timestamp>1363967443896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is right.. this stock will never more..</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1363969812934</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 12:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363970165058-19</Id><Topic><Title>Could the volume be any lighter?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363967316952</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:48:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one is...and the stock isn't falling.....what does that mean?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363970165058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 12:36:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363970622301-20</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good move. I will be expecting for more news.</Msg><Username>kreizenbeckmichele</Username><Timestamp>1363970622301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 12:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363972066687-21</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love this report.</Msg><Username>odnanehschristy</Username><Timestamp>1363972066687</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 13:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363972602051-22</Id><Title>Nvidia's automotive Tegra chips use a special TSMC flow</Title><Msg>Says it has exclusive intellectual property SAN JOSE: CHIP DESIGNER Nvidia said at its GPU Technology Conference (GTC) that it has exclusive intellectual property (IP) with TSMC in the fabrication of its Tegra automotive chips. Nvidia has shipped around 2.5 million Tegra chips into the automotive industry, with firms such as Audi, BMW, Lamborghini and Tesla using a mixture of Tegra 2 and Tegra 3 chips. Philip Hughes, director of Automotive sales and business development at Nvidia told The INQUIRER that the Tegra chips that end up in cars are fabbed using a specific "automotive flow' at TSMC. Hughes said that while the Tegra 3 chip in the Tesla has the same architecture as the chip that powers Google's Nexus 7 tablet, it is fabbed using a different process flow that is specific to chips intended for the automotive industry. By different flow, Hughes was referring to additional steps to ensure validation and reliability rather than a different chip geometry. Hughes added that Nvidia worked with TSMC to develop the automative flow, adding that there is Nvidia specific IP in that flow. So while TSMC has other customers that use it for producing chips for the automotive industry, it cannot take advantage of Nvidia's proprietary process features. Nvidia has enjoyed considerable success in the automotive industry given its relativley recent entrance into what is a very conservative market. Hughes said that the firm already has orders for a further 20 million Tegra chips from car makers, which is impressive given that its chips have typically ended up in high-end motorcars. Given that Nvidia has gone to the effort of working with TSMC to customise its process flow, it is safe to say the company is very serious about breaking into the automotive industry, an industry that many semiconductor vendors increasingly see as an industry that will drive revenue as PC sales decrease.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363972602051</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 13:16:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363972887299-23</Id><Title>GE! Bet you didn't see this one coming.</Title><Msg>GE puts new Nvidia tech through its paces, ponders HPC future From register story. Hybrid CPU-GPU chips plus RDMA and PCI-Express make for screamin' iron By Timothy Prickett Morgan • Get more from this author Posted in HPC , 22nd March 2013 16:27 GMT Free whitepaper – EMA advanced performance analytics report GTC 2013 A top General Electric techie gave a presentation at the GPU Technology Conference this week in San José, California, and discussed the benefits of Remote Direct Memory Access (RDMA) for InfiniBand and its companion GPUDirect method of linking GPU memories to each other across InfiniBand networks. And just for fun, the GE tech also specced out how he would go about building supercomputers using Nvidia's future hybrid CPU-GPU chips based on the "Project Denver" cores that Nvidia has been working on for the past several years. Don't be at all surprised that GE is fiddling about with Nvidia chippery. The company does a lot of different things, and one of them is make military-specification computing and visualization systems for fighter jets, tanks, drones, and other weapons systems. Given the nature of the systems it creates, GE has become an expert in chips and network-lashing technologies, particularly given the real-time nature of the data gathering and processing that military systems require. The GE techie who spoke at Nvidia's event was Dusty Franklin, GPGPU applications engineer at GE's Intelligent Platforms division, and Nvidia introduced his session at the conference saying he was one of the world's experts on RDMA and GPUDirect.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1363972887299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 13:21:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363972963972-24</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's automotive Tegra chips use a special TSMC flow</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363972602051</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 13:16:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like It. Orders for 20 million Tegra modules for cars. Over a number of years but heck...That's a lot of money at $75 per. Going the TI route What's a phone?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363972963972</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 13:22:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363974802289-25</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will take a look at this.</Msg><Username>oginsagaeleanor</Username><Timestamp>1363974802289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 13:53:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363975353107-26</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia's automotive Tegra chips use a special TSMC flow</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363972602051</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 13:16:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not knowing I was going to say 500 million. But it is the entire unit not just the chip. 1.5 billion in orders already! We have the absolute worst analysts on the planet following us.</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1363975353107</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:02:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363976674017-27</Id><Title>AMD Going The Semi-Custom Route is A Great Idea</Title><Msg>Probably have to drop out of discrete graphics at the next generation because of the cost...but the concept of Semi-Custom X86 AMUs should allow them to survive although in a much smaller foot print. Perhaps they can do an On-Live Type Transaction. Just saying</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363976674017</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:24:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363976957485-28</Id><Topic><Title>GE! Bet you didn't see this one coming.</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1363972887299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 13:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just read it - great endorsement</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1363976957485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:29:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363977027990-29</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Going The Semi-Custom Route is A Great Idea</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363976674017</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:24:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great idea ?? more like the beginning of the end... From selling products to selling engineers... But that's what you do when you're jumping on a life raft...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363977027990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:30:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363977672432-30</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Going The Semi-Custom Route is A Great Idea</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363976674017</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:24:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well if you can't succeed in on business one must try another. Later on this year some private equity firm might scoop it up for something like $1 and negotiate a reduce debt load and it will be re-born at 30% it's currently reduced size First to go will be all thought of a new generation of Discrete graphics cards. Noticed they are on 3 generations of AMUs at 32 nm with Richland with no intentions to move to smaller process nodes. Even if someone bought them for their IP they still will cease making standalone GPUs I think. Bodes well for Nvidia. Sad Turn of events though.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363977672432</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:41:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363977826778-31</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm looking for great articles. Nice to be here.</Msg><Username>punctuallidia</Username><Timestamp>1363977826778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363978902871-32</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Going The Semi-Custom Route is A Great Idea</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363976674017</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:24:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD went with GloFo... got screwed...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363978902871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 15:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363978947221-33</Id><Topic><Title>Guesses on Q4 sales?</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363961443495</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 10:10:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why not skip the share buyback and instead raise the dividend?</Msg><Username>markinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1363978947221</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 15:02:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363979999333-34</Id><Title>LI yui_3_8_1_1_1363983475588_791</Title><Msg>can't reply to many posts ?? keep getting the above instead of reply window... anyone else experiencing this ??</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363979999333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 15:19:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363980401601-35</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am from Chicago. I love your article.</Msg><Username>nantiparena</Username><Timestamp>1363980401601</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 15:26:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363981938389-36</Id><Title>Lowest volume in ages</Title><Msg>Could be</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363981938389</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 15:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363982010228-37</Id><Topic><Title>Lowest volume in ages</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363981938389</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 15:52:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now you know why NVidia declared a dividend and stock buyback... IMO, they anticipated this...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363982010228</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 15:53:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363982166690-38</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Going The Semi-Custom Route is A Great Idea</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363976674017</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:24:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excuse me, J7777, could you tell us whatis AMUs? AMD has no such product listed anywhere, including its website. And I doubled checked. amdDOTcom/US/Pages/NoResults.aspx?csquery=amu&amp;collection=all-us Could it be a new product that even ceo Rory Read is not aware of? ;p Or, did you mean AMD APUs? - I thought at first that it was a typo that you made a reference to AMUs, not APUs, but then I saw you use the term AMR several times consecutively during last week. Nothing personal - just wish to be enlightened on something new, or to make you aware of a recurrent error that you made. Not flattering for someone who wishes to establish credibility in a public forum about technology and stock market.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363982166690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 15:56:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363982452672-39</Id><Topic><Title>Lowest volume in ages</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363981938389</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 15:52:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure why but I think they were just tired of all the bad stuff the media says and thought what the heck...we have to do a buyback and issue a dividend to avoid the stock going lower. Probably didn't want to be shareholder friendly but turned out they are now. Ironic</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363982452672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 16:00:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363982596085-40</Id><Topic><Title>Lowest volume in ages</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363981938389</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 15:52:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"we have to do a buyback and issue a dividend to avoid the stock going lower." that's what I just said... glad you agree Jensen knows they're a year off their roadmap... stock reflects it...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363982596085</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 16:03:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363983945338-41</Id><Topic><Title>Lowest volume in ages</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363981938389</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 15:52:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It could be a combination of that and a more confident attitude about how things are shaping up across all product lines even though they are now late with T4. I think the stock has drifted to the 8's a couple times over the years with Jen not doing anything out of the ordinary. It just presented another great buying opportunity caused by the same crowd who keeps underestimating Nvidia's resilience. The stock will continue to drift in a narrow trading range until they can chain a couple impressive quarters together.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363983945338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 16:25:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363984545639-42</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Going The Semi-Custom Route is A Great Idea</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363976674017</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:24:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ibexx, You knew what I meant AMU....APU. The point was and is I believe in AMD's situation going the semi-custom route is best for them......They obviously can't compete with Intel and $$$$ will be a problem to compete with Nvidia so taking a 3rd path is not out of the question. Will they be public next year? I don't know.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363984545639</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 16:35:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363984836189-43</Id><Topic><Title>Lowest volume in ages</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363981938389</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 15:52:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It could be a combination of that and a more confident attitude about how things are shaping up across all product lines even though they are now late with T4. I think the stock has drifted to the 8's a couple times over the years with Jen not doing anything out of the ordinary." Chitown But he certainly did do something out of the ordinary this time! Dividend and buyback....completely unexpected by everyone! Of course I would rather have Tegra 4 in the new Galaxy S4! JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363984836189</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 16:40:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363985517901-44</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Going The Semi-Custom Route is A Great Idea</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363976674017</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:24:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will take this as a public correction of your error. I knew it wasn't a casual typo because you continually made references to the term of ÅMUs. The point you were trying to make was not the issue; what could be troubling was the casual attitude toward accuracy. Surely no one needs the perception of having loose lips, sloppy posts and faulty thinking. Well, an admission of the error is better than nothing. Happy posting!</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363985517901</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 16:51:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363985838902-45</Id><Topic><Title>ARM to help second-tier IC designers to catch up, DigiTimes reports</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1363921666940</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:07:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>found this thread amusing... still launghing about it... so much so...that I'm reposting the response... "ARM Holdings (ARMH) is considering plans to provide complete platform solutions to help second-tier IC design houses catchup with Qualcom (QCOM) and Nvidia (NVDA) in 2013" Really now... "The only way Arm can compete with Intel is to try to reduce cost." yet ARM keeps growing... and INtel hit with another PC declining forecast... " How cheap can Nvidia make a Tegra?" Tegra is 80 sq mm... so cheaper than anyone...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363985838902</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 16:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363985840875-46</Id><Title>Tegra4 design win folks!!</Title><Msg>Its coming... NOT.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363985840875</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 16:57:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363985899015-47</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra4 design win folks!!</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363985840875</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 16:57:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>then increase your short.... or just more air from you...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363985899015</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 16:58:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363986275646-48</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok cool. Thank you for sharing this.</Msg><Username>kvarjohnnie</Username><Timestamp>1363986275646</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 17:04:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363986293536-49</Id><Title>The One Bad Thing About Nvidia's New Business This Year</Title><Msg>Enterprise Grid and VCA are not sexy! Cloud Gaming yes...but that's later. What I mean is you will not be able to google and see something about a huge design win, or rumor of a huge design win with stock moving potential posted here of course. WS analysts will take on a much larger role. Even Digitimes Research will be left out. But we do have those road maps....which are interesting!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363986293536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 17:04:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363986394262-50</Id><Topic><Title>The One Bad Thing About Nvidia's New Business This Year</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363986293536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 17:04:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the business unit does well, NVIdia themselves will break it out for everyone to see... Money is sexier to investors than gaming...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363986394262</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 17:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363988491256-51</Id><Topic><Title>The One Bad Thing About Nvidia's New Business This Year</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363986293536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 17:04:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If the business unit does well, NVIdia themselves will break it out for everyone to see... Money is sexier to investors than gaming.." As long as the bottom line is better all is better. If not it's just a note for the analysts, with more wait and see from them. The reason for combining PSB and GPU into one reporting segment was to refocus analysts and media perceptions away from the silly notion that Integrated Graphics are killing Nvidia's businesses. Doubt they will open it up to show by segment for a year or so. But Cloud Gaming could really get a buzz under the stock if it really takes off. WS loves stories. Don't get me wrong Nvidia Grid will be a good business.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363988491256</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 17:41:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363993653185-52</Id><Title>from zacks story?????</Title><Msg>Moreover, NVIDIA’s newly introduced Tegra 4 has four distinct features and is increasingly being used in Google Inc's (GOOG) Nexus 7, Microsoft Corp’s (MSFT) Surface tablet, HTC's One X smartphone and Sony Corp’s (SNE) PSP hand-held gaming device. This new technology is especially attractive to game manufacturers as it consumes 45% less power. Most interesting!</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1363993653185</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 19:07:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363993987700-53</Id><Topic><Title>from zacks story?????</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1363993653185</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 19:07:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>from January</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1363993987700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 19:13:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363994341304-54</Id><Topic><Title>from zacks story?????</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1363993653185</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 19:07:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>huh? yahoo story 1 hr ago. #$%$?</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1363994341304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 19:19:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363994344023-55</Id><Topic><Title>ARM to help second-tier IC designers to catch up, DigiTimes reports</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1363921666940</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:07:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much does Tegra add to Nvidia's bottom line? Can Nvidia cut the price of the Tegra and still make a profit? More China smartphone vendors adopt MediaTek quad-core solutions Cage Chao, Taipei; Steve Shen, DIGITIMES [Wednesday 20 March 2013] Following the steps of Lenovo and Coolpad, two other China-based smartphone vendors, Huawei and ZTE, reportedly will also adopt MediaTek's quad-core MT6589 solutions for the production of their high-end smartphones – a move which will further enhance MediaTek's leading market position in China's smartphone solution segment, according to industry sources. With orders from Lenovo, Coolpad, Huawei and ZTE, MediaTek is expected to increase its previous goal of shipping over 200 million smartphone solutions in 2013, said the sources. The adoption of MediaTek's quad-core solutions by Huawei and ZTE comes only one month after the two vendors highlighted their latest high-end smartphone models powered by Qualcomm's solutions at the recently concluded Mobile World Congress (MWC) 2013, the sources noted. But Huawei and ZTE are being forced to use MediaTek's solutions due to increasing price competition in China's high-end smartphone segment, said the sources, adding that prices of high-profile smartphones in China have dropped to CNY1,200-1800 (US$193-289) recently. Huawei and ZTE are expected to launch smartphones powered by MediaTek's quad-core solutions in the second half of 2013, the sources noted.</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1363994344023</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 19:19:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363994757016-56</Id><Title>Question.. Will Nvidia's graphics marketshare drop to 14% this Q, from 16%</Title><Msg>last Q? Ivy bridge is just hitting its stride, and will take a bite out of discrete graphics for sure.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363994757016</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 19:25:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363994962598-57</Id><Topic><Title>Question.. Will Nvidia's graphics marketshare drop to 14% this Q, from 16%</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363994757016</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 19:25:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Irrelevant. Just thought I'd do it for that moron.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363994962598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 19:29:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363996020509-58</Id><Title>How many of those Win RT tablets have been returned.</Title><Msg>Ballmer is a stubborn dawg, he won't kill Win RT just yet.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363996020509</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 19:47:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363996728195-59</Id><Topic><Title>The One Bad Thing About Nvidia's New Business This Year</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363986293536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 17:04:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bingo.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363996728195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 19:58:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363998394934-60</Id><Topic><Title>Question.. Will Nvidia's graphics marketshare drop to 14% this Q, from 16%</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363994757016</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 19:25:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fact that it actually bothers you makes me very happy, especially since your posts are just as spammy.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1363998394934</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 20:26:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364000979990-61</Id><Topic><Title>The One Bad Thing About Nvidia's New Business This Year</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363986293536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 17:04:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly. MOney is the only thing that looks sexy to WS and its fund managers. Supercomputing is sexy, but it doesn't rake in enough to dress up the top and bottom numbers. What appears to be sexy to retail traders isn't the same as to WS professionals.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1364000979990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 21:09:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364006296519-62</Id><Topic><Title>The One Bad Thing About Nvidia's New Business This Year</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363986293536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 17:04:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree with Ibx. You ever hear of any earth shattering IBM product announcements? Yet they keep printing money year after year and stock is at $210 and market cap at $240B! One thing to be said of Nvidia's new VCA - Grid - Server Blades - whatever they call it - how often do you hear of IBM adopting somebody else product into their Enterprise offerings. This is a company so totally self sufficient that it's extremely rare - unless it is a BIG DEAL and they don't have an alternative. IBM is the KING of enterprise hardware and software solutions - often building everything themselves! All good ... all good Side note - the #$%$ about the LI yui_3_8_1_1_1364005622810_1257 message appears when one tries to do too many levels of replies - it seems.</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1364006296519</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 22:38:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>