<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372911726332-1</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Forecast May Miss on Dimming Outlook for PC Rebound, says Raymond James Email Print</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372902262458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 21:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2nd wave is not far behind, as always Mosesmann makes faulty assumptions on faulty data. Also Haswell is not cannibalizing anything as Ivy Bridge is being retired to make way for it, you sure have an odd way of looking at things especially as Haswell is the highest performing part Intel has released. New Intel mobile CPUs to launch in September Last week we reported on new desktop microprocessors, coming in Q3 2013. On September 1 in Asian region, and on September 29 everywhere else, Intel is going to introduce Core i3 and Pentium Haswell CPUs, along with several Ivy Bridge budget parts. Full list of forthcoming desktop CPUs was published by VR-Zone Chinese edition a week ago, and now they revealed processor numbers and launch dates of future mobile processors. According to a new slide, posted by VR-Zone, in September Intel will release more than 20 different mobile SKUs, including standard power and ULV Haswell products. Furthermore, Bay Trail-T and Bay Trail-M systems-on-a-chip (SoC) will be available as well at the end of Q3. The following mobile Haswell processors will be launched on September 1: Celeron 2950M, 2955U, 2980U, Pentium 3550M, 3556U, 3560Y, Core i3-4000M, i3-4005U, i3-4012Y, i3-4020Y, i3-4100M, Core i5-4200H, i5-4200M, i5-4202Y, i5-4210Y, i5-4300M, i5-4300U, i5-4300Y, i5-4302Y, i5-4330M, Core i7-4600M, i7-4600U, i7-4610Y, and i7-4960HQ. Some features of these processors can be guessed from the processor number's suffix. For instance, "M" microprocessors target mainstream notebooks. They usually have GT2 graphics, 35 watt TDP, and they are produced in a PGA package. "H" parts are similar to "M" processors, except that they have GT3 graphics unit. "U" ultra-low power SoCs are rated at 15 or 28 Watt, while "Y" ULV SoCs have even lower 11.5 Watt TDP. Lastly, the "HQ" is a high-performance SKU with 4 CPUs cores, HD 5000 series graphics, and higher, than mainstream, TDP. Bay Trail-T SoCs for tablets will be released from August 28 to September 13. The slide does not show their processor numbers, but it does list Bay Trail-M SKUs, that will be available "after PRQ". We already reported on a few of these Bay Trail-M microprocessors, or specifically on Celeron N2805, N2810 and N2910. Brief specifications and prices of these SoCs can be found in Intel's official pricelist. In addition to dual-core N28xx and quad-core N2910 parts, there will be also Pentium N3510.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372911726332</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 00:22:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372912421806-2</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Forecast May Miss on Dimming Outlook for PC Rebound, says Raymond James Email Print</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372902262458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 21:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'The demographic trend for the PC market seems to be migrating toward the lower-end, priced in the $500 range, which works in AMD's favor.' That's a BS assumption not backed up recent facts like AMD having to scrap hundreds of millions of dollars worth of cheap chips due to poor demand and the death of the netbook on Intel's side. I can't work out who's more clueless, you or Mosesmann ? It's a close run thing either way ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372912421806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 00:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372916331080-3</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Forecast May Miss on Dimming Outlook for PC Rebound, says Raymond James Email Print</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372902262458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 21:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think he is right on - on this one. A low resolution 900p X86 notebook with a 500GB disk, 10 hours play time and weighs 2.5 lbs or less should not cost more than $500. At this point INTC is only competing with itself - they have to come up with better faster CPUs at a lower ASP - just maintaining zero growth in its mainstream biz would be an achievement. ARM simply redefined the weight, the ASPs, Play time and Performance of the category. If not for arm we will still be lugging "Bo Jackson" Lap tops around at a cost of $1,500+, 2 1/2 hours play time and 768P! Go 1080P and the Haswells will be back to 3 hours playtime :)</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1372916331080</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 01:38:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372917787607-4</Id><Title>OUYA ready for a video game revolution?</Title><Msg>SOURCE: The Boston Globe, July 4 Here is the most interesting part: "......But here’s the thing: Just about everything wrong with Ouya can be fixed. The company is in talks with Netflix and other video streamers. It’s also trying to put together a deal with OnLive, an outfit that streams high-end video games via the Internet. With OnLive access, Ouya owners could play top-drawer titles for $10 a month. As for the skimpy selection of decent games, the same could be said for nearly all new consoles. There wasn’t much worth playing on the original Xbox or PlayStation, either. Android game designers could create excellent products for the Ouya. But it’s an open question whether Ouya can hold out that long. It may not matter. Other inexpensive Android game consoles are racing to market, such as GameStick and Gamepop. And the Wall Street Journal reports that Android’s creator, Google, is also building one. So the game console giants can look forward to lots of low-cost competition, no matter what happens with Ouya.""</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372917787607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 02:03:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372928239721-5</Id><Title>WHOSUNW</Title><Msg>Whosunw, Long time no see. It seems like such a long time ago. It was over ten years ago on the LSI board. KC Daytrader lost his alias. This was about a year ago. I read shortly there after Yahoo laid off 2000 employees. I liked KC, fighting him and learning a lot. All those people went their way. So many lost so much in LSI. It took those poor souls many years to get over all the loses. I was one of them. The tech crash was engineered out of NYC. We'll never know the full extent of all the insider trading and wolf pack hedge funds spreading rumors- destroying company after company. Interesting how no one was convicted. The corruption has now spread to every aspect of America. It seems the American people get ripped off over and over with zero accountability. I can say you're one of the best at knowing all the ends and outs of tech stocks. The knowledge you have goes far beyond DavidW35. You started as nobodydownhere. You were always well mannered to me. I appreciated it. Those were the days, the beginning of the message boards. Strike</Msg><Username>us_strike_command</Username><Timestamp>1372928239721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 04:57:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372928604533-6</Id><Topic><Title>SoC's with parallel processing technology?</Title><Username>morrowltd</Username><Timestamp>1372689801487</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 10:43:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wrote a little note on the board to you. I titled it, WHOSUNW. Good Luck.</Msg><Username>us_strike_command</Username><Timestamp>1372928604533</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 05:03:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372935019071-7</Id><Title>Ouya and that SHIELD Lemon Headed for an Early Grave on eBay for less than MSRP</Title><Msg>Ouya's grave has already been dug. And Cousin Broken SHIELD will be planted right next to Ouya if Nvidia ever gets its act together and ships one. Ouya can be had for a lot less than that lofty $99 MSRP on eBay now. There is an ample supply of Ouya consoles described as used once, new other, booted once, used 5 minutes, ..., you get the idea, with owners who want out. Ouya buyers seem intent on being Ouya sellers ASAP. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372935019071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 06:50:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372935204477-8</Id><Topic><Title>Any word on Project SHIELD Out Until Repaired or SOUR Lemon Nvidia fans? lol</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372438164435</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:49:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Day 9 and SHIELD is still Broken. And no word when that POS will be fixed. Now isn't that right Nvidia fans? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372935204477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 06:53:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372935365400-9</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Forecast May Miss on Dimming Outlook for PC Rebound, says Raymond James Email Print</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372902262458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 21:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Go 1080P and the Haswells will be back to 3 hours playtime' BS. 'ARM simply redefined the weight, the ASPs, Play time and Performance of the category. ' No they didn't otherwise the pseudo Windows RT would have taken off. Netbooks were light and had long play times and were around before iPads. You sure like making things up which is a common habit among the NVDA pumpers here.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372935365400</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 06:56:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372943183831-10</Id><Topic><Title>SoC's with parallel processing technology?</Title><Username>morrowltd</Username><Timestamp>1372689801487</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 10:43:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow, strike buddy, long long LONG time. How are you doing nowadays? hope you keep yourself well, c yar around</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1372943183831</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:06:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372943500831-11</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Forecast May Miss on Dimming Outlook for PC Rebound, says Raymond James Email Print</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372902262458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 21:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hans nvda-to-$40 Mosesmann has about as much credibility as Obama's' "nobody is listening to your phone calls".</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1372943500831</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:11:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372945546009-12</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Forecast May Miss on Dimming Outlook for PC Rebound, says Raymond James Email Print</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372902262458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 21:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am sorry - you sound like Balmer. Put it this way INTC can have 100% of the Wintel market and ARM the IOS and Android market. It's a new world Wintel is a tired dog trying to learn new tricks. WinRT is driven by the same mentality - it would be a long while before it amounts to anything. It's easier to continue with the overpriced - over weight bricks. Netbooks were severely underpowered and bulky, and got 5 to 6 hrs on a good day and forget about anything beyond 1280x800 - Intel made sure of that - I wonder why ... if they had gone with the1366x 768 10" - playtime would be back down to 3 hrs and price would have gone upto $400.</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1372945546009</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:45:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372945791427-13</Id><Title>Reply to WHOSUNW</Title><Msg>I'm still alive. It was two years ago that you posted to me on the LSI board. At that time KC Daytrader was posting. His post stopped in May 2011. Yahoo didn't delete his account and his message posts are still available for look up. It is possible he died. His name was "Gary" and he served in the Navy in the late 60's. So he was getting old. I don't post anymore on Yahoo. They censor and Yahoo doesn't like it when posters defend themselves. As you know I would always defend myself. Recall David W35/Lets go higher. Once I was looking up old alias and came across David W35 alias page. He had posted his photo on the page. He said he was headed to the Philippines. He lost his tech job, his wife and his holdings in LSI. That was in 2004 when I saw his alias page. Recall it was the old type page one could post a photo or picture. I sometimes read the old post from the LSI era. I have met many people in their late 50's who lost everything in the tech crash still struggling to survive. Around 2008 the US economy started to decline. It remains to be seen if structural unemployment will become the norm. It may take a generation to dig out of this. US budget over runs will be worse in 2014. Plus, the markets may have gone too far. A panic sell off could happen at the same time as a collapse in the bond markets. We don't know what will happen and I believe it is too early to say all is well. We may have a bond bubble and higher interest rates could trigger a slow or rapid meltdown. Again, those were the grand ole days on the LSI board. I really enjoyed and learned a great deal. I will keep reading your tech reports. You learned more than all of us and developed an understanding of many segments of the tech industry. Good Luck and continue on...</Msg><Username>us_strike_command</Username><Timestamp>1372945791427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:49:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372946309948-14</Id><Topic><Title>Reply to WHOSUNW</Title><Username>us_strike_command</Username><Timestamp>1372945791427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:49:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ah those good ole days when one could post photos... I used to post quite a few myself...until yahoo put a stop to that... an, nothing wrong with posting very nice girlie pics, no? I think the whole market/us is in serious trouble. Everything runs on feds goosing money supply and manufacturing output is not increased, w/exception of the oil frackling which will destroy and poison all the ground water. I don't know much about the bond market, but I think the stock market is way overpriced, even though techs are not. Not putting new money into the market until the next bust comes. europe/greece/portugal/spain type crisis will happen to the us, just a question of time. on msn news, same page shows n. carolina has a hunger problem because people are out of work when manufacturing left town. Same page the n. carolina legislators are so busy screwing around stricter abortion laws. something wrong with that picture somewhere.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1372946309948</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:58:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372950994122-15</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Forecast May Miss on Dimming Outlook for PC Rebound, says Raymond James Email Print</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372902262458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 21:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"At these levels, we believe a product lineup from Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) (without supply issues for this iteration) will participate between the high-end focus of Haswell and Intel’s low-end Atom. Thus, we believe the long awaited “rebound” in PCs may be a bigger driver of AMD share gains" This article is pounding the table for AMD and the only thing you clowns want to argue about is how hard did he slap Intel. Pay attention, even Jen said on the last conf. call that Nvidia's market share is tied to Intel's share and that Nvidia would be expected to LOSE share if AMD gains share. Since we all know there is litle need for an Nvidia anything with an AMD solution. Now if you can read and you know what Jen said then you know this is bad news for Intel and Nvidia. lol So for the Nvidia pumper who put the article up to bash Intel and the Intel pumper who disputes it, who cares who will hurt the most Intel or Nvidia. If you can read the only WINNER in this article is AMD! "Given our belief that PC units will continue to shift to the lower price points (generating share gains for AMD and ASP pressure across the board)" IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372950994122</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372952515659-16</Id><Title>Nvidia fan is so Clueless he is PUMPING AMD and unknowingly BASHING Nvidia.</Title><Msg>"Consumers (and subsequently OEMs) have become increasingly cost conscious with regards to PC purchases, and we believe the sweet spot for PCs will continue to move lower into the $400-600 range. At these levels, we believe a product lineup from Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) (without supply issues for this iteration) will participate between the high-end focus of Haswell and Intel’s low-end Atom. Thus, we believe the long awaited “rebound” in PCs may be a bigger driver of AMD share gains, while Intel (with ~85% PC market share) will likely be at the whim of the overall market." "Given our belief that PC units will continue to shift to the lower price points (generating share gains for AMD and ASP pressure across the board)" source: Ray Jay's Hans Mosesmann Here is Jen-Hsun Huang owns words from the Q1 Conference Call regarding Intel share: "The other factor, is it Intel versus AMD loses share. On balance, our share is higher on Intel than it is on AMD. As you could imagine. AMD CPUs. So if Intel were to lose share to AMD, it affect our share but so long as Intel share relative to AMD is stable or eventually were to gain share then our share would reflect that." source: seekingalpha Earnings Call Transcript An Nvidia fan put up that Ray Jay ariicle intending to bash Intel but as you can see the only problem with bashing Intel's share is that Jen said Nvidia's market share is linked to Intel's market share and that if AMD gains share then Nvidia would be expected to LOSE share. Now you can bash Intel all day you CLUELESS Nvidia fan but you should know according to Jen YOU ARE ALSO BASHING Nvidia and PUMPING AMD. lmao IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1372952515659</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:41:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372955040170-17</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Forecast May Miss on Dimming Outlook for PC Rebound, says Raymond James Email Print</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372902262458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 21:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clovertrail Atoms do 1366x 768 10" and they last longer than a Tegra 3 Surface does. The screen in the Haswell MacBookAir is 900p and it last over 12 hours. You are still spewing out of date BS.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372955040170</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372956031524-18</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Forecast May Miss on Dimming Outlook for PC Rebound, says Raymond James Email Print</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372902262458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 21:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung have released a 12 hour 1800p Haswell ultrabook, the ativ book 9 plus.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372956031524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:40:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372957537931-19</Id><Topic><Title>The FCC reveals Qualcomm is IN the Next Nexus 7 and Nvidia is OUT</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1371236280402</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 14:58:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google, in collaboration with Asustek, launched its first tablet Nexus 7 last year. Powered by Android OS, Nexus 7 comes with a 7-inch display and an NVIDIA (NVDA) Tegra 3 quad-core chip. Google sold 4.5–4.6 million units of the tablet in 2012. Powered by the newest version of Android, the second-generation tablet will come with a better screen resolution and have a thinner design. Google decided to install Qualcomm's (QCOM) chip, replacing Nvidia Corp's Tegra 3. Tablets with fast processors offer improved performance and therefore enjoy steady demand.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1372957537931</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:05:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372959432153-20</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Forecast May Miss on Dimming Outlook for PC Rebound, says Raymond James Email Print</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372902262458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 21:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We shall see what the real world results are when they are available? I must say that the GPU performance sure has improved since Intel signed the 1.5 billion incensing agreement back in '11. It sounds like Intel will be paying much more in about 4 years if they want to renew.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1372959432153</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:37:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372959698382-21</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Forecast May Miss on Dimming Outlook for PC Rebound, says Raymond James Email Print</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372902262458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 21:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>with none of the screen makers really making a move beyond 1080, this nvda's notebook share will take a dive because Haswell is good enough for 1080. "How do you model the non-gamer notebook sales?"</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1372959698382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:41:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372960561937-22</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Forecast May Miss on Dimming Outlook for PC Rebound, says Raymond James Email Print</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372902262458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 21:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung ATIV 9 plus starts at $1000 and goes far higher than that. This brings back the issue of pricing/ASP which is the dilemma of Intel. Do you ever "get" it?</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372960561937</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:56:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372963225913-23</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Forecast May Miss on Dimming Outlook for PC Rebound, says Raymond James Email Print</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1372902262458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 21:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bay Trails will be going for half that price with retina screens and don't worry Tegra 4 is sure going to "get" it lol.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372963225913</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372967446700-24</Id><Title>Watch for breakout</Title><Msg>Watching for a break of $14.49 here. Technical indicator at stoxline website is turning a buy with the $16.92 target price in six months.</Msg><Username>hpwamrs</Username><Timestamp>1372967446700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372977885228-25</Id><Title>Nvidia will have to use baytrail for their shield. No other option.</Title><Msg>tegra's just don't cut the mustard here.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372977885228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372981314090-26</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia will have to use baytrail for their shield. No other option.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372977885228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:44:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Either do your lame stupid posts.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1372981314090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>