<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373947856970-1</Id><Topic><Title>Techradar comments on the new ZTE U998S Geek vs the old one</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373929090697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:58:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Based on collective information on the web, including the China Daily article, there is NO CARRIER taking the Intel-inside version of ZTE Geek. (what kind of launch is that without a carrier sponsorship?) The Intel ZTE Geek is reportedly to be released on July 26, so we shall see what happens then. Meanwhile, you could buy the phone from some retail outlet in China for $307 - I wonder if ZTE is dumping the handset through the backdoor? ABSOLUTELY NO CARRIER mentioned (who would take the Intel ZTE Geek)</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1373947856970</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 00:10:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373948031648-2</Id><Topic><Title>Techradar comments on the new ZTE U998S Geek vs the old one</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373929090697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:58:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This guy gets completely hysterical and incoherent when he could no longer defend Intel based on widely known facts.....at least Ashraf has the good sense of remaining silent for now, about the cheating scandal as well as the falsely inflated performance of all shrunk ATOMs.</Msg><Username>moorelawyer</Username><Timestamp>1373948031648</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 00:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373949654706-3</Id><Topic><Title>Techradar comments on the new ZTE U998S Geek vs the old one</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373929090697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:58:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your point is spot-on, moorelawyer! It struck me as strange as there have been no carrier information what-so-ever for the Clovertrail powered ZTE Geek.....highly unusually for a high-profile partnership between Intel and ZTE. I am speculating that it is merely a political marriage between the 2 companies - ZTE is not serious about selling the Intel-inside Geek, or that no carrier would be willing to take it - as you stated in your post. ZTE needs the Intel name to move up in product image and, conversely, Intel needs ZTE to get a foot in the door of China, especially the mobile phone market. To quote the statement made by a ZTE executive as per China Daily, dated July 15: ""For Intel, it is also a marathon. So far, it has cooperated with Lenovo, ZTE and Motorola, but it has yet to gain more market share, because its Atom products entered the market later than their competitors and their power dissipation has been mistakenly considered high by the industry, although they are more competitive in processing."" Well, ZTE may have just found out that the Clovertrail's performance isn't so competitive either. ZTE U998S Geek (Tegra 4) was rushed out ahead of schedule based on several web reports. Additionally, for those who don't follow the topic closely, the Tegra 4 ZTE Geek will go to China Mobile, the world's largest phone carrier. This is no small feat as Apple has negotiated for YEARS to have iPhone adopted by China Mobile on its GSM/WCDMA network, but to no avail.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373949654706</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 00:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373962660543-4</Id><Title>NanoTech Selects NVIDIA Tegra 4 to Power Nuvola NP-1 Media Player</Title><Msg>Google title</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1373962660543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 04:17:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373974229266-5</Id><Title>Nuvola NP-1 using Nvidias Tegra 4 chip</Title><Msg>Very Cool !</Msg><Username>harit_rc</Username><Timestamp>1373974229266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 07:30:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373980053781-6</Id><Topic><Title>NanoTech Selects NVIDIA Tegra 4 to Power Nuvola NP-1 Media Player</Title><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1373962660543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 04:17:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>last year I said that nvda should pursue the media player biz with T3. They waited a whole year. This mediaplayer is really an T4 Android without any touch screens nor physical game controller - selling for $300. $200 would be a reasonable price. $300 is too high. $300, I'll get the shield.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1373980053781</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 09:07:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373990035959-7</Id><Title>TURDISGOINGRED AGAIN</Title><Msg>EOM..</Msg><Username>roundhose_c</Username><Timestamp>1373990035959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 11:53:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373991030834-8</Id><Topic><Title>NanoTech Selects NVIDIA Tegra 4 to Power Nuvola NP-1 Media Player</Title><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1373962660543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 04:17:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some details from the Inquirer: Nanotech's Nuvola NP-1 is a set-top box that supports streaming video up to 3840x2160 resolution, known more commonly as 4K video resolution. The firm said that the device will have a quad-core Tegra 4 chip with 72 GPU cores, 2GB of DDR3 RAM and 16GB of flash storage, and will run Google's Android 4.2 Jelly Bean mobile operating system. Nanotech's Nuvola NP-1 will also have one USB 2.0 and one USB 3.0 ports, HDMI 1.4, 802.11n WiFi and will come with a number of pre-installed applications such as Skype, Twitter, Pandora and Facebook. The firm said that the device will support video formats and containers such as MP4, MKV, AVI, MOV and OGG, with AAC, FLAC, MP3 and WAV audio formats supported. Nanotech CEO Jeffrey Foley talked up the Tegra 4's video capabilities and said, "Tegra 4 offers native 4K video support in hardware, including support for security and digital rights management with features including HDCP. "Beyond 4K, the power of the Nvidia processor helps us deliver a world-class experience with games, web browsing and a variety of other optimized apps."</Msg><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1373991030834</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 12:10:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373991320114-9</Id><Topic><Title>NanoTech Selects NVIDIA Tegra 4 to Power Nuvola NP-1 Media Player</Title><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1373962660543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 04:17:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like this : Streaming PC games to TV as shield does</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1373991320114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 12:15:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373994611099-10</Id><Title>This here stock is a YOYO on a.........</Title><Msg>One inch string!! talk about a Yawner, well...</Msg><Username>poundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1373994611099</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 13:10:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373997638685-11</Id><Topic><Title>This here stock is a YOYO on a.........</Title><Username>poundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1373994611099</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 13:10:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems to me that you are bouncing between your fake IDs like a YoYo: Poundhouse_c Roundhose_c Roundhouse_cc Have you no shame?</Msg><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1373997638685</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 14:00:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373999201771-12</Id><Title>The market wants to go up, so does NVDA</Title><Msg>I think NVDA will close out the OpEx week on Friday at $15 or higher. NVDA's up-volumes far exceeded down-volume so far, and Bollinger Band width at an all-time low - the level that usually serves as a launching pad....</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1373999201771</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 14:26:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374000472540-13</Id><Title>Complete Technical Specs of the Nuvola NP-1 4K UHD Media Streaming Player</Title><Msg>NanoTechs Nuvola NP-1 4k UHD WiFi Media Streaming Player is HERE !!! Operating on NVIDIA Tegra 4 Quad Core Mobile Processor with 2GB DDR3 RAM, 72gpu, 16gb HD, SD, BT-4.0' USB, 1.4 HDMI, Wireless Dual Band 802.11n 2x2 Mimo Wi-Fi &amp; Qwerty Keyboard 3motion Remote Control Controller. Operating on Android JellyBean 4.1 &amp; Access to all Google Play Apps, NVIDIA TegraZone Games and MiraCast. 10 PreLoaded 4k Movies, 10 PreLoaded Games, YouTube, NetFlix, NanoTech Video Player, Hulu, Fun Little Movies, VODWiz, Amazon Prime, IMDB, NanoTales, XBMC, Pandora, iHeartRadio, Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, NanoVOX, Skype. Only $299. Sorry Sony... Eat Crow !!</Msg><Username>harit_rc</Username><Timestamp>1374000472540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 14:47:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374003933042-14</Id><Topic><Title>Complete Technical Specs of the Nuvola NP-1 4K UHD Media Streaming Player</Title><Username>harit_rc</Username><Timestamp>1374000472540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 14:47:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Compare this to the SHIELD for me please...</Msg><Username>real_estate_bobby</Username><Timestamp>1374003933042</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 15:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374006418583-15</Id><Title>Computer Graphics Market Forecast To Soar</Title><Msg>By PETE BARLAS, INVESTOR'S BUSINESS DAILY  Posted 01:39 PM ET Dell (DELL), Hewlett-Packard (HPQ), Nvidia (NVDA) and Autodesk (ADSK) got some sone good news Tuesday with a new report that forecasts robust growth for the computer graphics market. Global sales of computer graphics hardware and software will reach $142 billion by 2016, up 17% from an expected $107 billion this year and up 53% from $93 billion in 2010, says a report from Jon Peddie Research. In 2016, sales of PCs, mobile devices and related computer graphics hardware will reach $124.4 billion, up 16% from an expected $106.9 billion this year. Dell and HP are among leading makers of graphics PCs, and Nvidia is a leading supplier of PC graphics chips. Global sales of computer graphics software will reach $16.98 billion, up 17% from $14.56 billion this year, the report said. Autodesk's software customers include the architecture, engineering and entertainment industries. The market growth is coming after several years of a recession-plagued economy, the report says. "The sharp curtailment of household and corporate spending during the recession has resulted in a renewed desire among consumers and businesses to begin increasing their spending on the latest graphics software and hardware platforms," the report said.</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1374006418583</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:26:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374007388859-16</Id><Topic><Title>Computer Graphics Market Forecast To Soar</Title><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1374006418583</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:26:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" $142 billion by 2016, up 17% from an expected $107 billion this year" Someone needs to work on either their math or their wording. "Up 17% annually" seems to be what they mean. I expect growth slightly less than half of that estimate, but both are far above the "computers are dead, and the phone business is already decided" viewpoint of some here.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1374007388859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374009546803-17</Id><Topic><Title>Complete Technical Specs of the Nuvola NP-1 4K UHD Media Streaming Player</Title><Username>harit_rc</Username><Timestamp>1374000472540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 14:47:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a evolution of the media PC, running Android and a streaming media application. It's approximately an evolved, open Roku: it promises to do "4K" resolution and run Andriod apps. It's pretty much permanently wired to the back of a TV. Shield is pretty much an Android mini-tablet that had a transporter accident with a gamepad and docking station. It is a self-contained portable device with a big battery and speakers. Shield has the hardware capability to do most things the NP-1 can do. The NP-1 has wired Ethernet, which is probably USB connected internally. You could get functional equivalence with an awkward external dongle. The IR receiver (for its IR remote), would be harder to substitute since it's likely connected to a Tegra hardware UART.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1374009546803</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 17:19:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374013987316-18</Id><Title>Nvidia Tegra just sent out a special shout-out to The Nuvola NP-1 on Twitter</Title><Msg>Great Endorsement from Nvidia.... 4k UHD streaming video IS gonna be the big thing this Christmas !</Msg><Username>harit_rc</Username><Timestamp>1374013987316</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 18:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374014466729-19</Id><Title>Get to know NanoTech Entertainment ....NTEK</Title><Msg>Developer of the Nuvola NP-1 4k UHD Streaming MediaPlayer. Even the Sony FMP-X1 can't do half of what the Nuvola can and costs more than TWICE as much ! Ground floor opportunity on NTEK (now partnered with NVDA on this device)</Msg><Username>harit_rc</Username><Timestamp>1374014466729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 18:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374019494549-20</Id><Title>NVDA technicals</Title><Msg>From StockConsultant July 16 after market close BREAKOUT ALERT for NVDA: "" BREAKOUT"" WATCH for possible breakout above 14.98, no resistance in area just above. Type: True breakout from double resistance. Target: 15.72, 7% Stop: 14.45, Loss: 1.6%, Profit/Loss ratio: 4.4 : 1 - Excellent "" BREAKDOWN"" None. ______ As usual, please read at your own discretion</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1374019494549</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:04:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374021403047-21</Id><Topic><Title>Complete Technical Specs of the Nuvola NP-1 4K UHD Media Streaming Player</Title><Username>harit_rc</Username><Timestamp>1374000472540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 14:47:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The great news here is that Tegra4 is being designed into a multitude of devices. Whether media streaming, gaming device, tablet, embedded computer, automotive display, or something we haven't imagined yet, Tegra provides powerful display rendering capability in a very small package. Lets face it, consumer electronics firms are all vying to produce the next ipod-like world changer. I am glad they're using Tegra. (OTOH, what other SoC offers the same power and efficiency? ;)</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1374021403047</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:36:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374021786991-22</Id><Topic><Title>Complete Technical Specs of the Nuvola NP-1 4K UHD Media Streaming Player</Title><Username>harit_rc</Username><Timestamp>1374000472540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 14:47:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why Jen Hsun emphatically said that ":Phone is not the only thing in mobile market..."</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1374021786991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:43:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374026599918-23</Id><Title>Glowing remarks by NanoTech ceo on Tegra 4 chip</Title><Msg>Source: Business Wire issued by NanoTech, July 16 "After evaluating the market and looking at the competitive landscape, the decision to upgrade our processor to NVIDIA's Tegra 4 was simple," stated Jeffrey A. Foley, NanoTech CEO. "Tegra 4 offers native 4K video support in hardware, including support for security and digital rights management with features including HDCP. Beyond 4K, the power of the NVIDIA processor helps us deliver a world-class experience with games, web browsing and a variety of other optimized apps." "Tegra 4 provides enormous processing power and realistic graphics to set top boxes," said Glenn Schuster, director of technical marketing for the Mobile business at NVIDIA. "Its optimized video capabilities, TegraZone games and Miracast(TM) support will allow these TV-connected devices to deliver a whole range of home entertainment experiences that are second to none." In addition to the native 4K Ultra HD video support, Tegra 4 allows the Nuvola to deliver ultra-fast web browsing, significantly improved app load times, and the most realistic gaming experiences from any media player on the market. ______ PS: NanoTech is taking pre-order on its new Nuvola NP01 media player. It will be available on Amazon later this month. Additional NanoTech will open its own retail stores across the country for direct sales, starting in August. WOW, NV has found a kiss#$%$ partner!</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1374026599918</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:03:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374029433979-24</Id><Title>AMD's highly anticipated Kaveri APU may face delay to 2014</Title><Msg>SOURCE: X-bit labs Advanced Micro Devices pins a lot of hopes onto its Steamroller micro-architecture as well as Kaveri accelerated processing unit since both could significantly improve competitive positions of the company. Unfortunately for the Sunnyvale, California-based chip designer, Kaveri, the first product to take advantage of Steamroller, could face delay in mass production.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1374029433979</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:50:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>