<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358660499822-1</Id><Title>Software Radio</Title><Msg>In the early days when we had to use dial up modems and the rates were 9600bauds - dedicated chips were used. As the dial up rates went up through the use of sophisticated modulation techniques and newer standards were added .... Wikipedia - ""As more sophisticated transmission schemes were devised, the circuits grew in complexity, mixing analog with digital parts and eventually incorporating multiple ICs such as logical gates, PLLs and microcontrollers, while the techniques used in modern v34, v.90 and v.92 protocols (like 1024-QAM) are so complex that implementing a modem supporting them with discrete components or general purpose IC's would be very impractical, and a dedicated DSP or ASIC is used instead, effectively turning the modem into a special embedded system, a dedicated computer in its own right."" The ideal solution became increasingly a software/hardware approach because of the flexibility. However as pointed out - the small piece of hardware have to have good DSP and Processor power for executing software algorithms very quickly to process the high bandwidth incoming and outgoing signals. Very high performance ADCs/DACs are also involved. Icera has 8 processors built in – that comforts me. A soft radio approach – once mastered is infinitely more powerful than a hardcoded approach. The performance in difficult or poor signal environments overall is better as the software self adapts/optimize to it. The key to Icera hitting 150MBits LTE are the horse power of the Icera processors and the max performance of the analog elements (LNA, ADCs, DACs, Mixers) in the chip. The downside of the Soft Radio approach tend to be Power consumption – it’s ALWAYS higher than a dedicated hardcoded modem - especially if the T4 has to pull some weight to run some of the algorithms. On the other hand Soft Radio solutions always result in lower silicon costs (QCOM stand alone LTE ASP was ~ $20 – at 40% silicon area savings Nvda ASP ~ $10 (yield goes up when the area gets smaller  ) – it’s a huge savings). Best of all you get to ship more products per wafer when at 20nM the silicon supply gets tight again. Bottom-line – the real clash between NVDA and QCOM and anybody else will be at the 20nM node – T4/i500 node is just the practice round – once they have the firmware and high Performance Soft Radio architecture nailed for full speed LTE – they will have the lowest cost solutions bar none. The hardcoded LTE will always be bigger whether it’s a stand alone or integrated in the CPU – in fact integrated in the CPU would make it cost even higher because the yields on the combined CPU/GPU/LTE would be impacted pretty drastically due to the larger silicon area (why do you think S4 Pro did not have an integrated LTE??? They would have shipped ZERO parts if they did that when the process was immature). The tradeoff is lower power. (Samsung with their own fab costs is a different arithmetic). Tegras performance per unit area per technology node, in general are already better than any processors out there and the soft radio technology integrated in the CPU will extend that advantage. It’s pretty easy to increase GPU performance – just integrate more GPU elements in the chip – ask Apple – look at their chip – none of them are commercially viable if they were to sell as a standalone chip – do you see anybody integrating 8 PowerVR GPUs into their Quad Cores to beat Apple? It's not a technology challenge.</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1358660499822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:41:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358661218994-2</Id><Topic><Title>Software Radio</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1358660499822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:41:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The Downside of icera's Soft Radio approach tends to be Power Consumption, – it’s ALWAYS higher than a dedicated QUALCOMM hardcoded modem." So that icera "soft modem" will be like the rest of Jen's mobile parts. They all suck juice like an Elephant.</Msg><Username>bestonica</Username><Timestamp>1358661218994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:53:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358662373827-3</Id><Topic><Title>Integrated Baseband v.s. Discrete?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358639330501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:48:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"if Icera's i500 is 4G capable, then why is it unreasonable to expect high end Tegra 4 + i500 devices to hit the market in 2013?" It's not and there should be nothing that technically restricts them from doing so. In fact, I am sure they have at least a reference design available, if not a dev-board. As for the differences, I am no expert but I am willing to add my .02 cents. The main advantages of having a single piece of silicon is, as you had mentioned; 1. cost not only for the manufacturer but the OEM as well, 2. ease of engineering, and 3. power consumption. Having one piece of silicon makes the design and implementation from the OEM a bit simpler as there is only one chip to add to your board as opposed to making room for an app processor, a baseband/communication processor, and most likely a DMA controller to manage the data exchange. This, as you might imaging, takes up a considerable amount of room on your board and makes the design/implementation a bit less turn key. Instead of 1 chip you are now dealing with three. In addition to that having the pieces spread among three chips degrades performance and power consumption a bit more than if you had it all on one piece of silicon. There are micro architectures/solutions, albeit probably still using DMA, that you can take advantage in a single chip solution that you can't with a multi-chip approach. The advantage of a multichip solutions is essentially TTM and risk. Sticking everything on one piece takes time, and adds considerable risk to you overall design as well as the manufacturing process. Now that being said I don't understand the comment; "is a waste of transistors". What do you mean by this, they have to go somewhere so why does it matter if its on a the same piece of silicon or not?</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358662373827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 01:12:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358662599778-4</Id><Topic><Title>Anandtech's update on Tegra 4 GPU ("nVIdia claims better performance than ipad4...."</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358661667131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 01:01:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whaaaat???? The Tegra attempt #4, and I quote, "does not support OpenGL ES 3.0" Man-o-man. Yet Another screw-up by nvidia. You see, Apple REQUIRES the OpenGL programming language on ALL of their third-party processor chips. Open GL -- that's it. No exceptions. And now we learn that the not-even-released-yet Tegra attempt #4, and I quote, "Does not support OpenGL ES 3.0" Did I mention? It looks like Yet Another Screw-Up by nvidia.</Msg><Username>bestonica</Username><Timestamp>1358662599778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 01:16:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358664114805-5</Id><Topic><Title>Software Radio</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1358660499822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:41:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are showing your ignorance as usual - probably a QCOM sales or marketing gul. T3 is a 40nm part that is almost at par with S4 Pro (Quad Core 28nM) on power - that is HUGE! S4 Pro should at least be 1/2 the power of T3!! Yes T3 is higher power than S4 Pro - Your IQ is 10 higher than my donkey and I guess that makes you the smartest DONKEY! The higher power to run the software radio is no worse than the fact that ALL MPEG decoding are now done in Software rather than Hardware - it is marginally higher and it's only when you talk. I guess in your case it's a lot higher since you talk from both ends 24x7!</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1358664114805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 01:41:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358665853103-6</Id><Topic><Title>Software Radio</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1358660499822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:41:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mark1289b, "The downside of the [Icera] Soft Radio approach tends to be Power consumption, – it’s ALWAYS higher than a dedicated hardcoded modem." YOU posted that yourself, right "mark1289b"? In the message at the top of this thread. Go take a look -- I'll wait for ya. He sure DID post that, now didn't he? Yes he did. So mark1289b, don't get all snarky and uncivilized this and that if you regret what you yourself posted here. Just don't post here again, okay?</Msg><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1358665853103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 02:10:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358666182427-7</Id><Topic><Title>"AMD accuses former staff of giving 100,000 secret documents to NVIDIA"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358384945597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 20:09:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ha ha ha ha ha! That was a GOOD one, Best!</Msg><Username>good_one_best</Username><Timestamp>1358666182427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 02:16:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358666717967-8</Id><Topic><Title>Software Radio</Title><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1358660499822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:41:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I also posted that YOU ARE THE SMARTEST DONKEY AROUND!</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1358666717967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 02:25:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358696533091-9</Id><Title>Buyout</Title><Msg>Is there is any chance NVDA will be bought by INTC or someone else. Thanks</Msg><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358696533091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:42:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358696714829-10</Id><Topic><Title>Buyout</Title><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358696533091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think so.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358696714829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:45:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358697012203-11</Id><Topic><Title>Buyout</Title><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358696533091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NONE !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358697012203</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:50:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358698805200-12</Id><Topic><Title>Buyout</Title><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358696533091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes! 100% - tomorrow.</Msg><Username>mark1289b</Username><Timestamp>1358698805200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:20:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358699468945-13</Id><Title>so where is the sales from i400???</Title><Msg>all these talks about LTE/i500, non-LTE i400 should be doing a quite a brisk business is it's any good? If i400 ANG, why would anybody think i500 would be any good??</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358699468945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:31:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358701834182-14</Id><Topic><Title>Anandtech's update on Tegra 4 GPU ("nVIdia claims better performance than ipad4...."</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358661667131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 01:01:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so 'better performance' eh.... so is nvda going to sell boat loads to aapl, samsung or amzn? If no, who else left to sell it to? technical bragging rights and cheering do nada for stock price, you know.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358701834182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:10:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358701890579-15</Id><Topic><Title>so where is the sales from i400???</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358699468945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:31:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>weak...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358701890579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:11:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358702127575-16</Id><Topic><Title>so where is the sales from i400???</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358699468945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:31:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How come we've never seen any Benchmarks for that elusive icera i400 modem? Like Ever. I'm thinkin' that if the icera i400 modem was any good, we would have seen the Benchmark test results posted here by ibbey, like 300-400 times now. But we haven't seen Any benchmarks have we? No, we haven't. It would be Really easy to do too. Oh so easy. You know how Jen was carnival barking about the Tegra #4 at the CES? Where he did a side-by-side test with two (2) wireless devices -- an unnamed device from probably some backwards communist bloc country, and the purportedly Tegra #4 powered device. Although we really don't know. And he had each device load like 27 webpages. Chunka chunka chunka chunka.... Yes yes yes, we all know which one was faster. 'Cause it was a rigged contest using the Slowest competitor found on the planet. But the point is, the same identical test could be done with whatever wireless device that icera i400 modem is in, if any. So Mr. Anand Lal Shimpi, the Founder of the world-renowned benchmarking firm AnandTech, could compare his own personal Apple iPhone versus the icera i400 modem device. If there IS such a device. Maybe Mr. Anand Lal Shimpi could make a youtube video of the side-by-side test too. Which we could all watch -- over and over -- Uproariously. Did I mention? So where are the Benchmarks for the icera i400 modem?</Msg><Username>good_point_best</Username><Timestamp>1358702127575</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:15:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358703073812-17</Id><Topic><Title>so where is the sales from i400???</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358699468945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:31:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You would think that an OEM would want to See some kinda Benchmark test of the icer i400 modem Before plunking down his cash, right? I would, and most Everybody would too. Well, maybe except for the pumper boyz, of course. So that youtube video from Mister Anand Lal Shimpi of AnandTech could serve as a marketing piece for the icera i400 modem. Well, IF the icera i400 actually wins the test of course. Otherwise QUALCOMM could use the video. And the folks from QUALCOMM could watch it -- over and over -- Uproariously.</Msg><Username>bests.idea</Username><Timestamp>1358703073812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:31:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358704939506-18</Id><Topic><Title>Buyout</Title><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358696533091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>22 bucks a share. Tomorrow. In the bag</Msg><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1358704939506</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:02:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358705187137-19</Id><Topic><Title>Buyout</Title><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358696533091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe a Leveraged Buyout lead by Jensen and the Board of Directors. Nvidia is the New Motorola Semi...LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358705187137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:06:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358705380763-20</Id><Topic><Title>Buyout</Title><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358696533091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as accurate as your other buyout predictions...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358705380763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:09:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358705465602-21</Id><Topic><Title>so where is the sales from i400???</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358699468945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:31:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jen's side-by-side demonstration at the CES -- where the Tegra #4 device appeared to beat whatever the other device was, in loading web pages? 'Cuda been total Fraud on the public, right? Think about it. What takes the longest amout of time in a web page search? Hummm? The first search. It takes Google somewhere around 0.7 and 0.8 seconds to find any random page the first time. Longer if the page is on some obscure corner of the internet, like in Romania. But once your browser finds it the first time, it caches the page, and your device can pull it up Really Really Fast the second time. So when Jen was on stage at the CES, carnival barking about how the Tegra #4 device loads web pages faster than Brand X -- how do we know that the Tegra #4 device didn't visit all 27 web pages BEFORE the show -- thereby saving them in cache memory -- yet the Brand X device had never been there before? Hummm? Did I mention? It 'cuda been total Fraud on the public, right? Without wood screws this time. C|B</Msg><Username>charlie_best_here</Username><Timestamp>1358705465602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:11:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358707703235-22</Id><Title>Nvidia's Q4 Earnings Will Beat Estimates Due To Fiscal Cliff Bill!</Title><Msg>In Q1, Q2, and Q3 Nvidia was paying US Taxes at a rate that is 20% higher than they will owe for 2012, because the R&amp;D credit had expired at the end of 2011. But Congress reinstated it retroactively for 2012 in the year end Fiscal Cliff Bill. Thus earnings should be boosted by $.04 on a GAAP basis and $.05 on a Non-GAAP Basis in Q4. Current Analyst Estimates for Q4 GAAP - $0.24 Non-GAAP - $0.29 With Tax Credit Retroactive for 2012 GAAP - $0.28 Non-GAAP - $0.34 Considering all else being the same.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358707703235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:48:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358708417492-23</Id><Topic><Title>so where is the sales from i400???</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358699468945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:31:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point, Charlie Best. I never thought about that before. But you're right. As always.</Msg><Username>good_point_best</Username><Timestamp>1358708417492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:00:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358708921658-24</Id><Topic><Title>Anandtech's update on Tegra 4 GPU ("nVIdia claims better performance than ipad4...."</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358661667131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 01:01:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's curious that Samsung changed GPUs. The existing dual core Exynos 5 uses the Mali 604, nominally 68GF. It may be that the cache coherence actually costs more in power than it returns in code efficiency. Not that the change moves then in the rankings.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1358708921658</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:08:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358709282051-25</Id><Topic><Title>Anandtech's update on Tegra 4 GPU ("nVIdia claims better performance than ipad4...."</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358661667131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 01:01:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you making a deliberate mis-statement? It does support OpenGL. The statement was that it doesn't have 3.0ES support, the version that was finalized a few months ago. That could simply mean that it hasn't passed the qualification tests yet, which seems likely given how recently it was introduced. You do seem to be a paid basher rather than someone interested in the products' market position and likely sales...</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1358709282051</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:14:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358710630036-26</Id><Topic><Title>Anandtech's update on Tegra 4 GPU ("nVIdia claims better performance than ipad4...."</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358661667131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 01:01:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the race has more to do with the role of the modem, whether it's integrated or not and/or the realized benefits of SDR vs. a set architecture for LTE, etc. Even though the performance/power of the graphics is always a bragging point, there's going to be a time when that part of the technology really becomes less significant in terms of advancement. It will be hard for consumers to see the difference. If anything, I think most friends I know buy the phone that has the best feature set and battery life. It's assumed that the graphics will be more than sufficient and it just becomes a standard. There's still room for better graphics and screens but there is less and less room left at the top to achieve or make improvements that the consumer can easily discern.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1358710630036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:37:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358719096895-27</Id><Title>I completely agree with Jen. Its GAME OVER for Nvidia.</Title><Msg>All you people can discuss tegra this, Kepler that.. But JenSun KNOWS. Its Game Over. If any of you are smart (which I doubt), you'd get out of the stock NOW.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358719096895</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:58:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358719175492-28</Id><Title>If Haswell kicks top of the line Nvidia Kepler butt, what has this Co have left..</Title><Msg>Project Shield? LOL.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358719175492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:59:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358720889793-29</Id><Title>What does Nvidia have as a followon to Kepler? TSMC's 20nm is</Title><Msg>horse manure says JenSun, so what is Nvidia going to do? Haswell is now equivalent to top of the line Kepler graphics. This is the END my friends. GAME OVER.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358720889793</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:28:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358724138467-30</Id><Title>OT: NINERS!</Title><Msg>advance to the big show, superbowl bound. Congrats!</Msg><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1358724138467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:22:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358724337783-31</Id><Topic><Title>OT: NINERS!</Title><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1358724138467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:22:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gp 9ers !</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358724337783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:25:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358728119268-32</Id><Topic><Title>EETimes comments on Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358651433979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 22:10:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey dipwad You might want to check broadcoms 5g.</Msg><Username>gwin2win</Username><Timestamp>1358728119268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:28:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358732647725-33</Id><Title>What Does This Mean - From 10Q</Title><Msg>Any experts out there? "As part of our stock repurchase program, we have entered into, and we may continue to enter into, structured stock repurchase transactions with financial institutions. These agreements generally require that we make an up-front payment in exchange for the right to receive a fixed number of shares of our common stock upon execution of the agreement, and a potential incremental number of shares of our common stock, within a pre-determined range, at the end of the term of the agreement." From 2Q FY2013 10Q "In fiscal year 2007, our Board of Directors, or Board, authorized us, subject to certain specifications, to repurchase shares of our common stock up to an aggregate maximum amount of $2.7 billion through May 2013. In October 2012, the Board extended the program through December 2014. The repurchases will be made from time to time in the open market, in privately negotiated transactions, or in structured stock repurchase programs, and may be made in one or more larger repurchases, in compliance with Rule 10b-18 of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934, as amended, subject to market conditions, applicable legal requirements, and other factors. The program does not obligate NVIDIA to acquire any particular amount of common stock and the program may be suspended at any time at our discretion. As part of our stock repurchase program, we have entered into, and we may continue to enter into, structured stock repurchase transactions with financial institutions. These agreements generally require that we make an up-front payment in exchange for the right to receive a fixed number of shares of our common stock upon execution of the agreement, and a potential incremental number of shares of our common stock, within a pre-determined range, at the end of the term of the agreement. We did not enter into any structured stock repurchase transactions or otherwise purchase any shares of our common stock during the three and nine months ended October 28, 2012. Through October 28, 2012, we have repurchased an aggregate of 90.9 million shares under our stock repurchase program for a total cost of $1.46 billion. As of October 28, 2012, we are authorized, subject to certain specifications, to repurchase shares of our common stock up to $1.24 billion."</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1358732647725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:44:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358737157914-34</Id><Topic><Title>EETimes comments on Tegra 4</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1358651433979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 22:10:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>”Their [Icera] software-defined radio is a very high-risk proposition", said Patrick Moorhead, principal of Moor Insights and Strategy (Austin)." "Your employer needs to hire someone smarter, period. They are wasting their money on you." -- writes ibexx88, snarkily. Hey ibbey! No need to get snarky and uncivilized here. Oh no no no. Nor post Libelous language about Best being paid money to post here. Which we ALL know simply isn't true. And you've been deleted How many times now for posting that? Hummm, ibbey? By Best's accurate records, a total of 62 messages were deleted last year alone, for posting or insinuating that Best is a "paid basher". When it just isn't true. Nope. Best has given "fair warning" Thirty Four (34) times now, right here on this very board, in writing, on a global venue, Behesting the poster to stop posting Libelous messages about Best being a "paid basher". So I'll tell ya what, ibbey. Write a decent Apology to Best -- retracting that Libelous language -- and Best will let you stay. Fair enough, right ibbey? Oh, and one more thing. Kindly address Best as sir -- as in, "Best, sir, I do Apologize. Sir." "It won't happen again, sir." Separately, as you may know, the Yahoo! Abuse-o-Meter goes on a point system, with each category of TOS abuse being assigned a different level of severity. Now, posting Libelous language is ILLEGAL in all 50 states (probably Puerto Rico, Guam and the U.S. Virgin Islands too, although that's somewhat of an unsettled "grey" area within Yahoo!) So as you might imagine, deleted Libelous messages get assigned high points. Okay, death threats are higher, but not by much. And when your account hits the fasmagorical total abuse-point threshold, *** PRESTO *** Your offending Yahoo! ID is gone. KaPut. Deleted forever. Something to give careful thought to -- The Yahoo! Abuse-o-Meter. Oh so careful thought.</Msg><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1358737157914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:59:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358740586160-35</Id><Topic><Title>so where is the sales from i400???</Title><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1358699468945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:31:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It looks like Mr. Anand Lal Shimpi of AnandTech has a HUGE opportunity here. To pull back the curtain on Jen's deceptionist Fraud on the Public. You know, like Toto did. And 75 years later, folks are still watching that video.</Msg><Username>perceptive.best</Username><Timestamp>1358740586160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:56:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358742546670-36</Id><Title>charlie_best_here</Title><Msg>I'm amused :P</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358742546670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:29:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358744309990-37</Id><Topic><Title>charlie_best_here</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358742546670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:29:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Simple minds = Easily amused.</Msg><Username>dr.bester</Username><Timestamp>1358744309990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:58:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>