<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360483232123-1</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Getanid61</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360460299515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 20:38:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"INTC @ 52 week low and ARMH @ 52-week high? Instead of gloating about your paper trades, why don't you do the smart thing at short ARMH/long INTC? Double whammy winner pair trade, actually." I am already long INTC...after a refocus... THE EMPIRE STRIKES BACK !! never short any stock... ARM64 era hasn't even started... but since you're worried about my ARMH... just fyi, stops at 40 now if things go south... "Also, go long NVDA since they make high margin things like GPUs and make more in profit per year than ARMH does by a lot." I am already long NVDA... but it's not about the profit per year, it's about the growth rates &amp; guidance... NVIdia just had a record Q, but guided down... They are also always aloof with Tegra projections during the CCs If they ever portray confidence about Tegra projections, it would do the stock well...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360483232123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 03:00:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360484759925-2</Id><Topic><Title>Other than tegra4 and Exynos5 is anyone using ARM's A15? Seems like a failure</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360455070571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 19:11:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You might be right about one aspect: the bulk of the tablet market won't be using A15 cores. The annualized sales rate of low-end ($40-$150) tablets is 50M units in China alone. Those are essentially all mediocre generic tablets with basic features. I find most of them to have barely usable touch screens, requiring a stylus, are slow, and are more than a bit ugly. But they work and are affordable, so they sell. Apparently really well. At that price point, the Tegra isn't viable. Nor is any A15 based chip. They are getting by with $5-$6 SoCs, which is a pretty slim margin for the chip vendor.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1360484759925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 03:25:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360489481110-3</Id><Topic><Title>The growth of the chromebook market</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360374381518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 20:46:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mars, Sorry but you are a technical incompetent...you really need to go back to replacing hard drives and making registry fixes at your full time IT repairman job. Regurgitating Wikipedia only gets you so far. Now, lets breakdown your bloviating. First of all don't spit out SMT as if it is a standard or specific implementation or better yet as if you have any idea as to what it means. Smt is a general term used to describe a concept and hyper threading is Intels implementation of such concept. However, SMT in and if itself means little - just because one implements an SMT solution doesnt inherently make it a good one let alone equivolent to a second fullcore. I.E. 2 x86 cores will ALWAYS perform on par or better than a single x86 hyper threaded core. Thus what, I argued is that having a hyper threaded core isn't the same as having a second fully concurrent core. So lets try this again shall we; hyperthtreading is a trick to add instruction concurrency (of multiple threads or processes) to a single core but with several caveats. It achieves this by not only executing multiple independent instructions per cycle but by also reducing other overhead normally associated with switching context; for example unwinding the stack and other state shifts. Just to dumb it down for you. Even though in some cases this will deliver you improvements in performance over serial execution on a single core it isn't equivalent by any means to a FULL second core. By Intels best benchmarks it can yield at max a 30% increase in efficiency over a single core without hyper threading. At best that is far less than what a full second core can do. 'I am afraid it is an apples to apples comparison because there is not going to be a native 16 core ARM server chip, there is not even going to be a native 8 Core ARM server chip' Really.? Why not because you couldn't google it? Enlighten me as well as everybody else on this board as to what the reasons are, technical or otherwise, why this cant be done? Arm has yet to move to the server so there is really no need for this scale right now but there will be. See...RISC processors scale much better CISC due to their reduced complexity, fixed width instruction length and reduced number of transistors so there is no reason that 16 isn't possible. ', there will only be duals (AMCC) and quads (ARM) and they will be be connected with an interconnect similar in performance to Ethernet which will have all the bandwidth, latency and coherency drawbacks of any cluster. ' very naive and bold with no empirical evidence or even reasonable argument as to why 4 is the limit...by they way...Ethernet is a poor chose of bus topology for this purpose and there are other topologies that would yield far better performance. Ethernet was chosen only because it was convenient . Implying that Ethernet is the best bus for the job is moronic. 'As it happens the benchmark tested was not even a coherent one so actual performance will be worse on a single system memory image like an RDBMS e.g. Oracle.' Isn't this my point; apples to oranges?!!! However, aren't most applications, inherently designed to work on contiguous memory on the box they are running? Aside from software that has been specifically designed for distribution or clustering done by the OS. 64 performance?. You are somehow trying to imply that a 64 bit proc gives you an inherent performance gain. This is not the case. Anyway I hope you learned much today and will remember our little lesson while you are swapping out a hard drives and upgrading customers to windows 8 on Monday.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1360489481110</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 04:44:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360496307001-4</Id><Topic><Title>The growth of the chromebook market</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360374381518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 20:46:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow you wrote much but said nothing relevant again perhaps you should change your name to strawmanagain or maybe just dumbagain or stupidagain would be more apt. You could not deny any of the facts I posted and just retreated into quoting abstract differences between Risc and Cisc and just hoping that will get you to the promised land where you get to strike x86 down. Hate to break it to you but much better Riscs than ARM have been competing against x86 on the server front for decades and they all have failed to halt the x86 rise. MIPS, PA-Risc, Alpha, Power, Sparc and I have worked on some of these architectures unlike you so I already know Risc does not contain any magic formula that makes it fundamentally superior to Cisc like IBM Z and x86 which I have also worked on in the server field. It is my job to work out and on the most efficient hardware/software solutions for multi million enterprise servers so I can't just wave my arms about pumping one architecture over another based on theoretical differences which may not bring anything substantial to the performance table when actually implemented. I have to provide the best solution in the here and now unlike fanboys like you wishing on a star that one day a native 16 core ARM solution will tip up to save my sorry bragging #$%$ ;-). When I started out the only competition was different competing mainframe architectures so I have had plenty of time to work out what really works and what does not in the computing field. p.s. if you look at x86 geekbench results you can see that hyperthreading often produces results much greater than 30%. Regardless of your strawman diversion it is still a simultaneous process that aims to unused resources on the processor that the other concurrent thread is not using.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360496307001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 06:38:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360508138884-5</Id><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro Launch Helps sell Microsoft Surface RT</Title><Msg>Microsoft's Surface Pro launch this weekend apparently sold out. Good for them. What's funny is the availability of Microsoft Surface RT tablets at Best buy stores has also dropped noticeably. Did some shoppers go for the 128GB $999 Pro but came home with the 32GB $499 RT? The ARM version of the surface tablet goes on sale in Europe on Feb 14th. "Three months after debuting its new Surface RT in the United States, Microsoft is is increasing the device’s overseas availability. The company said today that on February 14 it will launch the RT in Austria, Belgium, Denmark, Finland, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, the Netherlands, Norway, Portugal, Spain, Sweden and Switzerland." Just my own opinion...The Microsoft Pro at $899 for 64GB or $999 for 128GB sure is expensive and Microsoft office in not included!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360508138884</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 09:55:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360513856373-6</Id><Title>If qualcom in nexus 7 will the drivers be ready by christmas?</Title><Msg>Won't want to miss the selling season.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1360513856373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 11:30:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360514474016-7</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro Launch Helps sell Microsoft Surface RT</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360508138884</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 09:55:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surface RT = toy Surface PRO = full fledge computer kill the RT and make a 7 inch, $150 table that runs the window phone os</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1360514474016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 11:41:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360514543176-8</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Getanid61</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360460299515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 20:38:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>j7777kxx, None taken, especially since I was not at all bullish about Intel going into earnings. I won't link any of my articles here, because I would never want the denizens of Bestville to think I were trying to get clicks. And, of course, Seeking Alpha really doesn't like it when people copy and paste portions of articles, either, so I can't do that. But my sentiment going into Intel's earnings was that there was far too much uncertainty to really be near-term bullish.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360514543176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 11:42:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360514980943-9</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Getanid61</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360460299515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 20:38:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How are you doing on your Intel Investment?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360514980943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 11:49:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360515143002-10</Id><Topic><Title>Im "Out" before earnigns release.</Title><Username>rounhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1360464852857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 21:54:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good advice. Stay clear of NVDA before earnings, stock usually tanks after earnings.</Msg><Username>jermeoff</Username><Timestamp>1360515143002</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 11:52:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360516203957-11</Id><Title>Is Intel's Haswell A Has Been?</Title><Msg>It doesn't happen that often but a decent article appeared today on Seeking Alpha. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360516203957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 12:10:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360517566580-12</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel's Haswell A Has Been?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360516203957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 12:10:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel's reference design ultrabook at the ces had a detachable screen that could be used as a tablet. The screen was 10mm thick, nearly the same as apple's ipad and had battery life of seven hours. With the keypad, it had 13 hours run time.</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1360517566580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 12:32:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360518403005-13</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel's Haswell A Has Been?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360516203957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 12:10:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the Cost is? That's the problem. I can get a gamer laptop for $150 more than all these Intel toy computers. It's like putting a 650 horsepower superchaged V12 in a netbook at 4 times the price. I mean how much compute power do you need to touch that touch screen. By the way is Microsoft Office Included?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360518403005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 12:46:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360519678613-14</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel's Haswell A Has Been?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360516203957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 12:10:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The $1000 surface pro sold out in 24 hours People like toys, but need computers for work.</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1360519678613</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:07:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360522110127-15</Id><Topic><Title>The growth of the chromebook market</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360374381518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 20:46:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Moronsavian, Just take a moment or two away from installing the latest version of norton antivirus to think again about what I wrote. I will try to be more terse this time and dumb it down for you. First of all you presented little fact about the the subject at hand. Almost all of what you argued can be disputed simply by way of pointing out the two solutions in your argument are disparate and fundamentally different. Creating a distributed cluster of mobile class procs over a network and benchmarking them against single piece of server class silicon IS NOT an apples to apples comparison. You seem to be in denial about this. Btw: there is a reason I pegged you for an it/infrastructure guy which, by your own admission, is correct. I deal with these misguided technical arguments on a weekly basis. I have several infrastructure type guys in my engineering org ( we call them integration engineers) and several of them try to present stuff like this as if they've done it but once you push them past the first line of 'IT Today' :) the are lost. Saying things like 'a single memory system like an RDBMS' is always a dead give away. That statement is obscure and vague and I infer from it that you are trying to mask the substance of the statement by intertwining unconnected technical terms. You do realize enterprise apps can be scaled or clustered across nodes to improve throughput and concurrency, right? Anyways moving on ; I also factually stated how HT is NOT the same as having a second core, again you refuse to accept that. You clearly don't seem to understand its implementation and how rolls up to the developer. I can tell you from experience it's #$%$ with a lot of gotchas you don't have from running on a dedicated core. It's simple a HT virtualizes a second core and cmt IS a second core. Now I am not saying HT doesn't have it's place but that is for another day. The entire point of all my writing is to point out that RISC processors scale better and have a general overall power profile than x86. Shrinking Cisc cores is inherently more difficult than shrinking a RISc core. It's quite simple more transistors will always means more surface area - there is nothing magical about it. Additional the reduced complexity of the risc architecture makes connecting and scaling those cores easier. Hence HT - a virtualized a second core for less cost - smaller die fewer transistors less power. As for your p.s. I can't even respond as it is hardly a coherent and sensical statement more technical term babble. None of that makes any sense from a hw or sw engineering standpoint. Again ht works by attemptin to simultaneous execute 2 disparate instructions (mov eax, 5 - mov Edx, ESP + FF) for different threads but from the same pipeline in the same clock cycle. It's completely different from having 2 cores, 2 pipelines, 2 caches working on independent clocks. As for your alpha/dec other RISC procs have been here argument: that is simple it wasn't performance but content. Intel had windows as it didn't run on RISC procs(don't even mention NTas that was DOA much like 8). With Linux and virtualization, the cloud and the adaption of more non windows clients...well that day has come and gone. We will finally get to see how windows and intel hold up in a world that no longer is dependent on the win-tel monopoly. To sum this up you will see competitive server arm silicon that will be cheaper and more power efficient in the coming years.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1360522110127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:48:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360523909119-16</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro Launch Helps sell Microsoft Surface RT</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360508138884</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 09:55:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft Surface RT for $499 now sold out on line at Bestbuy. All 20 stores in my metroploitan area are sold out too. 2nd time this month. Looks like people came to buy the Pro for $899 without Microsoft Office but left with the toy RT with Microsoft office for $499.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360523909119</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 14:18:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360525231985-17</Id><Topic><Title>The Tegra, it is like elephant</Title><Username>naziba.adongo</Username><Timestamp>1349843708263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? Let's say that the dawdling board has finally decided to kill Jen's horrendous loss-making Tegra folly. Yeah, a Third of a Billion Dollars Lost per year is probably enough of that fun. So who gets the blindfold? The Tegra, Jen, or both? Jen led you boys into making commodity ARM chips, and competing with QUALCOMM on radio parts (pretty smart idea there, right boys?) -- but it doesn't mean he's the guy to lead you Out of this mess. {schick schick} "Pull two."</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1360525231985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 14:40:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360530286085-18</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Getanid61</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360460299515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 20:38:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just fine.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360530286085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:04:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360532046304-19</Id><Topic><Title>The growth of the chromebook market</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1360374381518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 20:46:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumbagain, I don't install PC software I write and tune bespoke server software as well as helping to pick the server hardware and I have done that probably more years than you have been alive back to the 1980s so all your handwaving strawmen arguments still don't wash with me. Let's address the latest you have written. 'Creating a distributed cluster of mobile class procs over a network and benchmarking them against single piece of server class silicon IS NOT an apples to apples comparison.' It is when each unit of the cluster runs its own copy of the application and the sum total throughput is what is being measured. As to this HT strawman route you have gone down, you initially said that HT was not a simultaneous threading system which is wrong. It uses unused resources at each processor cycle, I never said it was another core which is another strawman of your very vivid imagination. Look at the Geekbench scores for any x86 processor you often get much better scaling than 30% especially for integer applications. You still have not addressed the real fact that ARM is nowhere near x86 in performance or even performance/power given all the real comparisons that are out there already. You have touted ARM processors and I have given you real comparisons of the A9 and the A15 against OLD Core processors and they still fared badly in every metric and the A57 is only going to be 30-40% better than the A15 using ARM's own numbers. You just retreated into theoretical babbling whose terms and significance you don't really understand. Anyway I want you to believe the nonsense you are babbling, invest in ARMH, AMCC, AMD and any other ARM server ploy you can think of. Anyone who is stupid enough to buy into Jen's fairy tales here at NVDA deserves to lose more of their money on more ARM fairy stories ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360532046304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:34:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360533000194-20</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel's Haswell A Has Been?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360516203957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 12:10:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, it is the greatest Intel processor design since the Core 2 (Conroe/Merom). It will simultaneously lay devastating blows on AMD, ARM and NVDA. None of these companies will ever be the same again so be afraid ... very afraid ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360533000194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:50:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360533620972-21</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel's Haswell A Has Been?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360516203957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 12:10:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing like that best thing in the world selling at the highest price ever in an expensive PC that no one will pay for unless they are a gamer and then they will opt for high powered Nvidia discrete GPU and let Optimus turn off the graphics part of Haswell or use the cheaper Sandy Bridge microprocessor. Core Duo's are more than good enough today for consumer PC's. That really was a good fit for the market when they came out. Much Cheaper too. P.S. Your rant against ARM in servers is misdirected. Jensen said Nvidia has no attention of entering that market. Said they are looking at some Tesla products with ARM CPUs for HPC. That's all. someone was just making fun of your love of Intel. Intel is safe in servers for years to come.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360533620972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 17:00:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360535869291-22</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel's Haswell A Has Been?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360516203957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 12:10:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you think that Haswell will just appear in expensive PCs you are sadly mistaken. Just like Sandy and Ivy Bridge there will be cheap Haswell Celeron versions which will just devastate the quad A15s like Tegra 4. It will match their battery life but have much better cpu/gpu performance. It will have a better gpu than AMD's Trinity and means the bar is raised again for Nvidia in at what level a discrete gou starts. As to what Nvidia are planning for Project Denver they are the only ARM licensee that has any common sense WRT server plans. ARM architecture although relatively poor at integer is not bad at floating point and I could quite see a role for Project Denver SoC allied to Teslas in HPC sites. Even just relying on the ARM cores you could get respectable performance/bandwidth/price. The rest of them who think their general purpose micro-servers are going to take Intel down in general server apps are just living in cloud cuckoo land.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360535869291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 17:37:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360538032889-23</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel's Haswell A Has Been?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360516203957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 12:10:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you think that Haswell will just appear in expensive PCs you are sadly mistaken. Will they be cheap enough to run $300 to $400 laptops and tablets. I doubt it. Expensive is a relative term. The only consumer PC's that sell for a decent price are PC's for the Affluent where they sell as luxury goods like Apple Macbooks or Application specific PC's such as Gamer PC's or Workstation PCs. The rest are just good cheap petty functionary utilitarian tools. "The rest of them who think their general purpose micro-servers are going to take Intel down in general server apps are just living in cloud cuckoo land." Just the Tech Press doing what they do best....searching for clicks! JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360538032889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 18:13:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360545152862-24</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Getanid61</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360460299515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 20:38:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just gonna add then when you get out of school... and get some real industry experience... your views on the industry will change... "Instead of gloating about your paper trades" You wouldn't write a thread to me if they were...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360545152862</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 20:12:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360546596154-25</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Getanid61</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360460299515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 20:38:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem is, getanid61, is that you claim to be long INTC, and yet go on and on about how ARMH is at a 52-week high. Why don't you also point out how Netflix is at a 52-week high? Is that company *really* worth $10B?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360546596154</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 20:36:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360546857896-26</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Getanid61</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360460299515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 20:38:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The problem is, getanid61, is that you claim to be long INTC, and yet go on and on about how ARMH is at a 52-week high. " SO... why is that a problem... It's NOT a zero-sum game... fyi, my fun on the INTC board is for the naive who think it's only about the fabs... "Why don't you also point out how Netflix is at a 52-week high? Is that company *really* worth $10B?" weak... and entirely irrelevant...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360546857896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 20:40:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360547793165-27</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Getanid61</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360460299515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 20:38:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I find it somewhat remarkable that Ashraf as young as he is writes about value and growth and income stocks such as INTC and NVDA rather than chearing MOMO stocks like ARMH and Netflix. I always intended after I made my money in the high flyers to park the money in nice cushy comfortable growth and income stocks. And that is what I did. Love The Dividend...Don"t You?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360547793165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 20:56:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360552256684-28</Id><Title>If Nvidia dumps tegra, stock could go up because</Title><Msg>tegra is a loss leader, and Nvidia's profits will increase.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360552256684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 22:10:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360552381318-29</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro Launch Helps sell Microsoft Surface RT</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360508138884</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 09:55:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMG Microsoft Surface RT for $499 is Sold out of all 20 Best Buy stores in the San Jose Ca. metropolitan area. Only available in 4 stores in the New York City Metropolitan area. Still sold out online at Best Buy and goes on sale in Europe Feb. 14th. And this is the Toy Version with Microsoft Office Included. Crazy I know!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360552381318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 22:13:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360552550201-30</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro Launch Helps sell Microsoft Surface RT</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360508138884</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 09:55:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are returning Surface RT in droves. You can get conned at Best Buy, but when you take it home, you realize its really a POS.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360552550201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 22:15:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360553894834-31</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro Launch Helps sell Microsoft Surface RT</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360508138884</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 09:55:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you warn them....those silly fools....And why is Microsoft selling the RT version in Europe starting Feb. 14th. You would think the EU commission would step in and stop those sales. Checkout the Best Buy stores in your area. The RT version really has sold out! I know the customers came for a real Intel Pro Model at $1000 without Microsoft Office but those unscrupulous Best Buy clerks told those unwitting customers that the RT version came with Microsoft Office at $499.Shame on them. Did they know that Legacy X86 apps won't work on the RT. I'm sure they didn't....in fact they didn't even know what an X86 Legacy app was other than Excel......maybe Powerpoint...oh it works on RT too and is included. GrandMa sure is being confused by this misleading marketing! P.S. Pray tell me what Legacy X86 app you use Mr. Intel.. I wrote macros in DOS years ago, but then I found I could do them in Excel must easier. I'm all ears! LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1360553894834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 22:38:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>