<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368507638416-1</Id><Topic><Title>AMD @ an 8 month high and climbing</Title><Username>moreupsidethandown</Username><Timestamp>1368471368793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 14:56:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I would have considered AMD a good buy at the sub-$3 level, and at the current price I'd either hold just a little bit longer or sell it off now. I'd NEVER buy AMD at the current stock price . . NEVER." Only when it was $3 you didn't buy any then either did you? Did you? When it was $3 you spewed the same BS that you did when it was $2 and now again when its $4, now isn't that right? This message board has a long memory. No matter what AMD trades at we now know you are full of it sport. IMHO of course.</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368507638416</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 01:00:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368508721638-2</Id><Title>A 30 cent can of Market Spank clears this place out</Title><Msg>We had to put up with high fives and trash talking all day Friday as Nvidia post a modest gain but Nvidia fans made themselves scarce as Nvidia gave back a thin dime. So when the market takes 30 cents back it clears this place out. They may stick there heads up to bash a few techs and grumble but then its back into hiding to lick those market wounds.. 30 cents is all it took to put the run on Nvidia fans. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368508721638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 01:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368518301938-3</Id><Topic><Title>Get real</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1368203462628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:31:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the conference, NVDA's CFO told Tegra segment Q2 will be lower. Q1 rev @ $103.1M then Q2 could expect lower than $100M. NVDA's big gain on Friday might because of investors realized that discrete graphic card won't die. It lives well in PC gamers and it grows strong in enterprise workstation, server and data center. And suprised at Tegra's fail to contribute in Q1 NVDA's earning still beat expectation! NV might have seen SoC competetions from everywhere and they need stock buyback to escort the share price till early next year when, hopefully,Tegra could get out of the mud. There are downside possibilities and there are lots of upside potential. By the year end, we'll see more clear where NVDA is heading. Before then, risk in investing NVDA seems forseeable.</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1368518301938</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 03:58:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368533560578-4</Id><Title>Shorts are Toast...ASR with GS just announced.</Title><Msg>7:56AM NVIDIA enters into accelerated share repurchase agreement with Goldman (NVDA) 14.24 : Co entered into an accelerated share repurchase agreement with Goldman, Sachs &amp; Co. to repurchase a total of $750 million of NVIDIA common stock. NVIDIA will acquire the shares under the ASR Agreement as part of its previously announced intention to return in excess of $1 billion to shareholders in the current fiscal year. Under the ASR Agreement, NVIDIA will pay $750 million and will receive a majority of the shares underlying the ASR Agreement during the second quarter of fiscal year 2014. Any remaining shares to be repurchased under the ASR Agreement, if any, will be based generally on the daily volume-weighted average price of NVIDIA common stock during the term of the ASR Agreement, subject to certain adjustments pursuant to the terms and conditions of the ASR Agreement. At settlement, under certain circumstances, Goldman may be required to deliver additional shares of common stock to NVIDIA, or, under certain circumstances, NVIDIA may be required to deliver shares of its common stock or may elect to make a cash payment to Goldman. Purchases under the ASR Agreement are expected to be completed before the end of October 2013, although the completion date may be accelerated at Goldman's option. The actual number of shares repurchased will be determined at that time</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368533560578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:12:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368537153376-5</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are Toast...ASR with GS just announced.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368533560578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:12:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Impressive and Shield pricing also announced :-)</Msg><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1368537153376</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:12:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368537308529-6</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are Toast...ASR with GS just announced.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368533560578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:12:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>short interest is not high , just 5% + Now this CEO is gone MAD and going to destroy NVDA stock in the long run.. Cash has been main attraction to be long here, once CASH is depleted with desperate buy backs, this STOCK will make new lows NVDA is circled... INTEL has caught up in graohics too, AMD has new road map Mobile graphics NVDA is a looser ARMH Processors a commodity THIS CEO.. is now axing his own foot... BUY BACK is very disastrous move</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1368537308529</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:15:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368538457343-7</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are Toast...ASR with GS just announced.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368533560578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:12:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good price and specs, they can always drop it later if they need to shift more units. Tegra 4 shipping in June so only a month or so after the other quad-core A15, Exynos 5410. 4-5 hour playing time with a 28.8 Wh battery which makes it a 6-7W device. http://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonevangelho/2013/05/14/nvidias-project-shield-all-the-launch-details-revealed-including-the-price/?partner=yahootix</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368538457343</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368538878712-8</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are Toast...ASR with GS just announced.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368533560578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:12:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are wrong. As a percentage of equity NVDA held more cash than most companies, and the stock did nothing for long. If you as a CEO see strong growth down the road it makes perfect sense to purchase your company's stock when is relatively undervalue, unless you have some acquisition in mind. Who in their chip segment would they be they be able to buy??? No one worth their investment. Hence the logic of the share repurchase plan. If you are a short at this time, I wish you luck, because you'll need it.</Msg><Username>jtjgmtbt</Username><Timestamp>1368538878712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:41:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368539871395-9</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are Toast...ASR with GS just announced.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368533560578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:12:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is a rehash of old news. accelerated buyback big whoopee they are desperate for sure and intc and amd going into mobile and yes one day not now discrete graphics go the way of the dodo bird that's why stock is doing absolutely nothing today plus goldman probably has all the shares in there own company could sell them to nvda for a profit at where they bought them maybe in the 12's</Msg><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1368539871395</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:57:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368541582644-10</Id><Title>"Nvidia Hitches Ride to Future on Android Games After PS4"</Title><Msg>"The handheld-gaming machine, which Nvidia announced in January, will retail for $349, the company said today in website posting." source: bloomberg</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368541582644</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:26:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368541773480-11</Id><Topic><Title>"Nvidia Hitches Ride to Future on Android Games After PS4"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368541582644</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:26:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Start saving your pennies Nvidia fans, Nvidia wants $349 for a SHIELD Toy to play Android games you can play on your phone for FREE. lol How much will a real Game Console like the Xbox 720 or PS4 cost ? Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368541773480</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:29:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368542227007-12</Id><Title>Thoughts on Shield Retailers and Countries at Launch?</Title><Msg>Shield will only be carried by Newegg, Gamestop, Micro Center, and Canada Computers at launch. I think Gamestop was a good decision, as I think there is still some value in potential customers being able to hold a device before purchasing. Kind of concerning that there are not more retailers at launch though. Was hoping that they would also be available as an add-on/bundle through some of the PC manufacturers and/or at one or two other large brick and mortar retail chains (in addition to gamestop). Thoughts? I am guessing the lack of retailers is largely due to a lot of them wanting too much of a cut. Also, with the US and Canada being the only markets initially, is this too conservative or just the norm for a brand new product line? With the low break-even point, I do not see why they did not pick a few more developed countries to launch in simultaneously. I realize that shield is likely not priced into the stock yet as it is a wild card; any success is icing on the cake.</Msg><Username>morrowltd</Username><Timestamp>1368542227007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:37:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368542362773-13</Id><Title>After One Hour of Trading AMD Volume 17M shares, UP another 2%</Title><Msg>Will Nvidia move 17M shares in a full day of trading? Will Nvidia take back that 2% the market snatched away yesterday? Whatever is going on with one GPU outfit has skipped over your GPU outfit Nvidia fans. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368542362773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:39:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368542719987-14</Id><Topic><Title>Thoughts on Shield Retailers and Countries at Launch?</Title><Username>morrowltd</Username><Timestamp>1368542227007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would you pay $349 for what looks like a Game Controller to pay games you could play on your phone for free? Make room in your pocket Nvidia fans for a $349 Pocket Toy that does not make phone calls but plays games you could play on that phone in your other pocket. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368542719987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368543145074-15</Id><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Msg>PS4 and Xbox 720 Major Game Changers to play on any mobile device. This will crush the new Nvidia hand held game. Who will pay $350 for the Nvidia when you have this? The PS4 and the Xbox 720 will be industry game changers. With the PS4 and XBox 720, we're witnessing the newest evolution of video games, a shift that will turn high-quality video gaming into a play-anywhere, anytime experience. PS4 — as well as the soon-to-come Xbox 720, open the doors a completely re-imagined video game industry. Release date, price, and even what the console look like play second-fiddle to what users will be able to do on the device. The PS4 will integrate a wave of new ideas and technologies, from cloud computing to mobile gaming, all of which will redesign how we use and consume major video games. ((((Sony has said that every PS4 game will eventually be able to be played on its hand-held gaming system, the Playstation Vita. This effectively allows console gamers to be mobile gamers.)))) To do this, PS4 will utilize a cloud computing system ... so far the first major gaming platform to do so (Xbox is also reportedly said to be using this feature in its future 720 model). The cloud computing will utilize Gaikai streaming technology, creating no need for discs or downloads. (((Cloud computing, then, will allow Playstation to eventually stream content on other devises … imagine a Playstation App that allows you to use your PS4 console as a game mainframe and stream those games on mobile devises. Imagine playing a high-quality Killzone: Shadowfall on your train ride to work))).</Msg><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368543789945-16</Id><Topic><Title>Thoughts on Shield Retailers and Countries at Launch?</Title><Username>morrowltd</Username><Timestamp>1368542227007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd say they are also trying to get a feel for the market. Its a new product they probably want to see what sticks and what doesn't. They are most likely being conservative so they can focus resources. stuff like ad spending, target markets and logistics. Gamers tend to go to gamestop. Newegg is a great place to buy computer parts like graphics cards. I'd say they are targeting the right markets.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1368543789945</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:03:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368543809776-17</Id><Topic><Title>Thoughts on Shield Retailers and Countries at Launch?</Title><Username>morrowltd</Username><Timestamp>1368542227007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's see some patience here. Brand new idea, unproven, and we need to talk before we can run. The retailers are correct, they're targeting enthusiasts in the local markets. Best Buy and Walmart and Europe and Asia will come when and if the demand materializes. At this stage NVDA has heard from their loudest and most loyal early adapter types and I'm sure they are very gung ho on Shield. These guys will have the patience and knowledge to work through inevitable first gen issues. Whether shield can work through issues to have a great user experience, create a buzz and rally the momentum to transcend the early adopters into a broader group of enthusiasts will be the key to shield's success. This is going to take some number of months. NVDA is taking a very big gamble here, let's give it some time to develop.</Msg><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1368543809776</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:03:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368545156621-18</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are Toast...ASR with GS just announced.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368533560578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:12:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure why I don't have you on ignore, but will now. You do realize that they made more 'cash' last quarter and have continued to do so over the last several quarters? I think NVDA can handle a buyback that takes out say $1 billion out of a pot of almost $9 billion that continues to grow. You come across as desperate to post something like this now.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1368545156621</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:25:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368545336725-19</Id><Topic><Title>Get real</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1368203462628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:31:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ASR agreement with GS, the $750M repurchase to be completed by end of October? Something good are coming! Risk to invest at current level is forseeable limitted.</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1368545336725</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368545579046-20</Id><Topic><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing in this post shows that there is actually 'anything' ready for market, yet Project Shield is going out later this month. In fact, it feels like PS4 and Xbox 720 are responses to Nvidia leading the way, especially with PR that really shows nothing and promises the stars.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1368545579046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:32:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368545704818-21</Id><Title>Bloomberg just in: NVIDIA begins accepting orders for Project Shield</Title><Msg>$349 (exactly what I predicted a few months ago) ______ Nvidia Corp. (NVDA), the largest maker of chips for graphics cards in personal computers, today began taking orders for its Shield hand-held gaming device and said shipments get under way next month. The handheld-gaming machine, which Nvidia announced in January, will retail for $349, the company said today in website posting. Nvidia Chief Executive Officer Jen-Hsun Huang is betting on the device to accelerate a push into markets outside of the PC graphics-chip market, which provided 82 percent of the company’s revenue in the latest quarter. Shield, along with other devices such as the WikiPad and Ouya, is part of a growing array of gaming hardware that’s challenging more established console systems, such as Microsoft Corp. (MSFT)’s Xbox and Sony Corp. (6758)’s PlayStation, both of which will be updated this year. Shield is built around Tegra 4, newest in the company’s line of processors designed for tablets and mobile phones. The device uses Google Inc. (GOOG)’s Android software, and resembles a console’s video-game controller that also features a pop-up screen. It works with “Angry Birds” and other games that can run on Android. Along with a touch-enabled five-inch screen, the device has built-in speakers and a Wi-Fi connection for Internet access. Shield can also connect to larger screens for playing games. When Huang introduced the device at the Consumer Electronics Show in January, he showed it connected to a television. By linking it wirelessly to a PC, players will also have access to pricier titles such as “Call of Duty.” Shares of Santa Clara, California-based Nvidia declined 2.1 percent to $14.24 at yesterday’s close in New York, leaving them up 16 percent this year.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368545704818</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368545824020-22</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg just in: NVIDIA begins accepting orders for Project Shield</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368545704818</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SOURCE: businessweekDOTcom/news/2013-05-14/nvidia-begins-accepting-orders-for-shield-portable-gaming-device</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368545824020</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:37:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368546269359-23</Id><Topic><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Almost everything you talk about is basically what grid does.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1368546269359</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:44:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368546455228-24</Id><Topic><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what i meant to say(hit post by accident): Everything about the cloud that your taking about is what grid can do.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1368546455228</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:47:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368546480846-25</Id><Title>A $199 SHIELD Toy would be over priced so a $349 SHIELD Toy is DOA</Title><Msg>Who wants to pay $349 to play Android games you can play for FREE on your iPhone. Nvidia fans , that's who but no one else. lol Priced NOT to sell since they'll probably lose money on each one sold. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368546480846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:48:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368546572221-26</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg just in: NVIDIA begins accepting orders for Project Shield</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368545704818</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thats a great price - Expect a quick sellout of original inventory. Enough Nvidia Geeks out there who are jonesing for this. hmm... I wonder if Nvidia has been purposely lowballing revenue estimates for next qtr. This could easily add 40-50M to Q2 revenue. (150k sell through)</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1368546572221</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:49:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368546757644-27</Id><Title>NVIIDA Shield shipping in June, ahead of all refresh game consoles. Final specs</Title><Msg>"Nvidia's Project Shield handheld gaming device, now called simply Shield, will be available for pre-order on May 20 priced at $349, though it won't ship to customers until the end of June. Shield takes the form of a console game controller with a 5-inch, pop-up screen that can display images at a 720p (1280 x 720 pixel) resolution. It runs on Nvidia's latest Tegra 4 chip, which has four CPU cores and 72 graphics cores to support a maximum resolution of 3200 x 2000 pixels, so games can be played at full HD on an attached TV. Shield will be available for order through Nvidia's website and via retailers Newegg, GameStop, Micro Center and Canada Computers. The handheld was introduced at the International CES in January. NVIDIA Shield runs the Android 4.1 OS, code-named Jellybean. Games will be available for download from the Google Play store and from gaming libraries like Steam and Nvidia's TegraZone. TegraZone currently lists 76 games, including "Max Payne," "Sonic 4," "Grand Theft Auto: Vice City" and "NBA 2K13." Nvidia insists the gaming experience on Shield will be better than on smartphones. With 802.11n Wi-Fi, the handheld can also play PC games streamed from a computer with an Nvidia GeForce GTX 650 graphics processor or better. Shield has integrated speakers and a set of controls including dual joysticks, directional buttons and bumpers. It has a mini-HDMI out port so the controller can be hooked up to a TV. Other features include 16GB of storage, 2GB of RAM, Bluetooth and GPS. There's also a microSD slot for adding more storage. (To be continued)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368546757644</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:52:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368546828803-28</Id><Topic><Title>NVIIDA Shield shipping in June, ahead of all refresh game consoles. Final specs</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368546757644</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:52:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>part 2: Nvidia will compete with Nintendo, Sony and Microsoft in the gaming hardware market, which will undergo some big changes this year. Sony's PlayStation 4 will ship later this year, and Microsoft is expected to announce the next Xbox gaming console on May 21. Nintendo started shipping the Wii U late last year. Sony and Nintendo also offer handheld gaming products. While Shield will compete mainly with the handheld consoles, the gates are open for Nvidia to go after the PlayStation and Xbox, said Patrick Moorhead, president and principal analyst at Moor Insights and Strategy. "If Nvidia can get some AAA titles and a good experience connecting to an HDTV, I could see a small segment of consumers choosing Shield over a new console," he said via email. Some buyers, such as GTX PC gamers and Android gamers, will be willing to pay the $349 for the handheld, Moorhead said. "This doesn't have to be some big blowout to the general population for this to be deemed a success, only sales to their two target audiences. The key will be for Nvidia to deliver an amazing game experience to that audience," he said. Nvidia is traditionally known as a graphics company, and its GPUs were used by Sony in the PlayStation 3. However, Sony's PlayStation 4 will have chips from Advanced Micro Devices, which is also expected to supply chips for Microsoft's next Xbox. pcworldDOTcom/article/2038705/nvidias-shield-gaming-handheld-to-go-on-sale-may-20-for-349.html</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368546828803</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368546904241-29</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are Toast...ASR with GS just announced.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368533560578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:12:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shield will show the capabilities of Tegra could do and significant increase the value to their mobile devices.</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1368546904241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:55:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368547295089-30</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg just in: NVIDIA begins accepting orders for Project Shield</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368545704818</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great news, thanks!</Msg><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1368547295089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368547350489-31</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are Toast...ASR with GS just announced.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368533560578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:12:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Shorts are Toast...ASR with GS just announced." And you wander why some might think Nvidia fans are clueless about Nvidia. lol Try and keep up with current events. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368547350489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:02:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368547463023-32</Id><Topic><Title>A $199 SHIELD Toy would be over priced so a $349 SHIELD Toy is DOA</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368546480846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:48:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't realize every schoolchild had an iPhone ;-). Games with controller sticks are infinitely better/preciser than swaying and tapping a phone/tablet. This device will be bought by geeks and kids, they can always add a modem later if folks want to use it as a phone too.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368547463023</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368547565410-33</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are Toast...ASR with GS just announced.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368533560578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:12:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eat your heart out, XC paperhead!</Msg><Username>valleybard</Username><Timestamp>1368547565410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:06:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368547618631-34</Id><Topic><Title>A $199 SHIELD Toy would be over priced so a $349 SHIELD Toy is DOA</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368546480846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:48:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's hoping EVERY Nvidia fan on this message board shells out $349 to buy an Nvidia SHIELD Toy. I can think of no better way to WASTE good money than to blow $349 on JUNK. SHIELD is the DUMBEST idea Nvidia has ever had to date, who knows what DUMB ideas await us next. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368547618631</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:06:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368548351435-35</Id><Topic><Title>NVIIDA Shield shipping in June, ahead of all refresh game consoles. Final specs</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368546757644</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:52:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nvidia insists the gaming experience on Shield will be better than on smartphones" - Ya, actually having buttons to push and good sound practically guarantees that.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1368548351435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368548367908-36</Id><Topic><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who would pay $350 for a hand held game when you can by a PS4 or the new Xbox for about the same price, not to mention I can plan angry birds on my tablet or phone. This will be a flop for nvidia.</Msg><Username>fybsmells</Username><Timestamp>1368548367908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:19:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368548497833-37</Id><Title>NVDA Will Buy Back Shares, AMD Will Issue Cheap New Shares Soon</Title><Msg>The handwriting is on the wall, NVDA will continue to grow share value by the end of 2013.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1368548497833</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:21:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368548850620-38</Id><Topic><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Based on your description of the product, you don't know what you are talking about . . And why the 'strong buy' sentiment then?</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1368548850620</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368549219892-39</Id><Title>short the stock</Title><Msg>dump coming soon when dividends are taken</Msg><Username>markhwang2003</Username><Timestamp>1368549219892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:33:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368549353618-40</Id><Topic><Title>short the stock</Title><Username>markhwang2003</Username><Timestamp>1368549219892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:33:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>info. book value less than 8 1 year target about 14$</Msg><Username>markhwang2003</Username><Timestamp>1368549353618</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:35:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368549578771-41</Id><Title>HOT NEWS! Nvidia strikes deal with Goldman to buy back 750 million of its shares</Title><Msg>SOURCE: WSJ just in By Saabira Chaudhuri Nvidia Corp. (NVDA) said it struck an accelerated share repurchase agreement with Goldman Sachs Group Inc. (GS) under which the chipmaker will buy back $750 million of its stock. The company will acquire the shares as part of its previously announced intention to return over $1 billion to shareholders in the current fiscal year. Nvidia has a market capitalization of about $8.8 billion, according to FactSet. The Santa Clara, Calif., company is best known for making chips and circuit boards that help computers and videogame consoles generate visual effects. Over the years, the company has expanded into making chips for mobile devices, boosting its sales as companies such as Google Inc. (GOOG) and Microsoft Corp. (MSFT) use its chips in their tablets. ___ WOW! Such confidence!</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368549578771</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368549826232-42</Id><Topic><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You want one good reason? You want a reason above all other reasons. The thing that every gamer dreams of? What better reason could there possibly be other than playing games while on the toilet.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1368549826232</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368549885752-43</Id><Topic><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this posted in completely the wrong area</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1368549885752</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368549922275-44</Id><Topic><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>never mind my browser was acting weird</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1368549922275</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:45:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368550626781-45</Id><Topic><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lots of gamers would love to play in the bathroom. I cant count the times I've heard gamers refer this exact thing. with wireless controllers and mirrors to the Wii U's tablet controllers. It will be a dream come true with the shield. a real controller with great sound. Of course that wont be a primary reason but still one that cant be ignored.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1368550626781</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:57:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368550781860-46</Id><Title>AMD up 78% YTD, 35 M shares Traded Today, No Buyback Needed.</Title><Msg>If no one wants Nvidia then let Nvidia buy Nvidia, right? AMD UP 2% today with 35M shares traded today Nvidia UP 1% today with 6M shares traded today. Do you know which issue the market is chasing HIGHER? Is it sinking in yet? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368550781860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:59:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368551336205-47</Id><Title>Nvidia is struggling to get back to where it closed on Fri while AMD moves ahead?</Title><Msg>SHIELD Toys and Stock Buyback tricks are just more game playing with shareholder money. If the market wanted Nvidia then the market would have chased Nvidia up instead of Nvidia trying to chase Nvidia up. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368551336205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:08:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368551366802-48</Id><Topic><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can tell you that 2 of my family members wish they could play PC games in the bathrooms. And now they can......for the first time. There are a number of high-level games to be bundled with Project. I will summarize these later in the day with gamers' comments.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368551366802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368551960452-49</Id><Topic><Title>A $199 SHIELD Toy would be over priced so a $349 SHIELD Toy is DOA</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368546480846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:48:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I didn't realize every schoolchild had an iPhone ;-)." But you do realize that every school kid wants an iPhone don''t you? lol BTW How much does Apple's latest and gretest iPhone cost today? Do you have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368551960452</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:19:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368552784592-50</Id><Title>Nvidia At An Inflection Point</Title><Msg>Article at SA, RL Ting author. Good read longs</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1368552784592</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:33:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368552928259-51</Id><Topic><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poster's ID tells you what you need to know</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1368552928259</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:35:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368552931312-52</Id><Topic><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can stream PC games to this. And you can send games from this to the TV. Assuming you can do both at the same time, this is essentially a Steambox with a screen and controller, which is pretty damn amazing if you think about it.</Msg><Username>amdlongsrfools</Username><Timestamp>1368552931312</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:35:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368553786469-53</Id><Topic><Title>NVIIDA Shield shipping in June, ahead of all refresh game consoles. Final specs</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368546757644</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:52:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And thus is ushered in the end of the console!! $349 hell yes!</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1368553786469</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:49:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368553976452-54</Id><Topic><Title>A $199 SHIELD Toy would be over priced so a $349 SHIELD Toy is DOA</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368546480846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:48:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$649 to $849 unlocked and contract free which is considerably more than the $349 Shield which also has twice the cpu/gpu perormance over the iPhone5 as well as a 720p screen. Not a bad deal considering what you are getting. storeDOTappleDOTcom/us/buy/home/shop_iphone/family/iphone5</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368553976452</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:52:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368554911829-55</Id><Topic><Title>A $199 SHIELD Toy would be over priced so a $349 SHIELD Toy is DOA</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368546480846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:48:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"$649 to $849 unlocked and contract free which is considerably more than the $349" Yes $649 is more than $349 but who do you know paying $649 for an iPhone 5 when every phone company is offering it for $199 with a contract? Better yet who do you know paying $649 for an unlocked Tegra phone since you may no know anyone with an iPhone 5? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368554911829</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:08:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368555198590-56</Id><Topic><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone thinking a SHEILD Toy has a prayer is delusional including the knuckle heads over at Nvidia headquarters who came up with their DUMBEST idea to date. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368555198590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:13:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368555659248-57</Id><Title>"Google To Announce Next Nexus 7 Tomorrow"</Title><Msg>"Google To Announce Next Nexus 7 Tomorrow" ... "According to Ming-Chi Kuo, KGI Securities analyst, Google and Asus will partner and will announce the latest version, and I/O will be the venue for the unveiling of the next Nexus 7, which is set to be released in June or July for $199. Kuo has also provided the specs for Nexus 7, as per the review, the tab will sport a 7-inch LTPS 1920 x 1200 display, powered by 7-inch LTPS 1920 x 1200 display processor with multiple storage options. It will host a 5-MP rear camera and a HD front-facing camera. Packed with 4,000mAh battery, the tab would run on Android 4.3." source: siliconindia</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368555659248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:20:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368555733132-58</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are Toast...ASR with GS just announced.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368533560578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:12:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think he has missed that this isn't AMD, which continues to lose money and is desperate to raise cash in order to survive long enough to introduce new products. Nvidia is generating cash, increasing sales, margin and share in its primary market. With plenty of cash and a stable revenue stream it's an appropriate move to return some of the profits to the shareholders. Both buy-backs and dividends do that. Where's the problem?</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1368555733132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:22:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368555911694-59</Id><Topic><Title>"Google To Announce Next Nexus 7 Tomorrow"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368555659248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:20:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you Nvidia fans still think Tegra 4 will be in the Next Nexus 7 announcement on Wed? The world will find out "Tomorrow" even though we know Tegra 4 is DOA today, right? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368555911694</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:25:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368556457203-60</Id><Topic><Title>A $199 SHIELD Toy would be over priced so a $349 SHIELD Toy is DOA</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368546480846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:48:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phone contracts are not free especially to a kid lol. You asked for the device to device price comparison and I gave you it. You pay twice as much for half the cpu and gpu performance on a smaller screen. As pure gaming devices there is no comparison but of course you will develop another pointless strawman for your retort. Anyway why didn't Rory Read answer the GM analyst questions about the console chips ? Is that because he is not expecting anyway ? ;-). AMD's stock price is built on pillars of sand which Intel is continually hacking away at, at least Nvidia has learned to make serious money out of gpus while AMD have always seen it as an unprofitable hobby.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368556457203</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368556590155-61</Id><Title>Me Thinks a $199 Next Nexus 7 with a Beefier SoC will out sell a $349 SHIELD Toy?</Title><Msg>Google's Next Nexus will suck the wind right out of any SHIELD Toy, game playing, pre order BS Nvidia is trying spin for their dumbest idea to date. SHIELD Toy is Nvidia's answer to not getting in the PS4 and the Next Nexus 7. Since Sony and Google wouldn't, Go PLAY with yourself Nvidia, that's what SHIELD Toy is all about. IMHO of course</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368556590155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:36:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368556972872-62</Id><Topic><Title>A $199 SHIELD Toy would be over priced so a $349 SHIELD Toy is DOA</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368546480846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:48:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Phone contracts are not free especially to a kid lol" Correct again, phone contracts are not free. Impressive dedcution, did you figiure that one out by yourself? Did you ever hear of a Cell Phone Family Plan? I don't want to shock you but KIDS carry cell phones. lol I KID you not, pun intended. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368556972872</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:42:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368557463802-63</Id><Topic><Title>No volume on this pullback...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1368457873014</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:11:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Day low $14.26 then up</Msg><Username>new_day_high</Username><Timestamp>1368557463802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:51:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368557467144-64</Id><Title>Watch for a breakout above 14.60-63</Title><Msg>I only have a minute, but to those that thought the stock would not rally, today, you're about to learn a very valuable but painful lesson. Any move above the 14.60-63 level will likely result in a mad scramble to 15 and possibly a new high, before the week is out. Remember, any close above 14.63 will be a new closing high for the last 52 weeks. As always, we'll know in the fullness of time. Max</Msg><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368557467144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:51:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368558244017-65</Id><Topic><Title>Watch for a breakout above 14.60-63</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368557467144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:51:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>600 DMA at 14.66 is the hard resistance point, see last August stockchartsDOTcom/c-sc/sc?s=NVDA&amp;p=D&amp;yr=1&amp;mn=0&amp;dy=0&amp;i=t93538852384&amp;r=1368558105709</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368558244017</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368558443780-66</Id><Topic><Title>A $199 SHIELD Toy would be over priced so a $349 SHIELD Toy is DOA</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368546480846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:48:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rory Read said (reluctantly, at the last AMD earnings cc) that the gross margin for game console chips as a whole will be lower than AMD's (already low) overall GM. Which implies GROUND ZERO.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368558443780</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:07:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368559218134-67</Id><Topic><Title>Watch for a breakout above 14.60-63</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368557467144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:51:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pity they weren't watching when you pulled off your breakout. Do they know that you ended up on a message ranting about a "mad scramble"? lol The low volume says you are mistaken. UNCH from Fri does not a breakout make. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368559218134</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:20:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368559338264-68</Id><Topic><Title>AMD up 78% YTD, 35 M shares Traded Today, No Buyback Needed.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368550781860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As you point out, the AMD stock options you got as an employee at the end of the year are still underwater by nearly a third. Is that why you are disgruntled enough to troll the NVDA message board? Does that help?</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1368559338264</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:22:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368559480288-69</Id><Topic><Title>A $199 SHIELD Toy would be over priced so a $349 SHIELD Toy is DOA</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368546480846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:48:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"that the gross margin for game console chips as a whole will be lower" If he said it then Cut and Paste it up "reluctantly" then since you don't speak for the AMD CEO right. Have at it.</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368559480288</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:24:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368559795797-70</Id><Topic><Title>AMD up 78% YTD, 35 M shares Traded Today, No Buyback Needed.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368550781860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is just dying for negative attention. And the higher NVDA goes the more intense the pain, the agony and the craving for poisonous retort. Some folks just can't get enough. And to make matters worse he is pinning his hopes on AMD's strong revival.Oh well, we all have our cross to bear.</Msg><Username>jtjgmtbt</Username><Timestamp>1368559795797</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:29:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368559810341-71</Id><Topic><Title>AMD up 78% YTD, 35 M shares Traded Today, No Buyback Needed.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368550781860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"As you point out, the AMD stock options you got as an employee at the end of the year are still underwater" Do you like making up BS? Because you don't actually know anything do you? You don't know anything about options or employment or who bought what when do you? Here is something that is NOT made up BS, Nvidia is lower as I type than it closed of Friday. No BS imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368559810341</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:30:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368559945505-72</Id><Title>NVIDIA and its GRID partners will be at Citrix Synergy 2913, held on May 21-23 at Anaheim, CA</Title><Msg>A most luminary list of partners you can assemble.... IBM, Microsoft, Citrix, Dell, HP, Cisco nvidiaDOTcom/object/citrix-synergy-2013.html</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368559945505</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:32:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368560536051-73</Id><Topic><Title>"Google To Announce Next Nexus 7 Tomorrow"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368555659248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:20:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who will be here on Wed for Google's GOOD NEWS? Will I find you Nvidia fans here bright eyed and bushy tailed in the AM to cheer the Next Nexus 7 that you claim Tegra is still in despite ALL the rags reporting otherwise? lmao ONLY if Nvidia can make it back to Friday's close right? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368560536051</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:42:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368560637495-74</Id><Topic><Title>No volume on this pullback...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1368457873014</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:11:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>giving back early gains, while the dow, s&amp;p and Nasdaq head higher. don't hold your breath, nvda ain't going to rocket anytime soon.</Msg><Username>jiekemoff</Username><Timestamp>1368560637495</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:43:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368560677853-75</Id><Topic><Title>Watch for a breakout above 14.60-63</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368557467144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:51:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It should soon go to where it supposed to be. What different from last August is when mainly stimulated by Tegra 3. What now are GRiD, Shield and Accerated Share Repurchase of $750M. Not likely this stock could be suppressed any longer.</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1368560677853</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:44:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368560742678-76</Id><Topic><Title>Watch for a breakout above 14.60-63</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368557467144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:51:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It should soon go to where it supposed to be. What different from last August is when mainly stimulated by Tegra 3. What now are GRiD, Shield and Accerated Share Repurchase of $750M. Not likely this stock could be suppressed any longer.</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1368560742678</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:45:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368560864336-77</Id><Topic><Title>Me Thinks a $199 Next Nexus 7 with a Beefier SoC will out sell a $349 SHIELD Toy?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368556590155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:36:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey you Nvidia fans are OLD Nexus 7 tablet experts right? Can you play Android games on the $199 Nexus 7 tablet shipping now that are the same games you could play on a $349 SHIELD Toy shipping whenever? lol Say what? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368560864336</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:47:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368561379710-78</Id><Topic><Title>Watch for a breakout above 14.60-63</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368557467144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:51:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to Google Finance, NVDA closed above 14.63 five times back in August 2012. How are you getting 14.63?</Msg><Username>torchie4269</Username><Timestamp>1368561379710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368561398070-79</Id><Topic><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The cloud computing will utilize Gaikai streaming technology, creating no need for discs or downloads." Since Gaikai was working with Nvidia before Sony bought them, they most likely will be using Nvidia's GRID.</Msg><Username>fairbanksmorse1</Username><Timestamp>1368561398070</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:56:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368561498113-80</Id><Title>"Nvidia's Shield Is an Ambitious Mistake"</Title><Msg>"Nvidia's Shield Is an Ambitious Mistake" "Nvidia has finally priced its Project Shield gaming device, and it's not pretty. If you want this new game system/controller/accessory, you'll need to shell out $350 for a pre-order, which is more than any other game system currently on the market. That's the first mistake Nvidia is making with the Shield, which wouldn't be so much of a problem if Nvidia was also releasing a compelling ecosystem for the device. But instead - and here's mistake No. 2 - the Shield is getting a mish-mash of two separate ecosystems, one that isn't completely functional on the device and another that isn't impressive in size. I don't want to predict doom for the Nvidia Shield, but I don't see how it can survive as a feasible product in its current state" source: pcmag</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368561498113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:58:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368562149440-81</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is struggling to get back to where it closed on Fri while AMD moves ahead?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368551336205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia is STLL struggling to get back to Friday's close while AMD moved UP again today well past itss Friday close. And I know its starting to sink in Nvidia fans no matter how much you pretend NOT to notice. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368562149440</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368562214726-82</Id><Topic><Title>"Nvidia's Shield Is an Ambitious Mistake"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368561498113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:58:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The Nvidia Shield should have stayed a project, an experiment for the company to develop features and ideas it could pitch for future products. On its own, it's too expensive and doesn't offer enough gaming bang for the buck. Maybe an Nvidia Shield Gamepad compatible with any Tegra-based Android device (like the Editors' Choice Moga Pro Controller ) for a fraction of the price of the Shield itself, and offering the PC streaming app separately to any device that could handle it. On its own, the Nvidia Shield is a product nobody really asked for. " source: pcmag</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368562214726</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:10:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368562632394-83</Id><Topic><Title>AMD up 78% YTD, 35 M shares Traded Today, No Buyback Needed.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368550781860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>52 Millions AMD shares traded today, ending the day UP another 2% What did Nvidia do? 11 Million shares, UP 1% and still couldn't hold onto all of Fri gains? Now say it ain't so Nvidia fans. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368562632394</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:17:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368563375364-84</Id><Topic><Title>AMD up 78% YTD, 35 M shares Traded Today, No Buyback Needed.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368550781860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are the one who keeps pointing out that AMD is lower than it was a year ago. "8-month high" was, I believe your phrase. If you put your money in AMD a year ago, you are down about 40%. For NVDA, you are up about 5%. Hopefully not too much of your AMD compensation package is in stock or options. Hopefully you're not violating AMD HR policy too badly by monopolizing the NVDA message board during work hours. Underwater options are better than no job at all.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1368563375364</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:29:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368563952046-85</Id><Title>Titan unable to keep up with demand</Title><Msg>@ $1000 a piece. If you knew how many were sold you might discern how many shield would be sold in first wave. Is it still going to be "Shield"?</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1368563952046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:39:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368564171974-86</Id><Topic><Title>AMD up 78% YTD, 35 M shares Traded Today, No Buyback Needed.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368550781860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'"8-month high" was, I believe your phrase" No, That was not my post. Can you read? Are you goung to make up BS all day? Everyone on this board knows you are making up BS about who owns what, who bought what and when and on and on with made up BS. Its your BS you're playing in, so carryon sport. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368564171974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:42:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368564478088-87</Id><Topic><Title>"Nvidia's Shield Is an Ambitious Mistake"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368561498113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:58:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't understand who they think will buy this. And the name is not cool.</Msg><Username>skeeter_bug_</Username><Timestamp>1368564478088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:47:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368564604318-88</Id><Topic><Title>No volume on this pullback...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1368457873014</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:11:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No Volume period. Who cares about Nvidia away from this message board is the question to want to run up he volume. OVER 52 Millions shares traded today in the other GPU outfit though. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368564604318</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:50:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368564784558-89</Id><Topic><Title>"Nvidia's Shield Is an Ambitious Mistake"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368561498113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:58:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I don't understand who they think will buy this. And the name is not cool." SHIELD does sound like a $349 condom doesn't it? lol imho of course</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368564784558</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:53:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368565502350-90</Id><Title>Couldn't Nvidia come up with somthing that doesn't sound like a $349 condom?</Title><Msg>What were they thinking? Or were they even thinking? A Pocket SHIELD Toy for $349, really? I call SHIELD the dumbest idea Nvidia has ever allowed to leave the headquarters building and roam the streets amongst us. Who knows what DUMBNESS never made it out of that HQ "think" tank. lol SHIELD makes the Fermi fiasco look like a small mis-step. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368565502350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:05:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368567212756-91</Id><Topic><Title>AMD up 78% YTD, 35 M shares Traded Today, No Buyback Needed.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368550781860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Everyone on this board knows you are making up BS about who owns what, who bought what and when and on and on with made up BS." Everyone knows that? No, you are probably the only one with so much time on your unproductive hands to keep track of strangers' portfolios. I get that you are proud of how AMD has crawled back from sub-$2 to now being slightly over half where it was a year ago, but it is funny how you keep pointing that out as if everyone ought to be jealous. Well, I guess being down 40% TTM is better than being down 70%.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1368567212756</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:33:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368567613805-92</Id><Topic><Title>AMD up 78% YTD, 35 M shares Traded Today, No Buyback Needed.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368550781860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD has been the lovable technology underdog for so long. They have a strong position in some regards now, but their foray into ARM smacks of a me-too desperation move.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1368567613805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:40:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368567781619-93</Id><Topic><Title>Titan unable to keep up with demand</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1368563952046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you explain how they are connected in detail. because a direct correlation between the sales of titan and shield will be quite a bit different in my opinion. may still sell out, but shield is targeted to specific kinds of gamers. titan is far more versatile and may be used by anyone that needs the processing power. Movies, Game making, and other high powered use like super computers likely make up most of the sales.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1368567781619</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:43:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368568528875-94</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are Toast...ASR with GS just announced.</Title><Username>kvimax1</Username><Timestamp>1368533560578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:12:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Margin hell is developing next........at NVDA GPU cash cow milk drying phase is in play next CAN NVDA afford to pay out 5% DIV yield? If not this stock is stuck in the mud despite buy backs Intel still has Higher DIVIDEND yield than NVDA</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1368568528875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368570099143-95</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA and its GRID partners will be at Citrix Synergy 2913, held on May 21-23 at Anaheim, CA</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368559945505</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:32:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think you meant 2013 instead of 2913 . . I don't think I could wait 900 yrs for this . . Sorry, couldn't resist :).</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1368570099143</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 18:21:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368570954243-96</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA and its GRID partners will be at Citrix Synergy 2913, held on May 21-23 at Anaheim, CA</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368559945505</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:32:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whatever turns you on....</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368570954243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 18:35:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368571373820-97</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA and its GRID partners will be at Citrix Synergy 2913, held on May 21-23 at Anaheim, CA</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368559945505</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:32:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really ibexx? Just trying to lighten things up when I have a moment on here . .</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1368571373820</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 18:42:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368572060107-98</Id><Topic><Title>Ps4 and Xbox 720 can play games anywhere on most mobile devices</Title><Username>cueless_q129</Username><Timestamp>1368543145074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't see an integrated screen on a ps4 nor on the xbox. I think they cost more too. Can you play android AND pc games on them? A decent tablet costs more than the shield and no physical joypad/joystick/buttons there. Do you understand that at all?</Msg><Username>daysofshred30000000000</Username><Timestamp>1368572060107</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 18:54:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368574128059-99</Id><Topic><Title>Titan unable to keep up with demand</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1368563952046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah i don't think there is any correlation either. Just because i buy a Titan to make a super gaming computer or for the processing power doesn't mean i want a shield to stream or game from. In fact it might be the opposite. Personally i NEVER game on mobile devices. I'm one of those dudes who pimps out his PC, so i would go for a titan over a shield, but that is just my style.</Msg><Username>manski14</Username><Timestamp>1368574128059</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368574218951-100</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA and its GRID partners will be at Citrix Synergy 2913, held on May 21-23 at Anaheim, CA</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368559945505</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:32:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It feels like its been 900 years waiting for this stock to turn haha</Msg><Username>manski14</Username><Timestamp>1368574218951</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:30:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368574292495-101</Id><Topic><Title>AMD up 78% YTD, 35 M shares Traded Today, No Buyback Needed.</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368550781860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares about what you own? I am talking about YOU telling me what I own, how I came to own it, what I paid and when I bought it is made up BS. Are you that dense? Have someone read your own BS back to you and stop making a fool of yourself making up BS in public. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368574292495</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:31:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368574441671-102</Id><Topic><Title>"Google To Announce Next Nexus 7 Tomorrow"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368555659248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:20:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will there be WHIINING or CHEERING for the Next Nexus here on Wed? lol</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368574441671</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:34:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368574593209-103</Id><Topic><Title>Couldn't Nvidia come up with somthing that doesn't sound like a $349 condom?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368565502350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone know if the SHIELD Toy is made with rubber? Rubber knobs or a rubber touch pad might explain that name, hmm? lmao imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368574593209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368575384565-104</Id><Title>Its too funny watching Nvidia fans pretend that they DON'T WISH they sold at $26</Title><Msg>But when it was $26 all the talk was about $30 or more and now its nothing but excuses. I know $14 is just as good as $26 but without as many crooked numbers, thats all? OR We holding for $100 that Mr Cut and Plastered promised us before 2014, right? OR SHIELD Toy to the rescue and day now right? What Tegra 50.5% drop in sales? What PlayStation job? What Nexus job? Who guided lower when? lol Hey, how many here bragged about buying OVER $16 on this very message board? And remember now before you fib this message has a long memory. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368575384565</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368575998011-105</Id><Topic><Title>Its too funny watching Nvidia fans pretend that they DON'T WISH they sold at $26</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368575384565</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now Nvidia fans and Nvidia are PRETENDING that SHIELD is a challenge to real Game Consoles when the free press thinks Nvidia has lost its collective mind. PCMag says: " If you want this new game system/controller/accessory, you'll need to shell out $350 for a pre-order, which is more than any other game system currently on the market" That tells me THEY DON'T WANT TO SELL IT because its priced like a expensive joke. IMHO</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1368575998011</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368577030629-106</Id><Topic><Title>Titan unable to keep up with demand</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1368563952046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't know, but I believe rocks is saying Shield and Titan share some overlap in their market demographics: enthusiast, high perf user and early adapters. You have to admit some percentage of Titan owners will also be Shield owners at some point, no question. I don't agree Titan sells to the broad group of users you describe. To really get the value out of titan you need a high end PC and monitor, and some specific, recently released and upcoming entertainment titles. People doing content creation (movies and games) are more likely to be on Quadro than GeForce. cheers</Msg><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1368577030629</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:17:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368577782890-107</Id><Topic><Title>NVIIDA Shield shipping in June, ahead of all refresh game consoles. Final specs</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368546757644</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:52:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure they arrived at the price based on how well it was received at shows, and based on market research. Also, it;s just about a third of the cost of a Titan card. Any positive publicity coming from the upcoming E3 show in mid June will give the share price a nice little boost.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1368577782890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:29:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368579731867-108</Id><Topic><Title>Titan unable to keep up with demand</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1368563952046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not only Titan and Shield will share common ownership, I also think that Shield will even stimulate Titan's (and other high-end GTX cards) sales.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368579731867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 21:02:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368579849759-109</Id><Topic><Title>Titan unable to keep up with demand</Title><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1368563952046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for pointing that out on quadro. I was thinking something I said sounded like it may be a little off. I did a quick search and saw supercomputers. I had to wrap up quick so just posted what i had written so far. I was thinking there would be one big total number lacking any details but if it was more detailed then ya that percentage may allow an educated guess. Sales of shield are most likely needed as a baseline before you'd really start getting any real idea of whats going to play out. Kind of the problem Nvidia recently. so many new products and no baseline for them. Hard to guess how they will sell when none have sold before.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1368579849759</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 21:04:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368580772211-110</Id><Title>ZDNet: Why I am not writing off NVIDIA Shield</Title><Msg>SOURCE: zdnetDOTcom/why-im-not-writing-off-nvidias-shield-7000015375/ " This year Nintendo expects to sell 18 million 3DS consoles and Sony hopes to sell 5 million handheld consoles (PS Vita and PSP combined). The Android-based Shield offers some compelling advantages over these, and if only a fraction of customers opt for it, it will succeed as a showcase for Tegra 4 and TegraZone games."" Well said.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368580772211</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 21:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368584485575-111</Id><Title>Short short short!</Title><Msg>Love to add fuel to the fire. Profit from it one way or another. If anyone is suicidal, s/he is at his own risk.</Msg><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1368584485575</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 22:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368587280401-112</Id><Topic><Title>ZDNet: Why I am not writing off NVIDIA Shield</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1368580772211</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 21:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed. Open standards (like android ;) are huge.</Msg><Username>norcalnative_2</Username><Timestamp>1368587280401</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:08:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>