<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-01"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359695719572-1</Id><Title>High-risk Broadcom UPnP stack remote root vulnerability - may be the reason for today's sell-off?</Title><Msg>Recently, DefenseCode researchers have uncovered a remote root access vulnerability in the default installation of Linksys routers. Further research revealed that the vulnerability is even more dangerous, since the same vulnerable firmware component is also used by numerous other router manufacturers. The vulnerability is located within the wanipc and wanppp modules of the Broadcom UPnP stack, which is used by manufacturers that deliver routers based on the Broadcom chipset. A variety of routers have their UPnP interface available over the WAN interface, so the vulnerability can also be exploited over the Internet. It seems that, at the moment, the only popular UPnP implementation not hit by the remote preauth security vulnerability is MiniUPnP. The remote preauth format string vulnerability in the Broadcom UPnP stack can be exploited to write arbitrary values to an arbitrary memory address, and also to remotely read router memory. When exploited, it allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code under the root account. net-securityDOTorg/secworld.php?id=14335 BAD, BAD NEWS whosunw! Couldn't even wished anything worse than this on you!</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359695719572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 00:15:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359696230292-2</Id><Title>Apple shrinks BRCM sales view, Samsung looms...</Title><Msg>Apple (AAPL)-related woes may be largely to blame for Broadcom's (BRCM) lower-than-expected Q1 revenue outlook, analysts say, but the chipmaker could see more upside from Apple's smartphone rival, Samsung. Shares in Broadcom were little changed in early trading Wednesday. The chipmaker's Q4 profit of 45 cents per share beat views. It announced a 10% hike in its annual dividend to 11 cents per share. Broadcom said it expects Q1 revenue of $1.9 billion, missing consensus estimates by 5%. Analysts said the guidance was tied to Apple as well as lower spending by phone companies on their networks. But Broadcom supplies wireless chips to Samsung as well as Apple and isn't as dependent on Apple's fortunes in the smartphone market as some other chipmakers, like Cirrus Logic (CRUS), analysts say. "With weakness at Apple now apparent and infrastructure weakness widespread, we suspect the shock value has been minimized," said Citigroup analyst Glen Yeung in a research note. "While the battle between Apple and Samsung will wage on, we continue to view (chip) suppliers as a good way to avoid choosing the winner. When considering Broadcom's opportunities in related technologies, we view BRCM as a good way to gain exposure to major communications trends." Jefferies analyst Mark Lipacis was upbeat in a report published Wednesday. "We think the company is conservative and believe its new 3G product cycle at Samsung and 5th-gen WiFi products for handsets and routers give it better visibility than most," wrote Lipacis. "We've also argued that positive investor sentiment will shift from Apple to Samsung due to its product cycle." Nomura analyst Romit Shah said: "We believe Broadcom is one of the few names in semis that is not pricing in a stronger economic recovery. The company has potentially set a low bar by refusing to call a bottom. "While we are aware of the weakness at Apple, we expected Samsung and (Wi-Fi) to provide a bigger offset this quarter," Shah added. SOURCE: Investor Business Daily ________ I was saying EXACTLY the same thing on the day BRCM reported its earnings and guidance, but was attacked by a hysterical poster on this board. I guess she needs to hear it from an 'authoritative" source - well, here it is.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359696230292</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 00:23:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359696327606-3</Id><Topic><Title>Jews, they create problems, then drag you into them.</Title><Username>dean_martin_17</Username><Timestamp>1359696104732</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 00:21:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cigar or buffy, I just reported you for abuse.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359696327606</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 00:25:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359697803177-4</Id><Topic><Title>Responding to Getanid's post</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359685224916</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 21:20:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You don't seem to get the point. " Back at you... !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359697803177</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 00:50:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359706945650-5</Id><Title>Nvidia struggles to convince tablet vendors about Tegra 4</Title><Msg>Bad news: digitimesDOTcom/news/a20130201PD209.html</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1359706945650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 03:22:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359712039446-6</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia struggles to convince tablet vendors about Tegra 4</Title><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1359706945650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 03:22:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sony may be ending its partnership with nvda</Msg><Username>xxu0901</Username><Timestamp>1359712039446</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 04:47:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359718686710-7</Id><Title>Toshiba first to adpot Nvidia's Tegra 4 platform, DigiTimes says</Title><Msg>Yes.......</Msg><Username>luizimonti</Username><Timestamp>1359718686710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 06:38:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359721245041-8</Id><Topic><Title>Responding to Getanid's post</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359685224916</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 21:20:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>again, you haven't a clue. you are off on you own in left field while the man is telling you exactly what nvda is going to do with the product. And it is nothing like what you are thinking about.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359721245041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:20:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359721378103-9</Id><Topic><Title>High-risk Broadcom UPnP stack remote root vulnerability - may be the reason for today's sell-off?</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359695719572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 00:15:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>roflol, tegra crashes and burns with no way out and 'nvda longs' worry about.....</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359721378103</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:22:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359721668482-10</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba first to adpot Nvidia's Tegra 4 platform, DigiTimes says</Title><Username>luizimonti</Username><Timestamp>1359718686710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 06:38:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfortunately, the article also suggests that Toshiba might be the last adopter ...</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1359721668482</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:27:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359723269931-11</Id><Title>Why Is Nvidia Obviously Pushing Tegra for Tablets over Phones</Title><Msg>Nvidia is pushing Tegra into tablets for 5 reasons: 1) Average Selling Price of Tegra is significantly higher in Tablets compared to phones. 2) Nvidia comes from a PC background. Easier to play in a playground your familiar with and well respected in. Yougher slog in phones. 3) 100's of potential Tablet vendor customers vs. 10's of phone vendor customers. No one customer can burn them like Samsung did in 2011. 4) PC Systems engineering knowledge is much more valuable when working with Tablets. 5) Gaming - Link to discrete Nvidia GPUs through Tegra 4 chip. Project shield is a demonstration of what is possible now and later with Nvidia Grid. Remember Nvidia's management is a bunch of middle aged gamers who know where their salaries come from.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359723269931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:54:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359723912403-12</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba first to adpot Nvidia's Tegra 4 platform, DigiTimes says</Title><Username>luizimonti</Username><Timestamp>1359718686710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 06:38:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would seem improbable. They are also likely to be in the next NEXUS tablets.</Msg><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1359723912403</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:05:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359725445375-13</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba first to adpot Nvidia's Tegra 4 platform, DigiTimes says</Title><Username>luizimonti</Username><Timestamp>1359718686710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 06:38:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Besides according to Nvidia they already have more Tegra 4 design for tablets than Tegra 3.</Msg><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1359725445375</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:30:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359725756322-14</Id><Title>Digitimes article is wrong</Title><Msg>Considering that we saw a Vizio Tegra 4 tablet at CES, and further considering that Nvidia's PR materials have stated that T4 already has more design wins than T3, I would think that the Digitimes hit piece was, well, bogus.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359725756322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:35:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359726790501-15</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes article is wrong</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359725756322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deinitely a hit job. Good call</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1359726790501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:53:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359727148564-16</Id><Title>Check Out Dell - Jensen Take us Private!</Title><Msg>Who ever would have thought Dell would go up 50% in a month!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359727148564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:59:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359727434642-17</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA is definitely not looking excellent. Understand why.</Title><Username>mauro.lemmen</Username><Timestamp>1359723045473</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:50:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it time to load up now?</Msg><Username>merrill.jamaal</Username><Timestamp>1359727434642</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:03:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359727790320-18</Id><Topic><Title>What Project Shield Really Is</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359670103346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 17:08:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The moat is very wide when you have to build a 3 to 4 million transistor device!" Agree, but 3 to 4 million transistor GPUs were more than a decade ago, GK110 is said to have 7.3 BILLION transistors. I think NV3 (1997) was the last one in the 3 to 4 million range. By 1999 they were more like 15-16 million transistors (NV5).</Msg><Username>really_chris</Username><Timestamp>1359727790320</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:09:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359728124299-19</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes article is wrong</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359725756322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm inclined to believe Digitimes. They use fewer disclaimers than Jen does. "Before we begin, I'd like to remind you that today's call is being webcast live on NVIDIA's Investor Relations website and is also being recorded. A replay of the conference call will be available via telephone until we decide to take it down, and the webcast will be available for replay until our conference call to discuss our financial results for our fourth quarter of fiscal 2013. The content of today's conference call is NVIDIA's property and cannot be reproduced or transcribed without our prior written consent. During the course of this call, we may make forward-looking statements based on current expectations. These forward-looking statements are subject to a number of significant risks and uncertainties, and our actual results may differ materially. For a discussion of factors that could affect our future financial results and business, please refer to the disclosure in today's earnings release, our Form 10-Q for the fiscal quarter, and the reports we may file from time to time on Form 8-K filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission. All our statements are made as of TODAY, based on information available to us as of TODAY and, except as required by law, we assume no obligation to update any such statements." Digitimes has a Reputation to uphold and protect. Jen's words have a protected lifespan of an Egg McMuffin®</Msg><Username>todays.best</Username><Timestamp>1359728124299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:15:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359728643778-20</Id><Title>Nvida to dominate mobile using same strategy as applied in GPU business model</Title><Msg>I'm very encouraged by the rumors that NVDA will be building reference smartphones and tablets. IMO, mobile is about to transiton from an era of brand differentiated devices (ala Apple) to a proliferation of private labeled devices that will disrupt the domination by Samsung, Apple A sure sign is the fall off of Apple brand enthusiasm over the past year. The Apple brand accounted a significant component of the percieved value by consumers. But this year Samsung has proven the Apple armor is not durable and Apple's brand was penetrated by feature superiority and increased functional value. Proving that consumers buying motivations can change very fast. Initially Nvidia has found itself in an less than optimal position by having to compete for SOC business with QCOM (and other chip companies) on the basis of a single chip as opposed to a system. The entry of the Shield device (and hopefully other mobile devices soon ) exposes a strategy designed to leverage their core competency which is to produce completely functional reference designs and use a bevy of manufacturers, just as they do now in the GPU space to penetrate markets on behlaf or Nvidia for example, there are dozens of companies across the globe that sell almost identical Nvdiia GPUs cards but with slight differences ( packaging, clock rates, cooling etc.) - but a 690 GTX is a 690 GTX no matter which company you buy it from . EVGA may have a better warranty, or is slighlty more overclocked, but beyond that, not much difference. Why not enable the same eco system in mobile devices? The seemingly endless growth of mobile is powered by both consumer adoption rates and a very fast (2 year replacement) ) device refresh cycle and in a market in which brand loyalty gives way to price , feature and function. Nvidia is well suited to exploit this market transition and to focus on China and India where price sensitity is greatet is brilliant Nvidia was never a graphics chip company - it was a graphics card company Reference designs of GPU Cards - not Graphic chips Reference designs mobile devices - not Mobile SOCs Let Samsung and Apple battle for Brand Nvidia will become the mobile device " arms dealer" to a bevy of regional manufacturers that will steal market share from - riding on Nvidia reference designs all the way to the bank gee, why not a Walmart phone?</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1359728643778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:24:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359728716321-21</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes article is wrong</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359725756322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you were Gateway, Acer etc. etc., would you do another Android tablet? don't think it's got anything to do with the processor, just the reality of the tablet market. Either you do a</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359728716321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:25:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359728849137-22</Id><Topic><Title>Why Is Nvidia Obviously Pushing Tegra for Tablets over Phones</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359723269931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:54:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>simple, NO CHEAP RADIO</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359728849137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:27:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359729998095-23</Id><Topic><Title>Why Is Nvidia Obviously Pushing Tegra for Tablets over Phones</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359723269931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:54:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't want one...This is PC play.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359729998095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:46:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359730428859-24</Id><Topic><Title>Why Is Nvidia Obviously Pushing Tegra for Tablets over Phones</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359723269931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:54:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With nvidia's Tegra being relegated to those low volume tablets, -- 'cause nvidia has no decent radio to talk to the cellphone towers with -- what will nvidia do when all the tablets have smartphones in them too? You know. Like Dr. Paul Jacob's wife has. A "Pad-Phone". Jen's Tegra folly will really be Ka-put.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1359730428859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:53:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359730782953-25</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation UPDATED CHARTS!</Title><Username>meulyapril</Username><Timestamp>1359559169108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 10:19:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you shared this to us.</Msg><Username>otiositiesgeraldine</Username><Timestamp>1359730782953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:59:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359730881332-26</Id><Topic><Title>Nvida to dominate mobile using same strategy as applied in GPU business model</Title><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1359728643778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:24:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent post!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359730881332</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:01:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359731337512-27</Id><Topic><Title>Why Is Nvidia Obviously Pushing Tegra for Tablets over Phones</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359723269931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:54:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Best? The other half of the question which alluded me before is, Since Apple gets a carrier subsidy payment of $450 for each Genuine Apple iPhone or Genuine Apple iPad activated -- if they Combine the two into one "Pad-Phone" device, Apple should receive a carrier subsidy of $900 for that, right? It's two devices in one -- Tablet + Smartphone -- so two payments. I thought so.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1359731337512</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:08:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359732044763-28</Id><Topic><Title>Why Is Nvidia Obviously Pushing Tegra for Tablets over Phones</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359723269931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:54:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jeepers Best, If Apple will get a $900 carrier subsidy payment for their 2-in-1 Genuine Apple iPad + iPhone -- and the parts aren't all that different -- Apple could Slash the price of their 2-in-1 Genuine Apple iPad + iPhone to BELOW the price of either device alone -- and still make an obscene iProfit on it. Could be the beginning-of-the-end for those no-talkie Tegra tablets.</Msg><Username>jeepers.best</Username><Timestamp>1359732044763</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:20:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359732674988-29</Id><Topic><Title>Responding to Getanid's post</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359685224916</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 21:20:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>weak... your strength is faltering due to a steady diet crow... !!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359732674988</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:31:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359735387700-30</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba first to adpot Nvidia's Tegra 4 platform, DigiTimes says</Title><Username>luizimonti</Username><Timestamp>1359718686710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 06:38:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Toshiba first to adopt Tegra 4, say Taiwan makers Monica Chen, Taipei; Joseph Tsai, DIGITIMES [Friday 1 February 2013] Toshiba, among tablet and smartphone vendors, is so far the Only one to adopt Nvidia's Tegra 4 platform for tablets to be launched in June 2013, implying that Tegra 4 is Struggling to compete with quad-core platforms developed by Qualcomm, MediaTek and China-based IC design houses, according to Taiwan-based supply chain makers. Asustek Computer and Acer, which have been aggressive about the tablet market, have not yet decided whether to place orders for Tegra 4 as their focuses have already turned from 10-inch and above tablets to the 7-inch entry-level segment. As for Asustek's smartphone product line, the company's close partnership with Qualcomm is likely to prompt the two firms to continue smartphone cooperation in the future, leaving Tegra 4 to become just a Backup solution, the sources noted. To regain its momentum, Nvidia is considering Reducing the Tegra 3's price to attract entry-level orders from brand vendors; however, the sources pointed out that even with a cut, Tegra 3's price is still not likely to become competitive against solutions from MediaTek and China-based IC design houses in terms of price." Tegra #4 : She's lookin' like a scratch, boys.</Msg><Username>itsascratch</Username><Timestamp>1359735387700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:16:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359736363719-31</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba first to adpot Nvidia's Tegra 4 platform, DigiTimes says</Title><Username>luizimonti</Username><Timestamp>1359718686710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 06:38:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Master? With almost zero orders for the non-integrated LTE Tegra #4, will Jen's Tegra chip folly be folding? Like a cheap, frozen lawn chair.</Msg><Username>best.clone185</Username><Timestamp>1359736363719</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:32:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359737867937-32</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia struggles to convince tablet vendors about Tegra 4</Title><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1359706945650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 03:22:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Toshiba, among tablet and smartphone vendors, is so far the only one to adopt Nvidia's Tegra 4 platform for tablets to be launched in June 2013, implying that Tegra 4 is struggling to compete with quad-core platforms developed by Qualcomm, MediaTek and China-based IC design houses, according to Taiwan-based supply chain makers. Asustek Computer and Acer, which have been aggressive about the tablet market, have not yet decided whether to place orders for Tegra 4 as their focuses have already turned from 10-inch and above tablets to the 7-inch entry-level segment. As for Asustek's smartphone product line, the company's close partnership with Qualcomm is likely to prompt the two firms to continue smartphone cooperation in the future, leaving Tegra 4 to become just a backup solution, the sources noted. To regain its momentum, Nvidia is considering reducing the Tegra 3's price to attract entry-level orders from brand vendors; however, the sources pointed out that even with a cut, Tegra 3's price is still not likely to become competitive against solutions from MediaTek and China-based IC design houses in terms of price." digitimesDOTcom/news/a20130201PD209.html</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359737867937</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:57:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359738113361-33</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba first to adpot Nvidia's Tegra 4 platform, DigiTimes says</Title><Username>luizimonti</Username><Timestamp>1359718686710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 06:38:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Toshiba, among tablet and smartphone vendors, is so far the Only one to adopt Nvidia's Tegra 4 platform for tablets to be launched in June 2013, implying that Tegra 4 is Struggling to compete with quad-core platforms developed by Qualcomm, MediaTek and China-based IC design houses, according to Taiwan-based supply chain makers." lol</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359738113361</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:01:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359738956518-34</Id><Topic><Title>Responding to Getanid's post</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359685224916</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 21:20:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Shortly after Japan-based Sony announced a 20 February event to talk the future of the Playstation, a new report claims a next-generation console will indeed be announced by Sony executives. The Wall Street Journal reports, citing "sources", Sony will unveil the next-generation console and ship it by Christmas 2013. Sony is said to have scheduled the early event to beat Microsoft to its introduction of the Xbox 720. This tactic has been previously rumoured. In its event teaser, Sony was light on details as to what we might see at the event. Given the Wall Street Journal's reputation and other rumours, their report seems very likely. After the February announcement, several reports have noted that Sony will use the E3 trade show to talk games and keep promoting the console up until Christmas where a bevy of sales are expected. The next-generation PlayStation, dubbed the Orbis, is said to feature a AMD x86 quad-core processor at 3.2GHz, 2GB of RAM, Blu-Ray, 1080p output, and 320GB HDD. It is said to be 10x more powerful than the PS3 currently available on the market. Pocket-lint will be keeping you updated on the latest." PS4, Xbox and WII is what has Nvidia so upset. No console biz. lol SHIELD is JUNK which is why the market took Nvidia down on the very day they announced JUNK at CES. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359738956518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:15:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359739065385-35</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba first to adpot Nvidia's Tegra 4 platform, DigiTimes says</Title><Username>luizimonti</Username><Timestamp>1359718686710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 06:38:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, name some! Assuming there have been more than 30 devices using Tegra 3, you should be able to name at least 31 using Tegra 4. So ...? Where are they? For me, Barcelona will be the judge. If Toshiba and that Vizio thing are the only one vendors going with Tegra 4, them I'm out.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1359739065385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:17:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359739136738-36</Id><Title>Diditimes says Only One win for tegra 4. Is that right?</Title><Msg>Only one? Is Digitimes right? How will Nvidia break even with Only one? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359739136738</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:18:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359739228936-37</Id><Topic><Title>"Sony to announce PS4 at February event, launch it later this year"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359691271756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 23:01:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any reason Sony didn't go with Tegra 4? Anyone here have a clue? lol</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359739228936</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:20:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359739773522-38</Id><Title>Why no game console business for Tegra 4 if its so good at playing games?</Title><Msg>Anyone here have a clue why Sony, MS and Nitendo have NOT announced a Tegra 4 console? Didgitimes says one one win for Tegra 4. What seems to be the problem Nvidia fans? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359739773522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:29:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359739920244-39</Id><Title>Will Nvidia Incerease The Dividend?</Title><Msg>Must be why all the usual shorties are here today. I guess they just don't want to pay. Will AMD survive? It's getting kinda close</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359739920244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:32:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359740025810-40</Id><Topic><Title>Project SHIELD is another example of Nvidia playing games with YOUR money</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359656722583</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 13:25:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia was $13.15 before CES. How much did project SHIELD add to Nvidia's stock price when it was announced at CES? Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359740025810</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:33:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359740155809-41</Id><Topic><Title>Will Nvidia Incerease The Dividend?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359739920244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:32:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably not...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359740155809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:35:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359740371778-42</Id><Topic><Title>Will Nvidia Incerease The Dividend?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359739920244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:32:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just a touch....nothing attracts the growth and income funds like a small out of sequence dividend bump!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359740371778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:39:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359740526826-43</Id><Topic><Title>Will Nvidia Incerease The Dividend?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359739920244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:32:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe... but that doesn't mean you're gonna get one...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359740526826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:42:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359741016503-44</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA Corporation UPDATED CHARTS!</Title><Username>meulyapril</Username><Timestamp>1359559169108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 10:19:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got names to ignore. What value beside spam?</Msg><Username>nsmadison</Username><Timestamp>1359741016503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:50:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359741038209-45</Id><Topic><Title>Will Nvidia Incerease The Dividend?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359739920244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:32:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Constantly begging for a dividend increase on a message board day after day really shows us just how happy this shareholder is with his purchase, doesn't it? lol If the stock went up from $26 instead of down to $12 would you still be begging for a dividend increase everyday? Enjoy your Nvidia purchase. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359741038209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:50:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359741208470-46</Id><Title>Computational Photography via HDR on Tegra 4</Title><Msg>Always on Computational Photography will become a base requirement on all Smartphones - imagine the camera demo's in the smartphones Kiosks - suddenly your #$%$ phone camera keeps up with the best digital pocket cameras who has ? Not QCOM, Not Apple, nto Samsung</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1359741208470</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:53:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359741312994-47</Id><Title>Nvidia struggles to convince vendors to adopt Tegra 4</Title><Msg>Consumers will not see a lot of Nvidia Tegra 4-based smartphones and tablets in the later part of 2013, according to reports out of Taiwan. The Tegra 4 features 72 custom Nvidia GeForce GPU cores, which is purported to boast six times more horsepower than its predecessor—the Tegra 3. It also includes ARM’s quad-core Cortex A15 architecture, and 4G LTE voice and data support with the optional Nvidia Icera i500 chipset. Despite the performance increase as well as added functionalities in the Tegra 4, it seems like Santa Clara-based chip maker is struggling to woo tablet and smartphone vendors to adopt its next-gen SoC. According to DigiTimes, Toshiba is the only vendor, thus far, to confirm the launch of Tegra 4-based tablets some time in mid-2013. Major OEMs like Asus and Acer are putting a lot of effort into developing ARM tablets, but they have not confirmed any orders of Tegra 4. Asus has close ties with Qualcomm in the smartphone department, so it’s likely that Asus will continue to use ARM chips from Qualcomm for future smartphones. Rather than forcing the issues with the Tegra 4, Nvidia will try to remain relevant by lowering the price of its Tegra 3 to attract vendors that are developing entry-level devices. However, even with a price cut on the Tegra 3, there are still cheaper solutions coming from MediaTek and other China-based chip makers.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359741312994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:55:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359741685256-48</Id><Title>A Dividend increase can't cover Nvidia dropping from $26 down to $12, can it?</Title><Msg>You Nvidia fans don't expect a $14 dividend on a $12 stock do you? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359741685256</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:01:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359741828604-49</Id><Topic><Title>Computational Photography via HDR on Tegra 4</Title><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1359741208470</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:53:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who knew - The Walmart Phone with Tegra 4 for $199 without a contract outsells Iphone and Samsung combined</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359741828604</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:03:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359741840154-50</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia struggles to convince vendors to adopt Tegra 4</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359741312994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:55:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did you post the same article for the fourth time?</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1359741840154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:04:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359742578942-51</Id><Topic><Title>Will Nvidia Incerease The Dividend?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359739920244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:32:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes....but Jensen has been acting so much out of character recently. Retuning capital to share holders and all. Wonder if Blackrock met with him to discuss the issue?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359742578942</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:16:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359743005446-52</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia struggles to convince vendors to adopt Tegra 4</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359741312994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:55:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not the same article actually (by Monica Chen) but an editted version of it from somewhere else. It also takes out a significant line that says the lack of 'announced' Tegra 4 products 'implies' that it isn't doing well. I think that line which says implies is significant when considering Jen said they were still sampling the chip as they were presenting in Las Vegas. The article also stated that ASUS worked mainly with Qualcomm in smartphones. I didn't even know of any smartphones by ASUS but I have not tracked ASUS product line much beyond their tablets.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1359743005446</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:23:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359743854889-53</Id><Topic><Title>Check Out Dell - Jensen Take us Private!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359727148564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:59:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You go from begging for a dividend to begging for a buyer to take Nvidia off your hands, don't you? Is that what a shareholder who is pleased with his share purchase does? lmao</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359743854889</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:37:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359744054274-54</Id><Title>NVDA notes may be effecting stock performance</Title><Msg>Barclays Sells First Uridashi Notes Tied to Nvidia #$%$&amp;P Gains http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2013-02-01/barclays-sells-first-uridashi-notes-tied-to-nvidia-as-s-p-gains.html?cmpid=yhoo "Barclays’s five-month notes yield 9.02 percent monthly as long as Nvidia shares are at or above 90 percent of the stock’s Jan. 31 closing, while the coupon drops to 0.5 percent if the price falls by more than the 10 percent buffer, according to the prospectus for the product. If the shares gain more than 10 percent, the notes are redeemed at their full value. Should the stock close below 90 percent of its initial value on any day between Feb. 1 and 10 trading days before expiration on June 21, the notes convert into the Nvidia stock at maturity, according to the marketing materials. Nvidia shares closed at $12.26 on Jan. 31, after losing 34 percent of their value through last year since the end of 2009. In the latest earnings release in November, the company reported quarterly profit surpassing analysts’ estimates, helped by sales of chips used in tablet devices. Marina Totsuka, a Tokyo-based spokeswoman for Barclays, declined to comment on the reasons it picked the stock for the notes. "</Msg><Username>nsd870</Username><Timestamp>1359744054274</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:40:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359744203076-55</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes article is wrong</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359725756322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one can be sure but if you read the article it states 'implies' and doesn't state any quote from the companies being cited for not having products with Tegra 4 chips yet. Also, it stated that ASUS uses Qualcomm for their smartphones . . can anyone tell me the smartphones by ASUS out there now? Anyone? I maybe just too focused on the tablets to know.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1359744203076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:43:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359744712761-56</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes article is wrong</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359725756322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"No one can be sure but if you read the article it states 'implies' and doesn't state any quote from the companies being cited for not having products with Tegra 4 chips yet." Can we be sure that you can't buy a tegra 4 phone or tablet yet? Can we be sure that no one has announced an actual ship date for Tegra 4 anything yet? When you can post a link with an actual product for sale with Tegra 4 inside then we can be sure the article is wrong, right? lmao Untl there is a Tegra 4 anything on sale there isn't right? Can we be sure of that? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359744712761</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:51:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359745509772-57</Id><Title>NVDA can hit $20/- end of this year?????</Title><Msg>Onlt serious replies. Thanks</Msg><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1359745509772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:05:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359745781525-58</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA can hit $20/- end of this year?????</Title><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1359745509772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:05:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not likely probaly $15 to $16, but if Nvidia releases enough cash to buy 100M shares in the $12's then very possible. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359745781525</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:09:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359745922455-59</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA can hit $20/- end of this year?????</Title><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1359745509772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:05:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks so much. I wish, I will be happy with $16/-</Msg><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1359745922455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:12:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359746182286-60</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA can hit $20/- end of this year?????</Title><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1359745509772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:05:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>me too. I bought at $11.50</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359746182286</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:16:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359746309564-61</Id><Title>Its becoming clear why Nvidia is building its own Tegra junk</Title><Msg>The news is all over the net, Nvidia can't secure the Tegra 4 design wins that QCOM and others can. White box tablets and a SHIELD toy is Nvidia forced to eat its own cooking. No takers for Tegra 4? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359746309564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:18:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359746515315-62</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes article is wrong</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359725756322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>todays.best Of course you're inclined to believe Digitimes It supports your short imho</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359746515315</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:21:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359746686730-63</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes article is wrong</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359725756322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you never read cc disclosures before? You're quoting boiler plate to sew doubt. Poor form; not your "best" work.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1359746686730</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:24:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359748157299-64</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes article is wrong</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359725756322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does it really matter if Nvidia stays away from phones this year to increase Tegra's margins to the break even point. I sure management is sick of the phone market. These middle aged guys are gamer guys and are reverting back to their tried and true strengths honed in the PC market. Sure they will get a few major phone wins, but mucho tablet wins. I can see it now: Every store in Asia and eastern Europe will have a rack of Nvidia reference tablets selling away. Might even be some phones on the rack. Best prices will be at Newegg where you can get the Project Shield bundled with the $899 Titan GPU card. Only way to track success is through earnings. Wall street analysts just have no way of guaging anything like this other than Jensen what is your guidance please.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359748157299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:49:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359748284907-65</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia struggles to convince vendors to adopt Tegra 4</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359741312994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:55:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Despite the performance increase as well as added functionalities in the Tegra 4, it seems like Santa Clara-based chip maker is struggling to woo tablet and smartphone vendors to adopt its next-gen SoC. According to DigiTimes, Toshiba is the only vendor, thus far," Where are the Tegra 4 design wins to prove otherwise Nvidia fans? Digitimes says ONE. Tegra 4 looks like a dud. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359748284907</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:51:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359748426557-66</Id><Topic><Title>$11.11 on 2/22</Title><Username>arnab_chanda_huang</Username><Timestamp>1359607356262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 23:42:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nasdaq Q up 1.2% and beta for NVDA is 1.75, therefore, price increase should be 2.1% and $12.52 per share today for NVDA. However it is not. This is a hint. Mark it on your calendar.</Msg><Username>arnab_chanda_huang</Username><Timestamp>1359748426557</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:53:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359750742234-67</Id><Title>AMD= $1.81 to $2.6 (up 44%); MRVL=$6.98 to $9.47 (up 36%); MU= $5.16 to $7.81 (up 51%)!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>NVDA $11.15 to $12.36 = up only 11%</Msg><Username>qianz31</Username><Timestamp>1359750742234</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:32:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359750877609-68</Id><Title>NVDA $11.15 to $12.36 = up only 11%, well below the average 25-35%. should see $14.5 per share</Title><Msg>Go NVDA</Msg><Username>qianz31</Username><Timestamp>1359750877609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:34:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359751159315-69</Id><Title>Sony to unveil PS3 successor amidst video industry slump and concern about AMD chip compatibility</Title><Msg>""The videogame industry is undergoing a sea change. While videogames used to be limited to dedicated game machines and personal computers, the proliferation of smartphones and other Internet connected devices is opening the floodgates to free or inexpensive games."" ""Complicating the design of the new device will be the likely inclusion of chips designed by Advanced Micro Devices Inc., AMD which people familiar with the matter said have been used in prototypes. The chip is separate from the technology Sony currently relies upon for its PlayStation 3, known as the Cell chip, which was developed jointly with International Business Machines Corp. IBM +0.96% and Toshiba Corp. The move would both introduce compatibility concerns with existing games, built to run on the Cell chip, while also ending a long-running partnership with Nvidia Corp. which supplies graphics chips for the current PlayStation."" SOURCE: professionalDOTwsjDOTcom/article/SB10001424127887323701904578276672168365276.html?mod=WSJ_qtoverview_wsjlatest&amp;mg=reno64-wsj PS: It wouldn't surprise me if PS4 turns out to be a case of DOA due to the above,</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359751159315</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:39:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359751804995-70</Id><Title>NVDA make the best product, I don't like AMD chip.</Title><Msg>Compare the data</Msg><Username>qianz31</Username><Timestamp>1359751804995</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:50:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359752003820-71</Id><Title>Chart is so good, will test $13 again. Look at MACD RSI and 50/200. DOW pass 14,000!!!</Title><Msg>First NVDA will test $13, and then $15. If everything runs well, we are going to see $17 again.</Msg><Username>qianz31</Username><Timestamp>1359752003820</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:53:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359752193661-72</Id><Topic><Title>Sony to unveil PS3 successor amidst video industry slump and concern about AMD chip compatibility</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359751159315</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:39:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"while also ending a long-running partnership with Nvidia Corp." Say no more. Kicked to the curb to play with itself designed SHIELD toy. Buh Bye lmao</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359752193661</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:56:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359752424393-73</Id><Title>market noise is earthshattering, rich against rich</Title><Msg>I'm staying out of that game..</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1359752424393</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:00:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359752778986-74</Id><Topic><Title>Its becoming clear why Nvidia is building its own Tegra junk</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359746309564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:18:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you build it MAYBE they won't come. lol So play with it yourself Nvidia. One taker for Tegra 4 says Digitimes. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359752778986</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:06:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359752863776-75</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes article is wrong</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359725756322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to understand the basic difference between telco and PC//tablet before making an intelligent comment. Number one: the telco industry has an extremely high entry barrier, meaning that you can't just make a few phones here and there to try things out - you need CARRIERS, CARRIERS and CARRIERS who command huge volumes. That is why in the consumer business division of NVIDIA, there seems to be more senior management members than in a traditional tech/semi/PC company. They need the top guys to pitch their products (either handsets of components of handsets) to the senior execs of a carrier (usually VP) who are the decision makers. The component suppliers for a handset CAN"T just send a middle level manager to negotiate large contract - their counterpart simply won't talk to them. That is the reason for being seeming "top heavy" as phrased by some clueless posters. On the other hand, in the pharmaceutical industry, most of the sales are done by reps/details who call on physicians, thus the ratio of reps vs top echelon is entirely different. You can't just compare apples with oranges, or extrapolate a limited experience in one industry to another. Sick and tired of clueless comments.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359752863776</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:07:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359752978529-76</Id><Topic><Title>Sony to unveil PS3 successor amidst video industry slump and concern about AMD chip compatibility</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359751159315</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:39:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you know what it's like being kicked to the curb from when your parents did it to you when they found out what a putz you turned out to be.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1359752978529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:09:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359753013262-77</Id><Topic><Title>Sony to unveil PS3 successor amidst video industry slump and concern about AMD chip compatibility</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359751159315</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:39:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure Gaming Consoles are for kids But Android Mobile Gaming is for COOL KIDS Watch what happens.....</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1359753013262</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:10:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359753578957-78</Id><Topic><Title>"Sony to announce PS4 at February event, launch it later this year"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359691271756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 23:01:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia fans can read the writing all over the internet wall just like everyone else. Nvidia is out of the new play station and the PS4 sour grapes are starting already before the product is even launched. lol Why didn't Sony go with Tegra 4 Nvidia fans? Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359753578957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:19:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359753826548-79</Id><Topic><Title>Why no game console business for Tegra 4 if its so good at playing games?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359739773522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:29:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is Nvdia the only outfit that selected Nvidia's Tegra 4 for its game console? What happen with Sony, MS and Nitendo? Will we see someone other than Nvidia use Tegra 4? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359753826548</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:23:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359755047850-80</Id><Title>Do you think Sony already ended its PS3 GPU orders from Nvidia to ready PS4?</Title><Msg>If Sony plans to launch PS4 as reported all over the net shouldn't they start ordering parts for the NEW Playstaion and drop the PS3 supplier? What do you think Nvidia fans? Does anyone here have a clue who supplied the GPU for PS3? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359755047850</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:44:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359755517876-81</Id><Topic><Title>"Sony to announce PS4 at February event, launch it later this year"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359691271756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 23:01:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It is said to be 10x more powerful than the PS3 currently available on the market." Ten times more powerful sounds like a BIG improvemet over the old PS3 with that Nvidia GPU, doesn't it? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359755517876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:51:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359756062589-82</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia struggles to convince vendors to adopt Tegra 4</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359741312994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:55:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Toshiba is the only vendor, thus far, to confirm the launch of Tegra 4-based tablets some time in mid-2013." Any other vendors ready to "confirm the launch of Tegra 4-based tablets" anytime, anywhere? Can't you Nvidia fans post word of some other Tegra 4 design wins and prove the article wrong? Anyone? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359756062589</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:01:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359757263031-83</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia struggles to convince vendors to adopt Tegra 4</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359741312994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:55:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra 4 was just out of the oven... wise with Shield for it starts sales immediately... Hope to see design wins at MWC... though those telco folks sure do take their time...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359757263031</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:21:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359757289272-84</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes article is wrong</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359725756322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ibexx, The Consumer Products Division is top heavy with senior management because that's where most of employees went from the former Chipset division. Remember it was approaching $1B in annual sales so it was pretty large. All good people for sure, and that's why they could whip up the Project Shield console on a moments notice, but none of them had any experience working with phones or telcos coming from a PC background. Since Nvidia is a NO LAYOFF company and all of the Chipset senior management had been with Nvidia almost from inception...they all got to keep their titles which really don't mean anything anymore in the Semiconductor industry. I do believe this cadre of people from the old chipset division is behind Nvidia's more recent PC centric push into Tablets and Gaming with Phones taking the back burner. Not a bad thing, but those people who may be in Nvidia for the phone business might want to re think their position or at least wait another 12 months or so for any meaningful phone growth. GPUs, High performance Computing, and Tablets are this year's growth drivers. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359757289272</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:21:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359757607827-85</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia struggles to convince vendors to adopt Tegra 4</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359741312994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:55:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The trouble with shorts is that they are so time-sensitive. They need to drive the stock down NOW so they can get out. So, a new chip is working to be adopted, there are a couple of wins and some positive rumors, Mobile World Conference is less than a month away, but they demand proof RIGHT NOW that Tegra 4 has big wins or else... I guess or else they will keep whining. imho.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1359757607827</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:26:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359759196607-86</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia struggles to convince vendors to adopt Tegra 4</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359741312994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:55:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The undertone of the articles are that Tegra 4 is late to a crowded 28nm and already entrenched generation. What Tegra 4 has is that it packs a lot for its size... very small 80 sq mm die... margins will be very good, along with Tegra 4 being cheap... And NVidia drivers...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359759196607</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:53:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359760946665-87</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA notes may be effecting stock performance</Title><Username>nsd870</Username><Timestamp>1359744054274</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:40:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great another reason for somone to want the price to drop.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1359760946665</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:22:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359761244695-88</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia struggles to convince vendors to adopt Tegra 4</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359741312994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:55:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra 4's competitor is Snapdragon 800, which is due out the second half of 2013 and NOT integrated with a LTE radio at first glance. Tegra 4 has a number of second tier products already announced (ViZIO tablet, XOLO phone of India) and some leaked ones (Nexus 5, Nexus 7.7, HTC xxx flagship smartphone, Xiaomi M3 phone of China, Toshiba tablet etc), but nothing has been mentioned for Snapdragon 800 yet, not even rumors. Products based on both SoCs (Tegra 4 and Snapdragon 800) are intended for the middle of the year, and Tegra 4 gadgets likely will arrive a couple of months earlier than the Q 800 devices. Jen Hsun already said at the CES that individual vendors will announce their own product launches, and some will probably do so at the Barcelona meeting 3 weeks from now. So...any one wishes to comment on the design wins of Tegra 4 should put it into the context including Snapdragon 800. PS: The Digitimes article is obviously a hack job (some one already said this), and I suspect that (!) there is price negotiation currently going on between NV and some vendors; (2) some vendors in Taiwan may be pi$$ed off by NV's decision to manufacture and market its own hardware. If NIVIDIA could keep Shield a highly guarded secret, they can, also, do this with product information. The vendors want their own spotlight.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359761244695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:27:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359761958282-89</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia struggles to convince vendors to adopt Tegra 4</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359741312994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:55:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>About Xiaomi's Tegra 4 phone: "Rumors have been that Xiaomi, acting as a pocket-size powerhouse, is all set to launch Xiaomi M3, a smartphone powered by a quad-core Tegra 4 chip, 2.5GB of RAM and a 1080p display. It is expected to showcase Android 4.2 Jelly Bean as well. A gadget’s specifications of this sort from a less-known player like Xiaomi might leave your jaws dropped in awe. SOURCE: 0gadgetsDOTco/2013/01/15/xiaomi-m3-quad-core-tegra-4-powered-phone-quick-look/#.UQxQ4hwjHNo PS: Xiaomi is an extremely popular and well-known Chinese handset maker. It's previous products M1, M2 had been sell-off after market releases. M3 is rumored to be powered by Tegra 4 and will be launched in Q2.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359761958282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:39:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359763777256-90</Id><Topic><Title>"Microsoft Eyes 3 New Surface Tablet Servings for 2013"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1358193453852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 14:57:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Most notable of the planned release is the 8.6-inch Surface RT 2, which will do away with the Nvidia Tegra chip that used with the first iteration. This new Surface RT is set to be deployed with Qualcomm chipset. Already in the Microsoft hardware pipeline too is the Surface Book, a hulking tablet with a 14.6-inch screen display that will rely on Intel's 22-nanometer Haswell chip for its processing power. The 2013 Microsoft Surface thrust will be completed by the 11.6-inch Surface Pro, which according to MS_Nerd will be powered by AMD's Temash APU." Nvidia kicked to he curb AGAIN for a QCOM part Article says AMD, INTC and QCOM are in the new Surface tablets while Nvidia is OUT. No Tegra 4 here Nvidia fans. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359763777256</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:09:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359764307948-91</Id><Title>Reports say NO Nvidia in PS4, NO Nvidia in new Surface, Nviidia left to play with self in SHIELD</Title><Msg>"Sony to announce PS4 at February event, launch it later this year" A weak 32 bit Tegra 4 can't cut the mustard going head to head with 64 bit x86 "Microsoft Eyes 3 New Surface Tablet Servings for 2013" And Tegra 4 can't cut the mustard going head to head with QCOM in handsets and tablets. Looks like QCOM bumped Tegra out of the new Surfaceb and AMD kicked took Nvidia PS4 job. The writing is all over the net wall, Tegra 4 done. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359764307948</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:18:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359765250480-92</Id><Title>"Vizio's first Windows 8 tablet: hands-on with the AMD-powered, 1080p slate"</Title><Msg>"Vizio's first Windows 8 tablet: hands-on with the AMD-powered, 1080p slate" "it's a really good screen, but it creates some consequences. Intel's processors simply couldn't power such a dense, high-res screen, Vizio CTO Matt McRae told us, so the company used AMD chips instead. The Tablet is powered by a dual-core, 1GHz Z-60 processor, which based on our time with the device does a pretty good job powering Windows 8." Intel couldn't cut it and Tegra 4 can't run the full Windows 8 now, can it? Limping RT for Tegra 4 in some no name white box or the highway. Windows 8 require real x86 horsepower. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359765250480</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:34:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359766246705-93</Id><Topic><Title>Check Out Dell - Jensen Take us Private!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359727148564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:59:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this so called long begging Jen and company to buy his shares and bail him out of that Nvidia mess he stepped in with his wallet AGAIN? Another satisfied shareholder huh? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359766246705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:50:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359767432300-94</Id><Title>The Nvidia fanbois I notice like stroking themselves..</Title><Msg>Geez dudes get a real date.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359767432300</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 20:10:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359767535992-95</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA notes may be effecting stock performance</Title><Username>nsd870</Username><Timestamp>1359744054274</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:40:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you read the article correctly, the notes are insurance to secure a minimal profit and avoid any losses. These notes essentially would help keep the price above $12 imo. Nothing wrong with that.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1359767535992</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 20:12:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359767972603-96</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes article is wrong</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1359725756322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brrring! brrring! Brrring! brrring! Thank you for calling Kelly Girls... how may I help you? Hi, Jensen here. Yes, hello mister jensen. I hope you're not calling about our last interim -- 'cause your return period has passed. Oh no no no. I need some telecom salespeople this time. You see, I bought this license to make parts for cellphones -- but nobody here knows anything about selling cellphone parts. I see. Did you give that any thought Before you bought that license to make cellphone parts? Hummm, Jensen? Look, I'm desperate, okay? My Consumer Products Division is top heavy with senior management because that's where most of the redundant employees went from the former PC Chipset division. Which was shut down for lack of sales. All good people for sure... but none of them have any experience working with phone manufacturers or telecoms or this and that. None, nada, zilch, goose egg. And since my company is a NO LAYOFF company -- well, I've got a whole bunch of PC parts people with fancy titles, but not much good at selling cellphone parts to cellphone makers. So Jensen, are we talking outplacement here? Oh no no no. I'll keep all the ex-PC Chipset guys. I just need MORE people that actually know about selling parts to phone manufacturers and telecoms. And Jensen, let me guess. These new QUALCOMM type folks you want to hire. You are expecting them to work for the redundant senior management types from the old dead and buried PC Chipset division, right? Why, of course.</Msg><Username>brrring_brrring</Username><Timestamp>1359767972603</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 20:19:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359769240686-97</Id><Title>Best Buy has android tablets for $99 now.. tegra4 tablets will sell if</Title><Msg>they are priced at $69. Anything else and they won't sell.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359769240686</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 20:40:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359770358810-98</Id><Topic><Title>The Nvidia fanbois I notice like stroking themselves..</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359767432300</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 20:10:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Auto-eroticism is cheaper, easier and more satisfying.</Msg><Username>barjonicat</Username><Timestamp>1359770358810</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 20:59:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359770439534-99</Id><Title>Why Nvidia is Pushing Tablets over Phones....</Title><Msg>Average Selling Price has to be higher. Compare Q3 CPD revenue and operating income to Q2 sales and operating income and you will see why. Up until late Q2 2012 phones and Tablet processor sales were equal but in Q3 Tablet Sales exploded. Q2 Revenue $180M Oper. Loss -$90M Q3 Revenue $244M Oper. Loss -$42M In other words a revenue increase of $64M generated $48M to the bottom line. That is a gross margin of 75% for Tegra sold in tablets. It's obvious why they are pushing tablets over phones. Sure if someone wants to pay full price in phones they will take it. After all the phone mfg. have to keep QCOM honest on the price, so a nibble here are there will happen. Those expecting big phone announcements will be dissappointed I'am afraid. But we did get a design win on a KungFu phone in China this week. By the Way the Russian OEM that was mentioned in that piece on Nvidia reference designs...Wexler holds 35% of the Russian/East European tablet market with their current bestseller a Tegra 3 tablet. Now this Project Shield thing is intriguing. If everyone is sold at profit, what is the worry? Mucho MCP guys around with the skills and experience to design hardware. Back in the day when Nvidia built chipsets, Intel would withhold tech info and samples until they had their chipsets ready for production and these same guys had a better Nvidia chipset ready when Intel launched the new processor. I bet they were clamoring to be on on the team. Besides THE BUZZ from the announcement is PRICELESS! Sometimes holding on to redundancies is worth it. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359770439534</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:00:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359772003664-100</Id><Topic><Title>Why Nvidia is Pushing Tablets over Phones....</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359770439534</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:00:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Title should be" Why QCOM is pushing Nvidia out of the Surface tablet? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359772003664</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:26:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359772129472-101</Id><Title>Why Nvidia pushing tablets while QCOM is pushing Nvidia out of Surface? lol</Title><Msg>"Microsoft Eyes 3 New Surface Tablet Servings for 2013" Google the aritcle for a laugh. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359772129472</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:28:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359772941020-102</Id><Topic><Title>Why Nvidia is Pushing Tablets over Phones....</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359770439534</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:00:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey XC I remember when you use to pump AMD at $8. What happened you switched to QCOM. LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359772941020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:42:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359773839514-103</Id><Topic><Title>Why Nvidia is Pushing Tablets over Phones....</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359770439534</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:00:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And we all remember your Nvidia make GPUs as round and large as cookies post. Didn't you claim you were drunk when you posted that gem? And who can forget your "Took My Profits" post, putting the dump on your pump. Patting yourself on the back for dumping Nvidia to your long buddies. lmao The problem with you Nvidia fans is you act like Nvidia is the ONLY stock on the planet Buy low and sell high, did you hear of that or do you intend to whine on a message board for a dividend increase and for Jen to take Nvidia off your hands in some private deal? lol Keep making up nonsense and whining but no more dumb comment counting post or best seller list junk. You stopped that comment counting and Amazon best seller list nonsense when Nvidia warned and tanked during the Fermi Fiasco, didn't you? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359773839514</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:57:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359774193424-104</Id><Title>Nvidia is pushing tablets over phones because tegra consumes</Title><Msg>too much power for smartphones. Tablets have bigger batteries and can support the power needs of tegra.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359774193424</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 22:03:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359775339978-105</Id><Topic><Title>Why Nvidia is Pushing Tablets over Phones....</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359770439534</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:00:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jeez XC you seem upset. I took profits and waited and bought back in at the lows. That is what you are suppose to do I thought. It ain't about ego. Plus I posted my trade. You pumped AMD at $8 and now it's 2 something. Are you still in AMD? Now your riding QCOM good for you. I wish you luck. Long and strong in Nvidia at $11.50. Looking for $15 to $16 and collecting a nice dividend while I wait. Sincerely</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359775339978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 22:22:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359775628647-106</Id><Title>Hope this is true - Tegra 4 in HTC flagship phone M7</Title><Msg>Nvidia Tegra 4 chipset powers the HTC M7 January 28, 2013 ""Getting back to our today’s news HTC’s 2013 flagship smartphone — HTC M7 that we’ve seen captured in a couple of photos, according to one of our trusted sources will feature Nvidia’s most recent Tegra 4 chipset that features 72 custom NVIDIA GeForce GPU cores which if someone wonders has six times the GPU horsepower of Tegra 3, that’s how powerful these chips are, and to top that this is the first quad-core CPU in it’s portfolio to sport LTE technology, so no one will have to worry about 4G connectivity on the next flagship HTC M7. Another requirement criteria was that HTC needed a chipset powerful enough to highlight their Full HD Super LCD screen an easy task for Tegra 4 chips considering that it also has 4K ultra-high-definition video support embedded."" pocketdroidDOTnet/nvidia-tegra-4-chipset-powers-htc-m7/</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359775628647</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 22:27:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359777181659-107</Id><Title>How long before Nvidia starts selling SHIELD toys out of the back of a pcikup?</Title><Msg>The once high tech darling, Nvidia, rented the GPU crown jewels to Intel for peanuts only to help Intel take GPU business from Nvidia. Brilliant move Nvidia. Nvidia is helping Intel put the discrete GPU business on the fast track to obsolete. And now we hear Nvidia is making SHIELD toys and white box tabets so Tegra 4 has a home and idle GPU engineers have something else to play with at work. lol They call it SHIELD regression testing over at headquarters right? All day, every day making sure every Android games plays properly right? Carry on Green Team. So sad, but still funny how Nvidia fans really think those moves were brilliant. Nvidia can do no wrong and we all watched Nvidia do no wrong from $26 down to $12 didn't we. Enjoy your Nvidia purchase. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359777181659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 22:53:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359777309385-108</Id><Topic><Title>Hope this is true - Tegra 4 in HTC flagship phone M7</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359775628647</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 22:27:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True or Not that never stopped you from posting rumors and nonsene before why stop now. It is a RUMOR right? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359777309385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 22:55:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359778446563-109</Id><Topic><Title>Hope this is true - Tegra 4 in HTC flagship phone M7</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359775628647</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 22:27:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reposting an article published on Jan 29th by Fudzilla entitled, citing its own sources: "Tegra 4 is in new HTC phone" fudzillaDOTcom/home/item/30286-tegra-4-is-in-new-htc-phone?tmpl=component&amp;print=1 To be announced at a special news conference on Feb 19th, prior to MWC, and commercial release On March 8. NVIDIA reportedly in in volume production of Tegra 4 now.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359778446563</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 23:14:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359779410545-110</Id><Topic><Title>Why Nvidia is Pushing Tablets over Phones....</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359770439534</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:00:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Long and strong in Nvidia at $11.50. Looking for $15 to $16 and collecting a nice dividend while I wait." More like "Rather not be Long just looking for $3.50 gain for a strong 10 meter kick as you run to the nearest exit" hmm? lol Enjoy your Nvidia purchase. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359779410545</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 23:30:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359779856376-111</Id><Topic><Title>Hope this is true - Tegra 4 in HTC flagship phone M7</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359775628647</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 22:27:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We cannot confirm it at this time and we don’t know whether the M7 is HTC’s Tegra 4 phone, but we can confirm that Nvidia has won a design win for a future phone from HTC. It is coming in the next few months, but other than that, we don’t know much." Did you read it or just throw up a link? I think your link just said: "We cannot confirm it at this time and we don’t know whether the M7 is HTC’s Tegra 4 phone, " What does that mean to you? Rumor maybe, hmm? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359779856376</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 23:37:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359780958461-112</Id><Topic><Title>Why Nvidia is Pushing Tablets over Phones....</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359770439534</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:00:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The article says if it is not called M7, it will be called somethng else. THey confirmed this. Stupid, do you realize that AMD chip in PS4 is also a rumor? Sony never, ever announced it. LOL</Msg><Username>tomasmann</Username><Timestamp>1359780958461</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 23:55:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>