<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359895149872-1</Id><Topic><Title>HTC M7 shown off by CEO, Details of M4 and G2 leaked</Title><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1359866940171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:49:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so when is nvda folding the Tegra program? doubling down with white labels is simply tripling down the loses, won't accomplish anything.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1359895149872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 07:39:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359904656554-2</Id><Topic><Title>HTC M7 shown off by CEO, Details of M4 and G2 leaked</Title><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1359866940171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:49:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The HTC M7 is expected to have a 4.7-inch full HD screen with a 1920 x 1080 resolution. It will be powered by a 1.5GHz quad-core QUALCOMM Snapdragon S4 Pro processor. It will come with Sense 5.0, HTC’s homegrown skin, which is expected to be lighter and more flatter in terms of UI design. It will have 2GB of RAM, 32GB of internal storage, LTE connectivity and a 13-megapixel camera with 1080p recording and an f/2.0 aperture. The M7 is rumoured to be announced on February 19 at an HTC event and will allegedly launch on March 8. In other HTC-related news, Unwired View reports that the Taiwanese manufacturer will also be releasing the HTC M4 and G2 alongside the M7. These two will replace 2012’s HTC One S and HTC Desire C. The HTC M4 has a 4.3-inch, 720p screen and is powered by a 1.2GHz dual-core QUALCOMM Snapdragon processor. The M4 is expected to run Android 4.2 Jellybean at launch and will come with 2GB of RAM, just like the M7. Likewise, M4 is expected to carry a 13MP camera on the back. It will come with 16GB storage capacity. The handset will likely feature the new version of HTC’s Sense UI and will be LTE-ready. The G2 is decidedly low-end when compared to the M-series devices. It is possible that HTC might change the name of the handset as it already has a handset with that retail name. The reported specs are a 3.5-inch HVGA display, 512MB of RAM and 4GB of internal storage. A 5MP camera graces the back, but the OS version will allegedly be Android 4.0 Ice Cream Sandwich." So where's the Tegra #4 orders, boys? You know. From somewhere other than the nvidia toy Shield.</Msg><Username>where_is_nvidia</Username><Timestamp>1359904656554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 10:17:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359904954495-3</Id><Topic><Title>HTC M7 shown off by CEO, Details of M4 and G2 leaked</Title><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1359866940171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:49:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like you posting here incessantly.. won't appear accomplish. Anything...</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1359904954495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 10:22:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359905624501-4</Id><Topic><Title>HTC M7 shown off by CEO, Details of M4 and G2 leaked</Title><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1359866940171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:49:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one here eats more crow than thy... add another serving...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359905624501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 10:33:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359911500996-5</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Top End Gamer Card Is Almost Free--$157.00. Nvidia Top Card Still $499.99</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359833308293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 14:28:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My, my xc3155 doesn't understand the simple facts You know, how Nvidia is able to command an APPLE-LIKE command of the GPU market That's right, boys, xc3155 still thinks AMD's pathetic attempts to BEST Nvidia With the watt-sucking "Gigahertz" edition Will pay dividends Like Nvidia shares do Every quarter</Msg><Username>pixelshader9000</Username><Timestamp>1359911500996</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 12:11:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359915232530-6</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH NVDA Analyst Report !</Title><Username>christopherwhite331</Username><Timestamp>1359909792831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 11:43:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Useful report !</Msg><Username>woodham.sandra</Username><Timestamp>1359915232530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 13:13:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359917452430-7</Id><Title>Is This The First Of Nvidia's Reference Design Phones?</Title><Msg>BLU Quattro smartphones. Google: BLU Quattro smartphone for details</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359917452430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 13:50:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359918592798-8</Id><Topic><Title>Is This The First Of Nvidia's Reference Design Phones?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359917452430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 13:50:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well now j777kxx... if NVidia can get their stuff to market... what exactly did you telco guys do ... ?? is the new model to bypass you guys ??</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359918592798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 14:09:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359919890263-9</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Q4 earrings release date Feb 13</Title><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1359831010841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:50:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wait till Nvda starts putting out their white boxed smartphones and tablets.....they'll explode sales and bring in big revenue.</Msg><Username>uzioaitte</Username><Timestamp>1359919890263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 14:31:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359920401859-10</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH NVDA Analyst Report !</Title><Username>christopherwhite331</Username><Timestamp>1359909792831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 11:43:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big thanks !</Msg><Username>leonardo.bissonette</Username><Timestamp>1359920401859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 14:40:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359921674097-11</Id><Topic><Title>Is This The First Of Nvidia's Reference Design Phones?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359917452430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 13:50:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coming to rack at your local convenience store near you? Note: Target stores already have that rack. I have no idea whether this reference design thing is a good or bad thing for Nvidia. But It's exactly how the PC's became a commodity. Intel made a platform and reference design using Intel chips and hundred's of PC manufacturers came into being all making a few cents on each dollar sold. I mean they are phones for heaven sakes not some magical mystery tour devices. But with a Tegra phone you can play games with smoke, particles and special physical effects downloaded from GooglePlay if your into that sort of thing. Did you see the back of the phones stamped with Powered by Nvidia Tegra. Are we looking at a modern day version of "Intel Inside"? I don't think the 1st tier smartphone manufacturers are going to like what Nvidia is doing! I just hear it now at the earnings conference call. We have over 300 design wins for Tegra phones already. LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359921674097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 15:01:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359927233559-12</Id><Title>Developers about OUYA</Title><Msg>engadgetDOTcom/2013/02/01/ouya-developers-sound-off/ Pretty positive about console, support they got and hardware (Tegra 3), of course.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1359927233559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 16:33:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359927781929-13</Id><Topic><Title>Is This The First Of Nvidia's Reference Design Phones?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359917452430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 13:50:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is This The First Of Nvidia's Reference Design Phones? Nah. It looks like Jen's newest scheme to get rid of that mountain of unwanted Tegra #3's. Severely Chop the price, and sell 'em to the disposable cellphone trade. You know, for #$%$ and drug dealers and hit men and this or that. Yes boys, the Disposable Cellphone trade. Which might be somewhat more profitable than Jen's old way of getting rid of that mountain of unwanted Tegra #2's. You Do remember where all the unwanted Tegra #2's went, right? Samsung. Yep. At garage sale prices. Those Koreans are no dumb bunnies. Oh no no no. Just follow the curbside news of Nvidia order cancellations. And they show up with their own cargo containers. "Ten cent on dolly -- like last time -- okay?"</Msg><Username>perceptive.best</Username><Timestamp>1359927781929</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 16:43:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359932714395-14</Id><Title>Is This the 2nd of Nvidia's Reference Design Phones?</Title><Msg>Nvidia plans to make its own phones and sell it through local brands. Nvidia will soon create its own smartphones, tablets and other devices as part of the company's shift towards white label manufacturing. According to reports, the first devices featuring fully-developed Nvidia products will be sold in Russia and China. However, we believe India will be amongst the first country to get such a product. According to a report in Mobile-Review, a technology focused website, Nvidia will be working with regional device brands to sell its initial product offerings. Nvidia is believed to be working with Wexler in Russia to sell its hardware. It is to be noted that some time back Lava, which sells products under Xolo brand, had told The Mobile Indian of making Nvidia Tegra 4 based smartphones. "We are in the process of evaluating the option to launch an Nvidia Tegra 4 smartphone. While Nvidia is yet to release a reference design based on the latest quad core chipset, we are hopeful that we will be able to bring a product based on the chipset by the end of February or March this year," S N Rai, co-founder and director of Lava International, told The Mobile Indian recently. So we believe Nvidia is working with Xolo to bring quad core smartphones to India. Lava had earlier joined hands with Intel for its first Xolo smartphone, called the Xolo X900. Recently Lava also announced the Xolo X500 under the same business model. Xolo brand has been received well in India thanks to the very high quality first product - the Intel powered Xolo X900. Since Nvidia is expected to both design and manufacture the hardware to ensure the highest quality builds possible, this product could establish the Xolo brand as a formidable one amongst even the MNC players. According to the report in Mobile-Review, Nvidia will begin white label product in mid-2013 and will start with 7-inch and 10-inch tablets that will share the same core designs. However, this is in variance with our information which puts the launch in the first quarter itself and possibly a smartphone. But then we are just joining the dots and could be that these companies have different plans. Quad core phones in India is going momentum with Karbonn and Micromax already announcing their respective low cost quad core phones, and Nvidia needs to hurry if it plans to make it big in this emerging segment. _____________________________________________________________________________ Watch for the Nvidia Phone Rack at Walgreens or a convenience store near you. This just might have legs.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359932714395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 18:05:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359935104622-15</Id><Title>Nvidia is done in smartphones folks.. Qualcomm has cornered the market</Title><Msg>Just forget about smartphones for tegra OK?</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359935104622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 18:45:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359935149722-16</Id><Topic><Title>Is This the 2nd of Nvidia's Reference Design Phones?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359932714395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 18:05:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jen's desperation is getting painful to watch. Oh so painful. Why can't the guy just admit that his "let's make commodity ARM chips" folly was a very bad idea -- as evidenced by the One Third of a Billion Dollars of shareholder's cash that the Tegra/CPB lost last year -- and call it quits. Like Texas Instruments and Freescale wisely did. We've seen this Bad Movie before, right? We sure have. It's called Tin Cup. A movie about a desperate, broken-down, has-been, done for golfer. Oh, and you can find the movie at Walgreens too.</Msg><Username>epic.best</Username><Timestamp>1359935149722</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 18:45:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359937539318-17</Id><Topic><Title>Is This The First Of Nvidia's Reference Design Phones?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359917452430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 13:50:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very nice tegra site by Slashgear! Things are growing very fast now!</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1359937539318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 19:25:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359938518989-18</Id><Topic><Title>Is This the 2nd of Nvidia's Reference Design Phones?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359932714395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 18:05:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hahhahahhahaha your pain is only beginning! This is really going to be fun! choke on it dipstick.</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1359938518989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 19:41:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359938745451-19</Id><Title>Are These The 3rd and 4th Nvidia Reference Design Phones?</Title><Msg>CoolPad have equipped the CoolPad HD 9960 with a 1280 x 720 resolution 4.7 inch display, 13 mega-pixel rear camera with back illuminated F2.0 aperature, 1GB RAM 16GB of built-memory and a 2000mAh battery. If that’s not enough to get you excited a Gorilla Glass display should keep the front of this phone looking great while Android 4.1 Jelly Bean will ensure it keeps up to date with phones from other manufacturers and the quad-core Tegra 3 CPU along with 1GB RAM should dish out enough performance you could need. oolpad have taken advantage of the recent Nvidia Tegra 3 price drop to enter the quad-core, 5-inch market with the Coolpad 8730. While Oppo, ZTE and Huawei have gone for 1080 screens on their flagship 2013 phones, the Coolpad 8730 makes do with a 720p screen (720 x 1280 resolution) which should offer pretty stunning visuals never the less, while helping to keep costs low. The tried and tested quad-core Tegra 3 chip runs at 1.5Ghz with 1GB RAM, while the cameras are a 8 mega-pixel rear and 1.3 mega-pixel front. Android Jelly Bean 4.1 comes out of the box and features Coolpad’s own CoolLife Ui4.1. ___________________________________________________________________________ Nvidia Reference Design Phones are popping up all over China, Russia, India, latin America, and even starting to appear in the US. I look forward to buying Nvidia reference phone at Walmart or Circle K this year.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359938745451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 19:45:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359940747153-20</Id><Title>Is This The 5th of Nvidia Reference Design Phones?</Title><Msg>Gaoxinqi F1 – quad smartphone Nvidia Tegra 3 Recently, due to the stiff competition in the market for mobile quad core, manufacturers are forced to cut prices on its processors. Nvidia Tegra 3 chipset recently cut its price and Chinese companies began to use it in the production of low-cost quad-core smartphones. However, Gaoxinqi went further and released a budget 5.7-inch high-performance smartphone! With an eye to the Samsung Galaxy Note 2, Gaoxinqi F1 was created. But instead of the processor from Samsung, it received a powerful Tegra 3 chip with a frequency of 1.5 GHz and 1 GB RAM. F1 also has a 5.7-inch screen with a resolution of 720 x 1280 pixels, 4 GB of internal memory, 8-megapixel rear camera with LED flash, the battery capacity of 3000mAh and Android Jelly Bean as an operating system. Unfortunately cost of new items has not reported, but it is expected that it will exceed 1999 Yuan. _____________________________________________________________________________ I am beginning to see a pattern here. Have to ask the manager of local Circle K convenience store whenhe is goingto stock some of these Nvidia Reference Design Phones.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359940747153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 20:19:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359941579392-21</Id><Topic><Title>Are These The 3rd and 4th Nvidia Reference Design Phones?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359938745451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 19:45:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Coolpad has taken advantage of the recent Nvidia Tegra 3 price drop to enter the quad-core, 5-inch market with the Coolpad 8730." So Best? If Jen lost One Third of a Billion Dollars last year on the Tegra folly, how much is he gonna lose After the recent Nvidia Tegra 3 price drop? Hummm? Sales and revenues don't matter -- if there's no profit. Or worse, exponentially increasing Horrendous losses. Fire Jen. Get a Real profit motivated CEO. Before time runs out for nvidia.</Msg><Username>ask.best</Username><Timestamp>1359941579392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 20:32:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359941809090-22</Id><Title>Is This the 6th of Nvidia Reference Design Phones?</Title><Msg>You know, I once saw this world map that divided the world into how America sees it – and China was labeled as the “World’s Supermarket”. The thing is, one would not be wrong to think this way considering how they managed to churn out the ZTE U950, a 1.3GHz Tegra 3 powered smartphone that costs all of just 999 yuan, meaning it does not break the $200 barrier if you convert the local currency there to US dollars. In fact, we are talking about just $160 thereabouts here for an unlocked device, and it comes accompanied by 1GB RAM, 4GB of internal memory, a 4.3” display and a 2,000mAh battery powering the puppy. At the back lies a 5-megapixel camera, while the front has a VGA camera for your video call needs. All of those are stuffed into a body that measures a mere 9mm thin – pretty impressive, don’t you think so? Too bad it does not come with Android 4.1 Jelly Bean, but rather, you will have to rock to Android 4.0 Ice Cream Sandwich right out of the box. Doesn’t look likely that this will ever make it Stateside though. ________________________________________________________________________ ummm. ZTE outsells Apple in smartphones in China...i.e. #4 to Apple's # 6.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359941809090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 20:36:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359942231470-23</Id><Topic><Title>Are These The 3rd and 4th Nvidia Reference Design Phones?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359938745451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 19:45:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh I forget to Add. Bloomberg TV did a segment last week on CoolPad. Said they were the #3 bestseller of smartphones in China. Said their success was why Apple is working on a cheap Iphone so they could catchup with Samsung, Lenova, Coolpad and ZTE.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359942231470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 20:43:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359942365136-24</Id><Topic><Title>Took My Profits</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1311623376000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-07-25 15:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this dude working hard to put up anotrher "Took My Profits" or what? lmao</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359942365136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 20:46:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359942431689-25</Id><Topic><Title>Toms hardware: "Toshiba Currently the Only One to Adopt Tegra 4?"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359864931823</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:15:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There can be only one." lol</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359942431689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 20:47:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359942782998-26</Id><Topic><Title>Check Out Dell - Jensen Take us Private!</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359727148564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:59:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like someone wants out yesterday. Begging Jen to help him make a quick exit. Forget that long and strong nonsense he's no long he'd rather be gone. How much are you in the hole on thet Nvidia purchase? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359942782998</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 20:53:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359942840789-27</Id><Title>Is This The 7th of Nvidia Reference Design Phones?</Title><Msg>Beidou mobile phone netwrok is ready to launching the Small Pepper Q1 smartphone, for the first batch theh has ready to preparing 999 million unit smartphone. The price will be ready for only 699 yuan or about $112 USD. After a lapse of several months, this smartphone Q1 quad-core model such as about to come and you can making pre-order since January 16th, while the reservation quota limit of 20,000, the price of the previously announced is 999 yuan or about $160 USD. Officially released on the 19th of this month. This phone is powered by Tegra3 1.5GHz processor, packs with 5 inches screen size, the display resolution of HD level, running the Android 4.1 operating system, while hardware configuration need to wait until the conference. Q1 addition to follow-up there may be a high-pass, MTK platform version. Closing the formal appointment of the Beidou mobile phone network is not yet complete the announcement phone information. Back in November last year, the Beidou mobile phone network with ZTE launched a small whirlwind quad-core phone, same of TEGRA3 quad-core, but slightly lower frequency of only 1.3GHz. ______________________________________________________________________________ Do you cash $USD $1M and a website in an emerging market? Always wanted to own a phone company? Well Nvidia wants to talk with you. Cash ACCEPTED ONLY BEFORE SHIPMENT. Join thousands like the owner above and enjoy the fruits of capitalism!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359942840789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 20:54:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359943502908-28</Id><Topic><Title>Is This The 5th of Nvidia Reference Design Phones?</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359940747153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 20:19:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Due to stiff competition in the market for mobile quad core processors, manufacturers have been forced to cut prices. Nvidia recently Chopped its price on the Tegra 3, and Chinese companies have temporarily begun to use them." "And the Bottom Drops Out." Google it boys : Better Days (And The Bottom Drops Out) (Video) - YouTube</Msg><Username>brutally.best</Username><Timestamp>1359943502908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:05:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>24</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359943805483-29</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia is done in smartphones folks.. Qualcomm has cornered the market</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359935104622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 18:45:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They can dream and pretend that QCOM ddn't have a monster quarter and Nvidia is still $26. But when they wake up Nvidia is $12 and trying to hustle SHIELD toys. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1359943805483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:10:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359944155444-30</Id><Title>Its a fight for the bottom now with Nvidia.. Who can do the cheapest</Title><Msg>phone. Nvidia's philosophy now is to sell chips at a loss and make it up in volume.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359944155444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:15:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359944204980-31</Id><Title>Is This The 8th of Nvidia Reference Design Phones?</Title><Msg>Xiaomi mi-3 NVIDIA Tegra 4 chipset, LTE radio and an improved 4.5" screen,quad-core Cortex-A15 CPU with clock speeds between 1.8 GHz and 2 GHz with around 2.5 GB worth of RAM. Source: Youtube Jan 14th ________________________________________________________________________________ I don't know but this reference design thing seems to catching on...Note: Xiaomi is not small potatoes in China and the Chinese like their smartphones sharp and cheap. That's why Apple is struggling there. Notice the dare I say it.....LTE.....LOL</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359944204980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:16:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359945456772-32</Id><Topic><Title>Its a fight for the bottom now with Nvidia.. Who can do the cheapest</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359944155444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:15:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you know that in the Xolo Indian phone Tegra is replacing an Intel chip.....Ouch</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359945456772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:37:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359946127359-33</Id><Title>Engadget reviews Tegra 3-running Quattro 4.5, 4.5 HD and 5.7 HD - unlocked phones supporting AT&amp;T and T Mobile</Title><Msg>Yup, NVIDIA's last-gen SoC still rakes in serious money.... _______ It was just weeks ago that BLU Products' smartphones were largely dual-core models like the Vivo 4.65 HD. The company clearly wants to ramp things up, as it's kicking off the Quattro line based around Android 4.0 and the quad-core, 1.5GHz Tegra 3. At the entry level is the $250 Quattro 4.5, which includes a qHD display at its namesake size as well as a 5-megapixel camera, 4GB of built-in storage and a microSD slot. The next step is, unusually, the biggest: the $300 Quattro 5.7 HD (what you see above) keeps the same storage, but jumps to the extra-large category while upgrading to a 720p display and an 8-megapixel camera. BLU sees the $350 Quattro 4.5 HD as the real darling. It beats its non-HD cousin with a curved, 720p screen touting Gorilla Glass, and throws in a larger 16GB capacity as well as a more light-sensitive 8-megapixel camera. The two smaller models ship to the US early this month, to be followed by the 5.7-inch behemoth in late March. When they arrive, every one of them will carry unlocked HSPA+ 3G that supports both AT&amp;T and T-Mobile. SOURCE: engadgetDOTcom/2013/02/03/blu-products-unveils-tegra-3-running-quattro-smartphones/?utm_source=engadget&amp;utm_medium=twitter</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359946127359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:48:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359946407043-34</Id><Topic><Title>Its a fight for the bottom now with Nvidia.. Who can do the cheapest</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359944155444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:15:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lava launches Intel Lexington based XOLO X500 in India 25 January, 2013 | Comments (28) | Post your comment Tags: Lava, Android, Touch UI Lava International, the company that released the world's first Intel Atom-based smartphone in India - the XOLO X900 - is now set to launch the new XOLO X500. The new handset is based on Intel's new Atom processor, formerly known as 'Lexington', designed specifically for low-cost smartphones. The Atom Z2420 on the X500 is clocked at 1.2GHz and uses Intel's Hyper-Threading technology, which theoretically doubles the processor cores per physical core, making it more efficient. It also uses PowerVR SGX540 GPU, good enough for casual gaming and 1080p video playback. The XOLO X500 has a 3.5-inch, 480 x 320 resolution display, 512MB of RAM, 4GB internal memory with microSD card slot, 5 megapixel rear camera with auto-focus and 7fps burst mode, 1,500mAh battery, dual-SIM card support and Android 4.0 Ice Cream Sandwich. The Lava XOLO X500 is priced at ₹8,999 ($168) unlocked and will go on sale in India in the next 2-3 days</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1359946407043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:53:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359946641980-35</Id><Topic><Title>Engadget reviews Tegra 3-running Quattro 4.5, 4.5 HD and 5.7 HD - unlocked phones supporting AT&amp;T and T Mobile</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359946127359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:48:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Viva Nvidia Reference Design. Last year there was a 4 month gap between Tegra 2 products and Tegra 3 products and sales plunged. This year is shaping up to a seemless transistion. I mean Google Nexus 7 still selling well. Win RT still selling, and huge number of emerging market phones launched in the 4th quarter. Remember Nvidia's Tegra is still ruled by the Law of Small Numbers....i.e. it doesn't take much to move the needle. P.S. I wonder if the Blu phones have Icera modems...that would be just too much for the naysayers wouldn't it?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359946641980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:57:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359946759257-36</Id><Topic><Title>Engadget reviews Tegra 3-running Quattro 4.5, 4.5 HD and 5.7 HD - unlocked phones supporting AT&amp;T and T Mobile</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1359946127359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:48:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So where's the orders for the Tegra #4, boys? Sure, with Jen being forced to seriously Chop the price on the old, legacy Tegra #3's, -- to empty out the warehouse, don't u know -- they're finding some bargain shoppers from the never-heard-of-ems. But the Tegra #4 is the Future for nvidia. And there's still no orders.</Msg><Username>i_know_best</Username><Timestamp>1359946759257</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:59:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359946823194-37</Id><Topic><Title>Its a fight for the bottom now with Nvidia.. Who can do the cheapest</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359944155444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:15:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gsmarenaDOTcom/xolo-x500-gets-benchmarked-sports-intel-atom-z2420-cpu/ Xolo X500 and its Intel Atom Z2420 CPU get benchmarked, get pretty good scores January 31st, 2013, 20:20 bySunil26 comments Xolo X500, which was launched a week ago in India, has just been benchmarked. The smartphone is designed for emerging markets with low cost at higher priority than stellar performance, but it did surprisingly well. Perhaps a part of the explanation is that the Intel chip also uses its hyper threading technology, which has better multi-tasking ability. The smartphone is powered by a 1.2 GHz Intel Atom Lexington Z2420 processor along with Power VR SGX540 GPU. The Atom-powered Xolo X500 is right behind the Xolo X900, which is powered by the Medfield chipset in the Quadrant benchmark tests. However the X500 managed to beat its more expensive sibling at the AnTuTu benchmark. The smartphone aggregates 12859 points in the AnTuTu 3.0 benchmark, which is not bad at all. Xolo X500 is on top of Vellamo 1.0 browser benchmark tests too and scores a hefty 1168 and 421 points in the HTML5 web browser tests and CPU subsystem performance respectively. The X500 also managed to max out the NenaMark 2 benchmark. At the onscreen GLBenchmark test it only managed 18fps, but it should still do pretty well with all but the heaviest games.</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1359946823194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 22:00:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359947112110-38</Id><Topic><Title>Its a fight for the bottom now with Nvidia.. Who can do the cheapest</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359944155444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:15:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cnet Mobile Phones We've run the Samsung Galaxy S3 through a barrage of benchmark tests, with our results showing that Samsung's latest toy is a proper performance powerhouse that manages to beat the beefy HTC One X. Read on, folks, and brace for numbers. In the Antutu benchmark, which tests memory, CPU speed and graphics, the S3 racked up an impressive 12,112 points, beating the One X, which scored 10,827 in the same test. A similar benchmark, Quadrant, awarded the Galaxy S3 with 5,289 points, again beating the One X, which mustered a score of 4,904. The HTC One X ran GL Benchmark's Standard Egypt test at a rate of 52 frames per second, but was once more bested by the Galaxy S3, which ran the same test at 59fps -- the same score managed by the frighteningly powerful new iPad. The 4.8-inch Galaxy S3 even beat Apple's frighteningly powerful new tablet in one of our browser tests. When we ran the SunSpider JavaScript benchmark (in which lower scores are better), the S3 scored 1,498.9ms, while the new iPad and iPad 2 took slightly longer with scores of 1,890.9 and 1,884.6 respectively. The S3's result also aces the iPhone 4S, which scored 2,181.6ms. HTC clawed back one victory -- sort of. In the Vellamo browser test the S3's score of 2,077 wasn't as high as the app's database score for the HTC One XL, a phone that's not out in the UK yet. Despite the HTC One X also offering a quad-core chip and a slightly higher clock speed, our tests show that it's not quite as powerful as the Galaxy S3. That could be down to the S3's Exynos 4 Quad chip being made by Samsung itself, while the Tegra 3 processor in the One X is built by Nvidia. Number crunching aside, my expert colleague Natasha reckons the Galaxy S3 feels slicker to use than HTC's offering, with no lag or stutter as you cruise around the phone's Ice Cream Sandwich-flavoured interface. It's worth noting that while it's pipped to the post by the S3 in performance stakes, the One X is still a very powerful smart phone. For more on the One X's performance click here, and for more on the Galaxy S3, including test shots from the phone's 8-megapixel camera, observe our in-depth review.</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1359947112110</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 22:05:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359949974762-39</Id><Topic><Title>Its a fight for the bottom now with Nvidia.. Who can do the cheapest</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359944155444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:15:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To sumup justfine. In Antutu benchmark, Intel's low end ATOM scores 12859, Samsung top of line Galaxy S3 scores 12112, and the tegra3 HTC scores 10827. How much more of losses will Jensun take, before he scraps the whole tegra stuff.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359949974762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 22:52:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359950638538-40</Id><Topic><Title>Its a fight for the bottom now with Nvidia.. Who can do the cheapest</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359944155444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:15:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is Mobile Indian reporting that Xolo has stopped selling the Intel phone and is replacing it with a tegra chip phone?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359950638538</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 23:03:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359951763773-41</Id><Topic><Title>700,000 Cannibals</Title><Username>leftie_the_sockpuppet</Username><Timestamp>1358995688544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 21:48:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What was said was, "iMac sales were Down by 700,000 units year over year", Apple's CEO Cook said. He blamed the slip on a weak market, and the Cannibalization of iMac's sales by Apple's iPad products." I bet we hear Jen whine about the same thing too. At his upcoming 4Q confessional. "Nvidia's sales of iMac parts Plummeted because folks are buying the Apple iPad instead. And we don't make any parts for the Genuine Apple iPad."</Msg><Username>i_know_best</Username><Timestamp>1359951763773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 23:22:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359952138775-42</Id><Title>Fast Forward 24 months</Title><Msg>The majority of smartphones are sold at Convenience stores, websites, and drugstores. Like MPG players. Who will be on that rack....and at what price? Think die size......because Android operating is free. Google is pretty smart don't you think? Nvidia has the smallest die size and the best physics for games. Perhaps they will disposable. Remember $500.00 scientific calculators. Well now they are $49.99. TI adapted, HP didn't even though they were so cool with their "Reverse Polish" operating system. Nvidia is adapting, Apple isn't. Intel will say forget about it, because they can't fill $5B fabs with $20 chips. LOL Apple is just not cool anymore. If you don't believe me watch...they will introduce a cheap IPhone by Summer! Steve Jobs a leader but Tim Cook is a follower. JMHO</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359952138775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 23:28:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359952874291-43</Id><Topic><Title>Its a fight for the bottom now with Nvidia.. Who can do the cheapest</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359944155444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:15:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mobile Indian reads Ibexx?</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359952874291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 23:41:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359953348126-44</Id><Topic><Title>Fast Forward 24 months</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359952138775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 23:28:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Over the last year and half, Intel has produced $100 plus icore and $1000 server chips from its 32nm fabs. Now it is producing the lexington platform in those fabs. These fabs have been fully depreciated so the cost per platform will be very low. As Intel sells phone platforms at less than $15 dollars, they will still have a gross margin of over 60%. NO TECH COMPANY CAN COMPETE IN THE LOW MARGIN PART OF THE MARKET WITH INTEL. What Arm pumpers think is Intel's weakness is actually Intel's strength. Next year, after Intel moves to 14nm this fall, the low cost phones will get a 22nm platform which the clovertrail+ scored a 24,000 on the antutu benchmark.(tegra 3 scored 10,000)</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1359953348126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 23:49:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359953838246-45</Id><Topic><Title>Fast Forward 24 months</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1359952138775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 23:28:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I still use that $500 HP calculator from the early 90's. once you go reverse polish, it's hard to go back</Msg><Username>stockbooger</Username><Timestamp>1359953838246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 23:57:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>