<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-21"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363844184130-1</Id><Title>When will Win RT dissappear? Only MSFT knows.</Title><Msg>Ballmer is stubborn, He'll try with surface again and again. No one else is supporting Win RT. Even Asus and Lenovo and dumping it.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363844184130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 01:36:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363844965883-2</Id><Title>Someone give me a reason to buy a Win RT tablet. Please..</Title><Msg>I can't seem to find one. With the $100 free Office software now available on Win 8 tablets, that advantage is gone.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363844965883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 01:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363845075754-3</Id><Topic><Title>When will Win RT dissappear? Only MSFT knows.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363844184130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 01:36:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>btw, how are Win Pro sales... just read that RT is better than 2x in sales compared to Pro...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363845075754</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 01:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363845247006-4</Id><Topic><Title>Someone give me a reason to buy a Win RT tablet. Please..</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363844965883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 01:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>then buy a win pro tablet... and let us all know the outrageous price you paid for it... need a good laugh...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363845247006</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 01:54:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363847363395-5</Id><Topic><Title>Someone give me a reason to buy a Win RT tablet. Please..</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363844965883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 01:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spam</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1363847363395</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 02:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363863423774-6</Id><Topic><Title>Someone give me a reason to buy a Win RT tablet. Please..</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363844965883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 01:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Android is where it's at for the Tegra. Everybody knows Intel/AMD won the Windows tabs.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363863423774</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 06:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363870258958-7</Id><Title>Project Shield - Moor Insights</Title><Msg>"The important piece of information we don’t know yet is the price, but they have a lot to work with. You have to consider what it could replace and compete with: Apple iPod Touch- starts at $299 with 4″ display, 1136×640 display Sony PS Vita- starts at $249 with 5″, 960×544 display Nintendo 3DS XL- starts at $199 with 4.88″, 800×240 display and 4.18″, 320×240 bottom display Sony PlayStation 3: starts at $249 with no display Microsoft XBOX 360: starts at $199 with no display There are some big differences in the economics in the devices above. Each of the devices, except the iPod Touch, is significantly subsidized by games that cost between $25-$70. I expect NVIDIA to price SHIELD more like the iPod Touch, with an initial higher price point and I think they could garner $399-299 from gamers for the device. I would expect games to be priced between $1-$20, like Android games are priced today. Buyers can also play any games they may have previously purchased too, let’s say from their Android phones or tablets like the Google Nexus 7. Very important to stress, none of the competitive game devices can play PC games, and that will be very important to some gamers. PC gamers don’t always enjoy sitting at the table or desk and like to be mobile, too. It would be great if my son would leave the office where he is playing Pirate101 and Minecraft and come and join the family in the living room." Source: moorinsightsstrategyDOTcom/why-nvidia%E2%80%99s-project-shield-is-disruptive-to-game-consoles-and-portable-game-devices/</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363870258958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:50:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363871404246-8</Id><Title>Pay day for NVIDIA longs</Title><Msg>Dividend in account.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363871404246</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:10:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363871467170-9</Id><Topic><Title>Project Shield - Moor Insights</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363870258958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:50:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>honest assessment and not just the nvda pump. I might add one more point - that 1080 in the living room, for any serious gamer, is already hooked up to the gaming PC. In that case, do you really need a $400 remote joystick when you can get one for $100 to $150?</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1363871467170</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:11:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363871868961-10</Id><Topic><Title>Pay day for NVIDIA longs</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363871404246</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:10:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just got $1,575.00. Nice little bonus, although in do have some shares on margin son this pays my margin interest for a few months. This dividend alone has kept me holding more shares rather then calls. With the low volatility and little movement I would have been killed in the long term. I believe the dividend and stock buy back has put stability and a nice floor in thebstoock,. Best of luck with trades. Higgins</Msg><Username>ugs</Username><Timestamp>1363871868961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:17:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363871916703-11</Id><Topic><Title>Project Shield - Moor Insights</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363870258958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:50:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PC Gamers do whosunw....there are 55 million of them. Certainly a lot will buy. PAX EAST this weekend at Boston should give us some clues. Go to his website and read his original white paper on Nvidia Grid from last year (same technology just used in a different business). The Enterpirse VDI apparently is the Holy Grail of computing...who knew? Good analysis and written 8 months ago.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363871916703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:18:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363872322026-12</Id><Topic><Title>Project Shield - Moor Insights</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363870258958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:50:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would be nice to continue the gameplay in the bathroom, bedroom, or at a party. It is well worth the $350 (the price point I always speculated) for serious and semi-serious gamers - and there are lot of those in this world These guys could spend well over $500 for a high-end graphic card with regular refreshes - too rich for your blood, we know. Hourly-paid bashers like you aren't exactly the typical consumers.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363872322026</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:25:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363873927853-13</Id><Topic><Title>Someone give me a reason to buy a Win RT tablet. Please..</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363844965883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 01:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should buy two and download the swimfin app. Then go to the nearest deepest lake near you. Tie one to each ankle and enjoy. ignore</Msg><Username>nvdarocks</Username><Timestamp>1363873927853</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:52:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363876798477-14</Id><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Msg>First off, let me say that I'm a long. I currently hold about 10K shares of NVDA, and I have no intention of selling. I like the company, I like the CEO, I like it's future, and I like where it's going and what it's trying to do. That being said, I'm curious to know the opinions of the posters here, (flamers and NVDA bashers excluded), in terms of an approximate time that we could see some significant pps movement. We've been trading sideways for a while now, understandably, but with the roadmaps laid out by the CEO this week, I'm very excited for what NVDA is going to be bringing to market over the next 12-24 months. NVDA is without question, the leader in graphics, and with the announcements of Logan, Parker, Maxwell, and Volta, NVDA will soon be producing products that no other company will be able to match, to include QCOM. I think the GRID system is a genius idea on the part of NVDA to market to small to medium sized small businesses and I fully expect it to be a major seller. The capabilities are incredible. SHIELD will likely not be a major seller, but with NVDA's loyal fanbase in the gamer community, as well as a good holiday season, and we could see major additions to margins from that as well. Add in Tegra 4i and I think you have a very impressively diversified company, putting out quality, state of the art products, that are in demand. I'm a firm believer that when we start seeing revenue from the new products sometime around 1Q 2013, we'll easlily top $20 per share. NVDA has beaten estimates for the last few quarters, and I expect that to continue. Until that happens, I'm happy to collect the dividend and wait for the Street to finally take notice of a true tech industry pioneer in NVDA. Good luck to all longs.</Msg><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363877545230-15</Id><Title>So much for the near-term catalysts...</Title><Msg>Can't see any major move up till the 2H, at the earliest. They're writing songs of love, but not for NVDA!</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363877545230</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363877895354-16</Id><Topic><Title>So much for the near-term catalysts...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363877545230</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then sell...go trade elsewhere, and try to time your entry back in. Or just wait it out :)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363877895354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:58:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363879223081-17</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm subscribed. Cool</Msg><Username>mandelbaummargret</Username><Timestamp>1363879223081</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363879463650-18</Id><Topic><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The comments by Josh shredded the author to pieces. I don't mind a view one way or the other, but that article wasjust flat out unprofessional in tone, and downright silly on the merits.</Msg><Username>patent_killr</Username><Timestamp>1363879463650</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:24:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363879514764-19</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Price movement is dependent on Day traders and Option writers...volume is extremely low. Nothing to write home about say break above $13 for a month or two. Long term...I'm not as bullish as you although Nvidia has very impressive technology. Just see a small stair steps up to say $15 to $16 by fall. I too am long a lot of shares bought at a good price so I intend to hold....very limited downside risk.And like the dividend. In fact without the dividend I would not have bought back in in late November. Somehow I suspect the Jensen just doesn't get it about how to maximize share price, although I know he cares, because it is recognition. But in the last few months it appears that it's become very very personal to him. The change started with the dividend and the share buyback. Also, I have listened to the financial presentation 3 times now for tone rather than specifics. His tone was almost one of "Fxxx you to the analysts". Seemed he was under a lot of stress and very pointed. It showed in his voice. Sometimes almost flippant. Something makes me think that he is going to show all those guys that work for banks as he put it how great an investment in Nvidia is. But I do feel, and see his frustration. I don't know him personnaly but he does seem very bright, analytical, logical, and pugnacious. The emphasize is on the pugnacious. With all of that said I suspect he will do something dramatic to try and get his Baby the recognition it deserves. I'm not being flippant with my comments....Nvidia has all the pieces for a double....in a year. Hope they are using this time to cut the share count 15-20% over the next 2 quarters. They certainly have the capacity to do so. Just an opinion....</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363879514764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363881034363-20</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One last thing - I agree with your assessment of Nvidia's plan to market GRID to small and medium size businesses. A lot of dollars and profits there. But the Enterpirse Grid with IBM, Dell, and HP putting it in their servers is potentially even more lucrative. IT departments around the world will be all over this quickly. longer term - Cloud Gaming could just be "THE NEXT BIG THING" that all the Media are looking for every single day of their broadcasting careers.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363881034363</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:50:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363881364464-21</Id><Topic><Title>Article by Tom Luongo #1</Title><Username>chitownbarber20</Username><Timestamp>1363797053950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does the board pay so much attention to a SA article anyway? - it sure baffled me no end. SA is a trap set up to screuu the retail players, and SA writers earn a few pennies by rehashing known information dumbed down. I doubt serious $$$ ever looked at SA for ideas. Cramer's show at least has contrarian effect, SA has no effect either way.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363881364464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:56:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363882556760-22</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>delano, welcome. "approximate time that we could see some significant pps movement" that is the question isn't it. There are many of us who have been here for YEARS in disbelief about how undervalued this company is. Clearly the street is happy moving the stock 3-4% and scraping profit from day traders at will. If you are a trader, I would say good luck. If you are an investor, put your feet up and don't think about it for a year or three. This company is going to be waaaaay bigger than it is now. A double is a ridiculous goal. Jensen is looking to not only hit the ball out of the park, he's looking to hit the ball into orbit. So sell what ever you're worried about near term. Then park what you can afford to be without for the long term. Market Cap north of $100B is coming.</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1363882556760</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363882992770-23</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can confirm your expectation of small/mid-size businesses going for GRID-like solutions. It's a nightmare to maintain all of those workstations spread across the company. I'm more in IT development business, but expect the graphics business must be basically the same in this aspect since operation guys are always trying hard to centralize stuff due to the ease of maintenance.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1363882992770</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:23:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363883312657-24</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With all of that said I suspect he will do something dramatic to try and get his Baby the recognition it deserves Indeed, he does have a lot of money to do something dramatic. However, if he decides to go for another "Tegra-like adventure", the current margin of safety (primarily based on $6/share) might be gone.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1363883312657</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:28:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363883539422-25</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would seem to targeted at companies that need Quadro level GPUs, and promote BYOD...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363883539422</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:32:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363883574156-26</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Simplify... NVidia is building office space and hiring...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363883574156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363883774849-27</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's see cutting % cash to market cap from 48% to 33% seems plenty to me. Enough for significant share buyback.No I don't see Jensen doing another Tegra Like adventure. In fact I bet he just longing for the day of breakeven in Tegra...perhaps eventually doing a TI like move but who knows. He already is talking about It's not about investing in just Phones. Throwing a $100M or so into an Amazon Cloud Co-Host Gaming service is doable though</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363883774849</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:36:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363884646133-28</Id><Topic><Title>When will Win RT dissappear? Only MSFT knows.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363844184130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 01:36:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both of Microsoft's tablet lines are thoroughly disappointing. Unexpectedly good hardware, undercut by software that doesn't justify the premium price. Microsoft is uniquely able to port Office and Outlook to a new platform. But they don't have the corporate will to change. They must see the crisis. Perhaps they don't believe the world is changing. Or perhaps they all see it, but internal politics keeps them from effectively responding. Right now they have nearly lost the mobile market. Their best play was to leverage their strong advantage on the desktop. They aren't doing that with permanently incomplete versions of their key applications. For the near future WinRT will be just a sideshow. It will still make money for analysts and advertisers, but now that the introductory sales bump has happened, it's not likely to be much additional revenue for hardware ecosystem.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1363884646133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363885447634-29</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be waiting for more great news to come.</Msg><Username>parse1chelsea</Username><Timestamp>1363885447634</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:04:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363886370568-30</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bigger reward will go to the longs who are long enough. NVDA will be a significant player in wide variety of market segments in supercomputer, enterprise server, cloud server, small/medium size business IT server, gamer, tablet and superphone/smartphone. NVDA will soon translate their new products and investment into revenue and earnings. Before WS realized NVDA is real and serious, the long at least could keep collecting the dividen.</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1363886370568</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:19:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363886411475-31</Id><Topic><Title>Project Shield - Moor Insights</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363870258958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:50:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm a gamer - yep at 60 yrs old as well - mostly week nights and competitive team matches on BF3 it wont be a primary platfomr for serious PC gamers, but it wil be bought because they can get mobile around the house for the novelty and get full tablet capabilties . I got an Xbox with a $200 Driving Wheel that collects dust .. so go figure Would I buy Shield and get touch screen tablet to boot? absoutely - can't wait</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1363886411475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:20:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363888847592-32</Id><Topic><Title>Project Shield - Moor Insights</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363870258958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 08:50:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have 2 gamer/college students in my extended family. Both have said, "TAKE MY MONEY!" assuming that PS is priced under $500. They think it will be the greatest thing in dorms and frat houses - may even replace alcohol to some extent. :)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363888847592</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:00:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363890053073-33</Id><Title>Nvidia Grid</Title><Msg>Enterprise - Revenue this quarter - 75 trials VCA - Revenue next quarter - 15 trials Cloud Gaming - Revenue 4Q - 20 trials Not a bad start - I would imagine Enterprise equipment sells for the most</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363890053073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:20:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363891251747-34</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have it already. It's the best.</Msg><Username>scjedadele</Username><Timestamp>1363891251747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363892568554-35</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is great to have a real thread with real conversation..... In a nutshell, my opinion is that the market has been in its "show me, I'm from Missouri" mode for about 2 years with Nvidia, and will continue to be in that mode until they do (show them). Another observation is that the days of small semiconductor companies going on overnight moonshots is pretty much over. It ended more or less with high-frequency-trading which uses PE as part of the equation of trade and with hundreds if not thousands of traders all working the NVidia relative-market-BETA the whole dynamic of sentiment that used to be able to drive a stock up has been neutered. The market might price a semi stock up to a trailing PE of 20 if everything is unbelievably favorable, but there can be no weeds on the highway to do that. I do believe Nvidia could attain the status of a 20 PE stock, but this year will be decisive. There are also a few strategic decisions that the NVidia management has to make. This year is decisive because many investments that have been years in the making are coming to fruition. Tegra and the Icera Modem. The market asks whether Nvidia will be able to meaningfully penetrate the phone market with this? The believers say "yes", the Missorians say "show me". Grid, Shield, VCA and other streaming initiatives. The technologies required to bring streaming to market are almost overwhelming with high barriers to entry and Nvidia deserves buckets of Kudos for the foresight and prowess to develop these, but, the Market observes, there has not been a single dollar generated from this technology across any market....yet. High Performance Computing is something Nvidia, for all intents and purposes, invented. HPC has funded the development (along with core PC graphics) of the Tegra and streaming technologies. The overall concern by many here is whether Intel and Phi will eat NV's lunch as Intel has done with so many other's. The strategic decision...con't</Msg><Username>mv_mngr</Username><Timestamp>1363892568554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363892628134-36</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>con't...... The strategic decision that I am sure Nvidia is always weighing is when will management feel that they can return R&amp;D expenses to a more normal percentage of revenue? Think about where Nvidia was 5 years ago as a pure-play PC graphics card supplier. Integrated graphics was starting. Intel locked Nvidia out of the chip set business, and with the acquisition of ATI by AMD, they (Nvidia) also lost their one other major customer/partner for their core graphics business. Fast forward 5 years to today and in hindsight Nvidia has done nothing short of amazing in re-tooling its business (see decisive product above). The ideal answer is that business results are so good that the investments create their returns on the top-line with commensurate margin dollars so that R&amp;D investment can continue at existing rates but as a lower percentage of reveue. Will this happen? The answer is much the same…..probably from an Nvidia Management perspective, they need to continue their high rate of investment until the returns follow. I doubt in this day and age that there would ever be any comfort in cutting back on R&amp;D and riding for a while. QCOM, INTC, Sammy, AAPL have let it be known their respective intentions. Thank you, if you got this far, in allowing me to share my thoughts as inconclusive as they may seem. --mv</Msg><Username>mv_mngr</Username><Timestamp>1363892628134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:03:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363894010646-37</Id><Title>be realistic. . this isn't a religion</Title><Msg>Nvidia will never move... once you accept it you will move on</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1363894010646</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:26:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363894154626-38</Id><Title>Toms Hardware revisit of Shield ( flattering review)</Title><Msg>tomshardwareDOTcom/news/Project-Shield-Tegra-4-Hands-On-Pricing-Jelly-Bean,21649.html</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1363894154626</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363894728529-39</Id><Title>Honda and Audi show the future of driving at nVIDIA's GTC (GREAT READ)</Title><Msg>SOURCE: CNET cnetDOTcom/8301-13746_7-57575479-48/honda-and-audi-show-the-future-of-driving-at-nvidia-conference/</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363894728529</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:38:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363894838543-40</Id><Title>Tablets to overtake PC's by 2017</Title><Msg>If true, a double edged sword for our friends at NVDA seekingalphaDOTcom/article/1293161-how-microsoft-is-breaking-the-windows-siege?source=yahoo</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1363894838543</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:40:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363894851537-41</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice work.</Msg><Username>melanoxylonfatimah</Username><Timestamp>1363894851537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363894965465-42</Id><Topic><Title>"Nvidia may lose almost eight million processor shipments in 2013"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363734273144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eight MILLION processors GONE Walk About Nvidia fans. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363894965465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:42:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363895249054-43</Id><Topic><Title>Who is Nvidia kidding, they don't have a 64 bit CPU to sell Sony or anyone else</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363288742769</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:19:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That Nvidia talking heads must be brain damaged he can't tell the difference between a WEAK 32 bit Tegra toy and a REAL 64 bit x86 CPU. Do you know the difference 32 bit and 64 bit Nvidia fans? Sony knows the difference between 32 bit and 64 bit and you know it don't you Nvidia fans. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363895249054</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:47:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363895389916-44</Id><Title>So who's adding on the long side?</Title><Msg>Something has to give here, as this stock is just too cheap, given the cash on hand and the huge markets that the company is targeting. Either someone will bid for Nvidia or the market will come to recognize the earnings power that management is building here. The stock has been like a coiled spring for months. Just look at the yearly high and low -- I've never seen it so narrow. I hope kvimax1 is right and this thing explodes up on higher volume. Everyone is frustrated by this valuation. Clearlt Jen is. Must be driving him nuts...</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1363895389916</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:49:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363895409152-45</Id><Topic><Title>Have a new slogan for Nvidia: "Nvidia, Too Busy to WORK for it"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363723267998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:01:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did Nvidia pretend to PASS on Xbox yet? Why not put out a WHINE about the Xbox loss now and get it over with? Anyone here have a clue what they are waiting for this time? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363895409152</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:50:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363895506051-46</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd like to give more time to answer this question or open invitation, but I just don't have a lot of time to fill out a perspective on this investment. My work and other concerns take most of my time these days, though I obviously still read what a I can and point something out where it fits or catches something missing in someone's reference or comments. But I definitely am bullish on Nvidia more than I have been in the past, mainly because I think the company has matured as a company even if it is still viewed as an underdog by many analysts and other prognosticators. The reality is the company has performed remarkably well imo with the fruit of all it's R&amp;D just at the first stage of a perpetual growth cycle to be set forth by 2H of 2013, if not a little sooner. I think we already have indications of some revenue from GRID and other components of that ecosystem Jen likes to describe as a thesis for all the different products coming out now, including SHIELD. And Tegra is also in the early stages as well and is by no means a flop as some recent articles, trying to use the AMD console wins etc, have tried to convey. To build a successful product line and maintain the margins they have maintained all along the development of Tegra as well as their more established graphics business in dGPUs is really quite remarkable. We get cranky or impatient, or actually the analysts more so, when something is not on time or the road map needs to be tweaked as the products are developed and all of sudden it's time to say it's a failure. I think in a few years, this whole process will look quite impressive for what is achieved by this company and some of the comments about the attitude of Nvidia's management being arrogant will not be accurate, more knowing. I think some of the competition looks much more shrill and arrogant in comparison especially considering Nvidia has maintained a solid financial makeup throughout this period of reshaping their future.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1363895506051</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363895540674-47</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the 64 bit 8 CORE CPU+GPU to power the new PS4 Nvidia had to offer Sony?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363367895356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:18:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did Nvidia find their PRETEND 64 bit CPU yet? Anyne hre have a clue? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363895540674</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:52:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363895673440-48</Id><Topic><Title>"Qualcomm to Replace NVIDIA for Google's Next-Gen Nexus 7"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363724734020</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:25:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>REPLACE, did you look up this weeks word Nvidia fans? Get use to that word, REPLACE, we may revisit it later in the year. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363895673440</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:54:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363896636618-49</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My own feeling is that the month of June may see an inflection point for NVDA share prize. By end of June, Project will have shipped according to NV schedule, and by then WS can get a handle on how the new product is received by the targeted consumer group. Additionally, Enterprise Grid could be released in Q2 as it is scheduled to go into production in Q1. Looks like the VCA units will be slightly later - shipping could be expected in Q3 as production is scheduled for Q2. It is not clear if Grid gaming will be available for the holiday season as production is scheduled for Q4, not sooner. And there will be end devices based on Tegra 4, whose release dates are to be decided by the respective OEMs, not NVIDIA. All the above timelines are taken from JH Huang's analysts call on March 19. (slide #26)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363896636618</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:10:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363897055064-50</Id><Topic><Title>Stings doesn't it, all that Jen HOT AIR and the stock DROPS</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363737294870</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:54:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia is not a HOT AIR balloon Jen can't talk it up by filling a room with bad breath. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363897055064</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:17:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363897057542-51</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you know the specifics of the hiring?</Msg><Username>whitesandflow</Username><Timestamp>1363897057542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:17:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363897202544-52</Id><Topic><Title>"Nvidia may lose almost eight million processor shipments in 2013"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363734273144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many GPU parts were loss when the Sony PlayStation business walked out the door into the arms of an Nvidia rival? Anyone here have a clue? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363897202544</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363897547973-53</Id><Title>PlayStation money GONE, Nexus money GONE, $26 per Share LONG GONE</Title><Msg>What will be GONE next Nvidia fans? Not to worry though, Jen's comb over is here to stay for all you Nvidia fans who bought the stock because you like Jen. Jen groupies hug $12.42 then pucker up to blow Jen some more kisses. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363897547973</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:25:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363897560451-54</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia Grid</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363890053073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:20:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nvidia GRID plug-in cards are now available The overall name for Nvidia's cloud-based GPU stuff is "GRID," which includes cloud-based gaming platforms and all sorts of other things beyond desktop virtualization. There's a sub-brand called "VGX" which is the technology that specifically applies to our world of VDI and remote graphics delivery. As you might recall from last year, the way you get this GRID VGX stuff in your VDI environment is (1) you buy a VGX plug-in card for your server that has a bunch of GPU cores on it, and (2) you use a VDI product that supports VGX. This is what's basically new now. When it comes to the plug-in cards, gone are the days when we had to buy consumer gaming class graphics cards at Best Buy to support single users on XenApp. Instead we can buy the a GRID plug in card from Nvidia. They have two models which are both available now: The GRID K1 card is for general purpose VDI sessions. It has four Nvidia Kepler GPUs and 16GB RAM, and Nvidia figures it's good for 100 VDI sessions on the host. The price is about $3400. The GRID K2 card is a special purpose card designed for graphics-intensive environments. It only has 8GB of RAM and two GPUs (instead of four), though they're higher end with a lot more cores than the K1. This card would only be used by a few users at a time and costs $6200. You can buy these cards on their own (I could only find them via IBM today), or you can now spec them to be preinstalled in servers you buy from Dell, HP, or IBM. Source: wwwDOTbrianmaddenDOTcom/blogs/brianmadden/archive/2013/03/21/nvidia-moves-quot-grid-quot-products-to-the-mainstream-introduces-server-appliances-with-gpus-sets-standard-for-vdi-graphics-performance.aspx _____________________________________________________________________________ I verified on the IBM server site that the VGX boards are available now</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363897560451</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:26:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363897901699-55</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should read "price" , not prize. :)</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363897901699</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:31:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363898128058-56</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I did verify that the Nvidia Grid K1 and K2 plug in boards are available on IBM's server site Now $3400 for the K1 and $6400 for the K2. Still looking for the prebuilt server with the hypervisor. IBM were probably the people that installed Applied materials set-up but who knows. It does look like like some revenue from Grid in Q1 will happen.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363898128058</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:35:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363898193560-57</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this the CRY OVER A BAD INVESTMENT thread? Can anyone join in or ONLY thise who PAID OVER $16 for one share of Nvidia? lol Is this fan club cheering or what? "I like the CEO," Are yiou looking for a date or an investment? Anymore FANS here cheering Jen and IGNORING a $12.42 Nvidia that WAS $26? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363898193560</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363898514603-58</Id><Topic><Title>Long term future for NVDA</Title><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1363876798477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whitesandflow, yahoo won't let me reply to you, so hope you see this ? "Do you know the specifics of the hiring?" All R&amp;D... Very Healthy indeed...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363898514603</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363898820527-59</Id><Topic><Title>NVDA Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>monegaljanelle</Username><Timestamp>1363608679374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 08:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have it already. It's the best.</Msg><Username>recolliemillie</Username><Timestamp>1363898820527</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:47:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363898885928-60</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia Grid</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363890053073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:20:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I sell software to the Enterprise I'd be surprised if enterprise is the biggest because Citrix is good enough for most PC apps . You need NVDA Grid only if you have heavy graphics apps ; Engineering , vizualization etc. Cloud Gaming will be 1st and initially largest</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1363898885928</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363898934749-61</Id><Title>If all you want to hear is good News instead of ALL Nvidia News you a fooling yourself</Title><Msg>Reading the Bad News mixed with all that Nvidia love in to the moon nonsense News would have got you out near $26 to regroup and re-enter thet stock for HALF PRICE. Keep believing and signing on to those threads who call EVERYONE with a different view of Nvidia bashers and see where it gets you? If you like $12.42 better $16 then enjoy. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363898934749</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:48:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363899090446-62</Id><Topic><Title>PlayStation money GONE, Nexus money GONE, $26 per Share LONG GONE</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363897547973</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:25:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Playstation: I would rather see Nvidia focus on cloud computing and mobile development rather than consoles Nexus: Disappointing, but Nvidia is diversifying its mobile placement with the 4i, so it won't be leaning entirely on the Nexus like last year.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1363899090446</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363899378043-63</Id><Topic><Title>If all you want to hear is good News instead of ALL Nvidia News you a fooling yourself</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363898934749</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:48:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't want to hear about the Nexus business going to QCOM right? DON'T LIKE IT THEN IGNORE IT You don't want to hear about the PlayStation business going to AMD right? DON'T LIKE IT THEN IGNORE IT Tegra 4 is late and a dud. DON'T LIKE IT THEN IGNORE IT $12.42 DOWN 20 cents? DON'T LIKE IT THEN IGNORE IT imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363899378043</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:56:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363899772671-64</Id><Title>When will tegra be gone. Only Nvda knows.</Title><Msg>Its turning out to be a loss leader for the forseeable future.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363899772671</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363900071497-65</Id><Topic><Title>PlayStation money GONE, Nexus money GONE, $26 per Share LONG GONE</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363897547973</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:25:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One report claims Nexus accounted for 60% of Tegra sales. How is Nvidia going to replace that Nexus money ? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363900071497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363900431456-66</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia Grid</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363890053073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:20:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I sell software to the Enterprise I'd be surprised if enterprise is the biggest because Citrix is good enough for most PC apps . You need NVDA Grid only if you have heavy graphics apps ; Engineering , vizualization etc. Cloud Gaming will be 1st and initially largest" wonder why they are making the K1 card then. It's certified to work with Citrix and VMWare This is the card for up to 100 users. Perhaps Graphics Lite? The K2 card is for heavy graphics and just a few users. Too bad we don't have video of the Applied Materials presentation.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363900431456</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363900642260-67</Id><Topic><Title>"Nvidia may lose almost eight million processor shipments in 2013"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363734273144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nexus was the LARGEST Tegra deal ever and its GONE. Nexus accounted for as much as 60% of Tegra sales by one report and its GONE. And almost every Nvidia pumper posting has every post about the news of QCOM taking Nvidia's Nexus job on IGNORE. Now say it ain't so. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363900642260</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:17:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363901382655-68</Id><Topic><Title>When will tegra be gone. Only Nvda knows.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363899772671</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAM</Msg><Username>ltenow</Username><Timestamp>1363901382655</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:29:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363901495560-69</Id><Topic><Title>PlayStation money GONE, Nexus money GONE, $26 per Share LONG GONE</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363897547973</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:25:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Within this year, probably more tablets, and I know there is know definite way of knowing since T4 isn't in production yet, and management won't announce any design wins ahead of time. I will gladly take that hit though, especially if it helped get the T4i ahead of schedule like management said. T4i basically opens up the entire smartphone market up to Nvidia, which it was lacking due to radio integration, and given its performance and the T4 performance when compared to its competitors, I expect it to be a worthwhile investment. Relying on one product for 60% of Tegra sales is not good, especially given how Google likes to rotate through hardware suppliers. It would have been nice to somehow hold onto the next Nexus 7, but I will gladly have it replaced with a much more diversified mobile portfolio.</Msg><Username>lrkbik4</Username><Timestamp>1363901495560</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:31:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363901986269-70</Id><Title>Now I understand What That dongle will be on Project Shield</Title><Msg>Miracast support for NVIDIA Tegra 4-powered devices will be available in Q2 2013 Matt Wuebbling, Director, Tegra Product Marketing, NVIDIA "Pairing NVIDIA Tegra processors with Broadcom's leading wireless solutions will allow consumers to share photos, stream HD movies and play amazing games on the big screen seamlessly. We've worked closely with Broadcom to bring this groundbreaking wireless display technology to market."</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363901986269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:39:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363904033675-71</Id><Title>Read the NASDAQ "Article"</Title><Msg>I suggest reading the article posted by NASDAQ. The article is poorly written and has errors. It notes that upcoming HP Tegra 4 tablet is rumor and notes that instead they will be using an ARM processor in the near term. Huh? I think someone who doesn't know the industry is just spinning what they've heard and misheard into an article. It would be nice for Google to just annouce something and get these silly speculations out of the way.</Msg><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1363904033675</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363906157242-72</Id><Topic><Title>Read the NASDAQ "Article"</Title><Username>panacro</Username><Timestamp>1363904033675</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:13:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is also out on the net claiming Digitimes as the source that AMD is prepping a whopping price cut on all their AMUs. Another says Intel is considering closing 1 of their Portland advanced fabs. It's endless....but certainly everything on the Web is true because it has to be. Right?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363906157242</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:49:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363908569273-73</Id><Title>Best buy has an Asus Win RT tablet for $599, and a Win 8 tablet for $499.</Title><Msg>Give me one good reason to buy a Win RT tablet.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363908569273</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:29:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363908788026-74</Id><Title>No news of any tegra4 designs. For that matter, No news of tegra4 either</Title><Msg>Is the Power hog chip delayed?</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363908788026</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:33:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363914068079-75</Id><Title>Samsung Galaxy S4: the S600 variant mostly in major markets, Exynos 5 Octa model in fewer regions, mostly emerging countries</Title><Msg>Web chatter agrees that there are issues with Exynos 5 Octa to have led to this distribution patter. Among the problems: --Thermal issue. The Exynos 5 Octa processor in S4 to be shipped has been down-clocked to 1.5 GHz from a previously claimed 2.3 GHz at max HD resolution. --Availability is a serious problem. Samsung's 28nm process has YET to achieve acceptable yields. One article cited that volume production of Exynos Octa won't start until Q2.....Sammy jumped the gun anyway. --It is significantly more expensive to make Exynos 5 Octa than Snapdragon S600. This conclusion was reached by iSuppli as of a couple of days ago. Here are the regional distributions: ""So, the countries who will be receiving the Galaxy S4 powered by the Qualcomm Snapdragon 600 are: Austria, Baltic nations, Belgium, Bosnia and Herzegovina, Bulgaria, Cyprus, Czech Republic, France, Germany, Greece, Italy, Luxemburg, Macedonia, Nordic countries, Poland, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Switzerland, The Netherlands, United Kingdom, Hong Kong, Korea, Malaysia, Philippines, Saudi Arabia, Singapore, United Arab Emirates, and Australia. It seems that some of the above mentioned countries will receive both versions of Galaxy S4 namely Italy, France, UAE, Germany, Korea, the Philippines, Poland, Saudi Arabia, Malaysia, Hong Kong, and the UK. On the other hand, the countries where only the Exynos Samsung Galaxy S4 will be shipped are: Russia, Ukraine, Afghanistan, Algeria, Egypt, Kenya, Libya, Morocco, Nigeria, Bangladesh, China, India, Indonesia, Iran, Iraq, Kazahstan, Nepal, Pakistan, Sri Lanka, Taiwan, Thailand, Turkey, Uzbekistan, Vietnam, and Romania."" androidDOTgs/samsung-galaxy-s4-availability/</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363914068079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 21:01:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363918269824-76</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung Galaxy S4: the S600 variant mostly in major markets, Exynos 5 Octa model in fewer regions, mostly emerging countries</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363914068079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 21:01:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good find! I am totally unsurprised with all the issues. One thing nobody mentioned - which is HUGE! Normally people in the semiconductor business would only ship it to third world unknown markets when they know there are problems - especially reliability related issues - where it can potentially "die" in a year or two or less. They would normally not put their name on it if they can and sell it at a discount. Sammie may have "jumped" the gun and ran a ton of products and found that it's questionable reliability and lot dependent etc etc - instead of taking a huge write off - they'll deal with the fall out one at a time and hope most of them would last beyond the warranty time. I am not sure if any of you are aware - Samsung had a similar issue a couple of years back with their expensive LCD TVs where they were "died" between 12 months and 18 months right after warrantee - I had two friends that it happened to - one of them thrashed it after battling them - the other got a fix after painfully battlingthem. There was talk of class action but I didn't follow it. The reason they died was they used lower rated or lower quality electrolytic capacitors all over the TV board.... I checked - there was a class action and Sammie lost as of ~ April last year - they had to pay $650 to the lucky few who bothered to participate in the BS paperwork #$%$ the trial lawyers sent out. Well if it's in the 3rd world - no class action no problemo. Of course this is pur speculation - Samsung has a very good reputation when it comes to these kind of stuff like the class action mentioned.</Msg><Username>anvda20</Username><Timestamp>1363918269824</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 22:11:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363918370447-77</Id><Title>Europe weights Apple sale deals with carriers for anti-trust abuse</Title><Msg>New York Times nytimesDOTcom/2013/03/22/business/global/iphone-contracts-with-carriers-under-scrutiny-in-europe.html?_r=0</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363918370447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 22:12:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363919568340-78</Id><Title>Jensen On Nvidia Grid and Project Shield Revenue and Profitability</Title><Msg>from the Investor Presentation: Enterprise Grid and Nvidia Grid VCA will both meaningfully contribute this year margins in high 50's to 60%. Plus ongoing license revenue. Very confident based on partners IBM, Cisco, HP, and Dell feedback and number of trials and installs taking place right now. Plus the major VAR seller of VCA comments and number on trials in progress. Other VARS adding on for training. Project Shield will meaningfully contribute this year...but not sure of amount? but it will be profitable. Expects 30%+ margins for Nvidia because Retailer will expect 30% margin Really downplayed phones throughout the presentation waiting for Tegra 4i. Tegra in other new type devices this year -------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- That means if the Project Shield sells for $300 profit would $90 each. Hope they are working the costs down.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1363919568340</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 22:32:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363919841450-79</Id><Topic><Title>"Qualcomm to Replace NVIDIA for Google's Next-Gen Nexus 7"</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363724734020</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:25:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Qualcomm (NASDAQ: QCOM ) could be on the cusp of securing an order for several million additional processors. According to DigiTimes" That Nexus job represented 60% of Tegra sales leaving Nvidia scrambling to find a replacement job to replace that revenue. Replacing Nexus money is going to be a hard task with Tegra 4 being a dud. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1363919841450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 22:37:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363920873830-80</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung Galaxy S4: the S600 variant mostly in major markets, Exynos 5 Octa model in fewer regions, mostly emerging countries</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363914068079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 21:01:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, once Samsung is willing to admit that its way behind in the app processor/baseband space, and so is QC in a couple of years, it will become a NVIDIA customer again, JH Huang has said over again that the real competition is QC, and no one else on the horizon. IN this market, there are no permanent friends, nor permanent enemies. Hopefully, Sammy, Apple will all come aroundl.....and before you throw me a dagger, please note that I am not offering a set timeframe....nobody knows for sure.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363920873830</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 22:54:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363921666940-81</Id><Title>ARM to help second-tier IC designers to catch up, DigiTimes reports</Title><Msg>Yahoo News Fri, Mar 15, 2013 7:17 AM EDT ARM Holdings (ARMH) is considering plans to provide complete platform solutions to help second-tier IC design houses catchup with Qualcom (QCOM) and Nvidia (NVDA) in 2013, reports DigiTimes. According to Taiwan-based chipmakers, the strategy would also help the company to better defend against its competitors. The only way Arm can compete with Intel is to try to reduce cost. How cheap can Nvidia make a Tegra?</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1363921666940</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363922291058-82</Id><Topic><Title>ARM to help second-tier IC designers to catch up, DigiTimes reports</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1363921666940</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:07:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM needs help itself. ITs big.LITTLE architecture is not validated by Samsung; its graphic chips - the Mali T6xx series, was recently abandoned by Samsung, and there is NO ONE else adopting it. ÅRM should/could continue to go the way of commodity low-powered chips, as it's been doing with reasonable success. It hasn't shown the ability of springing off and leading the pack in SoCs.</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363922291058</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:18:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>