<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-08"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357621506736-1</Id><Title>QCOM launches DELL/HP WinRT tablets at CES 2013</Title><Msg>a few months later after Surface RT? QCOM CEO didn't have guts to release WinRT tablets powered by QCOM DOA snapdragon and asked Ballmer to help. QCOM is eat the dusts at CES. A truly best visionary. lol</Msg><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1357621506736</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:05:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357622002556-2</Id><Topic><Title>QCOM launches DELL/HP WinRT tablets at CES 2013</Title><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1357621506736</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:05:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>QCOM is eat the dusts at CES. A truly best visionary. lol</Msg><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1357622002556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:13:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357622033827-3</Id><Topic><Title>Received a heads up: several Tegra 4 based tablets will be released SOON after HTC launches its smartphone</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357618084654</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 23:08:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think they just showed two tablets with Windows RT at the opening tonight, but don't know the actual launch dates.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1357622033827</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:13:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357622348406-4</Id><Topic><Title>QCOM launches DELL/HP WinRT tablets at CES 2013</Title><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1357621506736</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:05:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>marketwatchDOTcom/story/qualcomm-kicks-off-ces-with-snapdragon-2013-01-07?siteid=yhoof2 Look at his disappointed face and empty hands. lol.</Msg><Username>best_ivideo</Username><Timestamp>1357622348406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:19:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357622539396-5</Id><Topic><Title>Received a heads up: several Tegra 4 based tablets will be released SOON after HTC launches its smartphone</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357618084654</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 23:08:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you can get this translated or another source that would be great. Couldn't figure it out.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1357622539396</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:22:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357622905079-6</Id><Topic><Title>Received a heads up: several Tegra 4 based tablets will be released SOON after HTC launches its smartphone</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357618084654</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 23:08:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I tried that, it was a general front page and it didn't pickup much of the text.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1357622905079</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:28:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357624565587-7</Id><Title>Apple's App Store : Now 775,000 apps and Forty Billion downloads.</Title><Msg>Apple's App Store reaches 40B downloads, almost half occurred in 2012 By AppleInsider Staff | Monday, January 07, 2013, 08:37 am Apple on Monday announced that more than 40 billion applications have been downloaded from the iOS App Store, with nearly 20 billion of those in 2012 alone. There are more than 500 million active accounts on the App Store, and those users helped to drive a record breaking December in which more than 2 billion applications were downloaded. There are now more than 775,000 applications for the iPhone, iPad and iPod touch, and developers have been paid more than $7 billion to date. "It has been an incredible year for the iOS developer community," said Eddy Cue, Apple’s senior vice president of Internet Software and Services. "Developers have made over seven billion dollars on the App Store, and we continue to invest in providing them with the best ecosystem so they can create the most innovative apps in the world." The press release issued by Apple on Monday comes as the annual Consumer Electronics Show gets underway. CES is the biggest tradeshow in the electronics industry, but Apple does not participate. The company used the opportunity to highlight a handful of apps on Monday that have found success among the hundreds of thousands of options on the App Store. Those mentioned include: • Temple Run, which was downloaded 75 million times. • DragonVale and Clash of Clans from developer Supercell, which earned more than $100 million. • Uber, a travel application. • Flipboard, a personalized social news reader. • Hotel Tonight, for finding last-minute deals on hotels. • Airbnb, which finds people who have space for rent. Among the 775,000 applications on the App Store, more than 300,000 are native to the iPad. The App Store is available in 155 countries, and options on the store fall under 23 categories." Twenty Billion (20,000,000,000) apps, boys. Were downloaded from the Genuine Apple App Store. During just the 12 months of 2012. That's what -- One Point Six Billion apps (1,600,000,000) PER MONTH! Another way to look at it is Apple apps per human on Earth. The world's population is 6,973,738,443 And Apple sold 20 Billion apps from their Genuine Apple App Store last year. So that's 2.9 apps PER PERSON ON THE PLANET. In just one year. Separately, so how's Jen's little GlowBall game doing lately? Ha ha ha ha!</Msg><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1357624565587</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:56:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357624885383-8</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's App Store : Now 775,000 apps and Forty Billion downloads.</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1357624565587</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:56:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All that creative energy in the world.. and you just sit an harass an anonymous message board..</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1357624885383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 01:01:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357625094976-9</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Steals Throne from Android : Number One in U.S.A.</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1357588605634</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:56:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The Genuine Apple iOS increased from 35.8% to 53.3% market share." That's a Massively Huge shift in market share, Best. In just 12 months. Massively Huge.</Msg><Username>the_best_always_wins</Username><Timestamp>1357625094976</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 01:04:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357625840738-10</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's App Store : Now 775,000 apps and Forty Billion downloads.</Title><Username>i_read_best</Username><Timestamp>1357624565587</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:56:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better than wasting your time being threatening, abusive, or otherwise objectionable. HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA!!!! The First Deletion of the New Year -- and it's only the 7th day of January!</Msg><Username>best.here</Username><Timestamp>1357625840738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 01:17:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357625931180-11</Id><Topic><Title>The Trend Setting Websites Say Epic Fail for The Shield</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357610367690</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 20:59:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Websites? Forget about websites, what did the market action tell you? Down how much on that SHIELD toy news? The MARKET said Nvidia is going down a dead end road. You Nvidia fans are so funny. Yesterday YOU NEVER HEARD OF NVIDIA'S SHIELD JUNK and today SHIELD will drive Nvidia back to your break even point. lol $26, $25, ..., $16, $12 what? Wake up Sony, Microsoft and Nitendo will clean Nvidia's clock. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1357625931180</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 01:18:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357626184840-12</Id><Topic><Title>Little guys selling....</Title><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1272554019000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2010-04-29 11:13:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CAUTION: Buying in at $16.01 can cause PANIC PUMPING on message boards on DOWN days. Don't let the $16.01 bargain basement price trap happen to you. lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1357626184840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 01:23:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357626552409-13</Id><Title>So is Nvidia in the condom business now with that SHIELD junk?</Title><Msg>Didn't Trojan claim that SHIELD name? lol If you Nvidia fans had a shield over your wallet when you jumped on that $16 and UP Nvidia bargain you wouldn't be in this mess. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1357626552409</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 01:29:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>18</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357626736404-14</Id><Topic><Title>Received a heads up: several Tegra 4 based tablets will be released SOON after HTC launches its smartphone</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357618084654</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 23:08:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's a lot of buzz about HTC putting out several tablets going back a couple of months and there was an assumption that at least one of them would use Qualcomm's chips but it's clear that HTC had been moving away from their dependency on Qualcomm. I did read that the two RT tablets announced by Qualcomm tonight are the dual core Krait chips, not quad core. So maybe Tegra 4 being out first has given further incentive for HTC to use Tegra 4 to get the tablets out sooner, RT or Android based.</Msg><Username>roundhouse_c</Username><Timestamp>1357626736404</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 01:32:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357630135698-15</Id><Topic><Title>Project shield estimated cost $79-99</Title><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357603949787</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:12:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have removed that $79-99 price quote now as it was probably not realistic. PS Vita has only sold about 3m in a year so your 10s of millions is not a realistic aspiration. enDOTwikipediaDOTorg/wiki/PlayStation_Vita#Sales</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357630135698</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 02:28:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357632717155-16</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA discussing Project Shield's business model (on morning after)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357614214146</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:03:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think it's a good idea too and I have not been known to be a Nvidia fanboi ;-). A kid could buy just this and use it as his TV console as well as a standalone HD portable console. Free/cheap games through TegraZone means the usual expense of console gaming is alleviated. The hardware is just powerful enough not to be disgraced with the new AMD consoles coming. I can't really see anything preventing this becoming Nvidia's cheap successful Playstation/Xbox substitute, should be a sales winner ... for a change ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357632717155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 03:11:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357647854501-17</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA discussing Project Shield's business model (on morning after)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357614214146</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:03:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the original and final question remains: without aapl, sammie, amzn, where can nvda nickel and dime enough accessible TAM to come close to coming out even when the Tegra program needs ¨ $1.3B sales a year to break. Jen still has not come up with an answer on that one.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1357647854501</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 07:24:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357653292476-18</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA discussing Project Shield's business model (on morning after)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357614214146</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:03:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The original and final question remains: Without aapl, sammie or amzn, where can nvda nickel and dime enough accessible TAM to come close to coming out even -- when the Tegra program needs $1.3B in sales per year just to break even. Jen still has not come up with an answer on that one", writes whosunw, the billion dollar question-asker girl. With Jen's folly -- the Elephantine tegra project -- losing One Third of a Billion Dollars per year, his break even point will continue to grow. And grow and grow and grow. Until it's mathematically Impossible to break even without the volume of aapl, sammie or amzn. Impossible. He might be at that point already. So Jen's Elephantine tegra project will continue to burn cash until the owners of the company -- you -- get angry about feeding your cash to the tegra. And when enough nvda owners are yelling "Kill the Tegra", "Kill the Tegra" -- both Jen and his mathematically impossible Tegra folly will be gone. Pink slipped. Terminus. Finis. With hopefully enough time and cash left for the new guy to go into the straight licensing of nvidia's graphics core designs to others. Gold, tea, swimmin' pools, movie stars -- ARM and Qualcomm style.</Msg><Username>frankenbest</Username><Timestamp>1357653292476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 08:54:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357654022149-19</Id><Title>un or down for nvda today???</Title><Msg>any ideas??</Msg><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1357654022149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 09:07:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357654320432-20</Id><Topic><Title>un or down for nvda today???</Title><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1357654022149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 09:07:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it is still building momentum, down 30 cents or up 3 dollars and favor up, pick you side, lol</Msg><Username>guy_8619</Username><Timestamp>1357654320432</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 09:12:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357655096956-21</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA discussing Project Shield's business model (on morning after)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357614214146</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:03:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Master? After Jen and his cash burning tegra folly have been pink slipped, and are terminus and finis -- will the new guy give a graphics licensing price break to Intel? Since they make One Million processor chips Per Day, and represent over 90% of the global PC processor business. And will we see genuine movie stars at future nvidia CES events? Heidi Klum with those angel wings would be nice.</Msg><Username>best.clone185</Username><Timestamp>1357655096956</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 09:24:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357655101925-22</Id><Topic><Title>Once again, the Project Shield specs at a glance</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357619069853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 23:24:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See shieldDOTnvidiaDOTcom</Msg><Username>frankduxbusborg</Username><Timestamp>1357655101925</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 09:25:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357655571036-23</Id><Topic><Title>un or down for nvda today???</Title><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1357654022149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 09:07:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh well tried to go upin first 30 seconds.... timber!!!!</Msg><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1357655571036</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 09:32:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357656333258-24</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA discussing Project Shield's business model (on morning after)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357614214146</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:03:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One thing you have to admit - they got big balls But after thinking about this over night- it became clear that a big driver today is vertical integration which allows a firm to control the user experince ala Apple. We've seen Google move to it, by doing the Nexus line, and Mcrosoft with the surface So while this trend led me to believe that either Microsoft or Googel would snap up NVDA, I admit i didnt expect Nvidia to act first But it makes sense. They have everything they need to expolit a gaming device - arguably more expertise and capability than anyone else. The console business model is head for extinction and nvidia is poking at its soft underbelly. I always thought gaming was going to be a big driver in mobile device differentiation because entertainment value is very high with tablets. Of course we'll have to wait and see if Nvidia can be successful with it, but I'm going to give them a shot and stay long. For one thing they don't have any direct competition, they are most loved by PC gamers - these are folks that dont rely on Mommy and Daddy for their gear - that resent the "lock-in" and razor blade business model. The redefintion of console gaming is refreshing and may catch on in a world of increasing Android dominance. Goog is going to love it, Microsoft will be terrified of it, Apple will dismiss it as being too niche If Nvidia is successful, its brand will slowly emerge from being hidden inside the PC case or listed as a specification , to being prominent on the coffee table - and that Brand recogntion is always a good thing</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1357656333258</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 09:45:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357658242236-25</Id><Topic><Title>(((AMD lands the new Wii, SP4 &amp; Xbox)))</Title><Username>keeperoftheq</Username><Timestamp>1357148663090</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:44:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another up day.</Msg><Username>yuorbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1357658242236</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:17:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357658284990-26</Id><Topic><Title>((((January and April calls say AMD 40% upside)))</Title><Username>keeperoftheq</Username><Timestamp>1356041634269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 17:13:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another up day.</Msg><Username>yuorbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1357658284990</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:18:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357658318792-27</Id><Topic><Title>(((AMD is a better investment than Intel or Nvidia)))</Title><Username>keeperoftheq</Username><Timestamp>1356041521016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 17:12:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another up day.</Msg><Username>yuorbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1357658318792</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:18:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357658345388-28</Id><Topic><Title>Will Nvidia do a double?</Title><Username>keeperoftheq</Username><Timestamp>1357163246704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:47:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another up day.</Msg><Username>yuorbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1357658345388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:19:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357658371193-29</Id><Topic><Title>(((MANY EXAMPLES WHERE AMD HIT LOWS AND RALLIED 224% - 509%)))</Title><Username>swims48184</Username><Timestamp>1356326329934</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 00:18:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another up day.</Msg><Username>amdisshyp</Username><Timestamp>1357658371193</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:19:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357658438526-30</Id><Title>AMD up over 50% from November lows</Title><Msg>AMD is up again today.</Msg><Username>yuorbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1357658438526</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:20:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357658849564-31</Id><Topic><Title>NVIDIA discussing Project Shield's business model (on morning after)</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357614214146</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:03:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your dream, it was a nightmare, yes? Microsoft is Not about mobile games They write productive software Google is Not about mobile games If folks are playing games, they're not causing Google search words to be purchased So neither have any interest in Jen's desperate toy business And when Mommy and Daddy don't buy Jen's toys, then what? Finis</Msg><Username>fumbe.bapoto</Username><Timestamp>1357658849564</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:27:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357660734973-32</Id><Title>The mojo seems all but gone now...</Title><Msg>What a difference a week makes! NVDA shares looked poised for a breakout last Friday... Now they're stuck in the mud again... Geez...</Msg><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1357660734973</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:58:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357660910562-33</Id><Topic><Title>Project shield estimated cost $79-99</Title><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357603949787</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:12:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a fake facebook page.</Msg><Username>a1nvestor</Username><Timestamp>1357660910562</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:01:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357661044974-34</Id><Topic><Title>The mojo seems all but gone now...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1357660734973</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:58:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CES Press Event... No display of Tegra 4 being in any customers' devices... It's late...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357661044974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:04:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357661173510-35</Id><Topic><Title>The mojo seems all but gone now...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1357660734973</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:58:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was suprised at the runup to show so missed it. Now it's sell the [as you rightfully point out disappointing] news.</Msg><Username>nvda_4_ever</Username><Timestamp>1357661173510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:06:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357661351056-36</Id><Topic><Title>Project shield estimated cost $79-99</Title><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357603949787</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:12:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not an official Nvidia facebook page.</Msg><Username>a1nvestor</Username><Timestamp>1357661351056</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:09:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357663070603-37</Id><Topic><Title>Project shield estimated cost $79-99</Title><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357603949787</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:12:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No doubt the $199 tablet came from NVidia putting together Shield... Note: Shield also has just a 5" screen... The best news is an NVidia branded product... Also a boost for Android games</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357663070603</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:37:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357663597934-38</Id><Title>Serious Dip Buyers</Title><Msg>Some Nice volume for dip buyers here... something to pay attention too</Msg><Username>marvin2357</Username><Timestamp>1357663597934</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:46:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357663847602-39</Id><Title>DOWN 3% Mon and DOWN 2% Tues is that the SHIELD effect kicking in?</Title><Msg>Was Nvidia's plan to #$%$ 5% back from shareholders when they named that SHIELD toy like a new condom brand? Anyone have a clue? Maybe someone over at Nvidia headquarters got upset that PS4, XBox and WII all seem to have passed on anything Nvidia so Nvidia decided to play with itself? Nvidia "don't need no stinking" XBox, PS4 or WII business right? lol imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1357663847602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:50:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357664171469-40</Id><Topic><Title>The mojo seems all but gone now...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1357660734973</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:58:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I remember last yr's T3 phone showed at CES that did not come out till end of Nov/dec. This time, nothing nada shown. Now you want T4 revenue when? How low will Tegra revenue drop until T4 starts to ramp? any guesses? can it stay above $100/Q? $240M sales to lose $40, $100M sales will lose how much? Regardless of technical merits of the announcements, the books just can't be squared without any contributions from aapl, sammie, nor amzn.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1357664171469</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:56:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357665485100-41</Id><Topic><Title>The mojo seems all but gone now...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1357660734973</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:58:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Almost all tech stocks are in the red today. I'm not too concerned. By all accounts, Tegra 4 is a success. That is definately positive news for NVDA. Shield is still a big question mark. I think it will be popular with hard core gamers, but depending on the retail price, it will be a hit or miss. If they can get it under $100, which they say they can do, I could see alot of these being bought for even the casual gamers, especially as gifts around the holidays. Personally, I like the idea of Project Shield. NVDA knows games better than almost anyone. Their GPUs are the best in the business, far better than AMD, so if they can bring their graphics experience to the gaming world, Shield will be a game changer. I'm still optimistic for the company, especially with the good reviews of Tegra 4. I'm holding for now. I expect an upward trend in the future, but until earnings, we might be in for a bit of uncertainty while the market corrects from a massive gain over the underwhelming "fiscal cliff' deal.</Msg><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1357665485100</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 12:18:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357666223025-42</Id><Topic><Title>The mojo seems all but gone now...</Title><Username>mslans</Username><Timestamp>1357660734973</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:58:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"T4 starts to ramp?" Depends how long it takes for bringup of the Icera part... RT devices will ramp relatively quick as MS takes the restrictions off... "Regardless of technical merits of the announcements, the books just can't be squared without any contributions from aapl, sammie, nor amzn." Interesting your companies all have their own user devices.. NVidia just launched their own user device And that is just the start... Do you think RT sales for 2013 will be lower than 2012... Do you think Android sales for 2013 will be lower than 2012... How about Shield sales...NVidia gets a higher dollar for the whole system not just T4 Plus Shield will give NVidia more public view... Now help yourself to another serving of crow... LMAO !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357666223025</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 12:30:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357671091668-43</Id><Topic><Title>(((AMD lands the new Wii, SP4 &amp; Xbox)))</Title><Username>keeperoftheq</Username><Timestamp>1357148663090</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:44:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WII, PS4 and XBox say hello to the Nvidia SHIELD toy. lol Who needs PS4 when you have POShield? imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1357671091668</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:51:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357671135154-44</Id><Topic><Title>Android Central: Hands on with Project Shield ("it's just friggin" cool!")</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357668290634</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:04:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More reviews are coming in and seem to all be very positive despite initial first impressions. Too bad that sub 100 price target was wrong. gamespotDOTcom/project-shield/videos/nvidia-unveils-portable-android-powered-console-6402066/?contsessid=1e75980d1411de2eda0940acfcc81369&amp;prevBounce=6402093</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357671135154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:52:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357674250264-45</Id><Topic><Title>P. Moorhead: NVIDIA's Project Shield connects disparate gaming worlds</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357673645425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:34:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The wireless streaming feature is a distinct point of differentiation for both mobile gaming devices as well smart tv set top boxes. I need one now!</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357674250264</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:44:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357674339492-46</Id><Topic><Title>DOWN 3% Mon and DOWN 2% Tues is that the SHIELD effect kicking in?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1357663847602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:50:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A cool device that won't sell. Market has too many players already AND the market is shrinking. NVDA just doesn't have enough IP to move the needle in any direction. Time to sell to INTC. Descrete GPU is dying and mobile CPU is a low-margin crowded space.</Msg><Username>sebanker123</Username><Timestamp>1357674339492</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:45:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357674350540-47</Id><Title>Nvidia seen leading in tablets</Title><Msg>SAN JOSE, Calif. – Revenue for mobile applications processors grew at a whopping 77 percent for tablets and 58 percent for smartphones in the third quarter of 2012, according to reports from Strategy Analytics. Nvidia held its lead in non-iPad tablets, taking a third of the sector and 17 percent of the overall tablet processor market. Apple still dominates with its A-series chips in 53 percent of all tablets, given the iPad’s success. Overall $900 million in integrated tablet processors sold in the quarter, up 77 percent from the same quarter in 2011, said the market watcher in its tablet report that tracks chips from 13 vendors. Only one percent of the tablet chips included basebands, limiting design wins for integrated parts from Broadcom, Mediatek and Qualcomm, the market watcher said. Design wins in the Google Nexus 10 and Microsoft Surface propelled Nvidia ahead of rivals Texas Instruments, Qualcomm and Samsung. “Nvidia is well-positioned to maintain its share in non-iPad tablets in the next few quarters,” said Sravan Kundojjala, a senior analyst at Strategy Analytics.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357674350540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:45:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357674589519-48</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia seen leading in tablets</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357674350540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:45:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Design wins in the Google Nexus 10 ..." High profile analyst from a dirty hole in Bagalore?</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1357674589519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:49:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357674660199-49</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia seen leading in tablets</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357674350540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:45:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>weak... is a typo all you got...??</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357674660199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:51:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357674863133-50</Id><Topic><Title>Gamers seem excited...especially about Project Shield's battery life</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357624826894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 01:00:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I went through a couple of local gamers forums and the general impression is mixed. Some find it useless, others are excited. The second group prevails a little bit. Just my impression though.</Msg><Username>sisula3</Username><Timestamp>1357674863133</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:54:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357675085374-51</Id><Topic><Title>Gamers seem excited...especially about Project Shield's battery life</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357624826894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 01:00:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Some find it useless, others are excited. The second group prevails a little bit. " The second group is a younger crowd... NOT represented on this board... Always new kids... always new gamers This device is for them... it will sell...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357675085374</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:58:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357675195050-52</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia seen leading in tablets</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357674350540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:45:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't you mean Bangalore?</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357675195050</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:59:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357675660578-53</Id><Topic><Title>Android Central: Hands on with Project Shield ("it's just friggin" cool!")</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357668290634</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:04:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Too bad that sub 100 price target was wrong.' Why ? You don't want to give it away. This is a chance for Nvidia to make some serious profit on its own consumer device and it should be aiming for at least $50 profit per unit. The PS Vita sells for over $200. All Shield has to do is undercut by say 10-15% and it should take off. Just 2m units at $50 profit is $100m which would cut some of CPB's losses. I suspect this a 4-5m annual unit product which with high profit margin could help turn CPB profitable.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357675660578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:07:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357675814608-54</Id><Title>Retail investors always get it wrong</Title><Msg>Hype is only thing left</Msg><Username>toddboehmer</Username><Timestamp>1357675814608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:10:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357676597389-55</Id><Topic><Title>Android Central: Hands on with Project Shield ("it's just friggin" cool!")</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357668290634</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:04:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with that somewhat and see your point but I think creating less of a purchase barrier has it's advantages. Considering the features it would appeal to the casual gamer who also wants a set top device (which may not be the market they are seeking to hit) and a lower price point it would be a "accessory" to the hardcore gamer who might otherwise dismiss it. This would also make the upgrade cycle much less painful if they were to upgrade it every couple of years. The other thing selling in larger masses does is allows them to increase the EOS in the production of tegra processors resulting in greater gross margins. This is all conjecture as I don't know where the optimum price point for either the tegra or will it will be for the shield. Just my .02 if its worth even that.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357676597389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:23:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357677161668-56</Id><Title>filled all gaps, now lets hold it</Title><Msg>also, we need some more positive articles,,,,LOL</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1357677161668</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:32:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357677228339-57</Id><Title>Picture the shield. Now picture a Microsoft logo on it!</Title><Msg>Or a Sony logo. Now what kind of value do you place on this announcement?</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1357677228339</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:33:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357677791768-58</Id><Topic><Title>DOWN 3% Mon and DOWN 2% Tues is that the SHIELD effect kicking in?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1357663847602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:50:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess all chip makers, console makers and other commodity centric tech companies should just fold then? BTW it's discrete not descrete.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357677791768</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:43:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357678515977-59</Id><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Msg>From the peanut gallery, since I don't have a dog in this fight anymore (not that I condone dog fighting) I am surprised that NVDA is not down even more. CES presentation was a disaster, before longs rant - process what I am saying - we all understand that market has a negative view on PCs. Yet Nvidia spent a lot of time on PC gaming and its "investments" in this particular field. - Every time Jen referred to his kids ideas as motivation for a new product - it sent a chill down my spine. It reminded me why this company does not have a CFO after 2 years. No respectable CFO would allow expenses without any regard of returns. - Icera 500 is vaporware. if Nvidia had any ongoing customer relationship - they would have touted the heck out of it. This product was mentioned only in passing. "We expect to start sampling chips to customer later this month" - absolute rubbish. Its pure marketing speak for - don't expect anything any time soon. - this morning, Nvidia announced at JP Morgan that "Grey" revenue is expected in FY 2014. Wow! lets all wait for that then. - Project Shield, #$%$ - see above for no CFO comment and responsible investments. Does anyone know the cost of marketing a consumer product? - yeah! well thought through I say. In some ways, I don't fault Nvidia for trying to something that emphasis their core competency - graphics allegedly. They should stick with HDR etc. and not these money losing effort. - and now we come to the grand finale, Tegra 4. The much anticipated launch without any dates or, products (ok Vizio would not commit to bringing their tablet to market). Tegra 4 is a hog and already yesterday's news after Qualcomm and Intel news. Worse, market is already reacting to news regarding heatsink on Project Shield. Tegra 4 was not even designed with unified shaders (kepler) - so good luck convincing market that they are indeed better than anything available today. Let alone next-gen products from Apple, Samsung, Qualcomm etc. This is preliminary but google "glbenchmark tegra soc 114" - results have leaked and you will see that it doesn't even compare to Apple Ipad 4. What Jen tried to pull as a web browser performance test at CES was an atrocity and a slap on the face of any objective observer. They used Chome on Samsung vs. stock development browser - no match. Good luck longs - its going to be a long haul.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357678886158-60</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good bye.. don't come back...</Msg><Username>fdigiovanni01</Username><Timestamp>1357678886158</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:01:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357679843010-61</Id><Topic><Title>Picture the shield. Now picture a Microsoft logo on it!</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1357677228339</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:33:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You means they could port Windows 8 to it as well ? But why did they go with Andorid? Gosh, Nvidia is creating problems for everyone except GOOG . Maybe GOOG could use needs a nice chip company to help its tablet and its MOTO phone business and drive Android into the home - whats next ? aTegra set top box and /or TV ? Oh no!</Msg><Username>livinlifeveryday</Username><Timestamp>1357679843010</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:17:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357680205937-62</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>O your bitterness is showing. You along with several others emphatically claimed/trumpted that there would be no new product introductions including the introduction T4 and an integrated modem and those claims were unequivocally wrong. Why should anyone take this as anything other than sour grapes? BTW: I am neither long nor short on the stock right now.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357680205937</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:23:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357680461637-63</Id><Title>It's going back to 11.8</Title><Msg>No brainer</Msg><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1357680461637</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:27:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357680518746-64</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you r an IDIOT!! best be runnin along little boy before dis here RASTA MON kicks you in de behind!!</Msg><Username>xienlomein</Username><Timestamp>1357680518746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:28:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357680615103-65</Id><Topic><Title>It's going back to 11.8</Title><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1357680461637</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:27:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>anutter brain dead chimp !! best run along little BOY your ignorance is showing big time!!</Msg><Username>xienlomein</Username><Timestamp>1357680615103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:30:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357680724289-66</Id><Title>all dem brain dead shorts de can't believe</Title><Msg>dis here stock is not lower. HAHAHAHA because dem is brain dead and again are on de wrong side of de track MON!! de will be run over and left for dead before too long by the NVDA train commin down de track!!</Msg><Username>xienlomein</Username><Timestamp>1357680724289</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:32:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357680801265-67</Id><Topic><Title>It's going back to 11.8</Title><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1357680461637</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:27:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good that way I can buy more and wait for the MWC run up!</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357680801265</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:33:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357680804114-68</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>brokeagain - I am definitely negative on the stock but I don't think bitter. I would not recommend selling this stock at this level as it has shown good support around 12. Chip industry is still out of favor, CY warning this morning is a great tell on generic consumer item demand. The only question is whether this is the new normal or, bottom of the cycle. Don't be fooled - there was no integrated modem. Icera 500 is a discrete modem. I am familiar with design, field certification cycles. If they are sampling 500 to customers in Q1, you can expect devices to sport it by Q3 and that is the best case scenario. Tegra 4 will gets its fair share of the tablet market but market demands growth. I don't see any growth in Tegra business with the state of affairs.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357680804114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:33:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357680830112-69</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's so bad about the heatsink, at least both the cpu and gpu will both be able to run at full clockspeed at the same time unlike the 8W Exynos5 fitted into a 4W TDP in the Nexus 10. Glbenchmark possible sighting implies 1.8GHz clockspeed ... forumDOTxda-developersDOTcom/showthread.php?t=2087129</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357680830112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:33:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357681162741-70</Id><Topic><Title>Picture the shield. Now picture a Microsoft logo on it!</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1357677228339</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:33:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whoops. Imagine a google logo on it!</Msg><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1357681162741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:39:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357681173607-71</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there is nothing wrong with a heatsink (worse there is even a small fan). It will extend the life of a unit but it has a negative market reaction as it doesn't look like its a well engineered smarthphone SOC. Now it may well be that Nvidia has decided that its going to stay in Tablet, Chrombook market and not pursue smartphones aggressively but that was not what market was expecting.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357681173607</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:39:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357681608541-72</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Chip industry is still out of favor, CY warning this morning is a great tell on generic consumer item demand." Well I do agree with this. Tough era for chips but part of the reason I like NVIDIA's move to create a top down consumer based product - at least they are taking the "right" direction. "Don't be fooled - there was no integrated modem. Icera 500 is a discrete modem. I am familiar with design, field certification cycles. If they are sampling 500 to customers in Q1, you can expect devices to sport it by Q3 and that is the best case scenario." I can concede this but with some reservation. "Tegra 4 will gets its fair share of the tablet market but market demands growth. I don't see any growth in Tegra business with the state of affairs." I agree that the market wants growth - absolutely but the dividend adds some stability and it's not like Tegra is there only product that can be viewed as a growth engine. That being said I do think that it will offer growth in three ways: 1. Tablets are growing and thus that rising sea takes NVIDIAS 15% share higher all things status quo. 2. They now have a more complete smart phone offering with Icera (when it gets to market - I unlike you think it will be sooner rather than later but lets agree to disagree) that should allow deeper penetration into a growing smart phone market. 3. Create a consumer product which uses your hardware indirectly adds growth to the tegra chips and directly to the CPD.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357681608541</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:46:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357681747247-73</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everybody will have trouble putting the ARM A15 in a phone at any sustained clockspeed over 1 GHz, it just burns too much power (at 28-32nm). The integer and especially the floating point power was beefed up too much going from A9. This high power consumption will probably get controlled at the 14-16nm FinFET process node but for now it is an issue and considering the dual-core Exynos5 peaks at 8W I was expecting a good cooling solution.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357681747247</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:49:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357681902656-74</Id><Topic><Title>Picture the shield. Now picture a Microsoft logo on it!</Title><Username>on2five</Username><Timestamp>1357677228339</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:33:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"whats next ? aTegra set top box and /or TV ?" They already have one.. its called the shield</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357681902656</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:51:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357682414906-75</Id><Title>Audi to Globally Roll Out NVIDIA Tegra Visual Computing Module This Year</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/news/audi-globally-roll-nvidia-tegra-213000008.html Looks like a Tegra chip in every new Audi vehicle for the future. More good news.</Msg><Username>delano_00</Username><Timestamp>1357682414906</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:00:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357682497457-76</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well my objection is not so much the heatsink - its the company's focus and market expectation. Market wanted a Qualcomm vs Nvidia brawl. But here, we see that Nvidia has quietly conceded the smartphone market and is instead focusing on "other things". I saw someone post a $79-$99 price estimate. Are you kidding me? Nexus 7 costs ~$170 to build in volume (1M units/month). Project Shield is not that different than Nexus 7 - replace 7 inch screen with 5 inch - remove camera - add more battery - add better wifi - add hdmi, micro sd, gamepad support - lower volume you are basically looking at ~$250 cost and $325 price for a 50% margin. you get the picture - its not very competitive product at that price range.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357682497457</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:01:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357682822968-77</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see that you are excited at Nvidia entering Consumer product market, well I am not - Please be realistic - Nvidia is not in the smartphone market anymore. They will have less than 1% market share in smartphones in 2013 (same as 2012). But that may not be a bad thing as they can truly focus on high-end smartphones and maintain their margins.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357682822968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:07:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357682964612-78</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcomm launches Snapdragon 800 - higher clocks and change in branding</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357679866367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:17:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>anandtechDOTcom/show/6568/qualcomm-krait-400-krait-300-snapdragon-800</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357682964612</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:09:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357683327904-79</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think broke is reading this one more right. just want to add: tabletd, without the usual top 3, will never make Tegra breakeven. The shield will help, but again, breakeven does not a viable business make. But shield is better than nothing. They absolutely positively needs i500 so they can sell into phones. Bundled solution IMO is good enuf. Unfortunately, this key point is also the weakest point for nvda in this whole CES. Assuming 9+ months for discrete solutions to devices, you are looking at CY14 seeing T4/i500 sales or even just T3/i500 sales (even with that qual at ATT, nobody showed this device, not a good sign). Feb earnings is going to be an eyeful - $100M Tegra loses and forecasting no slow down in loses in Q1. This stock won't go far the next 6 to 9 months.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1357683327904</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:15:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357683947563-80</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That post was from me and it was a mistake based on bad info but I don't agree that it's it will have same manufacturing costs as the 7 which is closer to 155/unit - the kindle fire is 20 less than that. The screen cost will be about 30% lower and the enclosure will be somewhat cheaper not to mention the processor will be at cost. Processor and screen are the main drivers of cost. I had the original cost of the device around $100 maybe $110. Nonetheless I agree that at 250 it is less appealing and have a hard time believing that would be the price target. It would have to be sub $200 which I believe it will be.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357683947563</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:25:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357684194511-81</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, brcm just took out ARM license to do their own v7 and v8 cores. So the only guy left using straight ARM cores are Exynos and Hauwei. On the modem front, brcm showed their first discrete modem a couple of months ago. It's 28nm LTE.</Msg><Username>whosunw</Username><Timestamp>1357684194511</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:29:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357684512839-82</Id><Title>A 24 inch Full HD Touch Enabled Monitor/Tablet For $499</Title><Msg>ViewSonic’s New 24” Smart Display Transforms PC Computing at CES January 8, 2013 by ludeb ViewSonic extends award-winning connected desktop display experience with VSD240; pairs full HD monitor with nVIDIA® Tegra™ 3 processor and Android™ Jelly Bean ____________________________________________________________________________________ Probably too expensive, right......?</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357684512839</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:35:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357684597022-83</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not exactly excited they have a vision beyond commoditized hardware. I don't think they've conceded the smart phone market. By that same definition you'd have to say that Qualcomm has conceded the tablet market. I can appreciate you not being excited but I get the feeling it wouldn't matter what they introduced you'd be negative on it. Who are you positive on?</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357684597022</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:36:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357685721856-84</Id><Title>NVDA competitive advantages.....</Title><Msg>Comments from a FORBES post: All the press focus seems to be on Shield yet, the true disruptive influence by NVIDIA is two new features related to the Tegra 4 smartphone/tablet processor. 1. hardware integrated photography acceleration: 10x the speed for photographs compared to the newest Apple chip. Being a hardware solution it will be harder for other chip makers to implement similar capability without running into patent issues. Should give NVIDIA a 2yr+ lead in picture taking capability for smartphones. 2. LTE modem with 40% less die space than competitors: A big advertised piece is greately reduced power usage compared to competitor LTE modems. Should give NVIDIA a 1.5+ year lead in power consumption when streaming data compared to other smartphone/tablet modem makers. What does this mean? Those that adopt the Tegra 4 for their smartphones will have a competitive edge in not only the fastest processor and graphics currently announced but also better photography capability and battery life. Those shopping for features will find the Tegra 4 in the lead for the first year after release and still highly competitive in the second year afteron release. $19 soon close to you...</Msg><Username>grkenvtech</Username><Timestamp>1357685721856</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:55:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357686037241-85</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Frankly, I am surprised that you are writing on this board. Did your parents have any children that lived?</Msg><Username>tj95b73</Username><Timestamp>1357686037241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 18:00:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357687221272-86</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Appreciate your posts because you seem to undertand market dynamics. Disagree with you though on advising people to hold and not sell at this time. Yes, $12 is strong support, but there seems to be little upside above $13 +/-</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1357687221272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 18:20:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357688108801-87</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you conclude that the Exynos 5 has a 8 watt max power use? It likely has a much higher potential peak electrical power, but thermally throttles down to about 4W in that physical mounting. The Exynos 5 Arndale board now recommends using a 25W power supply, after the original power supply resulted in flaky operation. I suspect that when the OpenCL libraries are available that the chip will come close to 20W, which is sustainable only with a really good heatsink. A tablet user will be really happy with instant response with intermittent use, such as web browsing. A gamer will be really upset if the game is fast only for the first five seconds, then drops back to drawing block figures at slide show frame rates.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1357688108801</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 18:35:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357688814127-88</Id><Title>Bestbuy..Almost sold out of Microsoft Surface RT</Title><Msg>Only 5 of the 20 Best Buy stores have inventory of the Tegra 3 Surface! Bestselling ranking is the higher each day. When the Microsoft Surface Pro hits at the end of Jan, I suspect will see the Microsoft Surface RT be upgraded with Tegra 4. Note: Saw an article today from one of the Tech Gurus saying Tegra 4's die size in 80mm sq. That's down from Tegra 3 at 89mm sq. This along with a nice a premium in price should yield a nice gross margin. And of course it can be bundled with the I500 LTE modem and undercut the competitors because the soft modem is 40% smaller in die size vs. QCOM's hardware defined modem used in high end phones. Bet AT&amp;T at MMW mobile congress announces certification of I500. HTC and LG announce Tegra 4 I500 phones!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357688814127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 18:46:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357690180539-89</Id><Title>NVIDIA Icera i500 Details - 28nm HP, Category 3 LTE At Launch, 4 Later</Title><Msg>anandtechDOTcom/show/6552/more-nvidia-icera-i500-details-28nm-hp-category-3-lte-at-launch-4-later "We've confirmed some more details about NVIDIA's newly-announced Icera i500 Soft Modem. First, the Icera i500 is built on TSMC's 28nm HP (High Performance) High-K Metal Gate process. NVIDIA's strategy with i500 is to take advantage of the lower active power compared to LP and power gate the core entirely while the modem is not active. In addition, NVIDIA claims i500 can actively power gate each of the individual 8 processing cores inside as load conditions change or depending on the software package loaded onto the modem. The i500 soft modem will also be paired with an entirely new transceiver, built on 65nm LP CMOS, I'm told this isn't TSMC's RF CMOS but rather some other "RF-friendly" 65nm process. In addition NVIDIA's target is a similar number of ports to Qualcomm, 7, before adding switches. I didn't get a high/mid/low band breakdown. Initially i500 will be capable of UE Category 3 LTE (100 Mbps downlink on 20 MHz FDD-LTE) and a later release will enable UE Category 4 LTE, which is one of the nice software upgradeable parts of an SDR architecture. On the WCDMA/HSPA+ side, DC-HSPA+ (42 Mbps downlink) is supported. I'm told that the initial 3GPP release will be 9, and later 10 with LTE Category 4 and carrier aggregation for LTE. i500 at present I'm told includes 3GPP family air interfaces (GSM/EDGE/WCDMA/LTE), no word on CDMA2000 1x/EVDO 3GPP2 suite making it. Voice modes including VoLTE are indeed supported as well."</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357690180539</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:09:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357690605169-90</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>anandtechDOTcom/show/6536/arm-vs-x86-the-real-showdown/13 'Throughout all of our Cortex A15 testing we kept bumping into that 4W ceiling with both the CPU and GPU - but we rarely saw both blocks use that much power at the same time. Intel actually tipped me off to this test to find out what happens if we try and force both the CPU and GPU to run at max performance at the same time. The graph below is divided into five distinct sections, denoted by colored bars above the sections. On this chart I have individual lines for GPU power consumption (green), CPU power consumption (blue) and total platform power consumption, including display, measured at the battery (red). In the first section (yellow), we begin playing Modern Combat 3 - a GPU intensive first person shooter. GPU power consumption is just shy of 4W, while CPU power consumption remains below 1W. After about a minute of play we switch away from MC3 and you can see both CPU and GPU power consumption drop considerably. In the next section (orange), we fire up a multithreaded instance of CoreMark - a small CPU benchmark - and allow it to loop indefinitely. CPU power draw peaks at just over 4W, while GPU power consumption is understandably very low. Next, while CoreMark is still running on both cores, we switch back to Modern Combat 3 (pink section of the graph). GPU voltage ramps way up, power consumption is around 4W, but note what happens to CPU power consumption. The CPU cores step down to a much lower voltage/frequency for the background task (~800MHz from 1.7GHz). Total SoC TDP jumps above 4W but the power controller quickly responds by reducing CPU voltage/frequency in order to keep things under control at ~4W. To confirm that CoreMark is still running, we then switch back to the benchmark (blue segment) and you see CPU performance ramps up as GPU performance winds down. Finally we switch back to MC3, combined CPU + GPU power is around 8W for a short period of time before the CPU is throttled. Now this is a fairy contrived scenario, but it's necessary to understand the behavior of the Exynos 5250. The SoC is allowed to reach 8W, making that its max TDP by conventional definitions, but seems to strive for around 4W as its typical power under load. Why are these two numbers important? With Haswell, Intel has demonstrated interest (and ability) to deliver a part with an 8W TDP. In practice, Intel would need to deliver about half that to really fit into a device like the Nexus 10 but all of the sudden it seems a lot more feasible. Samsung hits 4W by throttling its CPU cores when both the CPU and GPU subsystems are being taxed, I wonder what an 8W Haswell would look like in a similar situation...'</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357690605169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:16:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357691333011-91</Id><Title>techies here all tied up in details of products!! Sales matter</Title><Msg>do ya think apple has no tech problems,,,come on now..</Msg><Username>smallstock1</Username><Timestamp>1357691333011</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:28:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357691517177-92</Id><Title>Cloud gaming review - phandroid</Title><Msg>phandroidDOTcom/2013/01/08/hands-on-nvidia-grid-cloud-gaming-at-ces-2013-video/</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357691517177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:31:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357693586546-93</Id><Topic><Title>Patrick Moohead tweet: first experience with Project Shield positive; didn't experience latency in PC game</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357693097185</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:58:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ibexx You do know that he is paid a consulting fee by Nvidia. No worse I suppose than most of Tech press are paid.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357693586546</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:06:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357694292144-94</Id><Title>Project Shield Will Be Surprisingly Affordable</Title><Msg>We need to look no further than the BOM cost of Sony's PS Vita or Google Nexus 7 tablet. Here goes PS Vita - $150 Google Nexus 7 include Tegra 3 retail - $159 $199 sale price for Project shield generates $50 + $12(gross margin profit of Tegra 4 alone) or $62 gross profit from the device. Sell 2 million units and you add a gross profit of $124M from a product with very little operating expenses. Sweet!</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357694292144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:18:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357696208616-95</Id><Title>nvda destined is due for greatness/ by motley fool !!</Title><Msg>snooooze now and don't buy and you will reget later !! $20.00 stock by end of year PLUS !!!!!</Msg><Username>clintelkins</Username><Timestamp>1357696208616</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:50:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357697930319-96</Id><Title>Not one word from Nvidia fans on that 5% SHIELD slap down hmm?</Title><Msg>What 5 % right? Just more pretend time here. Pretending for 2 days now that a SHIELD will protect whatever is left of that dwindling Nvidia investment? $26, $25, ..., $16, ..., $12 The only people buying the SHIELD story are posting pretend notes by the pound on a message board as the market tears Nvidia a new one. Enjoy your Nvidia purchase. imho</Msg><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1357697930319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 21:18:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357698472687-97</Id><Topic><Title>Not one word from Nvidia fans on that 5% SHIELD slap down hmm?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1357697930319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 21:18:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt AMD would even hire a #$%$ like this...however typically, the least competent employees are last to leave as they are the ones who are unable to replace their jobs.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1357698472687</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 21:27:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357698985718-98</Id><Topic><Title>Project Shield Will Be Surprisingly Affordable</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357694292144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:18:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ibexx, Think of it this way...Tegra 3 sells retail for $21.50 according to ISupply Nexus 7 teardown. BOM cost including Tegra 3 is $159. But this is a 7 inch display, so a 5 inch display should be $20 less or a BOM cost of $139 or $117.50 without Tegra. So Nvidia sells for $199 and the cost without Tegra 4 is $117.50. That's like selling a Tegra 4 for $81.50. Now consider that Tegra 4 is10% smaller than Tegra 3. Surely you can see the wisdom of this price. Think of the volume......</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357698985718</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 21:36:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357699592862-99</Id><Topic><Title>Project Shield Will Be Surprisingly Affordable</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357694292144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:18:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Tegra 4 is10% smaller than Tegra 3" Where's the info for that ?? All info I find says their both 80 mm sq... btw... did you get paid for that... :)</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357699592862</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 21:46:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357699923177-100</Id><Topic><Title>DOWN 3% Mon and DOWN 2% Tues is that the SHIELD effect kicking in?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1357663847602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:50:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for correcting that material mistake. No, they should continue to innovate; but innovate for commercial purposes, not for innovations sake. Like I said, it's cool. It won't sell. Why? Limited market. You really think Nintendo and Sony aren't meeting the portable need? Why would a user invest in another platform device?</Msg><Username>sebanker123</Username><Timestamp>1357699923177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 21:52:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357700167559-101</Id><Topic><Title>Project Shield Will Be Surprisingly Affordable</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357694292144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:18:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL....Getanid? Ibexx; Use your head...silly. Project Shield...What a name will make money no matter you twinsters spin. Peaced</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357700167559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 21:56:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357700222106-102</Id><Topic><Title>DOWN 3% Mon and DOWN 2% Tues is that the SHIELD effect kicking in?</Title><Username>xc3155</Username><Timestamp>1357663847602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:50:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Like I said, it's cool. It won't sell. " weak... it's the best handheld going the distribution of games is as easy as it gets, it's already setup the new kids don't care about previous gen stuff... it's the new for youth</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357700222106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 21:57:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357700539836-103</Id><Topic><Title>Project Shield Will Be Surprisingly Affordable</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357694292144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:18:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" no matter you twinsters spin." tell me my spin... I'd sure like to know...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357700539836</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:02:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357700801260-104</Id><Topic><Title>Project Shield Will Be Surprisingly Affordable</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357694292144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:18:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>-The Shield will have a 5" retina display, not IPS as in the Nexus 6 Ibexx Nexus 6...Ibexx too much from the grape I suppose. Volume is not likely very high initially, but it may grow steadily as the gaming landscape changes. Just remember that it won't be a "mainstream" product off the gate. (I suspect this is one of the reasons Wall Street has not been jumping up and down - there are other possible reasons which I will express my opinions on a bit later...) Ibexx What in the world are you talking about? You and your sock puppet Getanid are opaque at best.pr5oject shield is a money maker. Oh I get it you already sold your cals for a too cheapprice....So Sorry.</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357700801260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:06:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357701004285-105</Id><Topic><Title>nvda destined is due for greatness/ by motley fool !!</Title><Username>clintelkins</Username><Timestamp>1357696208616</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:50:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did anyone see the reports suggesting INTC was in discussion to acquire NVDA (with MSFT's blessing) to counter against AAPL? It suggests that after the M&amp;A NVDA's CEO could either be appointed as the new CEO of INTC or the head of mobile?</Msg><Username>dd888i8</Username><Timestamp>1357701004285</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:10:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357701202560-106</Id><Topic><Title>It's going back to 11.8</Title><Username>tomasco3777</Username><Timestamp>1357680461637</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:27:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Plenty of cash is waiting for that entry point. Bring it on, shortie.</Msg><Username>dd888i8</Username><Timestamp>1357701202560</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:13:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357702402053-107</Id><Topic><Title>Project Shield Will Be Surprisingly Affordable</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357694292144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:18:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Volume is not likely very high initially, but it may grow steadily as the gaming landscape changes. Just remember that it won't be a "mainstream" product off the gate. (I suspect this is one of the reasons Wall Street has not been jumping up and down - there are other possible reasons which I will express my opinions on a bit later...) Ibexx What in the world are you talking about? You and your sock puppet Getanid are opaque at best.pr5oject shield is a money maker. Oh I get it you already sold your cals for a too ----------------------------------------------------------------------------- I agree on the first point... I have no idea either what he's talking about On your second point... What in the world are you talking about? Dude, put down the pipe</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357702402053</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:33:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357702758596-108</Id><Topic><Title>Frankly I am surprised that NVDA is not down more</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357678515977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:55:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That story shows anandtech's tight relationship to Intel. Intel is pushing the "scenario design power" story this week. See today's story in Ars Technica -- it's Intel's talking point for CES. All of the top end chips today are capable of doing more work than the power supply and thermals will support. Intel just "created" a lower power chipset by defining away the top performance range. Samsung does the same -- claiming 68 GFLOPs peak from the GPU, but without having the software or heatsink to support it on current platforms. No doubt the Tegra 4 will support higher continuous performance in the Shield, with its elaborate heatsink, than it will smaller devices.</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1357702758596</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:39:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357702850886-109</Id><Title>Ibexx/Getanid "the Netflix of Games"</Title><Msg>I'm sorry...but you already soldy our Calls....Better talk to Nvida and work on coordination. Peace</Msg><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357702850886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:40:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357705131889-110</Id><Topic><Title>Ibexx/Getanid "the Netflix of Games"</Title><Username>j7777kxx</Username><Timestamp>1357702850886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:40:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DESPERATE !!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357705131889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 23:18:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357706380775-111</Id><Topic><Title>JUST IN: NVIDIA CEO talks Shield with CNET - yes, there will be future models</Title><Username>ibexx88</Username><Timestamp>1357702556154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you guys catch that key comment - "Just don't call Project Shield a game console" There is more than one reason for that - if they call it a game console, it will be banned in China. I only recently found out that Nvidia is so popular in China because Xbox, PS3, Wii etc. cannot be legally sold in China (even though they are all manufactured there). Its because of a 2000 policy adopted by Ministry of Culture - imagine that. Youths (did you say yutes) in China enjoy gaming on high-end PC's instead. I think Project Shield type of device will be popular in China and Asia as long as they can avoid being branded as Game Console. There was a rumor in early Nov. (which contributed to Nvidia falling to 11's) that China was going to lift the ban, it was because of a safety certification for PS3. This was later clarified as a different agency than MOC.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357706380775</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 23:39:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>