<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-18"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345264225000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Is anyone boycotting AMZN because of Gay Marriage Support?</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1345229849000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:57:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You been chuggin' from the 'shine jug tonite?</Msg><Username>richie.90210</Username><Timestamp>1345264225000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345264593000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Is this true or a pump</Title><Username>vjack68</Username><Timestamp>1345255893000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 22:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfortunately we can't read the whole article without signing up. Any chance you could help? Looks interesting.</Msg><Username>weatherwhysguy</Username><Timestamp>1345264593000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345265160000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Is this true or a pump</Title><Username>vjack68</Username><Timestamp>1345255893000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 22:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pj--I think he just brought it up now because it is currently one of the main stories on the Yahoo home page.</Msg><Username>punbr</Username><Timestamp>1345265160000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:46:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345266435000-4</Id><Topic><Title>did Chalk get a margin call? what about techstrategy? Sybil? Kenji?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1345232015000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 15:33:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Syb, Skiidady claims to be in Sept. 265 Amazon calls. How do you think he will do?</Msg><Username>richie.90210</Username><Timestamp>1345266435000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 01:07:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345268136000-5</Id><Title>Contrarian Indicator Skiidady is Bullish</Title><Msg>Bulls should recall Skiidady's awful recent track record--pumping Chipotle at $440 top right before it crashed. Sell!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>grandapa.clampett</Username><Timestamp>1345268136000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 01:35:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345291754000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Is this true or a pump</Title><Username>vjack68</Username><Timestamp>1345255893000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 22:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...The One Company That Actually Terrifies Google Execs" it's always how AMZN is the threat: how about the other way around? the Companies with big cash being a threat to AMZN? the media is a piece of work. why can't one search and easily just buy from somewhere else? just sayin'.</Msg><Username>party_bistro</Username><Timestamp>1345291754000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:09:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345292121000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Is this true or a pump</Title><Username>vjack68</Username><Timestamp>1345255893000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 22:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.businessinsider.com/forget-apple-forget-facebook-heres-the-one-company-that-actually-terrifies-google-execs-2012-8</Msg><Username>party_bistro</Username><Timestamp>1345292121000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345293119000-8</Id><Topic><Title>did Chalk get a margin call? what about techstrategy? Sybil? Kenji?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1345232015000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 15:33:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amzn is on a breakout. Summer correction is over. Santa Claus rally has begun. Slow Stochastics in overbought territority, but it just got there and can remain overbought for some time. RSI is no where near overbought. RSI is probably the most important indicator to watch. What will happen over the next month? I dont know. Out of 4 predictions, I have only been right once. All of my predictions have been bearish. What does that tell you?</Msg><Username>Edison20</Username><Timestamp>1345293119000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345295444000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Is this true or a pump</Title><Username>vjack68</Username><Timestamp>1345255893000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 22:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People may search on Scamazon for pictures and reviews, but they buy from the lowest priced seller. With many stores now offering online pricematching, Scamazon is no longer the low price leader. The ever increasing cost of shipping is the key to preventing Scamazon to manage more than 1% profit margin.</Msg><Username>nje457</Username><Timestamp>1345295444000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:10:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345296987000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Is this true or a pump</Title><Username>vjack68</Username><Timestamp>1345255893000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 22:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is true. Amazon copies and steals everyone's business models. They even stole groupons. I get the lame emails. They are a competitor to everyone.</Msg><Username>bradpoleon</Username><Timestamp>1345296987000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:36:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345301015000-11</Id><Topic><Title>did Chalk get a margin call? what about techstrategy? Sybil? Kenji?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1345232015000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 15:33:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah im loving it...pushing this fraud to new very unsustainable heights....holding calls all the way from 220 and will be heavily loading puts on this scam fraud very soon...... keep pumping..........stairways up elevator shaft dowwwwn.........</Msg><Username>jbirks67</Username><Timestamp>1345301015000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:43:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345301153000-12</Id><Title>pump n dump</Title><Msg>insider sold shares like hot cake this company is trading up on no profit and lower guidance lol</Msg><Username>vinhhoixuan2000</Username><Timestamp>1345301153000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:45:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345301896000-13</Id><Topic><Title>CONGRATS TO ALL AAPL INVESTORS!! NEW ALLTIME HIGHS TODAY!</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1345231034000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 15:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just another hopium smoker addicted to what the punchbowl serves up....hopefully you dont really believe what is being served up as the "truth"...sure these stocks are up and yes they have surged however the reality is without the us adding 8 trillion to the national debt, did you here that 8 trillion, in 4 years all of these dream stocks would be 75^% lower which is where they are heading .............. if you live in the us you should be very aware of this surge in the debt....it will ensure a very low standard of life in the near future!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! stairways up elevator shaft down...........</Msg><Username>jbirks67</Username><Timestamp>1345301896000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:58:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345302167000-14</Id><Title>NO Way to Turn Off 1-Click Ordering on AMZN Streaming Video</Title><Msg>What a BIG programming FLUB as parents are discovering their curious kids are clicking on the 1-click order buttons and ordering who knows what for $100's. No sense in keeping and paying for AMZN streaming video if the the kids are BANNED from watching and clicking on it.</Msg><Username>amazing_aces_wild</Username><Timestamp>1345302167000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:02:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345302333000-15</Id><Title>AMZN Customer Service Reps Can Barely Speak ENGLISH</Title><Msg>Totally USELESS!</Msg><Username>amazing_aces_wild</Username><Timestamp>1345302333000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:05:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345302833000-16</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN Customer Service Reps Can Barely Speak ENGLISH</Title><Username>amazing_aces_wild</Username><Timestamp>1345302333000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sadly CS has been outsourced to El Salvador to people just learning to speak English by repeating a script a hundred times each hour.</Msg><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1345302833000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345304510000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Is this true or a pump</Title><Username>vjack68</Username><Timestamp>1345255893000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 22:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone that truly gets it. Everyone has assumed AMZN is always the tougher/better competitor and only the others get hurt. The method through which AMZN has done this has been to rely upon a tax subsidy ranging from 5-10% and aggressively pricing product to knock out weak retailers who have large fixed cost who couldn't match AMZN's effective tax subsidized price. First, that is changing. And it will be material, particularly on higher priced consumer electronics products. Anyone who says otherwise if full of crap. Second, AMZN's competition for digital music and books, going forward, will be Apple and Google. For those who missed it, Apple basically said to the DOJ "We're not settling. You did this all at the bidding of AMZN, holding 20+ off the record meeting with AMZN employees at AMZN HQ and it further cements AMZN's monopoly position. We're going to trial". Apple has plenty of money to go to trial and I suspect AMZN will take a brand hit on this one. Having said that, if Apple loses, I expect some scorched earth. Apple and Google could (in order to "promote tablets" price iBooks/GoogleBooks at 10% BELOW Amazon. Neither makes their money there and the "marketing cost" might amount to a few hundred million. But, the impact to Amazon would be devastating, losing its core source of monopolistid cash that it uses to attack others... The point is simple. Apple and Google have so much cash and make so much cash that they can LOSE CASH going after AMZN's crown jewel (and the DOJ would have NO GROUNDS for complaint since the current complaint is that Apple colluded to raise price to consumers). Would it move the needle for Apple? NO. Would it materially hurt Google? NO. Would it make AMZN vulnerable? Yes. Third, Rackspace OpenStack, HP Cloud and Google Cloud Platform are going to slowly erode AWS growth, margins and profitability. A few articles: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/OpenStack -- OpenStack is open source infrastrucure as a service project, started by NASA and RackSpace to overcome proprietary/lock-in effects. Has big momentum behind it to wipe away Amazon's lead. HP Cloud and Rackspace OpenStack offerings are just the beginning. http://www.rackspace.com/cloud/public/servers/compare/ -- Rackspace's propaganda showing its comparison to AWS. HP Cloud is matching AWS pricing everywhere AND providing higher service levels for free. HP has definitely been moving more in this direction, so it will be interesting to see if a desperate dying company still with vast financial resources and technological capability can compete here. My gut says this will be part of HP's comeback story, since HP NEEDS to get traction in a secular growth area. Fourth, eBay has got its mojo back and it going to be giving AMZN a better run for the money in the core (ESPECIALLY if MSFA doesn't pass and eBay's merchants don't have to collect tax while AMZN does...). All the analysts beat up Google for fighting too many fronts. The reality is that Google has a cash machine and $50B hoard. It could go years without revenue... Amazon has sprawled just as much, but has neither the cash hoard nor the cash flow to sustain aggressive responses from competitors in each segment. Amazon is WAY more vulnerable than anyone is making it out to be. Might AMZN overcome and grow into this valuation. It's possible. But, the odds are WAY higher that, aided by recession in 2013 (and just so we are clear, the US would already be in recession if the deficit wasn't 10% of GDP. Take it to 5% and we're negative folks...All the financial pundits conveniently ignore that) retail sales contract and price competition gets more aggressive in each business Amazon is in. Shorts, be patient. Don't buy ST puts. Don't buy what you cannot maintain for a year. If you aren't greedy, you'll do well.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1345304510000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:41:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345310821000-18</Id><Title>The CIRCUS Comes to Town</Title><Msg>Come one come all! The Greatest Show On Earth! The Great Skiidady! Sybil!</Msg><Username>richie.90210</Username><Timestamp>1345310821000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345311116000-19</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN Customer Service Reps Can Barely Speak ENGLISH</Title><Username>amazing_aces_wild</Username><Timestamp>1345302333000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, but look at the money 'zon saves.</Msg><Username>richie.90210</Username><Timestamp>1345311116000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:31:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345312947000-20</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN Customer Service Reps Can Barely Speak ENGLISH</Title><Username>amazing_aces_wild</Username><Timestamp>1345302333000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lots of money being saved now = lots of customer goodwill lost in the future. A good reputation takes years to build and can be lost in a second.</Msg><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1345312947000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:02:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345313178000-21</Id><Topic><Title>NO Way to Turn Off 1-Click Ordering on AMZN Streaming Video</Title><Username>amazing_aces_wild</Username><Timestamp>1345302167000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Betcha 50% of the current AMZN sales and income is coming from these 1 clicks. No wonder CS had to be outsourced to El Savador because of the flood of the customer complaints of unintended 1 click orders.</Msg><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1345313178000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:06:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345314420000-22</Id><Title>valuation</Title><Msg>I'm new to AMZN and short. If you think the company can triple the annualized EBITDA from last quarter over the next five years, assume a terminal value of 10x on the 5th year EBITDA (that has now tripled to $7.5B) and would be willing to take a 15% annual return if you purchased the company today, you would pay $111 per share. Ooops, I forgot to deduct the $2.4B in debt and the $4.3B in operating lease obligations that would have to be paid off at sale. So, after creditor claims, the stock would be worth $95 per share. What's on the near term (next 5 years) horizon that will propel AMZN's EBITDA to a 35% compounded annual growth rate just to get the share value to $95? What is the share value doing at $241 currently?</Msg><Username>darv2222</Username><Timestamp>1345314420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:27:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345317413000-23</Id><Topic><Title>valuation</Title><Username>darv2222</Username><Timestamp>1345314420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:27:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to the longs, AMZN is risk free. So, 15% is not required. Just 3%. Rerun your numbers with that mathemagic and you'll see...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1345317413000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:16:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345318056000-24</Id><Title>Kodaks patents</Title><Msg>I remember reading somewhere that you were rumured to be bidding on kodak's patent trove. Might be a good idea to keep them out of the hands of Apple/Google. Have you heard anything about this?</Msg><Username>mattglassman6363</Username><Timestamp>1345318056000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:27:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345319930000-25</Id><Topic><Title>valuation</Title><Username>darv2222</Username><Timestamp>1345314420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:27:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I'm new to AMZN and short." like a baby seal pup announcing himself into the water ofF the Farallon Islands of SF Coast to the Great White Sharks. Gotta love the shorts introducing themselves as if they will be the one to catch AMZN to profit: Hi I'm dinner!! Come and eat me!! or Hi! I'm now short AMZN! Here' wallet or purse! Take it all! YEAH BABY YEAH! YOU SHORTS ARE TOO FREAKIN' FUNNY!! Short the common I hope? 3 things: 1.)AMZN ROCKS AGAIN AND AGAIN! AND 2.) CRISIS LEADS TO MEETING LEADS TO BAILOUTS LEADES TO STOCK RALLIES LEADS TO AMZN ROCKING!! AGAIN AND AGAIN! 3.) YOUR FELLOW SHORT MAY BE YOUR GREATEST ENEMY! LOL!</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1345319930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345320114000-26</Id><Title>'HI I'M NEW TO AMZN AND A NEW SHORT! LOL!</Title><Msg>Who corners the shares!! Hilarious!! Gotta be the stupidest people i've ever seen like that guy kenji a few weeks ago doing the same.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1345320114000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 16:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345320276000-27</Id><Topic><Title>CONGRATS TO ALL AAPL INVESTORS!! NEW ALLTIME HIGHS TODAY!</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1345231034000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 15:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Birkes: you've been burned for about 40 points and counting. you lost. "STAIRWAYS UP ELEVATOR SHAFT DOWN..........." Umm! rocket ship up for 40 points since you arrived and counting. You are embarassing your fellow shorts. And they are pretty bad.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1345320276000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 16:04:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345322689000-28</Id><Topic><Title>valuation</Title><Username>darv2222</Username><Timestamp>1345314420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:27:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I'm new to AMZN and short." This won't end well.</Msg><Username>timberlane_99</Username><Timestamp>1345322689000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 16:44:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345323874000-29</Id><Title>"There's a Sucker Born Every Minute."</Title><Msg>You're the living proof, shorts.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1345323874000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 17:04:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345325704000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Sorry, shorts, it's over.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1344998030000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 22:33:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was another great week for me. God bless America.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1345325704000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 17:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345327174000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Sorry, shorts, it's over.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1344998030000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 22:33:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You'll be using those same words with the opposite meaning soon enough... It will be like out of the Princess Bride... "Inconceivable! " "You use that word a lot, I do not think it means what you think it means..."</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1345327174000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 17:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345328948000-32</Id><Title>I'll go you one better</Title><Msg>Down 105</Msg><Username>penystoc</Username><Timestamp>1345328948000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:29:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345329799000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Sorry, shorts, it's over.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1344998030000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 22:33:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You'll be using those same words with the opposite meaning soon enough..." another "the sky is about to fall. Any minute now... Chicken Little is coming to town... comment? starting to add up from you like that guy Chalk who disappeared...he must have taken a beating...the latest to come here all cocky and get it handed to him. His attitude was: "watch and learn" and those words don't end well. Along with of course: "I'm new to AMZN and I"m short." that's just a mindboggling WOW!</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1345329799000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:43:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345330160000-34</Id><Topic><Title>DOWN $100</Title><Username>jkanalysis</Username><Timestamp>1343267340000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-07-25 21:49:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It might not happen the day after the "losses" report, but it very well may happen within 3 trading days of that report. This stock is about to Crash, and the World Markets are about to Crash." Holy moly!! I forgot about this guy! He was alligned with Singh, coming over from the CMG board I think, or was it NFLX, one of those who thought AMZN was going to be NFLX,CMG, GMCR...something like that: those kind of guys have been tremeendous fuel for the power to run it up even higher. I think this was his last message before earnings whooped him like so many other shortys along the grave yard.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1345330160000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:49:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345330346000-35</Id><Topic><Title>I'll go you one better</Title><Username>penystoc</Username><Timestamp>1345328948000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:29:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll give you the reality: up from 202 lows in AH to over 240 and counting...after running from 170 to over 200... 106 to 170, 8 to 150.... higher highs , higher lows: you get the picture. lol!</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1345330346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:52:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345334601000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Is anyone boycotting AMZN because of Gay Marriage Support?</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1345229849000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:57:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Enjoy! http://playhabermanatyahoo.yolasite.com/</Msg><Username>themeatman45</Username><Timestamp>1345334601000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 20:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345335076000-37</Id><Topic><Title>Is anyone boycotting AMZN because of Gay Marriage Support?</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1345229849000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:57:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, I don't boycott a company that gives me amazing prices..Money saved is more money to invest with. Besides, no where in the bible does it specifically say that gay marriage isn't allowed.</Msg><Username>kabraxisx64</Username><Timestamp>1345335076000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 20:11:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345340504000-38</Id><Title>Can you see that white hot light down the way? Its soooo pretty</Title><Msg>Yes pumperz, we are nearing the end of the road for this play and soooooo many otherz.... Moths are attracted to the light as well, and like you will, they end up burnt to a crisp.... Good luck though!</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1345340504000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 21:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345341500000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Technical Chart</Title><Username>marleeneni960</Username><Timestamp>1345300144000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:29:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice Post</Msg><Username>florisurb473</Username><Timestamp>1345341500000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 21:58:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345345029000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Is anyone boycotting AMZN because of Gay Marriage Support?</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1345229849000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:57:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He spends 8 years of his life stalking me and you're going to treat him like that?!?!?!?!?!?!?</Msg><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1345345029000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 22:57:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345346196000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Sorry, shorts, it's over.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1344998030000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 22:33:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"My name is Inigo Montoya, you killed my father...prepare to die" Classic. - PJ</Msg><Username>pjlouie13</Username><Timestamp>1345346196000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 23:16:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345347488000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Is this true or a pump</Title><Username>vjack68</Username><Timestamp>1345255893000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 22:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Punbr, I've tried to copy and paste the article but the Yahoo! police keep blocking me! It must be copy written? If your on Yahoo!, look up AMZN, go to the headlines tab under News and Info, look for articles on Aug 17th, 7th article down titled "Two to take short". Sorry, I thought the link would of taken you to that article. - PJ</Msg><Username>pjlouie13</Username><Timestamp>1345347488000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 23:38:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>