<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347249966930-1</Id><Topic><Title>I bought 50,000 AMZN shares on sale 3 days ago..</Title><Username>lekinsh01</Username><Timestamp>1347075153894</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only 50,000 share, your too cheap. I got 100,000 shares at about at about $350. Had nothing to with $3,500,000. Looking to buy some more at $350.</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347249966930</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 00:06:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347250955604-2</Id><Topic><Title>One Million Moms say "boycott Amazon" for Bezos $2.5M support of gay marriage</Title><Username>wmartinez1980</Username><Timestamp>1347152452014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 21:00:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One million moms can kiss my happy white #$%$</Msg><Username>alphashort</Username><Timestamp>1347250955604</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 00:22:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347256215515-3</Id><Title>Wow, Amazon just peaked on Friday</Title><Msg>interesting stuff, I finally look a the market and all I see are stocks at their exact peak. I better short 100 shares of this tomorrow, could make 50 to 100 per share or more.</Msg><Username>semiprotrader</Username><Timestamp>1347256215515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 01:50:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347273939485-4</Id><Title>Hey phil.... Joelle's got some crow for you to eat</Title><Msg>Again, Stupid ... Sybils going to win big on this trade too.... Are you going to follow sybil to the next one after amzn? You should think about betting the sybil trade rather than bashing it, dummy. Imagine what you could do with a double on your 800.00 acct... You could scrape up a down payment for a nicer car to live in...</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347273939485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 06:45:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347275673223-5</Id><Topic><Title>The urgly news : The Catch in Kindle’s Data Plan</Title><Username>me_novice</Username><Timestamp>1347154665826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 21:37:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You never heard of wifi?</Msg><Username>sg1757</Username><Timestamp>1347275673223</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 07:14:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347275925128-6</Id><Title>Hey idiots....</Title><Msg>This pig is going to make sybil a fvckin fortune... Sybil shorted arsloads of this trash az other weak shorts and bozo buyerz of expensive crack addict weekly puts murdered each other and then shot themselvez.... Stupit peoplez in stupit scam markets.</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347275925128</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 07:18:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347276361065-7</Id><Topic><Title>800 billions Rev and $12 Earning per Share</Title><Username>cityhomemaker</Username><Timestamp>1347076139994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:48:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rick James approved this message</Msg><Username>equity_pool</Username><Timestamp>1347276361065</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 07:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347277335388-8</Id><Title>PE of 317 #$%$</Title><Msg>for a mature company that iis insane. Bezos should go into politcs!!!</Msg><Username>bogdanmiltchev</Username><Timestamp>1347277335388</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 07:42:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347281690724-9</Id><Title>Christmas will be huge</Title><Msg>Very huge.</Msg><Username>beachdan1234</Username><Timestamp>1347281690724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 08:54:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347283153076-10</Id><Topic><Title>NTWK $4.8...UP!!... RECORD 4Q and FY 2012 EARNINGS.....GUIDES FOR $1/SHARE NET AND 30%+ REVENUE GROWTH IN 2013......3M SHARE FLOAT......TO DOUBLE REVENUES/NET BY 2015</Title><Username>joeyggrecco</Username><Timestamp>1346951199757</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:06:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep an eye on this one. Acquisition Cloud Play. Analysts Upped Target from $11 to $16/shar</Msg><Username>dianakibsion</Username><Timestamp>1347283153076</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:19:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347283248212-11</Id><Title>short the stock to the bone and cober in Oct.</Title><Msg>Election issues, Obama's tax issues ...etc. will drive markeyt down and amzn will lose at least 50 points</Msg><Username>bogdanmiltchev</Username><Timestamp>1347283248212</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347284484934-12</Id><Title>AAPL announing this week and and amzn has no permit to sell this new kindle</Title><Msg>Bezos is a swindler!!! Wow! and the insiders sold last week to hide before the huge dip</Msg><Username>bogdanmiltchev</Username><Timestamp>1347284484934</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:41:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347284842309-13</Id><Title>Buy, 264 level, next.</Title><Msg>from here</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1347284842309</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:47:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347285093587-14</Id><Title>CFO sold 20% of his shares of AMZN last week</Title><Msg>When that happens guess what follows! $50-70 down from here folks. tighten your seatbelts!!!</Msg><Username>bogdanmiltchev</Username><Timestamp>1347285093587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:51:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347285932620-15</Id><Title>amzn bad for the economy: eliminates jobs and encourages Chinese sales</Title><Msg>as soon as profit surfaces tax wax axe will drop and stock will land at $100.</Msg><Username>bogdanmiltchev</Username><Timestamp>1347285932620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:05:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347286579286-16</Id><Title>Shorts will be sad later today.</Title><Msg>Because AMZN will test 254 later today and many shorts here who saw their 255 puts expire worthless last Friday will realize that they got timing wrong. Comical, isn't it?</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347286579286</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347287059697-17</Id><Title>NTWK $5.3 UP 33c....BREAKING OUT!! NEW TARGET $16...NEW CLOUD DIVISION ANNOUNCEMENT IS HUGE!!..September 6, 2012. NTWK created a new division, NetSolCloudVM, that will offer infrastructure-as-a-service (IaaS), initially targeting the North American market. Set to launch in September as a division of NetSol North America, NetSolCloudVM will provide clients with IT infrastructure on a monthly tiered subscription basis</Title><Msg>NTWK'S OTHER CLOUD DIVISION VROOZI ALREADY EXPLODED IN REVENUES IN Q4 2012.. ACQUISITION CANDIDATE GUIDED FOR $1/SHARE NET INCOME ON 40% REVENUE GROWTH FOR 2013....................3M SHARE FLOAT......AFTER EARNINGS PROFIT TAKING OVER.....MAGNIFICENT CHART In its updated public cloud forecast in June, Gartner estimated that IaaS was the fastest growing cloud segment with a projected GAGR of 41.7%, and exceeding a $20 billion global market by 2016. "We made a calculated decision to enter this growing market given our years of experience as a software developer, the minimal investment required, and the revenue potential given just the breadth of our current relationships," said Najeeb Ghauri, chairman and CEO of NetSol. "I am fully confident in our highly capable team, reinforced by our talented group of IT professionals, to scale the business quickly and capture a portion of this burgeoning industry, creating an additional revenue driver and further diversifying our revenue mix by geography." "What we are offering, in essence, is private cloud performance at an elastic cloud price -- giving potential customers in our target market segment the performance, flexibility, reliability, and a no-nonsense fixed pricing model that they have long desired," added Imran Haider, COO of NetSol North America and head of NetSolCloudVM. "As a growing software company ourselves, we have critical insights into the efficiency and productivity needs of NetSolCloudVM's target customer base and look forward to unveiling our new services in the coming months." TARGET $10+ .......5 FWD P/E - WITH 30% 2013 GROWTH AND $1/SHARE NET INCOME IN 2013 NetSol Technologies Reported RECORD Fiscal Fourth Quarter and Year-End Results - 9/4/2012 - Fourth Quarter 2012 Revenue Surges to an all-time quarterly record of $14.3 Million on Increased License Revenues and associated maintenance and service agreements going forward - Fourth Quarter 2012 Earnings Advance Significantly to $0.25 per Diluted Share - Full Year 2012 revenues a record $38M - Full Year 2012 Earnings of $0.39/share - Company Expects Record Fiscal 2013 Annual Revenue Growing over 30% to $46 million to $49 million, With Earnings per Diluted Share Advancing to $0.80 to $1.00 - Per the CC, Company anticipates doubling revenues and net income by 2015 NTWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Only 3 million share float - Fast growing profitable US-based global cloud and license-based software company with 8 offices worldwide (US, China, Australia, UK, Pakistan, Singapore, Thailand, Saudi Arabia) – - Trading at 5 PE and 1 times sales – This is about 25% of sector average - Revenues are increasing at double digit rates, - Guidance calls for 30% revenue growth in 2013 - 3 consecutive quarters of profitability, - Guidance calls for $1/share net income in 2013!!! - Global alliances with Mercedes Benz and SANY Corp of China. - No. 1 in China and the APAC region in its niche market of leasing and financing software - It’s Vroozi Division is a fast growing Cloud Computing Play with strong relations with SAP, ORCL, MSFT. - Vroozi’s SAP-approved smartOCI procurement search catalog software built on SaaS is being adopted rapidly. Revenues exploded in 4Q 2012 and are expected to multiply in 2013 and a big reason for the 30%+ 2013 projected revenue increase - Vroozi has been created as independent entity to potentially IPO it or sell it to a cloud-acquiring giant like SAP and others - Strong balance sheet with $1/share Cash - With every license they sell a lucrative 5-year service and maintenance agreement building strong recurrent revenues - Huge and consistent insider buying. Insiders bought over 5% of the outstanding shares since 2010 - Strong institutional investor support grew to almost 20% from 11% last year - NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc.</Msg><Username>nick.jr40</Username><Timestamp>1347287059697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:24:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347287147081-18</Id><Title>Lotto Mania</Title><Msg>The stock market is 99% emotional near term. Problem right now is that the government is printing $ to pump up stocks. This will stop in the future due to loss of confidence in the scam, and the bubble stocks will collapse because there is no real earning or dividend to support current stock value. Right now, Scamazon is acting like a lottery ticket. Millions of buyers but only one winner...the few who sold at the top. No stock in the history of the market can sustain absurd valuation. They all collapse when reality does not meet expectation. Traders and the average investors are conditioned to act to make them feel good "right now", even though 99% of these people are wrong in the long term. Successful people filter out these short term noises and stay focused on the big picture. This is a Marathon. Those with a KISS steady approach will always come out on top with less stress</Msg><Username>nje457</Username><Timestamp>1347287147081</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:25:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347287457138-19</Id><Title>Lets see here- open interst on scam 260 strike weekly puts iz 475 contracts</Title><Msg>Lets see how many crackheadz throw their money away this week on this weekly scam...</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347287457138</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:30:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347287463103-20</Id><Title>Last QTR Net earnings only $7 million?...wow!</Title><Msg>How is this stock so expensive? This is unreal - I may have to short some. Unbelievable that Cramer would say buy....maybe he jinx Amazon.....lol.</Msg><Username>michael_d_angelo</Username><Timestamp>1347287463103</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:31:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347288718640-21</Id><Title>Ebook settlement and Ebook pricing</Title><Msg>Last weeks Kindle announcements, which so excited the Amazon fans, included a very explicit statement from Jeffy that he does not want to make money on the Kindle devices themselves but on the usage of the devices (does anyone want to tell me I heard this incorrectly). Last week in a legal finding, Judge Denise Cotes accepted the Ebook settlement with 3 publishers, which basically says that Amazon can go back to selling Ebooks at below cost. Jeff loves to go around telling everyone that they deserve low-cost Ebooks and I think he will have a customer revolt on his hands if he now tries to sell Ebooks for more the $9.99. I'm a little slow in understanding the business plan on this one. Where are the down-the-road earnings going to come from on the use of the Kindle's?</Msg><Username>bbyboomer50</Username><Timestamp>1347288718640</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:51:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347288737253-22</Id><Title>257.50 will be tested withn 18 minutes.</Title><Msg>That means in 36 minutes.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347288737253</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:52:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347288820927-23</Id><Title>Let me say, amzn taking share from Apple, Google, reason for</Title><Msg>the profit taking in those two</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1347288820927</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:53:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347290345706-24</Id><Title>caustion LONGS</Title><Msg>The stock will drop eventually by $30-80. You have been warned!</Msg><Username>bogdanmiltchev</Username><Timestamp>1347290345706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:19:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347292959203-25</Id><Topic><Title>PE of 317 #$%$</Title><Username>bogdanmiltchev</Username><Timestamp>1347277335388</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 07:42:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You just don't get it. I hope you're not investing in AMZN, since you don't understand the stock.</Msg><Username>barbaraspratling</Username><Timestamp>1347292959203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:02:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347293057881-26</Id><Topic><Title>caustion LONGS</Title><Username>bogdanmiltchev</Username><Timestamp>1347290345706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:19:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's "caution". We've been warned SO many times, and we keep making money!</Msg><Username>barbaraspratling</Username><Timestamp>1347293057881</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347293680500-27</Id><Title>AMZN is new apple...don't short</Title><Msg>This is heading to $345.</Msg><Username>checking_here</Username><Timestamp>1347293680500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347293950788-28</Id><Title>256.25 critical.</Title><Msg>If broken, 255 will be tested.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347293950788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:19:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347294511927-29</Id><Title>amazon to sell tickets</Title><Msg>Amazon is going to have a major news conference next week that starting soon you can pre-order ticket(s) $99 each to the Mars. Amazon will have the option to cancel the tickets if the space shuttle can not be built or for all other logistical problems. Pre-order now to reserve your flight...</Msg><Username>rimm_dn</Username><Timestamp>1347294511927</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:28:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347295504449-30</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN is new apple...don't short</Title><Username>checking_here</Username><Timestamp>1347293680500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:14:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This new message board format effin blows. Doesn't even load the reply button 80% of the time. I officially can't stand it anymore. The MB's were the last thing i used on Yahoo! Anyway, regarding your claim, the only problem with your theory is that AMZN hardware sucks and they don't have proprietary rights to their operating system. Besides that, the stock moves like AAPL. So cheers! Btw, should we expect an Amazon store soon in Grand Central?</Msg><Username>inursha</Username><Timestamp>1347295504449</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:45:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347295684484-31</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil's mouth is getting pretty dry</Title><Username>philandjoelle</Username><Timestamp>1347246675136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 23:11:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did I tell you how Sybil was wiped out by shorting CMG below 300? Dried up off the message board and blew away.........</Msg><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1347295684484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:48:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347296846974-32</Id><Title>Shorts here are very patient.</Title><Msg>Their patience will kill them. It's sad, really.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347296846974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:07:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347297667241-33</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN is new apple...don't short</Title><Username>checking_here</Username><Timestamp>1347293680500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:14:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'd be selling and taking profit ahead of iphone 5 launch!!</Msg><Username>cramerstrophywife</Username><Timestamp>1347297667241</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:21:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347297920615-34</Id><Title>TRUE STORY; I SHORTED AMZN AT $60 BACK IN THE DAY</Title><Msg>&amp; COVERED AT $60; GREAT TRADE; 100% TRUE</Msg><Username>sellbby</Username><Timestamp>1347297920615</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347297957645-35</Id><Title>320 PE LOOKIN A LIL TOPPY</Title><Msg>BY ABOUT $200</Msg><Username>sellbby</Username><Timestamp>1347297957645</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:25:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347298579457-36</Id><Title>Two serious questions for shorts here.</Title><Msg>Is shorting AMZN some kind of penance for you? What did you do to deserve this kind of suffering?</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347298579457</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:36:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347298828740-37</Id><Topic><Title>Two serious questions for shorts here.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347298579457</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:36:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would say buying here at $260 would be more of a suffering how much did you buy here? I knew it, none</Msg><Username>sellbby</Username><Timestamp>1347298828740</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347299404030-38</Id><Topic><Title>amazon to sell tickets</Title><Username>rimm_dn</Username><Timestamp>1347294511927</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In fact, after seeing no one is really impressed by the offer, Bezos paused and said, you can also pre-order your personal vehicle to the Mars or anywhere in the universe using N-G technology for only $499. Now are you impressed by amazon's once in a life offer ???</Msg><Username>rimm_dn</Username><Timestamp>1347299404030</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:50:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347300117250-39</Id><Title>What do you think about EUFN ?</Title><Msg>any good advice ?</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1347300117250</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347300388523-40</Id><Topic><Title>Two serious questions for shorts here.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347298579457</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:36:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've been all cash since last Friday's close. Waiting for the next call buying opportunity. At least I'm not trapped with any short positions.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347300388523</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:06:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347300569636-41</Id><Title>longs counting hours of pain and frustration .... Yes , down it comes and ends lower and lower ...</Title><Msg>PE of 317 for a mature company is a call to sell</Msg><Username>bogdanmiltchev</Username><Timestamp>1347300569636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347301091767-42</Id><Title>AMZN PE</Title><Msg>about 100...AAPL about 13...I just do not get people buying AMZN.........The day of reckoning will come...I just do not know when.</Msg><Username>eelong1945</Username><Timestamp>1347301091767</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:18:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347301411745-43</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN PE</Title><Username>eelong1945</Username><Timestamp>1347301091767</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:18:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is irrational exuberance, but difficult for longs that have done well to comprehend. For Amazon to depend on the Kindle to propel them above $300 may be far fetched. I do not see that product doing that well up against the ipad or other devices even with the sort of free service. I am looking objectively and on another note, I have seen the tablets and I am amazed with the ipads, but I am more of a laptop person...owning 2 of them, one the mac air, the other the MGP....lol.</Msg><Username>michael_d_angelo</Username><Timestamp>1347301411745</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:23:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347302050724-44</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN PE</Title><Username>eelong1945</Username><Timestamp>1347301091767</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:18:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about earnings over last 3 years: March June Sept Dec 2010 .66 .45 .51 .91 2011 .44 .41 ..14 .38 2012 .28 .02 Are these the earnings of a 100 PE stock??</Msg><Username>eelong1945</Username><Timestamp>1347302050724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:34:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347302250050-45</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN PE</Title><Username>eelong1945</Username><Timestamp>1347301091767</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:18:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone is getting on the tablet bandwagon...AAPL, MSFT, HP, DELL, AMZN, GOOG, Samsung, Vizio, Barn &amp; Noble, Toy R US, and countless no-name mfrs. This is a huge bubble about to pop. After a major consolidation, we will have three players (AAPL, MSFT, and Samsung).</Msg><Username>nje457</Username><Timestamp>1347302250050</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:37:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347302826722-46</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN PE</Title><Username>eelong1945</Username><Timestamp>1347301091767</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:18:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point! Who is next, Sesame Street or Crackle Barrel.....lol.</Msg><Username>michael_d_angelo</Username><Timestamp>1347302826722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:47:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347303436820-47</Id><Title>Lower Cash, Slower Growth, No Earnings, Stock Doubled?</Title><Msg>Makes sense. Take $117B (amzn's market cap) and buy a 10 year treasure notes and you will get almost $2B in cash with no risk to principal. What do you get with amzn? temporary bump maybe or wicked sell-off when reality hits.</Msg><Username>dutchboyinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347303436820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:57:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347303541921-48</Id><Title>Facebook shares will hit the $5 area within three months.</Title><Msg>Move your money out of FB and shove it into AMZN.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347303541921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:59:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347305239316-49</Id><Topic><Title>NTWK $5.3 UP 33c....BREAKING OUT!! NEW TARGET $16...NEW CLOUD DIVISION ANNOUNCEMENT IS HUGE!!..September 6, 2012. NTWK created a new division, NetSolCloudVM, that will offer infrastructure-as-a-service (IaaS), initially targeting the North American market. Set to launch in September as a division of NetSol North America, NetSolCloudVM will provide clients with IT infrastructure on a monthly tiered subscription basis</Title><Username>nick.jr40</Username><Timestamp>1347287059697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:24:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just the start of a massive rally. Significantly higher upside than this one because NTWK will double in a hurry</Msg><Username>joeyggrecco</Username><Timestamp>1347305239316</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:27:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347305277326-50</Id><Topic><Title>NTWK $5.3 UP 33c....BREAKING OUT!! NEW TARGET $16...NEW CLOUD DIVISION ANNOUNCEMENT IS HUGE!!..September 6, 2012. NTWK created a new division, NetSolCloudVM, that will offer infrastructure-as-a-service (IaaS), initially targeting the North American market. Set to launch in September as a division of NetSol North America, NetSolCloudVM will provide clients with IT infrastructure on a monthly tiered subscription basis</Title><Username>nick.jr40</Username><Timestamp>1347287059697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:24:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just the start of a massive rally. Significantly higher upside than this one because NTWK will double in a hurry</Msg><Username>joeyggrecco</Username><Timestamp>1347305277326</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:27:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347305278782-51</Id><Topic><Title>NTWK $5.3 UP 33c....BREAKING OUT!! NEW TARGET $16...NEW CLOUD DIVISION ANNOUNCEMENT IS HUGE!!..September 6, 2012. NTWK created a new division, NetSolCloudVM, that will offer infrastructure-as-a-service (IaaS), initially targeting the North American market. Set to launch in September as a division of NetSol North America, NetSolCloudVM will provide clients with IT infrastructure on a monthly tiered subscription basis</Title><Username>nick.jr40</Username><Timestamp>1347287059697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:24:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just the start of a massive rally. Significantly higher upside than this one because NTWK will double in a hurry</Msg><Username>joeyggrecco</Username><Timestamp>1347305278782</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:27:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347305424850-52</Id><Title>Investors got scared of Toys R Us news</Title><Msg>I hear that Toys R Us will take over the Tablet market next year. LOL!! sorry that what I hear from some people on the street.</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1347305424850</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:30:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347305991251-53</Id><Topic><Title>longs counting hours of pain and frustration .... Yes , down it comes and ends lower and lower ...</Title><Username>bogdanmiltchev</Username><Timestamp>1347300569636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pain and frustration? I bought at $135 3 years ago, it's over $250. YOu know nothing about Amazon, you probably don't own any stocks. Pain and frustration???</Msg><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1347305991251</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:39:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347306711189-54</Id><Title>This sell off, is Amazon taking share from APPLE! will be 265</Title><Msg>soon</Msg><Username>riskreversal777</Username><Timestamp>1347306711189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347308908975-55</Id><Topic><Title>Facebook shares will hit the $5 area within three months.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347303541921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:59:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly the opposite of what any decent INVESTOR would be doing. I hope FB announces some major social commerce play...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1347308908975</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347314820159-56</Id><Topic><Title>Facebook shares will hit the $5 area within three months.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347303541921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:59:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If FB were to trade at the same earnings multiple as AMZN it would be $90. If AMZN were to trade at the same Multiple as FB, it would be $53. To dangerous trying to call a top for AMZN, but when the wheels come off ( and they will eventually ) AMZN will be headed to $50.</Msg><Username>marketman219</Username><Timestamp>1347314820159</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347316048446-57</Id><Title>Skiidaddy the dope was wrong on nflx, wrong on cmg and he's wrong on amzn</Title><Msg>Sybil has beat this dicklessclown over and over again. Sybil made arsloads of coin in the process of working this pumper over, yet he insists that sybil iz wrong and still hasnt figured out where his $500.00 of etrade money went...... Notice how all these idiots say 'sybil went broke on pcln' and 'sybil lost on nflx', or 'sybil covered pcln from 550 to 774' AFTER they all tanked while in the middle of idiots like skiidady and 'philjoe' pumping them.... Amzn is another case where sybil will make a sheitload on the short side while the pumperz fantisize sybil covering huge losses on ficticious numbers that they assign. Plain and simple, amzn will remain flat until wed to ring out leveraged shorts, and the retrace... If it doesnt retrace then amzn will leg up again to fvck a new batch of leveraged shorts to a higher level where sybil will short another batch to 'subtract' another lot from a HUGE pile of existing borrowed sharez... Stoopids</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347316048446</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347316443076-58</Id><Title>This market iz fvcked, its filled with pig stox like amzn</Title><Msg>Sybil iz a "dirty short" thats going to watch the whole pile of sheit swirl aroubd the bowl and flushhhhh - wwwwoooosssshhhhhh, baby... Sybil ownz the sewer plant and is going to charge buyerz and pumperz stox a hefty premium to process their sheit stox....</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347316443076</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:34:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347317564187-59</Id><Title>Hey stoopids - heeeeeeeeeeere's sybil!</Title><Msg>Get ready for lower highs and lower lows to rope some dopes. After a while we can expect to see some cascading water fall drops around the time of q3 reports... More idiots will buy at 160 for a bounce to 180-190 (sybil reshorts 160 coverz).... Get ready for a fun ride fvckerz...</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347317564187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:52:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347318816918-60</Id><Topic><Title>Hey stoopids - heeeeeeeeeeere's sybil!</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347317564187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:52:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kind of sad, isn't it? "Sybil" is a deranged woman.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347318816918</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:13:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347319162343-61</Id><Title>Who bought goldman sac's target price of 260.00?</Title><Msg>Most likely it wasnt a long, but it could have been someone drunk on koolaid. Chances are it was a deceased brokedick retail short that could take no more and did himself in with at "stop loss - buy to cover - 5 shares @ 260.00". Ooor it could have been an institutional bot that inadvertanty bought the $260 mark while holding that hot potato "bid" up on the board for 10 miliseconds too long..... Hmmmmmmmmmm.... Sybil wonderz, who bought 260? Some poor soul or their robot had to.</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347319162343</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347319560230-62</Id><Title>Sybil had a hard day... Sybil worked the mcd's fry vats and covered at 260.00 to satisfy a margin call</Title><Msg>That really didnt happen but some idot will bash sybs so this makes their job easier. Sybil likes to help when possible.</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347319560230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:26:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347319591689-63</Id><Title>$AONE A123 Systems (AONE) Hit Volatility Trading Pause today on Massive Price Spike!! Rallying in After Hours RIGHT NOW!! AMZN PCFG AUMY</Title><Msg>$AONE A123 Systems (Nasdaq AONE) Hit Volatility Trading Pause today on Massive Price Spike!! Rallying in After Hours RIGHT NOW!! AMZN PCFG AUMY</Msg><Username>hogolddigger</Username><Timestamp>1347319591689</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:26:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347319886495-64</Id><Title>Spammers found a new way to molest the 'new and improved' yahoo board format...</Title><Msg>They cant place hyperlinks so now they pump stupid stox with page long subject headers</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347319886495</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:31:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347320662736-65</Id><Title>Seekingaplha: AMZN should be less than $180</Title><Msg>Read under yahoo. Just released.</Msg><Username>cybercash28</Username><Timestamp>1347320662736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:44:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347321280545-66</Id><Title>RETAIL LEAP PUT WEAPON ON USA FRAUD STREET CASINO AND SCAMAZON IS BEST</Title><Msg>THIS NOT WALL STREET ..IT FRAUD STREET CASINO RETAIL...................REVENGE AND WIN IS IN LEAP PUTS JAN 2014</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1347321280545</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:54:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347321750321-67</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil had a hard day... Sybil worked the mcd's fry vats and covered at 260.00 to satisfy a margin call</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347319560230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:26:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They let you go tranny at Mickie D's?????</Msg><Username>skiidady5</Username><Timestamp>1347321750321</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 20:02:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347325334617-68</Id><Title>Rob Enderle is a complete #$%$..</Title><Msg>Even worse than Mark Mahaney. As stupid as they come. Just wrote an article how Amazon is going to crush Apple because Apple cannot match Amazon's prices, therefore AMZN will dominate the tablet market. A few points. 1) Apple has superior hardware unit economics. As the largest purchaser of electronic components in the world, it has pricing power with all suppliers. It also has superior marketing/promotion economics as it reaches a wider audience than Amazon with fewer SKUs to promote. 2) All of the "spin" on the ebook ruling is that it is great for Amazon because it can now cut prices. But, AMAZON'S MODEL IS NOW ENTIRELY DEPENDENT UPON REALIZING ITS PROFITS FROM CONTENT. The irony is priceless. Apple and Google can simply undercut Amazon's content pricing across the board by 10% and Amazon is hosed. The DOJ will have NO CASE against them because it forced the issue in the first place. It is a business model competition and one that Apple and Google will win by getting hardware costs relatively close to Amazon and then undercutting on content (plus, they should find some infringing IP and file a suit to boot). Apple's Pandora like play is just the beginning. Expect it and Google to launch a NFLX like service as well. When it is all said and done, Amazon will find that it can extract very little in the way of rents on digital content. And it will have burned insane cash on the experiment... The point is that Apple and Google have the cash to take the fight to Amazon on kick it in the #$%$ And, now that this is just good old business model competition that Amazon started, no one will be able to protect it...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1347325334617</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347327201857-69</Id><Topic><Title>Rob Enderle is a complete #$%$..</Title><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1347325334617</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:02:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rob and most of the analyst community seems to be living in the past on this issue. Now, Apple and Google can attack Amazon's cash generating machine with impunity. Amazon sells hardware at a loss. They can sell content at cost, ensuring near zero content profit contribution for Amazon. How long will Amazon soar in that environment??? It's going to create a very interesting survival challenge over the next 2 years since it has exploding overhead/fixed costs and personnel costs (and when the stock stops going up, other compensation will have to increase to retain people since the valuation scam will no longer create wealth for top performing employees). The bottom line is whatever price Amazon can offer on content, Apple and Google can offer a better one because that it not where THEY make they majority of their money (and they generate 10's of billions in profits a year that they can afford to deploy strategically to blunt Amazon's consumer value proposition).</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1347327201857</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347327513800-70</Id><Topic><Title>Rob Enderle is a complete #$%$..</Title><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1347325334617</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:02:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post - thumbs up dude.... Amzn iz a scam bubble that iz ran out of reasons at 125 but still seemed to make it to 260... Its the short of a lifetime as current shorts short the past shorts' big ball squeeze.</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347327513800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:38:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347327726528-71</Id><Title>ProfitBricks...</Title><Msg>Just came across this. Google "profitbricks-targets-amazon-rackspace-with-per-minute-cloud-pricing" (certainly don't Bing/Yahoo it... boycott until they fix these pages...) A little more competition with a more flexible model is always a good thing. Maybe Google picks these folks up to improve its cloud offerings...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1347327726528</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347328277445-72</Id><Topic><Title>longs counting hours of pain and frustration .... Yes , down it comes and ends lower and lower ...</Title><Username>bogdanmiltchev</Username><Timestamp>1347300569636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bruce the harmonica guy also plays the organ and the skin flute... He should be thinking of selling the 3 shares he bought 3 years ago... Its a double bruce...</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347328277445</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:51:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347328479667-73</Id><Topic><Title>$AONE A123 Systems (AONE) Hit Volatility Trading Pause today on Massive Price Spike!! Rallying in After Hours RIGHT NOW!! AMZN PCFG AUMY</Title><Username>hogolddigger</Username><Timestamp>1347319591689</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is a penny stock now, you are on your own risk....</Msg><Username>me_novice</Username><Timestamp>1347328479667</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:54:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347328500834-74</Id><Topic><Title>Facebook shares will hit the $5 area within three months.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347303541921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:59:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tech, fb is a scam of rich dudes dumping their one time illiquid private equity on the backs of the sheeple using the public markets as a vehicle to do so... Fb will continue to get hammered because that is what is working now and will continue to work until the s&amp;p finds long term trend value somewhere in the 450 range.... Stox are scamz bro - plain and simple... There are no sacred cows in a fraud market....</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347328500834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:55:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347330645638-75</Id><Topic><Title>Facebook shares will hit the $5 area within three months.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347303541921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:59:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But there is always internal rotation and reallocation. The long only investors behind this will be selling and buying FB because FB has a LOT more support for its valuation should things get ugly (starting with 25% of its market cap in cash and a higher ROIC/cash generating business).</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1347330645638</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:30:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347331169469-76</Id><Topic><Title>Facebook shares will hit the $5 area within three months.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347303541921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:59:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMZN goes $350 in dec. Buy</Msg><Username>listen_jockers</Username><Timestamp>1347331169469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:39:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347331348203-77</Id><Topic><Title>Facebook shares will hit the $5 area within three months.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347303541921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:59:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are no sacred cows in a market full of pigs.... FB will be 7.00-10.00 - 50 or 60% lower... If rich dudez are getting pummeled to breaking even the imagine whats in store for the sheeple? A sign of a market turn is failed ipo's. there are plenty of other signs indicating these markets are fvcked as well.... So sybil asks why lose 50% on fb when you coulddivest of amzn and make 80%? Dont over think it into stoopidity tech... Just listen to sybil, and you'll be ok... There's no rotation anywhere but out of stox....</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347331348203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347331681904-78</Id><Topic><Title>Facebook shares will hit the $5 area within three months.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347303541921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:59:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not long FB right now. Sold some puts, so I might own it if it falls a lot. GMCR served me rather well but I am out again now (I take some pride in having pivoted to long at $17 and taking abuse from shorts on that board after having been short it at $110 while taking abuse from longs and having made the right call both times based upon fundamentals, although I have to admit that I think what drove it was the rumor of the day that Einhorn was covering...) Fundamentals do actually matter as AMZN longs will find out the hard way.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1347331681904</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:48:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347331792518-79</Id><Title>Amzn is on the green mile</Title><Msg>Its about to get fried....</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1347331792518</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347333256443-80</Id><Topic><Title>NTWK $5.3 UP 33c....BREAKING OUT!! NEW TARGET $16...NEW CLOUD DIVISION ANNOUNCEMENT IS HUGE!!..September 6, 2012. NTWK created a new division, NetSolCloudVM, that will offer infrastructure-as-a-service (IaaS), initially targeting the North American market. Set to launch in September as a division of NetSol North America, NetSolCloudVM will provide clients with IT infrastructure on a monthly tiered subscription basis</Title><Username>nick.jr40</Username><Timestamp>1347287059697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:24:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NTWK has been up every day after a minor post-record earnings profit taking. The stock is just starting to rally and with a 3 million share float $15 soon is just around the corner (see chart). That would make it a 12 forward PE which is conservative for a company expecting to deliver $1/share net income and grow revenues 40% in 2013.........still very cheap even at $15. More importantly it's cloud division Vroozi is growing exponentially and they just announced another North America cloud business unit. Larger companies are swallowing fast growing enterprise cloud providers with SAP and ORCL certification and compatibility. NTWK has a much greater upside than AMZN......NTWK will for sure double/triple or more. AMZN is maxed out and will NEVER reach $500 or higher</Msg><Username>nick.jr40</Username><Timestamp>1347333256443</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 23:14:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347334361387-81</Id><Title>#$%$ bought all the way to 260, every buyer today is a bagholder way to start my puts out in the green</Title><Msg>I told you, you should be loading in RENN long and getting oct jan apr puts on Scamazon The scamazon song will go something like this I loaded in Amazon because of the messiah kindle fire Soon amzn was suppose to go 350 and even me the crackhead can retire. But only 10% OF THE KINDLES WE MADE MOVED AND SCAMAZON LOST ITS GROOVE ALL BECAUSE OF ANOTHER 600 TOY 20 MILLION GALAXY S 3 IN 100 DAYS OH BOY AT 100 MILLION BY JANUARY BEZOS WILL SAY TO SHAREHOLDERS NOBODY COULD HAVE SEEN THIS HAPPENING OR PREDICTED SAMSUNG CORNERING THE MARKET AS GOOD AS THEY COULD. BUT WHAT DO YOU DO WHEN YOU CAN'T SELL PRODUCTS YOU ALREADY DECIDED TO SELL AT COST? WELL YOU EAT A BIG LOSS, EAT A BIG LOSS, EAT A BIG LOSS AND EVEN A POOR MAN WHO WAS HOLDING A TON OF WAY OUT OF THE MONEY PUTS GETS RICH WHEN AMAZON GOES TOWARDS 50. ONLY IN AMERICA, THIS IS THE NEXT NFLX GMCR SCAM CRASH ON BAD NEWS!</Msg><Username>classactionlawsuitsonnakedshrts</Username><Timestamp>1347334361387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 23:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347335271858-82</Id><Title>175 SUPER FAST FROM THIS LEVEL LAST TIME CAN YOU IMAGINE?</Title><Msg>How much money will be made off the puts here if the market gets bad around election time or a big fight about the results most of us know will already be a scam but can anybody prove it, do they have the guts? if you look at the max charts on bidu and amzn you will see just what renn is about to do, go straight up for a long time, that stock has a reason to trade funny and it has been, what is scamazons reason? 175 came so fast from right where we are currently. Dang acting a little strange also, when the volume comes back to those two, wow they will be fun to trade in and out of.</Msg><Username>classactionlawsuitsonnakedshrts</Username><Timestamp>1347335271858</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 23:47:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>