<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347770814141-1</Id><Topic><Title>Sold some at $260</Title><Username>barbaraspratling</Username><Timestamp>1347672442581</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 21:27:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The wisdom of decisions is based upon the set of information one has available at the point in time they are made. Those that make decisions where the distribution of potential outcomes (risk/return profile) is systematically skewed in their favor will outperform over time. Any institutional long accumulating at this valuation given the micro uncertainties (tax impact, AAPL eBook price competition, kindle success) and macro (too many to list) is simply negligent IMHO... Ski, you gotta do more homework. I'm not going to share the answer key. I already schooled you badly on CMG and will school you here as well (would have responded directly to your attack, but either you or the Yahoo police have killed the reply button on that post).</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1347770814141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 00:46:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347785143784-2</Id><Title>Another translation of Techstrategy's Nonsense</Title><Msg>"The wisdom of decisions is based on blah, blah...over time..." He must be referring to the fact that at one point in the short term he claims to have made some money shorting stocks but that now the time factor is setting in and he on a trend that will lead over time to his racking up huge losses.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1347785143784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 04:45:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347806923465-3</Id><Topic><Title>Another translation of Techstrategy's Nonsense</Title><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1347785143784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 04:45:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's actually quite humorous. He's obviously a paper trader as nobody could withstand his losses.</Msg><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1347806923465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:48:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347816534053-4</Id><Title>AMZN at PE of 318 unsustainable</Title><Msg>AMZN's extremely high PE is said to be because of very high technology expenses to generate revenue growth with the expectation that when they reduce technology expenditures profit margins will increase. They plan to add more warehouses to support same day delivery so that means expenditures are not going to go away for a while so AMZN will continue to report losses and negative cash flow and PE will keep rising. Stock buyers are putting a bet that when they do reduce expenditures PE will come down but it may still be too high. Besides when they reduce expenditures it's safe to assume that revenue growth will decline also. So then the question would be would investors still pay a premium on PE if revenues don't grow as much? It's very iffy business model (spend today, reap profits tomorrow - but what environment is different tomorrow and and those expectations are not realized). To generate more revenues, they are selling Fire devices at cost or even below cost when you factor in S&amp;A expenses. Also, California will add sales tax on Internet sales and that will spread to other states - no one knows how this would negatively affect AMZN's sales. In cloud tecg area there are other competitors so any future growth is speculative and not guaranteed given we are in a global competitive world. So the risk/reward ratio is definitely turning very negative for AMZN on valuation basis. Yes, momentum has carried it this far, but now we are at a point of diminishing return - everything has a limit.</Msg><Username>sm081969</Username><Timestamp>1347816534053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 13:28:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347821459715-5</Id><Title>The rotten shorts....</Title><Msg>The creme de la creme of the low lifes. They have no conscience and could care less if their neighbor loses $$$$. Many get paid for trashing stocks. i haven't had any wood in the fire for a few years, but If you don't care about your neighbor, you will lose in the end....</Msg><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1347821459715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 14:50:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347824304919-6</Id><Topic><Title>Another translation of Techstrategy's Nonsense</Title><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1347785143784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 04:45:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is where you are wrong. Having been an entrepreneur for a decade, the pain from financial losses is trivial. Ever had to let 75% of your people go? A small business is a family and you care about those who work for you. That's pain. Riding out a short term squeeze on a preposterously valued stock that is at its peak vulnerability despite all the hype, that's not remotely hard. Besides, I could lose all my money and start over just fine. I'm very lucky. I went to Kellogg in the late 90's when it was ranked #1. I worked with world class, decent human beings at McKinsey for 4 years and then I spent over a decade trying to build our science based (specifically nano) entreprenuial ecosystem and commercial next Gen technologies with people are doing things that matter and will eventually change the world and rebuild this country through innovation and productivity, rather than financial innovation and trading... It has been one helluva tough ride. Even should the market take my money (which isn't happening, but I'd be lying if I said it was impossible for me to lose), it cannot take my knowledge, my experience, nor my relationships. More importantly, I've got an amazing wife and five kids that are what gives meaning to my life, not the few bucks I might make investing in the markets... To each his own. Will see soon enough who proves to be right on this one...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1347824304919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:38:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347839174432-7</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN at PE of 318 unsustainable</Title><Username>sm081969</Username><Timestamp>1347816534053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 13:28:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read latest articles from Seeking Alpha this weekend saying AMZN is the juice shorts and way overpriced. Be patient. With the new sales tax law, lass people will buy. Tax plus shipping cost, it is better to buy locally.</Msg><Username>cybercash28</Username><Timestamp>1347839174432</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 19:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347841982659-8</Id><Topic><Title>Another translation of Techstrategy's Nonsense</Title><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1347785143784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 04:45:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good attitude - I like it.</Msg><Username>dutchboyinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347841982659</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 20:33:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347845686523-9</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN at PE of 318 unsustainable</Title><Username>sm081969</Username><Timestamp>1347816534053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 13:28:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea the pe ratio will be unsustainable when it reaches the cost of the new kindle HD recall when amzn first came on the scene no profit and a similar pe where did that get you?</Msg><Username>babybackribsrule</Username><Timestamp>1347845686523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:34:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347849547746-10</Id><Topic><Title>Another translation of Techstrategy's Nonsense</Title><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1347785143784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 04:45:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It has been one helluva tough ride. Even should the market take my money (which isn't happening, but I'd be lying if I said it was impossible for me to lose), it cannot take my knowledge, my experience, nor my relationships. More importantly, I've got an amazing wife and five kids that are what gives meaning to my life, not the few bucks I might make investing in the markets..." That's not a good attitude when you're in a fight. For one reason or another you picked a fight against one of the most magnificent stocks, and you've been losing for weeks (if not for months or years). You have to do something about this whole situation NOW. There are only two things which can happen from now: your situation gets worse or gets better. But remember that your situation is worse than when you started this fight. So the situation getting better from this point on does not guarantee your winning (making a profit). It is likely to be only making your loss diminished somewhat, at best.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1347849547746</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 22:39:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347853093876-11</Id><Topic><Title>Another translation of Techstrategy's Nonsense</Title><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1347785143784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 04:45:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Geeg, you misunderstand me. Being an entrepreneur for a decade has been a really rough fight. Investing in the markets, not at all. I am once again down overall in Amazon, but a relatively trivial amount (I made a lot last fall and prior to earnings). And I've made plenty elsewhere to continue this fight. And, it is a fight I welcome. Geeg, I will reprioritize my investments as necessary, but I will be here holding an even larger position when the scam breaks. As I said, not remotely concerned about this scam...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1347853093876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 23:38:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347853579487-12</Id><Topic><Title>Another translation of Techstrategy's Nonsense</Title><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1347785143784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 04:45:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the way, did you see the flaw in your attempt at Algebra? It must be a blind spot for you because the implication there as in your post above is that AMZN cannot/will not go down. At least Bruce understands the more complete distribution of potential returns...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1347853579487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 23:46:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>