<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349583831098-1</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN earnigs growth required to justify current stock price</Title><Username>gb0743</Username><Timestamp>1349472502746</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 17:28:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one seems to care about AMZN's valuation and it's stock keep going up. It has the high PEG ratio in the industry - almost 1.5 times the industry average and it's P/E ratio is also 1.5 timies the industry average. AMZN is no longer the cheapest option for a number of products - Walmart online is often cheaper for common items after considering that both AMZN and WMT charge Sales Tax now. AMZN stock is way overpriced and it isn't worth any more than $100.</Msg><Username>actingarmi</Username><Timestamp>1349583831098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 00:23:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349588458806-2</Id><Topic><Title>Money coming out of IBM and shoved into AMZN</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1264000045000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2010-01-20 10:07:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You guys do know that both IBM and AMZN are manipulated by the same bad people. They love screwing shorts.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1349588458806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 01:40:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349607793173-3</Id><Topic><Title>Will be a bad quarter</Title><Username>buford_puser</Username><Timestamp>1349554093629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:08:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't see how you can do anything but go short here, possibly 150 points down after the election and maybe 10-15 points up until the election, and if the kendels don't sell even at cost or a loss look out 85 is possible, not 185....just 85! Hot money leaves as fast as it comes in, the bulls in Amazon always seem to forget that, netflix could drop 20 points, 15 easy in a 1 or 2 day period. I keep telling you same recipe in effect on RENN that they pulled on Bidu, kill the stock over a 2 year period, get all the shares then run it over 100 very quickly so to leave the little guy out!, Watch the oct calls for a triple in Oct priced in on the options!</Msg><Username>classactionlawsuitsonnakedshrts</Username><Timestamp>1349607793173</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 07:03:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349610043773-4</Id><Title>50 down or 30 up, puts are really expensive, whole world looking for major tankage from SCAMAZON!</Title><Msg>They are trying super hard to hold this up. Just like the players, the former underwriters for BIDU as well as RENN are trying even harder to keep RENN down, of course it is about to triple next week or the week after, the specialist has been front loading and seriously good news is expected, pr's are a huge deal with RENN becase Master CEO CHEN does not do fluff pr's or #$%$ ones of any kind ever, only serious pr's from CHEN. I have mentioned many times why the Kendel will be the biggest mistake and the most gigantic flop Amazon has ever had but here are a few The Ipad The Google Nexus Samsung Tablet back on the market The Nook The Samsung Galaxy s3 (parents can keep track of kids with a pone, it is a gift to them also) The Samsung note 2 the kids can draw on it And the Nintendo wii u already selling out everywhere preorder style The Ipad mini Nice expensive 1000.00 bicycles with gas going higher and higher, and everything worse after Obama wins the election, then he does not have to try anymore, we are talking about a guy that went back on his promise to end tax cuts for the rich immediately, bailed out wall street guys, and rammed a healthcare bill his 1st 2 years when that should have been all about jo#$%$, he deserves to lose for those reasons alone, he wainted till he could not do anything to all the sudden want to do all these things, we could have been building better roads, bridges, how about renovate and build better bathrooms in what has become a 3rd world hell hole because of all the pos illegals popping out 12-14 kids with 6 different daddies that we pay for, then the dog takes back the little maker who moves in with her and lives free and drinks beer all day and abuses the poor girls and picks on the boys, mexican and indians are almost always trash, that is why they ryhme with trash can. Does it look like any money is left to buy the kindle that is not even that good and full of advertising, bezos is late to the game and he should have cut a deal for more data for less money or he is going to have a ton of paperweights he can't even sell at cost!</Msg><Username>classactionlawsuitsonnakedshrts</Username><Timestamp>1349610043773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 07:40:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349611197809-5</Id><Topic><Title>50 down or 30 up, puts are really expensive, whole world looking for major tankage from SCAMAZON!</Title><Username>classactionlawsuitsonnakedshrts</Username><Timestamp>1349610043773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 07:40:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Class your right about RENN, the company they were 2 years agow when they launched at 28 are not even close to what they have today. 1.5 Billion in Cash Richest man in the entire country of China now on the RENN board of directors. A groupon site better then groupon. Nuomi online TV site that reaches 285 million viewers, good tv they like is very difficult to see in China, An auction site, An Amazon site, A cell phone videogame site geared towards the newest best smartphones, (they even keep 4 out of the top 20 games constantly on the charts. RENN RENN china facebook but better, growing faster, better mobile technology and 35% logging in and starying on by CELL PHONE, this is huge. And perhaps most telling, they have 9 to 29 year old male and female locked up exclusively to RENN with 5 billion more online users to come online within the next 5 years! And after the handover and change of power, the largest stimulus China has ever seen to jumpstart it and get it back going as well as the global economy. That is before 2012 or 1st week of it, if the new people in their have to talk about maybe going even bigger the the biggest ever, we are at the end of a 3 year slowdown in China and a 3 year downtrend in China stocks, frankly I am excited when Chen and his Billionaire Bulldog says they will not be happy "until RENN has a 100 Billion market cap minimum" He said his company is so underpriced and overlooked by Wall Street he feels insulted, I happen to agree with him! If I told the board how many things I have gone without that I usually blow money on to get more long in Renn then I have any stock in the last 25 years, you would not believe me. I started buying stocks at 12 years old out of newsweek magazine and a fullservice broker, my 1st or second stock was biotechnology group that did not move for years, when it finally did wow. I have plenty of money mainly due to the fact I got in Sina and Bidu at just the right times. I am very short Amazon, instead of losing premiums and watching puts expire worthless for months till the big fall, I have chose to short Amzn and hold it for as long as I possibly can, if the market goes down as much as I think it could, I might cover 90 or 100, course that is with Amazon really screwing up and not just the market correction doing that.</Msg><Username>interactivebrokerssucks20soon</Username><Timestamp>1349611197809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 07:59:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349615241480-6</Id><Topic><Title>Money coming out of IBM and shoved into AMZN</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1264000045000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2010-01-20 10:07:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi geegenjar, Thanks for the broker info earlier! I'm all set up and ready to start trading tomorrow. :-) But what's this about AMZN and IBM being manipulated?? No stock can be manipulated, it just moves from people buying and selling, right? If some people were changing it themselves it wouldn't be fair to everyone!! ~Jenni</Msg><Username>sparkle.jenni</Username><Timestamp>1349615241480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349616590102-7</Id><Topic><Title>Will be a bad quarter</Title><Username>buford_puser</Username><Timestamp>1349554093629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:08:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Scamazon has to tack on a $15 ads-free fee to recoup the $ losing Fire HD! The Fire HD is already inferior to Nexus 7. Why would anyone pay a $15 premium for an inferior product?</Msg><Username>nje457</Username><Timestamp>1349616590102</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:29:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349623196385-8</Id><Topic><Title>Will be a bad quarter</Title><Username>buford_puser</Username><Timestamp>1349554093629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:08:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nje457 well could be the biggest loser short on this message board. He claims he established his core short position last October when AMZN was around 240. He saw AMZN dive to 170s in December 2011. Didn't take any profit. In January of this year he saw AMZN dive to 160s. He didn't take any profit. Then AMZN started climbing back up. Instead of taking a profit, he started going for scalping on occasional pops making nickels and dimes. But he got caught on 1000-share lot at 196 a few months ago. He doesn't know how to take a small loss, so he's still hanging onto it. Now that AMZN is above $246.11 (last October's high), he's lost all the profit he once had (on paper) on his core-short position as well. He put me on "ignore" a long time ago, so he doesn't answer my question asking how big his core-position is. Can somebody ask him how big his-core position is and also if he has additional shorts he made this year aside from the one made at 196?</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1349623196385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:19:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349629440803-9</Id><Topic><Title>oh no!! AMZN is down 40 cents!!! lol!</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1349439312895</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 08:15:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For some reason i couldn't reply to your post on this .. so i figured i would repy here... Re: Re: Re: Re: Re: Goog Pullback To $650 This Week By frtgrdn21 . Sep 12, 2012 8:24 AM . Permalink Another $8 down the drain yesterday. Lets see how much it will bleed out today, despite the markets opening in the green. The real punishment will come in the next two days. Book it! Remember i said i would not only book it.. but buy more shares? well on sept 12 at the time of your post it was 690 a share... and now its 767.65.... Hurtsie Durtsie.... and now i see you are trying your same nonsense with Amazon... lol....</Msg><Username>chillen2307</Username><Timestamp>1349629440803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:04:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349646838388-10</Id><Topic><Title>Will be a bad quarter</Title><Username>buford_puser</Username><Timestamp>1349554093629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:08:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But it has been a terrible quarter for shorts here. The damage has been done.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1349646838388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349652661145-11</Id><Topic><Title>Will be a bad quarter</Title><Username>buford_puser</Username><Timestamp>1349554093629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:08:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow iif that is true, that is some horrible trading indeed. NFLX will make a new 52 week low pretty soon, everytime it goes up 10 or so points, all those new people end up bagholders. AMZN to 170 will happen again, I just feel the kendel will be a disaster and big chargeoff like znga with the 95 mill. I wonder how many are going to load up on weekly puts and how many get weekly calls also for AMZN earnings znga could go to 75 cents intraday to set a bottom then finish at 95 cents or a dollar. GRPN is not done reeling in new bagholders, the 3's will be tested. Also GOOG has to top out soon! Very interesting time to be not IN THE MARKET but trading it with puts 90%</Msg><Username>classactionlawsuitsonnakedshrts</Username><Timestamp>1349652661145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:31:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349653050905-12</Id><Topic><Title>Markets ain't buying O'bummer's FAKE jobs report.</Title><Username>ershon911</Username><Timestamp>1349466265926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 15:44:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...Haiti's poverty and economic backwardness. But that is EXACTLY what this Muslim wants to accomplish: Destroy America economically.</Msg><Username>ershon911</Username><Timestamp>1349653050905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:37:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349656693557-13</Id><Title>Google Chrome commercial on self publishing...</Title><Msg>Awesome. Google's Chrome campaign is getting better all the time. The new commercial has a dad self publishing a Children's book. Whoulda thought that Google might just start coming after Amazon's core business? Unlike Amazon, Google has the cash flow to take this fight to the end... First Target drops Kindle Fire. Then Wal Mart. Then Apple matches eBook pricing. Then Google settles the digital publishing lawsuit (at least with the publishers and the Author's Guild will come soon enought) and then starts marketing self publishing, I almost forgot to mention Oracle getting aggressive about the enterprise cloud... Looks like Amazon is going from bullying mom and pop retailers to being the little fish in a big ocean. Lastly, anyone else notice that while Kindle Paperwhite are 4-6 weeks, Kindle Fire is available for immediate shipping? Maybe, just maybe, Amazon misallocated capital...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1349656693557</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:38:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349664897609-14</Id><Topic><Title>Markets ain't buying O'bummer's FAKE jobs report.</Title><Username>ershon911</Username><Timestamp>1349466265926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 15:44:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What a disastrous four years its been in total. No economic progress. NONE! ZIP! ZERO!" Hmmm . . . AMZN; Jan 20, 2009 50.75 51.70 48.27 48.44 6,767,200 48.44 . . . Oct 5, 2012 261.20 261.90 257.49 258.51 2,806,500 258.51 up 434.67% DOW: Jan 20, 2009 8,279.63 8,291.98 7,939.93 7,949.09 4,192,000 7,949.09 . . . Oct 5, 2012 13,569.18 13,661.87 13,568.75 13,610.15 1,155,000 13,610.15 up 71.22% What more do you want? You shorts are not only stupid, deranged, and greedy, but also BLIND! No wonder you NEVER make money. Bwahahahahaha . . .</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1349664897609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:54:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349665551513-15</Id><Topic><Title>Markets ain't buying O'bummer's FAKE jobs report.</Title><Username>ershon911</Username><Timestamp>1349466265926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 15:44:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spanking your monkey.....</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1349665551513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 23:05:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349667209283-16</Id><Title>Seeking Alpha good article re: BBBY. Retail is also up 4% yoy</Title><Msg>Plenty of bullish indicators and the shorts still don't get it. At this rate, the hedge funds will be out of business is 6-months, lol.</Msg><Username>hatepolitics101</Username><Timestamp>1349667209283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 23:33:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349668379558-17</Id><Topic><Title>Seeking Alpha good article re: BBBY. Retail is also up 4% yoy</Title><Username>hatepolitics101</Username><Timestamp>1349667209283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 23:33:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the "bullish indicators" are weak at best and theses markets have priced in the best case scenario five times over. This 4 year bull market has run its' course. The overbought scenario is beyond all rationale.</Msg><Username>hot1tip</Username><Timestamp>1349668379558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 23:52:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>