<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351311927326-1</Id><Topic><Title>Buy stuff from Amazon Now</Title><Username>buzz5352</Username><Timestamp>1351292153424</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:55:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or you could just buy local. Support your local businesses! Amazon is bad for all of us. Except bezos and his staff of vultures and their investors. Amazon even poaches business from their third party partners. Shameful.</Msg><Username>i.alaric</Username><Timestamp>1351311927326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 00:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351312396395-2</Id><Title>Amzn to $500 a share</Title><Msg>I really really hope.</Msg><Username>basshead554</Username><Timestamp>1351312396395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 00:33:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351315883370-3</Id><Topic><Title>I decided to look at shorting when PE approaches 1000</Title><Username>johnrobertkosanovic</Username><Timestamp>1351296339766</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 20:05:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are wrong...The PE is exactly 3184.18...This means that AMZN will go to 2380 a share when the PE will get to 300....I have not seen anything more idiotic than AMZN in my entire 30 years of trading life</Msg><Username>gsarc2000</Username><Timestamp>1351315883370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 01:31:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351317947387-4</Id><Title>Overpriced POS</Title><Msg>PE of 2800 and a horrible cc yet this pos moves up and aapl drops, wall street crooks at it again.</Msg><Username>mikelamothe0675</Username><Timestamp>1351317947387</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 02:05:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351318363689-5</Id><Topic><Title>Here's what's going to happen.</Title><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1351290751919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:32:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Romney is elected the market rallies for maybe a week at most and then dies. Look at history. Although Wall Street always wants the low tax candidate of the rich, the market knows better and collapses when Wall Street gets its wishes. Cutting taxes for the middle class means they have more money to spend, which can fatten corporate profits; cutting taxes for the top 2 percent simply throws resources away . They already buy whatever they want. You have to be a foolish toady of the greedy rich class to think otherwise. If Romney wins, you need to get out of the market before year end. (I don't think he can win; the teapulbicans have antagonized the Hispanic population with their attitude toward immigrants. That is likely to be enough to tip the tide in Colorado and a few other states to re-elect Obama. Don't get me wrong. I am no fan of Obama, but Romney is worss for the market and the country.)</Msg><Username>mbl0822</Username><Timestamp>1351318363689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 02:12:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351335705346-6</Id><Title>I told you to buy when the PE was 300 now the PE is 2100.....</Title><Msg>if the PE drop to 2000 buy immediately all you can for all that do not get AMZN rally here is the explanation AMZN is a religion JB is the Messiah the analyst are the priests AMZN site is the temple and all investors that beleive in AMZN are the followers (like all other followers) one day all will wake up and they will discover that JB is not Messiah AMZN site is not temple and Analyst abuse children and was preaching fake to all of you that is when all blinds..... no one can escape from the true and the true is AMZN is loosing money.....</Msg><Username>magiv_hegyoni</Username><Timestamp>1351335705346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 07:01:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351341595548-7</Id><Topic><Title>Who recalls TYCO, or Conseco or Bear Sterns. All blue chippers loved by Joo Street.</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1351282170259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:09:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love being an American, and I love democracy. But given the choice, I would take communism over being a Nazi. - PJ p.s.- I've been to Germany, beautiful country and some wonderful friendly people. Shame they have Hitler and Nazis tied to their history.</Msg><Username>pjlouie13</Username><Timestamp>1351341595548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:39:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351342698872-8</Id><Topic><Title>HERE IS PROOF SYBIL IS A LIAR!!!</Title><Username>skiliondaddy</Username><Timestamp>1351308781501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 23:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybs broker providez the option to perform direct trades and chose one of many exchanges or trading houses to trade. From 4:01 to 8:00 pm, sybil can trade all the live long after hours day douchbag, without being locked into any particular trading house for order execution.. If you have enough money in your account to get level 2 then watch it jump around on a report day for a stok between 4 and 4:15, showing you all the tradez that you are missing .... When you tealize that sybil iz correct and really think about it as you watch prices hopping around like crazy, think "thats old sybil scalping my money" arshole.</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1351342698872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:58:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351342730362-9</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN price action not hard to understand</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351340332035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I added to my position at close. I will add much more Monday if it remains elevated. The overconfident longs are gonna get taken to the woodshed. I suspect the big shorts squeezed weak shorts out and used cheap calls to cover many more shorts, all while buying very inexpensive puts. I added 50% late Friday (although around $236, so I'm down on those). I will adjust the strikes on all my options Monday for black Tues/Wed. Pretty soon, we will see carnage from the behind the scenes battles amongst funds to juice performance, even when knowingly investing in scams like this. Those who bought Friday will literally have an IMPOSSIBLE task in explaining to LPs why they did when amazon does crater. It's cavalier. It's negligent. Not one would do it with his/her own money. Responsible LP's should be closely examining this event. It will tell them a lot about the true character of the people managing their funds... even if it worked for a day, it will lead to massive losses in time.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1351342730362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351342880916-10</Id><Topic><Title>Here's what's going to happen.</Title><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1351290751919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:32:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney may end up being worse for the market, but not for the reason you give, You need to turn off MSNBC and stop spouting the lefts mantra of "lower taxes on the rich at the expense of the middle class". It is a lie, just like everything else that comes out of their mouth. Romney may be a negative for the market because 1) he will fire money printer in chief Bernanke and 2) he is going to have to take measures to reduce our deficit which may not be the best for the economy. I believe his economic policies will help negate the effect of reduced spending in other areas so #2 isn't as big of a concern to me.</Msg><Username>mjoertwig</Username><Timestamp>1351342880916</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:01:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351342889519-11</Id><Topic><Title>Here's what's going to happen.</Title><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1351290751919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:32:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I happen to believe the opposite. I think as it becomes clearer and clearer over the next couple weeks that Romney will win, the market rallies into and then a few days after the election will be the high for the year. The market will back down and try to rally back. Earnings season will be essentially over by election day and there won't be any earnings news. Obama will not lift a finger to avoid the fiscal cliff and the Dems in Congress will not do anything either to help. So there will be uncertainty until inaugeration day. Congress will do what it always does, and just extend everything another few months or so. The market doesn't like that so we will start to sell off. There might be a rally soon after Romney is sworn in, but it too, will fade as we get back into Washington gridlock. 2013 will be a dismal year in the stock market. AMZN will peak here pretty soon. I see it going back up even more. I see a double top looming.</Msg><Username>warnbeeb</Username><Timestamp>1351342889519</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:01:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351343717390-12</Id><Title>question</Title><Msg>if u follow this stock for a long time can u post the current average stock cost basis for mutual funds</Msg><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1351343717390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:15:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351344435509-13</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN price action not hard to understand</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351340332035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Techstrategy, you're stupid and deranged. There's not fund buying here. I mean knew buying. What happened on Thursday AH and Friday is simply the beginning of short covering by those who knocked down AMZN since around $250. The price will settle back to $250 area within a month or so WITHOUT any new buying.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1351344435509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:27:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351344901216-14</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN price action not hard to understand</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351340332035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thumbs up, tech...</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1351344901216</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:35:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351344971559-15</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN price action not hard to understand</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351340332035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thumbs down geegee, you papertrading dope.....</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1351344971559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:36:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351345476769-16</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN Trading Action</Title><Username>whiteonyx52</Username><Timestamp>1351296489158</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 20:08:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you shorts are all idiots and too greedy. AMZN had fallen from $264 just about a month ago all the way down to $204. Then it bounce, but it's still under $240, isn't it? So, what are you complaining about? Because you shorted below $220? Bwahahahaha . . .</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1351345476769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:44:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351345761266-17</Id><Title>Same old story . . .</Title><Msg>If AMZN falls significantly for no apparent reasons, shorts boasts that they've been right. If AMZN doesn't fall or actually goes up on bad "news," they complain of manipulation. I don't see longs complaining of manipulation when the stock goes down hard.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1351345761266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351346170395-18</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN price action not hard to understand</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351340332035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>u think shorts would cover day after bad earning?</Msg><Username>julie_w_lo</Username><Timestamp>1351346170395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:56:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351346227491-19</Id><Topic><Title>Same old story . . .</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1351345761266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>geeg, i've noticed u are some kind of fixture on this board, but my feeling is u are shallow.</Msg><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1351346227491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:57:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351346308157-20</Id><Topic><Title>question</Title><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1351343717390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:15:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cash ard to say what "mutual funds" own it at... They are usually the last to own pigs because they are the buy high dumping grounds for the sister company angency hnw managed wealth account robots.... FMR, TROW, LONG TERM CAPITAL, GLOABAL CAPITAL, BLACKROCK et al own this from 40 up.... 80 is the stealth phase, 80 - 120 is the smart money awareness phase, 120 and up is the Mania phase, 264.11 is when a new paradigm was hit "amazon iz different, it can be everything to everybody across many 'integrated' businesses all of which it either svcks at in execution (paying too much for unneeded realestate), timing (ie amzon bank just before the next crash) while spending and losing truck loadz of coin because it iz different, and focus (its a retail web site, no its a gadget company, wait its a bank, no its a delivery company, hold on its a forex!!!??) - holy sheit these guys are all over the place.... Right now its in the blow off phase before it collapses to bk on any one of its poorly executed business plans.... Happy shorting cash....</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1351346308157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:58:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351346435174-21</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN price action not hard to understand</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351340332035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First, how about a thumbs up for the irnoy in someone who cannot who says knew rather than new buying? I mean it's just a little over the top. Second, Geeg short interest is 33% below its peak of last year. If you follow the daily short reporting, there's been net covering over the past week (the big shorts always try to screw the little ones). And there is BIG TIME distribution at play here. This pig won't fly much longer. only real question is who will have cement shoes being tossed overboard for EOY performance reporting whether that be FY or CY... There will be some massive last second volatility because the risk of perpetuating this scam will grow exponentially as more events transpire (just as I was correct from last Oct Geeg, we are just getting started with Apple and Google going after Amazon's cash generating digital prayer). The Playground opens soon...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1351346435174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:00:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351346475564-22</Id><Title>Lets all pray that hurricane sandy knocks out wallstreet and the fed completely as this could put a stop</Title><Msg>To whatever held up this plucking fig forever and bring back a semblance of our free marketplace again... a.....men.</Msg><Username>fig_plucker</Username><Timestamp>1351346475564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:01:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351346490827-23</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN just hammered on Fast Money</Title><Username>dimondboy</Username><Timestamp>1351286726472</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 17:25:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahhh Mining. Your "PHD" is in being an idiot. Top of the class, with honours.</Msg><Username>nining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1351346490827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:01:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351346579871-24</Id><Topic><Title>Who recalls TYCO, or Conseco or Bear Sterns. All blue chippers loved by Joo Street.</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1351282170259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:09:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very well said sir good to meet u</Msg><Username>xdon69</Username><Timestamp>1351346579871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:02:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351347258184-25</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN just hammered on Fast Money</Title><Username>dimondboy</Username><Timestamp>1351286726472</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 17:25:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, these guys have recommended shorting or buy AMZN puts at least 5 times in the past few years. Not working even once. I just can't believe they even dared to try again.</Msg><Username>blust34442</Username><Timestamp>1351347258184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:14:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351347320262-26</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN price action not hard to understand</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351340332035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poetic justice. Irony at work. I have a typo when mocking GeeGee (it is too easy and I wasn't concentrating). GeeGee, I have many faults in this lifetime, but being stupid simply isn't one of them. I'm light years ahead of you and most invested in this stock in terms of understanding how the competitive landscape will evolve. There is a non negligable chance that Amazon will start to have cash flow problems and will need to either issue debt or new equity. Apple and Google will go after Amazon's core. People freaked on Pandora with Apple moving into radio (should have affected Amazon as well). Similar moves are coming in the rest of digital media that will affect Amazon more directly. And Google is about to announce more of the same. Bring it chump.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1351347320262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:15:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351347573561-27</Id><Topic><Title>Here's what's going to happen.</Title><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1351290751919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:32:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe Asian governments are just a little late. On the latest episode of Money In Motion, they reported that Japanese government will crave in and has their first QE type easing very soon. They also said Chinese who didn't believe in QE will reconsider.</Msg><Username>blust34442</Username><Timestamp>1351347573561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351349157380-28</Id><Topic><Title>question</Title><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1351343717390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:15:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Friday's action looks like a discontinuous synthetic short (via calendar spread) to me... Looks like someone pushed the prop and dump strategy to a while different level.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1351349157380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:45:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351349699429-29</Id><Topic><Title>Who recalls TYCO, or Conseco or Bear Sterns. All blue chippers loved by Joo Street.</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1351282170259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:09:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LION BROADCASTING: MASSIVE CIVIL UNREST IN USA 2013, prepare for survival USA is a failed state(ROME did not burn in a Day Americans are History without Revolution: Dr. Paul Craig Roberts ----------------------- Thomas Jefferson and Eisenhower warned us long time ago: I believe that banking institutions are more dangerous to our liberties than standing armies. If the American people ever allow private banks to control the issue of their currency, first by inflation, then by deflation, the banks and corporations that will grow up around [the banks] will deprive the people of all property until their children wake-up homeless on the continent their fathers conquered. The issuing power should be taken from the banks and restored to the people, to whom it properly belongs. Thomas Jefferson, (Attributed) 3rd president of US (1743 - 1826) Andrew Jackson quotes: Gentlemen, I have had men watching you for a long time and I am convinced that you have used the funds of the bank to speculate in the breadstuffs of the country. When you won, you divided the profits amongst you, and when you lost, you charged it to the bank. You tell me that if I take the deposits from the bank and annul its charter, I shall ruin ten thousand families. That may be true, gentlemen, but that is your sin! Should I let you go on, you will ruin fifty thousand families, and that would be my sin! You are a den of vipers and thieves. Catherine Austin Fitts: "They're Going to Depopulate or Bankrupt the Rest of Us" Catherine Austin Fitts calls what happened to the U.S since the market meltdown of 2008 a “fiscal coup d’état.” Fitts should know because she is a former Wall Street insider who has managed investments worth $300 billion. She is also a government insider. Catherine Austin Fitts was an Assistant Secretary for HUD in the first Bush Administration more than 20 years ago. She says our leaders are “. . . doing a number of things that are going to depopulate or bankrupt the rest of us.” Why are people so ill-informed? Fitts says it’s because, “Corporate media is lying to you and wasting your time.” She also says, “Were going through a period of great change, and the pace is going to accelerate.” And, “Gold will be at the center of a new currency that will emerge.” Join Greg Hunter as he goes One-on-One with Catherine Austin Fitts of The Solari Report. ---------------------------------------- RED ALERT IN USA MARY SCAHPIRO/ROBERT KHUZAMI/ROBERT COOK IS A CRIMINAL SCAM GANG AT S.E.C SERVING FRAUD STREET FINANCIAL BANKSTER TERRORISTS AND CORPORATE THUGS TO LOOT EVERY PENNY IN USA WORKING CLASS PENSIONS...... NEW SLOGAN IN USA WALL STREET IS NOW PURE FRAUD STREET CASINO AND RIGGED WITH ALL SCAM LEGISLATION AGAINST 99% WORKING CLASS AND ALL FRAUD LOOT PROTECTION FOR CORPORATE THUGS AND BANKSTER FINANCIAL TERRORISTS AT S.E.C ENFORCED AND ALL LOOT MANIPULATION SCAM WEAPONS AT THEIR DISPOSAL LOOT/SCAM/BANG USA 99% WORKING CLASS PENSION CONTRIBUTIONS IN BILLIONS WITH DARK POOLS AND HIGH FREQUENCY TRADING MACHINES WITH FRAUD PRICE/VOLUME MANIPULATION WITHOUT ANY FEAR IF, BY MISTAKE YOU ARE CAUGHT? NO PROBLEM COME TO MARY SCHAPIRO/ROBERT KHUZAMI/ROBERT COOK SCAM WATCH PARASITES AT S.E.C AND P[AY LITTLE FINE, NO TRIALS AND KEEP YOUR LOOT IN BILLIONS AND YOU ARE FREE TO GO BACK AND START YOUR SCAM LOOT ASAP................. Gene Burnett - Jump You F*#kers (A Song For Wall Street) --------------- A Lonely Redemption He is no less suspicious of Goldman Sachs, which has alumni sprinkled across the upper reaches of government. In a tough spot, Goldman obtained extraordinary permission to make an overnight metamorphosis from investment bank to traditional bank holding company. “Can I prove this was a wired deal? Absolutely not,” Mr. Lewis said. “Am I certain of it? Only 100 percent.” As for the whirling, three-million-shares-per-second casino of Wall Street? He sees it as rigged. “I would not risk stocks under any circumstances,” he said, “because we don’t know when this thing is going to blow.” Nothing about Mr. Lewis is easy. He delights in sending scabrous, insulting, free-associative mass e-mails to journalists, financiers and members of Congress. Show annoyance, and he doubles down. “You know what I do with tension?” he said. “I ratchet it up!” ------------------------------------------------------------ The Mayan calendar points to the end of the world coming in December. It may not end on that date but major disruptions can be anticipated. CENTRAL banks have fully uncorked the printing presses to meet the waves of insolvency set to STRIKE the banksters, public servants and the elites. Transferring your wealth to themselves and their something for nothing societies to PAY for their moral and fiscal insolvencies. There is an incredible number potential crisis in the short term (3 to 6 months); any one could spark a major financial, economic and political crisis by themselves. Taken together they practically GUARANTEE it. Fat tails and black swans loom. They really are only black swans and fat tails to Keynesian economists, for those of the Austrian camp they are PREDICTABLE and INEVITABLE! Look at this litany of UNFOLDING CATASTROPHES from a recent Financial Times............ Collapsing economies, capital flight from weak to the strong (target 2 sends the funds right back to the failing central banks), planned tax increases and mandatory spending cuts, and chronic current account and BUDGET deficits. You must understand that the US fiscal cliff was the ONLY answer for politicians who need someone else to blame for what MUST come to pass. So they did the deal and now can point to each other with no one specific to blame. My opinion: the spending cuts need to be retained and all government spending must be frozen. The government does not need any more money for INVESTMENTS (spending). “Nothing in government happens by accident, if it happens you can be certain it was planned that way.” --Franklin Delano Roosevelt Now let’s look at the greatest BLACK swan of them all, one far from the headlines but the HEART of the currency and financial system EXTINCTION event</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1351349699429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:54:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351349998752-30</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN price action not hard to understand</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351340332035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Techstrategy: "I will add much more Monday if it remains elevated." Hello deranged. Has it ever occurred to you to some, the statement is "I will add (buy) much more Monday if it remains depressed." After all AMZN is far below 264.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1351349998752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351350337505-31</Id><Topic><Title>USA 99% HAVE TO SMOKE THESE FRAUD STREET BANKSTER TERRORISTS AND HANG THEM INA PUBLIC SQUARE: NO OTHER CHOICE IN USA FOR 99% WORKING CLASS</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1351258857625</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 09:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LION BROADCASTING: MASSIVE CIVIL UNREST IN USA 2013, prepare for survival USA is a failed state(ROME did not burn in a Day Americans are History without Revolution: Dr. Paul Craig Roberts ----------------------- Thomas Jefferson and Eisenhower warned us long time ago: I believe that banking institutions are more dangerous to our liberties than standing armies. If the American people ever allow private banks to control the issue of their currency, first by inflation, then by deflation, the banks and corporations that will grow up around [the banks] will deprive the people of all property until their children wake-up homeless on the continent their fathers conquered. The issuing power should be taken from the banks and restored to the people, to whom it properly belongs. Thomas Jefferson, (Attributed) 3rd president of US (1743 - 1826) Andrew Jackson quotes: Gentlemen, I have had men watching you for a long time and I am convinced that you have used the funds of the bank to speculate in the breadstuffs of the country. When you won, you divided the profits amongst you, and when you lost, you charged it to the bank. You tell me that if I take the deposits from the bank and annul its charter, I shall ruin ten thousand families. That may be true, gentlemen, but that is your sin! Should I let you go on, you will ruin fifty thousand families, and that would be my sin! You are a den of vipers and thieves. Catherine Austin Fitts: "They're Going to Depopulate or Bankrupt the Rest of Us" Catherine Austin Fitts calls what happened to the U.S since the market meltdown of 2008 a “fiscal coup d’état.” Fitts should know because she is a former Wall Street insider who has managed investments worth $300 billion. She is also a government insider. Catherine Austin Fitts was an Assistant Secretary for HUD in the first Bush Administration more than 20 years ago. She says our leaders are “. . . doing a number of things that are going to depopulate or bankrupt the rest of us.” Why are people so ill-informed? Fitts says it’s because, “Corporate media is lying to you and wasting your time.” She also says, “Were going through a period of great change, and the pace is going to accelerate.” And, “Gold will be at the center of a new currency that will emerge.” Join Greg Hunter as he goes One-on-One with Catherine Austin Fitts of The Solari Report. ---------------------------------------- RED ALERT IN USA MARY SCAHPIRO/ROBERT KHUZAMI/ROBERT COOK IS A CRIMINAL SCAM GANG AT S.E.C SERVING FRAUD STREET FINANCIAL BANKSTER TERRORISTS AND CORPORATE THUGS TO LOOT EVERY PENNY IN USA WORKING CLASS PENSIONS...... NEW SLOGAN IN USA WALL STREET IS NOW PURE FRAUD STREET CASINO AND RIGGED WITH ALL SCAM LEGISLATION AGAINST 99% WORKING CLASS AND ALL FRAUD LOOT PROTECTION FOR CORPORATE THUGS AND BANKSTER FINANCIAL TERRORISTS AT S.E.C ENFORCED AND ALL LOOT MANIPULATION SCAM WEAPONS AT THEIR DISPOSAL LOOT/SCAM/BANG USA 99% WORKING CLASS PENSION CONTRIBUTIONS IN BILLIONS WITH DARK POOLS AND HIGH FREQUENCY TRADING MACHINES WITH FRAUD PRICE/VOLUME MANIPULATION WITHOUT ANY FEAR IF, BY MISTAKE YOU ARE CAUGHT? NO PROBLEM COME TO MARY SCHAPIRO/ROBERT KHUZAMI/ROBERT COOK SCAM WATCH PARASITES AT S.E.C AND P[AY LITTLE FINE, NO TRIALS AND KEEP YOUR LOOT IN BILLIONS AND YOU ARE FREE TO GO BACK AND START YOUR SCAM LOOT ASAP................. Gene Burnett - Jump You F*#kers (A Song For Wall Street) --------------- A Lonely Redemption He is no less suspicious of Goldman Sachs, which has alumni sprinkled across the upper reaches of government. In a tough spot, Goldman obtained extraordinary permission to make an overnight metamorphosis from investment bank to traditional bank holding company. “Can I prove this was a wired deal? Absolutely not,” Mr. Lewis said. “Am I certain of it? Only 100 percent.” As for the whirling, three-million-shares-per-second casino of Wall Street? He sees it as rigged. “I would not risk stocks under any circumstances,” he said, “because we don’t know when this thing is going to blow.” Nothing about Mr. Lewis is easy. He delights in sending scabrous, insulting, free-associative mass e-mails to journalists, financiers and members of Congress. Show annoyance, and he doubles down. “You know what I do with tension?” he said. “I ratchet it up!” ------------------------------------------------------------ The Mayan calendar points to the end of the world coming in December. It may not end on that date but major disruptions can be anticipated. CENTRAL banks have fully uncorked the printing presses to meet the waves of insolvency set to STRIKE the banksters, public servants and the elites. Transferring your wealth to themselves and their something for nothing societies to PAY for their moral and fiscal insolvencies. There is an incredible number potential crisis in the short term (3 to 6 months); any one could spark a major financial, economic and political crisis by themselves. Taken together they practically GUARANTEE it. Fat tails and black swans loom. They really are only black swans and fat tails to Keynesian economists, for those of the Austrian camp they are PREDICTABLE and INEVITABLE! Look at this litany of UNFOLDING CATASTROPHES from a recent Financial Times............ Collapsing economies, capital flight from weak to the strong (target 2 sends the funds right back to the failing central banks), planned tax increases and mandatory spending cuts, and chronic current account and BUDGET deficits. You must understand that the US fiscal cliff was the ONLY answer for politicians who need someone else to blame for what MUST come to pass. So they did the deal and now can point to each other with no one specific to blame. My opinion: the spending cuts need to be retained and all government spending must be frozen. The government does not need any more money for INVESTMENTS (spending). “Nothing in government happens by accident, if it happens you can be certain it was planned that way.” --Franklin Delano Roosevelt Now let’s look at the greatest BLACK swan of them all, one far from the headlines but the HEART of the currency and financial system EXTINCTION event</Msg><Username>aagfire007</Username><Timestamp>1351350337505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:05:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351351993469-32</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN just hammered on Fast Money</Title><Username>dimondboy</Username><Timestamp>1351286726472</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 17:25:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They could not have said it better. There is no way that this stock can remail elevated at these levels. PE ratio north of 3000 !!! You have got to be kiddin' me.</Msg><Username>bullish1_2</Username><Timestamp>1351351993469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351352056237-33</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN IS A $30 STOCK</Title><Username>sellbby</Username><Timestamp>1351299913156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 21:05:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, but it will take time before the stupid people realize that!</Msg><Username>titomuch</Username><Timestamp>1351352056237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:34:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351352274282-34</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN price action not hard to understand</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351340332035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Geeg: Only to those who do not understand cognitive biases and behavioral investing. It's why people like you catch knives and ultimately (I guess) how natural selection works. In a rational world, Amazon would never have gone above $150 (and even then it would be extended). I normally try to protect people from that which they don't yet see, but will become apparent in time. As you posted from my prognostication last year, I see evolving competitive dynamics very clearly. Because I invest my own money, I don't play the #$%$ games of WS analysts who are trying to get people to buy overpriced crap. I post intellectually honest and clinical assessments of the fundamentals. Let's take a few: 1) Claim: Gross margins are going up. Fact: Only because of malinvestment in redundant (in the macro sense since warehouse and distribution is anything but scarce in this country) fulfillment centers, which has dramatically reduced the return on invested capital. 2) Claim: Amazon will have enormous leverage going forward. Fact: Operating Cash flow per dollar of revenue has decreased dramatically since 2009. FCF is MUCH worse. 3) Claim: Amazon will make ton on digital content. Fact: it already dominates books and really mainly has downside there. Conjecture: Further, as distribution channels proliferate and HW vendows seek to embed more value in their offering, they will compete economic rents out of digital content distribution/retailing. This source of cash flow will collapse. Dude, you are in over your head. Don't try to mess with me. I don't fall prey to the psychological #$%$ that you and other wannabe predators perpetuate. I have a compass called fundamentals and competitive strategic insight that makes it easy to ride through this crap. Please load up GeeGee. You deserve to get all that is coming...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1351352274282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:37:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351355891375-35</Id><Topic><Title>Same old story . . .</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1351345761266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can you with this valuation? Let's face it Bezos carries a ton of credibility which I don't fully understand since I admittedly never followed this company closely. The valuation always looked nuts to me. If he said he was leaving and transitioning out over the next 6 months the stock would get cut in half in a heartbeat. I have shorted this for short term gains previously in the high $250's and over $260 and I'll look for the opportunity again but to be fair I will try to see it from both sides. One thing I do know is that when the market gets frothy and the MOMO stocks like AMZN keep going up without improved fundamentals, they typically go down harder and faster when the market corrects.</Msg><Username>hapihammer</Username><Timestamp>1351355891375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:38:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351356671266-36</Id><Topic><Title>looking for massive fall next week once the short squeeze scam to make optoins holders WHOLE...fails</Title><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1351293232419</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 19:13:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its very simple they bought the dip into support...and the naked short stock scam squeeze ensued the conf call sucked. there no answers. even apple went and retested the AH lows yesterday before revesing back green again and then down due to pinning, etc amazn will retest that 203 alot sooner than you all think IMO. probably now that all shorts are out it will fall like a rock as the fidelities of the world liqudiate into the scam bid</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1351356671266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351357645478-37</Id><Topic><Title>looking for massive fall next week once the short squeeze scam to make optoins holders WHOLE...fails</Title><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1351293232419</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 19:13:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No way this will happen. Last time AMZ retest 260 was when the indices are at multi year high. No way the indices can get back up there not without some encouraging economic data. If AMZN is going against the economic current than it will be crushed once it get there. AMZN already show a double top in the chart. Triple top is unlikely in this environment.</Msg><Username>tung_5000</Username><Timestamp>1351357645478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 13:07:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351364775203-38</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN price action not hard to understand</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351340332035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be adding my weekly short put 240 strike</Msg><Username>ngrti</Username><Timestamp>1351364775203</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:06:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351365721105-39</Id><Title>Any of you using beyond-trading websit by Vieira?</Title><Msg>I just visited his site and it looks very interesting. His most recent call was to buy amzn after hours at $207 and sell it yesterday for $237. He switched to a sell at the end of the day.</Msg><Username>likesky78</Username><Timestamp>1351365721105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:22:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351365822696-40</Id><Title>OH NO!! CRAMER HAS ABANDONED AMAZON!! WHAT DO WE DO NOW??</Title><Msg>I am so scared what will happen. On his show late Friday, Mr. Cramer was deriding Amazon for its opacity and overvaluation, and praising Amazon. I am so scared for how Amazon stock will react next week! What do we do?</Msg><Username>bob.bull99</Username><Timestamp>1351365822696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:23:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351365888412-41</Id><Topic><Title>OH NO!! CRAMER HAS ABANDONED AMAZON!! WHAT DO WE DO NOW??</Title><Username>bob.bull99</Username><Timestamp>1351365822696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:23:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was praising Apple, not Amazon. All but said sell Amazon and buy Apple.</Msg><Username>bob.bull99</Username><Timestamp>1351365888412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:24:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351366122296-42</Id><Title>Techstrategy</Title><Msg>Hi! I left you a couple of messages on cmg board a while ago but I don't know if you saw them. First of all, I'd like to congratulate you again on your amazing call on CMG.. wow. What a ride from $440 to $235 in just 6 months. You were right all along on the fall. Also, your long pick NSPH - wow, more than doubled since January. So what are you trading now? Any more stocks like NSPH on your list? Also, have you heard about beyond trading website? I came across it this morning and after watching a couple of M. Vieira's videos I'm super intrigued since his track record is amazing.</Msg><Username>likesky78</Username><Timestamp>1351366122296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:28:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351366457316-43</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN price action not hard to understand</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351340332035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Short percentage is not high enough to support this argument. It is an HFT short squeeze by institutional movers defending Nov call options from an abysmal earnings, an easy way to abuse shorty for a making a make sense play. it is destructive of market confidence and stronly highlits the disparity between earnings and price discovery. It means the market is DEAD for the retail investor. Shorty should not cover in this range, but add if he has the power, just like Techstrategy. 11M shares is pure churn. I strongly suspect some insider hedge fund backroom deal for a back and forth exchange on high frequency shares. This is tape paint and churn one hundred percent. Look at that PE! The stock is behaving as if there were a massive beat and the trend on earnings is more than abysmal. I remember the last tech bubble pop. That is what is happening here, a massive tech bubble. Yahoo is showing 2800x earnings and you want to chase that manipulated green. There is evil, and then there is this. What is to stop the manipulation and cause a resumption of sanity? Nothing but jail time for manipulator HFT trade firms. Can it continue to fly up? Yes. Strong yes. Is it a gamble that relies on further manipulation? STRONG YES. But let's put nothing past these crooks. What keeps it from trading at 1M times earnings? Nothing at all until something is done about this crooked market. If even Cramer says sell, the corporate pusher, you know something stinks.</Msg><Username>ireallyhopeimnottalkingtoadude</Username><Timestamp>1351366457316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351367320896-44</Id><Topic><Title>amzn today was possibly the most bizarre action ever for a stk</Title><Username>chan432000</Username><Timestamp>1351305929489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 22:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We love all you shorts over here at the Amazon board. I myself, love how negative you are on Amazon. I know you don't get it, most of the shorts on here would need to see videos of the best warehouses for 30 minutes straight to get it. After the shorts were shown wal mart, fedex and ups warehouses, then lastly they were shown how much faster, wiser, and simpler the Amazon warehouses move product around. Then they would finally get it and understand why Jeffie spends so much on research and development of his warehouses. You see the longs are at the point where they park money on the side, waiting for the instance AMZN gets whacked a little to get a bigger and bigger long position. They have learned they get 1 day tops to add to AMZN whenever it gets whacked, so they add immediately. Now that the longs always add at the same time or day,it scares the chit out of the shorts who must cover thus helping to send AMZN higher then it was going to go anyway. 1st major squeeze to 300, 2nd major squeeze to 360, amzn will top at 360 and drift slowly down to 320 after that before another lift off starts. I have taken my time to explain and help you shorts. You can take my advice or donate more money to myself and the loyal amzn longs, your choice.</Msg><Username>namfong43</Username><Timestamp>1351367320896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:48:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351367490789-45</Id><Title>who is buying Amazon heavy monday, be honest your bashing but buying Monday hugh?</Title><Msg>Who will step up and buy, who will cover at the sight of just a little Amazon buying to say 245 monday?</Msg><Username>dramatic_move_up</Username><Timestamp>1351367490789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351368223365-46</Id><Topic><Title>amzn today was possibly the most bizarre action ever for a stk</Title><Username>chan432000</Username><Timestamp>1351305929489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 22:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who gives a #$%$ about their fancy warehouses if they can't make money?</Msg><Username>likesky78</Username><Timestamp>1351368223365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:03:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351368914218-47</Id><Topic><Title>Techstrategy</Title><Username>likesky78</Username><Timestamp>1351366122296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:28:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. This is the best short in the world at this point. Hands down, bar none. I added Friday and will add a lot more. In terms of longs, the best long in the world right now is INTC, by far. There's a lot of analysis underlying those positions, but I think anyone with common sense gets it intuitively. The two bit hypester above talked about Amazon's amazing warehouse. Rocket science. Not. Yet, Amazon while losing money and seeing its cash balance and cash flow degrade rapidly is shooting through the roof. INTC is trading at less than 5X cash flow. Intel is pioneering 14nm tri gate (3D FINFET architecture) transitors and no one else is close. They are vastly more energy/power efficient, which is why INTC is dominating servers. Those capabilities will enable it to dominate mobile as well. The economics of chip production depends heavily on feature/die size. INTC is a generation ahead (14nm can fit roughly 2x the number OE chips per wafer) so it has a structural cost advantage. That is rocket science. Anyone not selling AMZN at these levels and buying INTC is not an investor. I never look at BT or any of that. Mainly a bunch of people trying to sense which way the wind is blowing instead of charting a course to the right destination. I think like a sailor. You can get to where you want even with the wind blowing against you the entire way.... It's called tacking and what I've done here....</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1351368914218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351368975030-48</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN price action not hard to understand</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351340332035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll buy 'em from you if it hasn't already cratered by Monday morning...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1351368975030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:16:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351369048798-49</Id><Title>Finally!!! Even CRAMER calls out the Amazon ABSURDITY</Title><Msg>Finally admits there is no plausable reason for any increase in stock price of this MONEY LOSING sham. About time.</Msg><Username>spyeman</Username><Timestamp>1351369048798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:17:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351369306394-50</Id><Title>WE MUST ALL BUY AMAZON MONDAY TO KEEP THE PRICE UP--CRAMER IS A WRONG!!!!</Title><Msg>EVERYONE GET IN THERE AND BUY BUY BUY!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bob.bull99</Username><Timestamp>1351369306394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:21:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351369439876-51</Id><Topic><Title>WE MUST ALL BUY AMAZON MONDAY TO KEEP THE PRICE UP--CRAMER IS A WRONG!!!!</Title><Username>bob.bull99</Username><Timestamp>1351369306394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:21:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUY BUY BUY UNTIL IT HURTS!!!!!!!!!! AMAZON IS A VALUE STOCK!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bob.bull99</Username><Timestamp>1351369439876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:23:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351369550947-52</Id><Title>SELL SHOT EXTREME OVERVALUE APPLE---BUY BUY BUY EXTREME VALUE STOCK AMAZON!!!!!</Title><Msg>AMAZON IS THE GREAT BARGAIN OF STOCK!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bob.bull99</Username><Timestamp>1351369550947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:25:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351369813515-53</Id><Topic><Title>Techstrategy</Title><Username>likesky78</Username><Timestamp>1351366122296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:28:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Tech. INTC is looking pretty good on the daily chart as well. RSI, tsi, full stoch, cci - all turning up. Also, 4day ma line is just about to cross the 9day ma line on the way up. I'm definitely adding it to my buy list. As for AMZN, it's still pretty shocking that "they" managed to drive it up +7% while aapl is down. Doesn't make any sense.. esp. since the markets have been so sensitive this earnings season to any type of underperformance. Do you follow FFIV or RAX? If yes, what are your thoughts, whether long or short. Thanks again.</Msg><Username>likesky78</Username><Timestamp>1351369813515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:30:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351370057278-54</Id><Topic><Title>WE MUST ALL BUY AMAZON MONDAY TO KEEP THE PRICE UP--CRAMER IS A WRONG!!!!</Title><Username>bob.bull99</Username><Timestamp>1351369306394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:21:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I won`t buy. $ 238 for AMZN very expensive , long will loose, just wait and watch what happens to amzn before election.I will buy only at $180.</Msg><Username>vermaatul1</Username><Timestamp>1351370057278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351370210464-55</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN IS A $30 STOCK</Title><Username>sellbby</Username><Timestamp>1351299913156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 21:05:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think amzn is $150 to $180 stock no more then that.</Msg><Username>vermaatul1</Username><Timestamp>1351370210464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:36:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351370367238-56</Id><Topic><Title>amzn today was possibly the most bizarre action ever for a stk</Title><Username>chan432000</Username><Timestamp>1351305929489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 22:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EVERONE BUY MONDAY!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bob.bull99</Username><Timestamp>1351370367238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351372165488-57</Id><Topic><Title>OH NO!! CRAMER HAS ABANDONED AMAZON!! WHAT DO WE DO NOW??</Title><Username>bob.bull99</Username><Timestamp>1351365822696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:23:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope cramer causes amzn to go down a bunch monday and tuesday so I can add. Thanks cramer, he finally did something for me. As for his buy aapl, no thanks, that stock is not acting right, if I bought aapl, in 3-5 days,maybe ten days I just know I would be a major bagholder, rather buy Netflix then aapl before msft bids130 a share for it or at the very least an exclusive partnership is formed.</Msg><Username>gruen7</Username><Timestamp>1351372165488</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 17:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351373294565-58</Id><Topic><Title>Finally!!! Even CRAMER calls out the Amazon ABSURDITY</Title><Username>spyeman</Username><Timestamp>1351369048798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:17:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please take this lower cramer sheep, I want cheap shares and even cheaper calls. Translation to me is Goldman said cramer we need much more Amazon shares fast, do something, and Cramer was like I got you, he puts Goldman first and always will.</Msg><Username>nanotechmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1351373294565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 17:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351373490539-59</Id><Topic><Title>Techstrategy</Title><Username>likesky78</Username><Timestamp>1351366122296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:28:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC is definitely a very good play for the next 4-6 months. It's the real deal. No ponzi scheme there. Further, the chip buyers are getting more numerous as competition really heats up for tablets and smart phones; this will drive component prices up. I think a much better-returning but speculative play is AMD, though.</Msg><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1351373490539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 17:31:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351374043819-60</Id><Topic><Title>Finally!!! Even CRAMER calls out the Amazon ABSURDITY</Title><Username>spyeman</Username><Timestamp>1351369048798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:17:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy Puts!</Msg><Username>seanw06804</Username><Timestamp>1351374043819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 17:40:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351375370704-61</Id><Topic><Title>Techstrategy</Title><Username>likesky78</Username><Timestamp>1351366122296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:28:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not a trader, but it looked to me that Apple was used as a source of funds to squeeze Amazon. Makes perfect sense in this perfectly dysfunctional market. Shake out weak Apple longs and weak amazon shorts and try to screw everyone who is right... A perfect case study as to why people should and will keep taking capital out of the market and investing in local physical assets... it's all predatory.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1351375370704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 18:02:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351375463440-62</Id><Topic><Title>Techstrategy</Title><Username>likesky78</Username><Timestamp>1351366122296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:28:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't follow those. I stay focused on no more than 8 stocks at a time. Not looking to learn more. Too much opportunity with the stocks I am in...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1351375463440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 18:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351377359481-63</Id><Title>triple buy signal--cramer says "no"</Title><Msg>always works</Msg><Username>bachrachjeff</Username><Timestamp>1351377359481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 18:35:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351377483599-64</Id><Title>digital growth is y amzn went up fri--also the east coast storm</Title><Msg>blowwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww</Msg><Username>bachrachjeff</Username><Timestamp>1351377483599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 18:38:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351377860637-65</Id><Title>east coast storm increasing amzn sales</Title><Msg>too obnvious</Msg><Username>bachrachjeff</Username><Timestamp>1351377860637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 18:44:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351378698887-66</Id><Topic><Title>OH NO!! CRAMER HAS ABANDONED AMAZON!! WHAT DO WE DO NOW??</Title><Username>bob.bull99</Username><Timestamp>1351365822696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:23:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yo stinky Jr.!!! exgoldbug ID just too embarrassing to use anymore??? Sorry for your huge option losses..........</Msg><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1351378698887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 18:58:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351379906525-67</Id><Topic><Title>$238 FOR A $30 STOCK; BEZOS HAS 2B INVOLVED IN THE SCAM</Title><Username>sellbby</Username><Timestamp>1351292167034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:56:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sooner or later the game will be up. AMZN price defies logic!</Msg><Username>bullish1_2</Username><Timestamp>1351379906525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 19:18:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351382221162-68</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN Trading Action</Title><Username>whiteonyx52</Username><Timestamp>1351296489158</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 20:08:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tech, I see 2 flaws with your proposition. #1- I've tried to educate friends and family about the abuses of WS and what's being done by the Fed and people look at you like your some conspiracy theorist. You lose most of the general public if the conversations doesn't start with "did you watch American Idol?" or "OMG! did you see Snookie?" #2- Does it really matter what the earnings/revenue/outlook is? I mean last quarter it was all about the revenue, that's why it went up. This quarter revenue didn't matter. It went up because of....why did it go up?? They showed a loss of 23c, what if it was 50c? or a dollar? does it sell off? I think this game plan was in place from the get go. But I think your right, the game is coming to a close. Added Jan DITM puts on Wed because the premiums was too expensive on every thing else. But I know this was possible so i left enough cash to add more. I doubled down right at the close on Fri and can double down again if need be. But should I go out to April? - PJ</Msg><Username>pjlouie13</Username><Timestamp>1351382221162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 19:57:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351383931188-69</Id><Title>Stop the Buying, You keep increasing the PE ratio</Title><Msg>PE ratio is off the charts. Overvalued stock will come down to earth in a few weeks.</Msg><Username>bullish1_2</Username><Timestamp>1351383931188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 20:25:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351384010860-70</Id><Title>All the reports say "AMZN had disappointing numbers", yet the stock soars</Title><Msg>What gives?</Msg><Username>titomuch</Username><Timestamp>1351384010860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 20:26:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351384298568-71</Id><Topic><Title>OH NO!! CRAMER HAS ABANDONED AMAZON!! WHAT DO WE DO NOW??</Title><Username>bob.bull99</Username><Timestamp>1351365822696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:23:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I actually saw that spot when the show reran late last night. To your point he didn't actually say it but he said exactly what he should have. Why exactly does AMZN get a pass when they missed and guided down and my comment, let's face it the stock is vastly overvalued. Wall Street will love it until they decide to sell it off and short it. At this point they are all in the game together and they don't want to hurt the golden goose. Please go back up near the old highs on no news so I can short the c.r.a.p. out of it.</Msg><Username>hapihammer</Username><Timestamp>1351384298568</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 20:31:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351385599006-72</Id><Title>These new "shorts" are pumpers.</Title><Msg>Real shorts couldn't be as dumb as these new ones. Right? I mean no human beings can be this dumb. These new shorts' job is to appear so unbelievably stupid so that normal people lean toward thinking, "Hey, lots of idiots like these must have gotten trapped, so there will be a good short-covering rally for weeks ahead," and get in on the long side.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1351385599006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 20:53:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351386543675-73</Id><Topic><Title>Techstrategy</Title><Username>likesky78</Username><Timestamp>1351366122296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:28:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Also, have you heard about beyond trading website? I came across it this morning and after watching a couple of M. Vieira's videos I'm super intrigued since his track record is amazing." I didn't know that techstrategy is a peddler for another site.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1351386543675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351388224440-74</Id><Topic><Title>Who recalls TYCO, or Conseco or Bear Sterns. All blue chippers loved by Joo Street.</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1351282170259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:09:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMZN will tumble.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1351388224440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:37:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351388301904-75</Id><Topic><Title>Who recalls TYCO, or Conseco or Bear Sterns. All blue chippers loved by Joo Street.</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1351282170259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:09:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For starters democracy is a form of government, opposite a dictatorship. Communism is an economic system where the government is in control of the economy, an extreme form of socialism if you will. In the US, there has been a shift to a more socialist agenda then there has been in decades but still a far cry from communism. There maybe forces at work behind the scenes (similar to what happened to AMZN on Friday) but the system is still intact and still strong and the people still make the final call. While I will not make any excuses for American war time propaganda against Germans, Japanese, Iraqi or Mexican nor will I ignore American travesties against Blacks and Native Americans. I will call #$%$ on your ignorance of the Holocaust. I have been to Auschwitz. The place still reeks of death. I've talked to the Polish people from the area, none deny what happened there and some have stories that will make the hair on your neck stand up. In your free time Google "Chelmno", the stories are all there, with pictures for you to believe. War is ugly, no doubt, and brings out the worst in people but what happen to the Jewish people was evil. - PJ....for the record I'm Roman Catholic p.s. Also, what happen in Dresden was a massacre. But if Germany stays in her borders none of that ever happens.</Msg><Username>pjlouie13</Username><Timestamp>1351388301904</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:38:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351388424367-76</Id><Topic><Title>Who recalls TYCO, or Conseco or Bear Sterns. All blue chippers loved by Joo Street.</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1351282170259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:09:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>likewise!</Msg><Username>pjlouie13</Username><Timestamp>1351388424367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:40:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351388437207-77</Id><Title>My shorting profits are being donated to the Wilhelm Friedrick holocaust museum</Title><Msg>in order to promote education of the real WW2 holocaust; Dresden, Hamburg and 41 other cities that were fire bombed by international war criminals.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1351388437207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351391986587-78</Id><Topic><Title>Techstrategy</Title><Username>likesky78</Username><Timestamp>1351366122296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:28:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>geegenjar, not sure what your post means... I asked him if he knows about this site and he said he doesn't follow it.</Msg><Username>likesky78</Username><Timestamp>1351391986587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 22:39:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351394936039-79</Id><Topic><Title>Here's what's going to happen.</Title><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1351290751919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:32:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's ridiculous. Romney's economic advisor is Glenn Hubbard, the architect of the deficit. He sold W on the tax cuts against the advice of hundreds of the leading economists from all sides of the political spectrum. Hubbard and Romney are clueless about running the country. (All they know is how to rip people off for themselves. Hubbard appears to have had some conflict of interest problems; After the heat died down Columbia, where he now dean, seems to have tightened their conflicts rules.) Romney only fared okay in Massachusetts because he went along with the Democratic legislature. (They raised taxes and fees dozens of times.) With the Tea Party destroying the House, he won't get anywhere even if he had some idea what to do, which he doesn't. I am out of the market immediately if he wins. I would be out now if I thought he would win, but I think the Latinos will put Obama over the top because the Teapublicans seem to hate immigrants, both legal and illegal, and I suspect Gallup and Rasmussen are under counting them.</Msg><Username>mbl0822</Username><Timestamp>1351394936039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 23:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>