<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356152552880-1</Id><Topic><Title>The conditionz Are ripe and the stage iz set</Title><Username>yhoosuxkox</Username><Timestamp>1356117885695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:24:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am their legal representative and I will be available to address all your direct questions. At the same time I run a.hole management company and you appear to qualify to be a customer.</Msg><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1356152552880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 00:02:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356155842404-2</Id><Topic><Title>Did Any Of You Short Idiots See How Much Real Estate AMZN Bought?????</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1356110248037</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:17:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Skiidaddy iz here. Short at will and be comfortable in doing so.</Msg><Username>yhoosuxkox</Username><Timestamp>1356155842404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 00:57:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356162445378-3</Id><Title>Bought An Amazon Paperwhite Kindle</Title><Msg>Spent most of my time on an iPad learning how to download public library books to it. Because it costs $50 more than the non-backlight eReader, you would think Amazon is making a profit on it.</Msg><Username>edison20</Username><Timestamp>1356162445378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 02:47:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356175064155-4</Id><Topic><Title>Did Any Of You Short Idiots See How Much Real Estate AMZN Bought?????</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1356110248037</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:17:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>amazon has a spending problem. How much of the 3 bil it got is left probably not much soon they will need more</Msg><Username>rocketman2001ab</Username><Timestamp>1356175064155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 06:17:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356180803547-5</Id><Topic><Title>Did Any Of You Short Idiots See How Much Real Estate AMZN Bought?????</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1356110248037</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:17:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looking for validation on Yahoo message boards. Doesn't soundm like "skiidady" the d'ckless clown will EVER find any love. Get a life, d'ckless. You're the laughing stock of the Yahoo message boards.</Msg><Username>buylowvvv</Username><Timestamp>1356180803547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 07:53:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356187828206-6</Id><Title>For christmas pumperz are gonna get chained up to concrete blocks stampted with 'AMZN'</Title><Msg>and tossed into the puget sound within eyeshot of bezos' exclusive look out. The blocks were placed on order through amzn prime free of taxez and shipping chargez, so they should be arriving any time now. There are lots of blox on order. Fittingz and a shackling ceremony will begin on Monday night from where pumperz will shove off and be dumped at the market open on wed. Pumperz will have to carry the weight around with them between monday and wed. Meeeerrrry christmas!</Msg><Username>yhoosuxkox</Username><Timestamp>1356187828206</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 09:50:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356187973257-7</Id><Title>question</Title><Msg>is there a way for shorts to collude and take the casino down. look, cmg longs never really sold, still there ping ponging the stock to each other, but einhorn organized those sell offs on earnings so brilliantly. or is this one guarded so well that nothing could be done.</Msg><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1356187973257</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 09:52:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356188186767-8</Id><Topic><Title>Remember the Enron</Title><Username>sammmy220022</Username><Timestamp>1356124564936</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 16:16:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mci worldcom, global crossings and a host of others had a biz model based on a dramatic increase in top line growth but couldn't produce the bottomline numbers. thats how pyramid schemes work, predicated on the future when the eventual requirement is to sell something to everyone in the world in order to satisfy the business model.</Msg><Username>erbium_doper</Username><Timestamp>1356188186767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 09:56:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356188522712-9</Id><Title>ackman and einhorn</Title><Msg>were are you guys? Ackman too busy correcting HLF this week, whats the next target? we need a hedgie to fight the hedgie that owns Amazon. An ability to leverage significant resources to break the pyramid. Takes alot of firepower....billions required.</Msg><Username>erbium_doper</Username><Timestamp>1356188522712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 10:02:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356188703900-10</Id><Topic><Title>int: Retail gasoline ros</Title><Username>saundrabanveloslyqfv6074</Username><Timestamp>1304004402000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2011-04-28 11:26:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am very happy to be a new member.</Msg><Username>williamgoldsmith80</Username><Timestamp>1356188703900</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 10:05:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356191175906-11</Id><Topic><Title>question</Title><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1356187973257</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 09:52:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, cash.... The shorts are forcing bernanke to print more money so that the bot havin momo's can put other peoplez moniez into pumping up worthless stox like nflx, cmg, and amzn to noze bleed valuationz while 'maintaining adequate capital reservez'. The shorts make the bot havin institutionz manipulate the low float stok day in and day out with their nano second bid ask manipulated 100 share block tradez. Then they force to institutionz to write weekly puts and callz systemically killing the retail crack headz that buy this craaaaap every week. Then the shorts are coluding to force bezos and hiz exec palz to unload their optionz, dilute the existing float and cash the fvck out at 200 million of gainz at a clip. The Shorts Secrete Society iz powerful. They are forcing bezos into difficult decisionz that go woth being a 'loss leader' such az switching business stratedgiez every week while operating at a constant money hemoraging rate. Az you can see, thoze nasty shorts did the exact same thing to hastingz at pig flix. He waz very upset az he unloaded hiz free sharez between 220 and 300. Thingz got so bad at Nflx that the shorts made the cfo quit and cash out while the stok waz trading at 220 and forced him az he was preparing to 'spend more time with his family' to say , "dont short my stock". Yes the cfo of nflx was distraugt. Cash, you got it all figured out... Thoze bad mean shorts. Its all of their fault.</Msg><Username>yhoosuxkox</Username><Timestamp>1356191175906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 10:46:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356192206154-12</Id><Topic><Title>Jump off cliff, and get those 50 million off food stamps for starters:)</Title><Username>fig_plucker</Username><Timestamp>1356105904061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:05:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All subsides when extended beyond a very short period cause market inefficiency through inflation on the very items the gvt is tyring to help the poor purchase. It also reduces the need for workers to demand higher wages, which further exaserbates the issue and keeps the low class in the lower class. Minimum wage is also a form of subsidy that has the same effect. The increase in the cost of the items from subsidies (llike food, housing, college, etc..) does not impact the middle and upper class to nearly the same extent, so it is ironic that the very programs intended to help lift people up in the name of fairness, over the long-haul actually make it harder to climb the class ladder. The governemnt (fed+state+local) now spends $54,000 per year per US household and what do we have for it? I'll tell ya - $165k per household in debt and not a lot else!</Msg><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1356192206154</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 11:03:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356192253240-13</Id><Title>amazon and bby</Title><Msg>Amazon should just buy bby before schultz gets the chance in feb.</Msg><Username>kcmalibu5457</Username><Timestamp>1356192253240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 11:04:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356196641751-14</Id><Title>Anyone actually serious about analyzing AMZN as an investment??</Title><Msg>All I see on these boards are political statements. For those of you interested, you should check out some real analysis like that below and than comment here... http://seekingalpha.com/article/1048431-amazon-already-has-optimism-priced-in-it-s-fundamentally-overpriced For the rest of you, I'm curious... why did you choose the AMZN as your political commentary dump? advertise78</Msg><Username>advertise78</Username><Timestamp>1356196641751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 12:17:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356201571362-15</Id><Topic><Title>Jump off cliff, and get those 50 million off food stamps for starters:)</Title><Username>fig_plucker</Username><Timestamp>1356105904061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:05:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The entire sound bite 'fiscal cliff' is a ruse. It should be called fiscal sanity. As in what gvt takes is what gvt should be able to spend. As in balancing ones books.</Msg><Username>fig_plucker</Username><Timestamp>1356201571362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:39:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356201795408-16</Id><Topic><Title>ackman and einhorn</Title><Username>erbium_doper</Username><Timestamp>1356188522712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 10:02:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What happens if the hedgie that props amzn is gvt backed with unlimited firing power? Don't wanna get caught in that pickle....</Msg><Username>fig_plucker</Username><Timestamp>1356201795408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:43:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356203698403-17</Id><Title>The fly in the ointment, shipping inducements...</Title><Msg>The fly in the ointment, shipping inducements...</Msg><Username>elmojitogatico</Username><Timestamp>1356203698403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 14:14:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356217521687-18</Id><Topic><Title>ackman and einhorn</Title><Username>erbium_doper</Username><Timestamp>1356188522712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 10:02:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fig, Gvt intervention already water under the bridge and haz long been priced in This iz the end my freind.... Bernanke cannot continue to print... Besidez think nflx and other crashed pigs... Under your assumption theze pig stox would be on their way to infinity... These low floaterz collapse despite govt intervention, which iz finite in ability to do so and being done with diminishing effecacy. Your thought process iz gonna fvck you out of a good short.... Good tradez never look good when they are made - thats what makes them good tradez. If a trade were easy, then everybody would have fat coin like old sybs. Sybil thanks the powerful trading gods for 'difficult' blood tradez. Sybil tradez pain - not stok.</Msg><Username>yhoosuxkox</Username><Timestamp>1356217521687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 18:05:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356230325865-19</Id><Topic><Title>Remember the Enron</Title><Username>sammmy220022</Username><Timestamp>1356124564936</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 16:16:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but how high can P/E be with Ben printing mega bucks ? Soon investors will realize that if we really have to deal with debt , that Ben will have to stop inflating the stock market and whole think will implode. Stocks like AMZN to drop the most.</Msg><Username>riverwins2001</Username><Timestamp>1356230325865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 21:38:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356234435579-20</Id><Title>the ointment on the fly</Title><Msg>If they don't have a very profitable quarter they will have a PE of 5000 with no hope of making it up in the next few quarters. HOw do you reduce the PE IF the current quarter is not a blow out in profits. HINT you don't. Here comes 5000.</Msg><Username>penystoc</Username><Timestamp>1356234435579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 22:47:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356235721248-21</Id><Topic><Title>the ointment on the fly</Title><Username>penystoc</Username><Timestamp>1356234435579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 22:47:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously, no one cares about the PE. 3K or 5K, no difference. Ur PE metric is meaningless.</Msg><Username>plashadpobedy</Username><Timestamp>1356235721248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 23:08:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>