<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-08"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354953630410-1</Id><Title>I believe too many are still having nightmares of 2000 bubble , and recreating</Title><Msg>that bubble in their heads , thus getting distorted in their heads as to what may happen with Apple. Apple has reached many milestones and time to time needs to consolidate its huge upwards move it has made in the past six months. After the recent November reversal from the low $505 number, it jumped to a high open leaving a gap up as it was under a pressure cooker. Well what it did was simply to come back to where it took off from as to say , here I am , signaling a support level as it should , from which it will once again set out to rise due to , not speculation but real profits , I mean record profits. And that my fellow people is what ultimately decides the direction of a company's stock price. Not what cnbc or msnbc blab all day long. Yes I believe Apple is setting up for a big move towards $650's in the coming months. now I know that some of us are so used to instant gratification and want to see that happen overnight, but some things take a little bit more time to be realized. Well that's about it from here. I am not a professional writer , and I hope I haven't made too many mistakes writing this little piece of my mind . Hope you enjoy and find some support in what I have written here. Have a good weekend and Happy Holidays. A.D</Msg><Username>adavidson_nyc</Username><Timestamp>1354953630410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 03:00:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354973994408-2</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon--Easy come, easy go--capital gains will be taken</Title><Username>bob.bull99</Username><Timestamp>1354920930539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 17:55:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I also believe sales will be the best ever fantastic results and never again so high. But let the people that have bought now be the bagholders when the crash occurs. Bezos will be out</Msg><Username>rocketman2001ab</Username><Timestamp>1354973994408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 08:39:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354981742438-3</Id><Topic><Title>that asks businesses,</Title><Username>kathrinegillespiwxjfhvl7309</Username><Timestamp>1304354512000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-05-02 12:41:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a great day!</Msg><Username>goergerichard10</Username><Timestamp>1354981742438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 10:49:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354981999865-4</Id><Topic><Title>I believe too many are still having nightmares of 2000 bubble , and recreating</Title><Username>adavidson_nyc</Username><Timestamp>1354953630410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 03:00:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All Bubblez are a matter of psychology, the dot bomb bubble, housing bubble, and now the money printing bond bubble... The fed iz buying up so much trash in bonds that bezos / amzn, with no verification of meanz of incomeor plan for bond funds use, and a trainwreck balance sheet, waz just able to secure a low interest high grade bond. Bezos iz the corporate wellfare image equivalent of 2006's no document immigrant landscaper securing a no doc home mortgage for a new mcmansion in arizona. In a couple of yearz, issuerz of trash bonds that have gone default will be caught robosigning foreclosure and bankruptcy noticez to companiez like scamazon as their stock value drops from 8.00 to 55 cents before the corporate assets are seized, which iz when the stock goez BK and share holderz get 0.00. Once again, because the Fed iz being the ultimate backer of this bond trash circulating everywhere, the 'tax payer' (middle class) will be on the hook for bond defaults. Resolution of massive bond defulats wont come in the way of increased taxes because there will be no economy to tax. Rather, it will come in the way of eliminated 'entitlement' programz such az SSI, Unemployement, and Medicare health insurance (notice sybs said eliminated and not reduced). Also notice that sybs put 'entitlement' in quotes, because theze are not 'gift' or 'free handout' programz az polititianz would have the middle class believe az they are cutting and eliminating theze 'dirty handouts' - the funding for theze programz actually comez out of you pay checks automatically, every pay period without hiding or hope of ever getting that money back, and if you are lucky enough to be able to collect it you will be labled a 'free handout recipient product of a welfare nation' Sybs got a little side tracked here.... What sybs meant to say iz that amzn iz a phlying pig stok in a phat pig market place, and that amzn and the stok markets a phully phvcked. The end.</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1354981999865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 10:53:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354982096304-5</Id><Topic><Title>Goal 4: Explore political and cultural environments</Title><Username>esmeraldanicklascuv1579</Username><Timestamp>1303832851000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-04-26 11:47:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice Post</Msg><Username>goergerichard10</Username><Timestamp>1354982096304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 10:54:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354982311389-6</Id><Title>Exterme case of inefficiency in internet era ...</Title><Msg>Amzn doesn't produce any products they sell. Then, why they collect their stock in their storage space. It is waste of money. It's no wonder why its PER is around 3,500 level. They can just arrange the traffic route. With potential buyer &amp; producer information, it could easily ( ? ) calculate the delivery cost. So, they can just save those costs involved in keeping those stock in their space. Can't they just manage the information ? It was always weird any competitor just showed up and do that to defeat this inefficient entity ? Why is that so dfficult ? -.-?</Msg><Username>yirich815</Username><Timestamp>1354982311389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 10:58:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354983516272-7</Id><Topic><Title>Exterme case of inefficiency in internet era ...</Title><Username>yirich815</Username><Timestamp>1354982311389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 10:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe FDX could be the most likely competitor in time ? :)</Msg><Username>yirich815</Username><Timestamp>1354983516272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 11:18:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354984710920-8</Id><Title>If the government couldnt control the Fed funded credit and fannie / freddie housing bubble then what makes you think that they could manage the bernanke bond bubble any better?</Title><Msg>All Bubblez are a matter of psychology, the dot bomb bubble, housing bubble, and now the money printing bond bubble... The fed iz buying up so much trash in bonds that bezos / amzn, with no verification of meanz of incomeor plan for bond funds use, and a trainwreck balance sheet, waz just able to secure a low interest high grade bond. Bezos iz the corporate wellfare image equivalent of 2006's no document immigrant landscaper securing a no doc home mortgage for a new mcmansion in arizona. In a couple of yearz, issuerz of trash bonds that have gone default will be caught robosigning foreclosure and bankruptcy noticez to companiez like scamazon as their stock value drops from 8.00 to 55 cents before the corporate assets are seized, which iz when the stock goez BK and share holderz get 0.00.</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1354984710920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 11:38:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354985541418-9</Id><Topic><Title>Exterme case of inefficiency in internet era ...</Title><Username>yirich815</Username><Timestamp>1354982311389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 10:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or Goog considering mapping tech ?</Msg><Username>yirich815</Username><Timestamp>1354985541418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 11:52:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354986042374-10</Id><Topic><Title>I believe too many are still having nightmares of 2000 bubble , and recreating</Title><Username>adavidson_nyc</Username><Timestamp>1354953630410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 03:00:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The little flea like you don't move the market. It's the big boy speculators, traders, and so called mutual funds that ride these momo POS stocks. Earning don't matter till they all rush for that tiny exit!</Msg><Username>nje457</Username><Timestamp>1354986042374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 12:00:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354986159503-11</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon--Easy come, easy go--capital gains will be taken</Title><Username>bob.bull99</Username><Timestamp>1354920930539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 17:55:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bozo the Clown obviously didn't want to wait till next year. That's why he unloaded a boat load of Scamazon this month. Seeing is believing.</Msg><Username>nje457</Username><Timestamp>1354986159503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 12:02:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354986248099-12</Id><Topic><Title>Cloud = Bubble</Title><Username>bezosghost</Username><Timestamp>1354896311076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:05:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Village Idiot #1.</Msg><Username>nje457</Username><Timestamp>1354986248099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 12:04:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354989093777-13</Id><Topic><Title>"Sharktooth" distribution chart followed by "Amazon Falls"?</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354911239095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:13:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you sad?</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1354989093777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 12:51:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354990103497-14</Id><Topic><Title>Best case for bears would be a low volume retest of the old high at $262</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354913046063</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:44:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There is a reason that all the real companies with real valuations are getting crushed first..." If you knew the reason, why did you start buying INTC calls a.mosy three months ago? Why didn't you buy puts instead?</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1354990103497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 13:08:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354991965488-15</Id><Title>Officia Announcement: 12/08/2012</Title><Msg>This message board's newest Three Stooges: Techstrategy Philandjoel1e (AKA Sybil) ex.goldbug. Congratulations!</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1354991965488</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 13:39:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354992089805-16</Id><Topic><Title>Best case for bears would be a low volume retest of the old high at $262</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354913046063</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:44:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Best case for bears would be a low volume retest of the old high at $262" Ex.goldbug, what would be the WORST case for bears then?</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1354992089805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 13:41:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354993976801-17</Id><Topic><Title>Best case for bears would be a low volume retest of the old high at $262</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354913046063</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:44:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because those of us that aren't paper trading tigers and aren't operating with inside information or informal collusion cannot time the market. So, we must act like real investors and scale in and out as companies become more undervalued or more overvalued respectively. You are the only clown Geeg. Many of the core shorts on this board have seen me proven correct on every major call in time (I guess we can now add long GRPN at $3.30 to that call, although I quadrupled up at $2.65 and sold everything by $4. Too much hot money for my taste. But LT, GRPN will prove a vastly better investment at $4 than Long scamazon here... I see that which you cannot. In the short term, I feel pain for that. In the long term, I make a lot while voting my values with my wallet. I encourage others to do the same. Amazon destroying real wealth daily because it is pirsuing value destroying growth where it has no structural advantage and is in fact less efficient. Shorts, you can help effect change. If you have Amazon Prime, order all you very low density items (toilet paper, paper towels, etc) from Amazon and buy all your higher value density items from the grocery store. Make sure to order them independently. Better we expose this sham sooner than later because it is hurting real retailers in your communities, robbing your state of tax revenues and reducing the velocity of money in your community at the same time. It is time to use our wallets to end the financial market games and effect change.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1354993976801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 14:12:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354996406882-18</Id><Topic><Title>Officia Announcement: 12/08/2012</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1354991965488</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 13:39:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Geegee iz jerking off while sybs stockpiling shorts like a squirl doez nuts, getting ready for the hard cold winter.... Who do you think will survive and thrive? Click thumbz up if you think shorty sybil astute in the trade Click thumbs down if you think paper trading idiot geegee will soon lose hiz pride by way of stupid posts that he puts up. He haz no coin and doesn't bet, therefore he cannot lose money.</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1354996406882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 14:53:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>