<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-09"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355064919915-1</Id><Title>The perfect BUYOUT - Amazon buys RSH</Title><Msg>Amazon is a big faceless cloud warehouse of merchandise . At $2 a share , Amazon could buy up RSH and have a presense everywhere. AMAZON SHACK !</Msg><Username>booyahbuster</Username><Timestamp>1355064919915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 09:55:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355071554165-2</Id><Topic><Title>Best case for bears would be a low volume retest of the old high at $262</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354913046063</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:44:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Techstrategy wrote: "Because those of us that aren't paper trading tigers and aren't operating with inside information or informal collusion cannot time the market. So, we must act like real investors and scale in and out as companies become more undervalued or more overvalued respectively. "You are the only clown Geeg. Many of the core shorts on this board have seen me proven correct on every major call in time (I guess we can now add long GRPN at $3.30 to that call, although I quadrupled up at $2.65 and sold everything by $4. Too much hot money for my taste. But LT, GRPN will prove a vastly better investment at $4 than Long scamazon here... "I see that which you cannot. In the short term, I feel pain for that. In the long term, I make a lot while voting my values with my wallet. I encourage others to do the same. Amazon destroying real wealth daily because it is pirsuing value destroying growth where it has no structural advantage and is in fact less efficient. Shorts, you can help effect change. If you have Amazon Prime, order all you very low density items (toilet paper, paper towels, etc) from Amazon and buy all your higher value density items from the grocery store. Make sure to order them independently. Better we expose this sham sooner than later because it is hurting real retailers in your communities, robbing your state of tax revenues and reducing the velocity of money in your community at the same time. It is time to use our wallets to end the financial market games and effect change. You know what I mean? Techstrategy is deranged.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1355071554165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 11:45:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355073036101-3</Id><Title>Here it is; Johnny Dirtbag "Movie Star" versus Charlie Sheen---</Title><Msg>Tough luck Charlie------Johnny Dirtbag "Movie Star" by Hunter S. Anton Available now----RIGHT HERE at AMZN!!!</Msg><Username>crookedhedgefundmanager</Username><Timestamp>1355073036101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 12:10:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355074739450-4</Id><Title>Recently I found AMZN product is lot more expensive than store price</Title><Msg>Does anyone also notice?products on AMZN used to be lot cheaper than in any store, and than I don't have to pay tax, now not only I need to pay tax, I'm surprised to find out the price is more expensive. the sony nex 7 is selling at $1,248 on amazon, but in local sony store, it's only $1,100, the acer 7 is selling at $1,249 on amazon, but in microsoft store, it's selling only $1,299. and all the toys I'm searching is either the same or more expensive than store price, such as toys r us. why is amazon doing this? is this convenience fee they start to charge now? I'm not buying anything on amzn so far this season. so easy to compare price on my cellphone while in store, if amzn doesn't have a discount, what advantage do they have?</Msg><Username>avalon88888</Username><Timestamp>1355074739450</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 12:38:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355079083128-5</Id><Topic><Title>Best case for bears would be a low volume retest of the old high at $262</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354913046063</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:44:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. You've learned how to do ctrl-c and ctrl-v. That's good. You are learning. I guess I underestimated you. You have an interesting definition of deranged. Correct on nearly EVERY call over the medium term (NFLX short, GMCR both short and long, short CMG, GRPN long from $3.30 while quadrupling at $2.65, loading up on GOOG at $475, loading up on AAPL post SJ at $320, loading up on NSPH at $1) is a "deranged" that most would strive for GeeGee... The fact that folks like you with limited vision and/or critical thinking capacity cannot see where things are headed simply means the win will be even bigger when it comes.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1355079083128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 13:51:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355083571960-6</Id><Title>AMZN prices 20% higher than WMT yet they still dont return a profit and GM on sales lower</Title><Msg>Walmart prices both online and in stores are 20 percent lower on average than Amazon’s, according to consulting company Kantar, which compared the prices of 36 items across a variety of categories. Still, Amazon might not be sweating the price gap, as the online retailer is generally better stocked and has a following of consumers that “trust Amazon will have a low price,” Kantar analyst Anne Zybowski told</Msg><Username>racecap</Username><Timestamp>1355083571960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:06:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355084217473-7</Id><Title>Geeg, the irony is amazing...</Title><Msg>I get a good laugh out of you. The paper trading cyber bully who weekly posts about picking up his you lady friend calling the always civil family man "deranged"... what is in fact deranged is that people like you without any compass whatsoever consider yourselves to be phenomenal successes. I've done well in the markets and will continue to because I play a game the machines cannot. But what I value isn't the paper wealth that I amass through said efforts, it is the time I spend with my wife, children, family and friends. I am always investing in the future, whether in the public markets, private technology companies and most importantly making my children decent and extraordinarily capable human beings. Your posts on reaffirm for me that I am on the right path. God forbid we continue devolving in the the self indulgent, abusive, mean spirited, valueless society that you represent...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1355084217473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:16:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355084998700-8</Id><Title>Amzn prices still 7% higher than exact WMT product prices yet amzn gross profit lower than WMT</Title><Msg>A recent study confirmed that fact. So while online retail sales grow and AMZN IS HIGHLY VISITED, NOONE SAID THEY ARE MAKING SALES nor profits!! While losing to Target, Wal-Mart still can claim an advantage over Amazon, according to a study conducted in June by Kantar Retail, a London-based research firm. It compared prices on a range of 36 items and found that on average goods are 20 percent more expensive at Amazon than at Wal-Mart. On the companies’ websites, Wal-Mart’s advantage fell to 7 percent.</Msg><Username>racecap</Username><Timestamp>1355084998700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:29:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355103323305-9</Id><Title>Headline reads</Title><Msg>"Fed Is Likely to Sustain Its Stimulus Program" Ben will be buying more bad bonds.... The Fed haz officially become housingz fannie mea and freddy mac. Enjoy it while it lasts, pumperz. Bernanke keeps pushing on a rope, but we all know what happenz in the end.... Except this one being bonds instead of 2nd and 3rd no doc mortgagez will end very, very badly... 08 - 09 iz gonna look like an OK day in the markets relative to what's comming when this spree driez up.... Its ok - sybs can wait it out. Keep up the good work, ben. The uber wealthy class doesnt have enough wealth yet.</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1355103323305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 20:35:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355104529461-10</Id><Topic><Title>Headline reads</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1355103323305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 20:35:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybs: Fed printing is bad for Amazon in the real world. Reducing purchasing power of those with higher marginal propensity to consume and adversely affects the relative TCO. There a reason I fo cused on the stocks I did. Pumpers have been too fuzzy in their thinking. Printing helps AAPL, GOOG and INTC (biggest lift), not AMZN...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1355104529461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 20:55:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355105046132-11</Id><Topic><Title>If the government couldnt control the Fed funded credit and fannie / freddie housing bubble then what makes you think that they could manage the bernanke bond bubble any better?</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1354984710920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 11:38:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil knows she's in trouble. She started justifying holding onto her losing short position by give "fundamental" reasons. Yet, she refuses to face the reality: the price has gone up trapping her deeply and there's no sign it heading lower.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1355105046132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 21:04:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355106091664-12</Id><Topic><Title>Headline reads</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1355103323305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 20:35:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fiscal cliff will mean roughly 2MM lose extended unemployment benefits. Another 1MM or so over the next few months. The welfare state is going to get pared back alongside tax increases for the very wealthy. Directionally speaking, it sure won't be helpful to Amazon...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1355106091664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 21:21:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355107718194-13</Id><Topic><Title>If the government couldnt control the Fed funded credit and fannie / freddie housing bubble then what makes you think that they could manage the bernanke bond bubble any better?</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1354984710920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 11:38:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Geegee will be spanking hiz monkey - thats a certanty.</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1355107718194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 21:48:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>