<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-29"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348892803573-1</Id><Topic><Title>funny thing AMZN could go to $500, and Sybs will say "trading gods" are good to him! lol!</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1348857947925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And I've learned that when techstrategy gets hostile and personal, it means he's lost a heap of money on his most recent short. Let's check. He re-entered he tells us at $230. Yes, my calculations tell me he has again lost a heap of money. No wonder he has been so hostile and personal recently.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1348892803573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 00:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348893764492-2</Id><Title>If AMZN breaks 245 and closes, it goes to 178, the charts say that not me</Title><Msg>This is a major POS, up 9 dollars on wine sales, really? 85 for this pos, 120 at the highest a year from now</Msg><Username>classactionlawsuitsonnakedshrts</Username><Timestamp>1348893764492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 00:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348896626288-3</Id><Topic><Title>funny thing AMZN could go to $500, and Sybs will say "trading gods" are good to him! lol!</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1348857947925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It seems that Nememsis somehow is able to make his posts such that the Reply bottom is not available. Funny, I've only experienced that with his posts... Must be part of the Yahoo filtering police. Nemesis, I don't get hostile or personal. To be fair, I have commented that both you and Geeg seem to have relatively modest intellectual capacity (modest as your CPU speed seems to be, it is like a supercomputer compared to Geeg's) as it relates to understanding fundamental economics and competitive strategy. I hope for your sake that you are right about Amazon's amazing success. Granted, I live in a wealthier area that isn't as likely to fit within Amazon's price sensitive demo, but I've yet to hear a single person say they are ordering a new Kindle and that includes several Prime members. I think Amazon is in trouble. Google beat it to a superior $199 7" tab and everyone else will wait to see what the competitive landscape looks like for the holiday season. There just isn't a compelling reason to rush into purchase now. I'll say this. Bezos is all in. Committed most cash and working capital to Knidle hype. Commercials non stop. 3rd party financing just in time for recession. Poorly timed Kindle release designed to hide declining sales growth associated with having to collect taxes. I hope some of the analysts do their job for a change and ask some pertinent questions (daily sales ex-kindle post tax collection in California versus pre tax collection ex-kindle. The reality is that Amazon is in the most vulnerable position it has ever been...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1348896626288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 01:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348919706047-4</Id><Title>huge rise on thirsday</Title><Msg>can anyone explain why amzn went up so much?</Msg><Username>loumops</Username><Timestamp>1348919706047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 07:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348920414811-5</Id><Title>Tech, you waste your time with these pumper idiots</Title><Msg>Its a pig - just short it... You dont have to Explain why because the parabolic chart tells the story... You just need to ignore the pumper idiots - they dont even bet for godsakes, and stay away from optionz.</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1348920414811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:06:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348930125838-6</Id><Title>AMZN will collapse after Oct or on January 2013</Title><Msg>this company is pumped to much</Msg><Username>emanuel_dabah</Username><Timestamp>1348930125838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:48:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348931083122-7</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, you waste your time with these pumper idiots</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1348920414811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Techyboy is just another obessive compulsive like yourself who spends waaaaaaaaaay too much time ranting on message boards. I'm beginning to suspect he's a federal employee.............</Msg><Username>skiidady7</Username><Timestamp>1348931083122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:04:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348932614549-8</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, you waste your time with these pumper idiots</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1348920414811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've heard the same story for the 3 years I've been on this board. I bought at $135, and shorts were saying it has to go down. Of course none of them has read JB's letter to the stock holders.</Msg><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1348932614549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:30:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348952834193-9</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, you waste your time with these pumper idiots</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1348920414811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I spend time posting and explaining so that retail investors who happen to come to this board get a fundamental perspective and so that they realize the behavorial investing games that are being played (designed to draw them in and, as you often say, transfer money from the many to the few). On most boards, I find some intelligent longs with a reasonable and cohesive, if flawed, investment thesis. Amazon's board has been devoid of any such longs for awhile now. Geeg and Nemesis try, but Nem has many gaping holes and inconsistencies in his arguments and Egg, well he doesn't really have any content to add. Bruce wisely took about 2/3 off the table, which I respect, but his entire thesis is based upon cult worship of Bezos, which will prove massively misplaced (but to Bezos' credit, he will suffer more than anyone else because he has held most of his shares where in most of these scams management is dumping shares into the company buybacks)</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1348952834193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 17:07:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348952963462-10</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, you waste your time with these pumper idiots</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1348920414811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still hurting from me schooling you on CMG I guess...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1348952963462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 17:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348959285300-11</Id><Title>Shorts, celebrate and rejoice the upcomming windfall.... Skiidady iz posting, which means a BIG pullback is around the corner</Title><Msg>Like Cramer and in cramer fashion, this bozo only showz up when the top is in....</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1348959285300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:54:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348961651234-12</Id><Topic><Title>huge rise on thirsday</Title><Username>loumops</Username><Timestamp>1348919706047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 07:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did it really go up "so much"? I don't think so. It's all relative. Wasn't the high on Thursday noticeably below $264.11, AMZN's all-time high, reached on September 14 of this year. To me, AMZN appears to be in the latest distribution/accumulation phase. She will remain in this phase indefinitely until AMZN's price level changes. Will the next price level higher or lower? If you're short already or thinking of shorting, odds are great that AMZN will go up. If you're long already or thinking of going long, odds are great that AMZN will go down.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1348961651234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:34:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>