<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-30"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348979942135-1</Id><Title>Consumer Reports</Title><Msg>November 2012 Consumer Reports mentions Amazon in two places. Page 14 to 16 "Best online retailer" ranks Amazon 11 out of 52 with a score of 87 (very high). It was only average in shipping (which local shipping should improve) and customer service. Costco ranked 4th and eBay was 23rd. Macy's, Bestbuy, Walmart, Samsclub, Target and Sears were in the lower half. Page 33 ranks Kindle in 4th,6th and 7th place under 6 to 7 inch e-book readers. Barnes &amp; Noble Nook with Glowlight ranked 1st. Kindle Fire was not mentioned under 7 inch tablets. I expect AMZN to bottom at 247 next week.</Msg><Username>edison20</Username><Timestamp>1348979942135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:39:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349003192315-2</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, you waste your time with these pumper idiots</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1348920414811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I spend time posting and explaining so that retail investors who happen to come to this board get a fundamental perspective and so that they realize the behavorial investing games that are being played..." Yes, so that he can explain how the game led to his shorting from $230 a share and then losing lots of money, and how we should pity the fool for having done so.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1349003192315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 07:06:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349010295835-3</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, you waste your time with these pumper idiots</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1348920414811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bruce, You can't use pass performance to predict future appreciation. If you bought at $135 do you have a price that you expect to sell? With these "growth" stories PPS can evaporate in a flash ( NFLX,GMCR,CMG etc) I was long MNST and watched 20% appreciation turn into down 10% in a day. On the other hand I was down 25% shorting CMG before closing out that position up 200%. To be transparent, I had AMZN short briefly, but realized quickly that now was not the time to short, so I'm on the sidelines for now. I'm thinking it (and the markets) have one last squeeze in it.Thinking 270-275 range as an entry to a solid short position. - PJ</Msg><Username>pjlouie13</Username><Timestamp>1349010295835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:04:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349012650627-4</Id><Title>Sell confirmed on AMZN</Title><Msg>check the weekly candlesticks on Americanbulls.</Msg><Username>jai_hakim</Username><Timestamp>1349012650627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:44:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349014568516-5</Id><Title>Tech makes some well researched and adaquately supported points when arguing a case to pumpers, but........</Title><Msg>Its all useless because stox havent traded on fundementalz since 1968 and have become more of a scam today then at any point in history, and now the bond market iz in the same scam catagory as stox. Its also useless arguing with bubble blowing pumperz of scam stox on a number of levelz: 1. They dont actually bet, their only purpose iz to bash. 2. They are unable to reason because of the point number 3. 3. They are severely retarded.</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1349014568516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349014861562-6</Id><Title>PJ, you dunce. Sybil already called a top, which sybil rarely does. Its 264.11.</Title><Msg>Sybil delivered that message to the masses, as the trading gods had spoken them to sybil..... Do not doubt them - short at will here at these levelz, or pay the price of being "out" and missing a nice fvcken drop dude.... Sybs just saying - dont be stupid.</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1349014861562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:21:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349015255888-7</Id><Title>The muni bond market, and gvt bond market az a whole iz like bernanke being in a match the pot game and losing</Title><Msg>You got a sheit pile of money, watchez, a car title to the car outside, and a couple of ious in a pot of a big game of Acey Duecey sitting their between 3 pals (the US, China, and the EU), benanke after catching an ace on the last acey duecy and matching the pot with an iou, just got a king - four and went "pot" with QE 3 and now has a fvckin three sitting in front of him.... Now he's gotta figure out how he is gonna make good on this one without gettung his ars kicked....</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1349015255888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349022855794-8</Id><Topic><Title>The muni bond market, and gvt bond market az a whole iz like bernanke being in a match the pot game and losing</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1349015255888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:27:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The muni bond market, and gvt bond market az a whole iz like bernanke being in a match the pot game and losing" This shows shorts' desperation. They shorted AMZN for Amazon specific reasons (high p/e, sales tax issues, low margin, slowing growth, prospect of reporting negative earnings, blah, blah, blah). Once they realize that they are deeply in the red, they resort to macro-economic reasons. Pathetic losers.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1349022855794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349026795164-9</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, you waste your time with these pumper idiots</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1348920414811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ski talked the same kind of smack as you as CMG rose from 330 to 450. I double up above 400 and rode it down to about 310 on a weighted average basis. Made a killing. Will here as well. In fact, I almost doubled my position above 260 last week (only increased it 60%) on the silly up days. I have plenty of cash to see this scam through to its implosion. The lengths Bezos and analysts are going through to mask the real situation is amazing. If anyone dissects the vendor financing logically, you can only conclude that Amazon is being hurt by sales tax collection and it is a play to avoid sales tax in California and elsewhere by only "fulfilling" the orders. If so, one might look to value Amazon based upon the same metrics given to UPS and FedEx.... Hopefully, at least a few of the analysts will be intellectually honest and start digging into what is a VERY material issue. I'll dive a little deeper in the week leading up to earnings. There are so many holes to the Scamazon story at this point, it is nuts.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1349026795164</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:39:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349028308117-10</Id><Topic><Title>The muni bond market, and gvt bond market az a whole iz like bernanke being in a match the pot game and losing</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1349015255888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:27:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. I short Amazon because its fundamentals flat out suck. And I mean suck. And are getting worse in the real world (lower ROIC, lower inventory turns, greater overhead -- and that'wes before the massive TV blitz / desperation attempt to maintain revenue growth, if at the expense of cash flow and profitability). Amazon's competitors maintained a strategic cash stockpile, recognizing that a down drat would eventually come and hit hard. They are all in a great psoition to be more aggressive than ever through a downturn. Amazon burned through most of its cash on a completely unnecessary hardware play (the right move was to stay out of hardware and simply offer a killer app for integration into its content ecosystem). It has opened a 3 front war against Apple, Google and Wal-Mart, but Amazon lacks the cash on the balance sheet and the cash flow to win. They should each take a specific portion of the Amazon portfolio and undercut Amazon's price (Apple in content, since it makes money in hardware, Wal-Mart in electronics since it is big ticket, high value density stuff which would leave Amazon fulfilling low value density high relative shipping cost stuff and Google in Cloud, with a scorched earth on AWS). I suspect they see it too, which is why Apple is already matching price on e books. Add in a nice recession (which will hurt Amazon disproportionately because it relies upon customer financing through effectively negative working capital) and this will be a fun year. Nemesis, almost all of my puts are 2013 at this point (Jan and April), so good luck keeping the scam running for another 6+ months. Any move up, I adjust strikes and add contracts...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1349028308117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:05:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349031360168-11</Id><Topic><Title>The muni bond market, and gvt bond market az a whole iz like bernanke being in a match the pot game and losing</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1349015255888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:27:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Add in a nice recession (which will hurt Amazon disproportionately because it relies upon customer financing through effectively negative working capital) and this will be a fun year." Can you explain to us why a recession should impact the stock market at all? I don't see why it should.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1349031360168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:56:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349031812495-12</Id><Topic><Title>The muni bond market, and gvt bond market az a whole iz like bernanke being in a match the pot game and losing</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1349015255888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:27:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where to start... First, the fundamentals will degrade and eventually, that always leads to declines. But, I get the logic behind your question is if Benny B is going to print, will stock prices drop? The short answer is yes. While you and others talk smack about the macro, it turns out that macro has been what has propped the US equities up... Like bonds, the cleanest dirty sheet. But, the valuatn gap is too large to hold if we too are headed into recession (which we are). Give it a few months. You'll see and it will be much bigger than expected. Shorts, be patient. Time is on your side. Do not pile in. Scale in and you will do very well...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1349031812495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:03:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349044495930-13</Id><Topic><Title>The muni bond market, and gvt bond market az a whole iz like bernanke being in a match the pot game and losing</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1349015255888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:27:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazon has a very expensive distribution system. All these "fulfillment centers with bozos milling around, and air freight costs rising. And the price advantage now going bye bye with sales taxes. This is the most compelling short idea around. The fact that skiidady has shown up to push the bull**** (like he did with CMG) nearly clinches a major top may be in, soon if not already.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1349044495930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349044727838-14</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, you waste your time with these pumper idiots</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1348920414811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch the pumpers all go away when Amazon does a cliff dive. They always do.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1349044727838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:38:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349044986742-15</Id><Title>This is going to do a "Chipotle" dive</Title><Msg>I can sense it.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1349044986742</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:43:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349045105303-16</Id><Topic><Title>This is going to do a "Chipotle" dive</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1349044986742</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:43:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the spooky thing for the bulls is that skiidady has shown up on the bull side and sybil on the bear side, and we all know where that ended for poor Chipotle this summer.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1349045105303</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349047181451-17</Id><Topic><Title>This is going to do a "Chipotle" dive</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1349044986742</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:43:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't get too eager. I doubt they let another fall off the cliff like that. Will likely take more patience, persistence and pain tolerance....</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1349047181451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:19:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349048511656-18</Id><Title>Just got Sybil a new box of salty crackers</Title><Msg>He's gonna need something to chew on when his statement comes in the mail</Msg><Username>philandjoelle</Username><Timestamp>1349048511656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:41:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349050558539-19</Id><Topic><Title>The muni bond market, and gvt bond market az a whole iz like bernanke being in a match the pot game and losing</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1349015255888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:27:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its kind of sad actually.... They should take away his internet access at prison.</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1349050558539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 20:15:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349050879277-20</Id><Topic><Title>Just got Sybil a new box of salty crackers</Title><Username>philandjoelle</Username><Timestamp>1349048511656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:41:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil cashed in shorts for saweet 20% gainz and moved on with that dieck's faaaaaagy handle.... Now he chases sybil arounfd the internet trying to get 'even'. What an idiot.</Msg><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1349050879277</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 20:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349054703408-21</Id><Topic><Title>Facebook $FB Popped today. What you should know. amzn</Title><Username>stockman821</Username><Timestamp>1348852227568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:10:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why on earth would you buy FB, they are stuck in the sand with little growth and they don't know what to do. RENN, the Chinese Facebook will triple in OCT! Scamazon is going under 200 very soon!</Msg><Username>classactionlawsuitsonnakedshrts</Username><Timestamp>1349054703408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:25:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349055614854-22</Id><Topic><Title>Just got Sybil a new box of salty crackers</Title><Username>philandjoelle</Username><Timestamp>1349048511656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:41:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a broke donkey and the PCLN board is still laughing at you How's your TOL trade working out for ya? LMAO at you yet again!</Msg><Username>philandjoelle</Username><Timestamp>1349055614854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:40:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349056354290-23</Id><Topic><Title>The muni bond market, and gvt bond market az a whole iz like bernanke being in a match the pot game and losing</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1349015255888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:27:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"First, the fundamentals will degrade and eventually, that always leads to declines." Why "always"? Here's interesting statistics: Financial (Non-Home) Wealth owned by Top 1 percent Next 19 percent Bottom 80 percent: 2007 42.7% 50.3% 7.0% 2010 42.1% 53.5% 4.7% [Edward N. Wolff at New York University (2012)] The above data show that in 2007, the top 20% of the U.S. households owned about 93% of the total wealth (excluding residential houses), and in 2010 (after the recession of 2007/2008 or whatever you'd like to call it), the situation got even more pronounced: the top 20% own 95.6% of the wealth (excluding residential houses). No wonder "bad" employment numbers do not affect the stock market AT ALL. Do you honestly believe that the bottom 80% own enough numbers of shares of stocks and/or mutual funds to affect the market in any significant ways even if they decide to liquidate all of their holdings? There you have it: the reason why the stock market has been detached from the real economy.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1349056354290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349059237700-24</Id><Topic><Title>PJ, you dunce. Sybil already called a top, which sybil rarely does. Its 264.11.</Title><Username>philandjoel1e</Username><Timestamp>1349014861562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:21:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Sybil!! You spend all those gains from shorting CMG yet!? I gave some back shorting AMZN before earning and shorting FAS before Bernanke but plan on loading up before this quarter is out. I still see a push before earnings, so maybe it only goes to 264.01. Missed getting in on Thursday by a quarter. This won't cliff dive before earnings, we got time. So what color candles the gods like? I'll make sure to light some this week, while paying my respects! Make sure you put in a good word for me will ya?! - PJ p.s. Does Sybil wear expensive yoga pants?</Msg><Username>pjlouie13</Username><Timestamp>1349059237700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 22:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>