<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367994852286-1</Id><Topic><Title>Next stop for AMZN: 220! Flag this post and revisit it...</Title><Username>soonersof_ou</Username><Timestamp>1367975178738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:06:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I approve this message</Msg><Username>mikeylucky_daddy</Username><Timestamp>1367994852286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 02:34:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368010882760-2</Id><Topic><Title>Look out over yonder from the hieghts of a mkt blowoff top</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1367610749178</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 15:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Sometimes it better to keep you mouth shut and let people think you're and idiot, then to open it up and prove it." Looks like rick haz got some sour grapes... Perhaps you showed showed up to go long az the party iz winding down? Sybil will dig through a sheeeeeiiiitpile of amzn iou'z that sybil haz in sybs Master Margin Power Trade Account to see if any have are emblazened with a seal "PROPERTY OF RICK". If found, Sybs promisez to return them back to you, but they'll be slightly depreciated, and perhaps worth $120.00 or less, dummy.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368010882760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 07:01:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368011617269-3</Id><Title>Sybil iz making preparationz for friday, for it iz an extra special day</Title><Msg>We will begin the day az usual with libationz and festivitiez while we are entertained by watching crack head optionz buyerz torn appart from limb to limb by robots in the collesiun. To wind down the day, at 2:20 pm est we will bow our headz and hold up one finger in a moment of silence in rememberance of the phat phingered phlash crash that crippled the markets 3 yearz ago. While we still don't know exactly what happened to creat a catastrophic failure in the markets, we will belive the official word of the SEC like good sheeple and blame the whole thing on one trader'z phat phinger that punched in an extra 0 or 3 on a stok dump, but it had nothing to do with scam bitcoin markets being operated by benevolent robots that create the very liquidity, toutedby HFTVrobot runnerz , that vanished entirely that fateful day az the market wide bids dropped to 0 and the asks went to infinity in the matter of millisecondz.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368011617269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 07:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368018908182-4</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil iz making preparationz for friday, for it iz an extra special day</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368011617269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 07:13:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hasn't this Sybil lady been claiming all these months that she doesn't care about short-term market moves? Well, I guess she is indeed a woman. Hahahaha . . . .</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1368018908182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:15:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368019497019-5</Id><Title>CNBC talking about Fraud non stop today...</Title><Msg>Allowing for the possibility that it is, yet encouraging people to invest and participate because the fraud may take it higher before it craters. Highly responsible... Here is the answer people. Scale out of the financial markets. Do not invest in "liquid" / HFT manipulated markets. Invest locally in physical and productive assets where there is MASSIVE multiple arbitrage between the liquid/public manipulated markets and the fundamental economics...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1368019497019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:24:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368024596215-6</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil iz making preparationz for friday, for it iz an extra special day</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368011617269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 07:13:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Geegee, you dummy... Where in this thread do you read that sybil iz trying to short term 'time' the markets.... Abject retread.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368024596215</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:49:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368025192376-7</Id><Title>Huh.... Imagine that? No volume to be found anywhere in the scam markets</Title><Msg>Like an air plane hitting stall speed on the wing tips following a steep ascent... Hey stupidz, do You know what comez next following a stall??? Thaaaaats right! An uncontrolled descent into tail spin and crash... Very good sheeple. Very good, indeed at answering sybby's aeronautics 101 question.... Unfortunately bernanke iz not az good az old sully who stuck a landing in the hudson, he's more like danszel washington's character in flight thats been partying the good party az he pressez hiz luck getting up to the canopy.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368025192376</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:59:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368026723101-8</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC talking about Fraud non stop today...</Title><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1368019497019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:24:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Overpriced can on be good for one thing...shorting once the dam breaks. It's dangerous to be in because there's always the possibility that you're a bag holder.</Msg><Username>tung_5000</Username><Timestamp>1368026723101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 11:25:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368027816872-9</Id><Title>Tesla earnings today- Short squeeze?</Title><Msg>So almost 50% of the shares are short, I am going to look more into it. Definately not touching it today, but if they do a short squeeze will look at it Friday. Meanwhile the market is chugging along, along with my two shorts AMZN and LNKD.</Msg><Username>kenji100</Username><Timestamp>1368027816872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 11:43:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368028665901-10</Id><Title>Sybil iz an equal opportunity shorter of pig stox</Title><Msg>Why not open a fresh position in a pig? Status: FILLED at $364.09 Symbol: CMG Description: CHIPOTLE MEXICAN GRILL INC Action: Sell Short Quantity: 100 Filled Quantity: 100 Route:</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368028665901</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 11:57:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368029102902-11</Id><Topic><Title>FPE of 80</Title><Username>lived666or12</Username><Timestamp>1367977551664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:45:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Analysts forecasted $3-4 for 2012 and 2013 as well, and of course their estimates turned out horribly wrong. It is amazing to see that they are doing this with a market cap of $120 billion.</Msg><Username>kenji100</Username><Timestamp>1368029102902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:05:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368029212852-12</Id><Title>Will Sybil take a few pennies today?</Title><Msg>Her average AMZN short price is $260.04.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1368029212852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368029659929-13</Id><Title>$15 bucks in 5 days, nice retrace now @ 50% of the drop.</Title><Msg>Investors must love the reduced revenue outlook, reduced earnings and cash flow outlook. Reduced discretionary spending of consumers, implimentation of sales tax everywhere, ROIC near 0% (lowest ever for AMZN), eBay market share gains, $95 oil, etc.... Has there been any good news for AMZN this CY? My broker tells me to just buy it as none of that financial stuff matters with this stock (just chase the money).... those were the discussions brokers had with me in 2000 .... here we go again!</Msg><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1368029659929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:14:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368030378200-14</Id><Topic><Title>Between yesterdayz close and now, sybs account value climbed by a whopping:</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1367005327786</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 15:42:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil: "Right now sybs net profit iz roughly 147,000, which iz about to rock and roll biatchez" A loser. Sybil just doesn't know when to quit.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1368030378200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:26:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368030656071-15</Id><Topic><Title>In celabration of todayz all time highz, sybil opened up a fresh short position</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1367517657826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 14:00:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time to add, Sybil, you random shooter. 417.07 now. It's plummeting!</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1368030656071</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:30:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368031063356-16</Id><Topic><Title>FPE of 80</Title><Username>lived666or12</Username><Timestamp>1367977551664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:45:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And someday, they will be held accountable. Hopefully by investors because the alternative may well end up much more serious for them. How many people committed suicide because of Enron? What if people realize that the money was effectively stolen from them by a large scale trading scam? They might decide to ensure the perpetrators feel their pain this time...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1368031063356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:37:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368031450085-17</Id><Title>See massive sell-off</Title><Msg>Too far too fast on nothing but printing money world wide. Massive debt world wide that will never be re paid . All games trying to buy time.All worthless paper money especially in USA. Just one massive pryamid scheme.All chasing yield worthless paper.</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1368031450085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:44:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368031562354-18</Id><Title>Aaaaaaaaaand how about this one for an opening position? Good time to short, kidz, but stay away from those crack head optionz</Title><Msg>Status: FILLED at $731.72 Symbol: PCLN Description: PRICELINE INC Action: Sell Short Quantity: 50 Filled Quantity: 50 Route:</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368031562354</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368031767649-19</Id><Topic><Title>Will Sybil take a few pennies today?</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1368029212852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:06:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Her average AMZN short price is $260.04." Actually its 266.82, dummy. The broker spits out an avg cost basis When you hold an underlying position for more than an hour, rather than trying to time with optionz by the minute</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368031767649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:49:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368033639301-20</Id><Topic><Title>FPE of 80</Title><Username>lived666or12</Username><Timestamp>1367977551664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:45:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tech after the 2008 debacle, I don't believe anybody will be held accountable. We had a chance to clean up the system, but everybody went into dreamland and preffered to get back to the old games. Problem is next crash is going to be so much worse, hope I am wrong.</Msg><Username>kenji100</Username><Timestamp>1368033639301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:20:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368034337513-21</Id><Topic><Title>See massive sell-off</Title><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1368031450085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:44:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agreed, debt bubbles are everywhere: student loans, car loans, mortgages, credit cards etc... all chasing the almighty yield that are not supposed to be there since most of western world the GPD is either zero, negative, or minimal growth. Stocks is just a microcosm of the bad behaviors of the central bankers chasing growth to keep up with appearances to the rest of the world. Everybody knows it's phony but it's just too good to end. I don't think they even contemplate the consequences of their actions until there are people on the streets calling for heads will roll.</Msg><Username>tung_5000</Username><Timestamp>1368034337513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:32:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368034735961-22</Id><Title>Someone must be building a massive short position, the bots are having tough time lately pushing it up</Title><Msg>they are working over time and getting little results</Msg><Username>zbc407</Username><Timestamp>1368034735961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368034774227-23</Id><Topic><Title>FPE of 80</Title><Username>lived666or12</Username><Timestamp>1367977551664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:45:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Suicides rates (especially amongst 50+ males) are rising. The propaganda machine known as the financial media is inducing depression amongst those struggling with its incessant propaganda (lies really...) about the state of employment and the economy are making people think it is their fault rather than a broader systemic issue. IMHO they are complicit in the scam and partially responsible for the elevated suicide rates. The failure of the system to hold those responsible to account is what is likely to eventually lead to a change from suicidal tendencies to anger and violent ones. I hope TPTB recognize it is time to change course while there is still a path for a relatively smooth and peaceful transition. They have to give up the excesses and actually earn money from creating value rather than skimming from others. They have to allow balance to return. But, right now, it seems they are playing the infinite leverage takeout game that will only lead to destabilizing outcomes in time...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1368034774227</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:39:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368035902518-24</Id><Topic><Title>Someone must be building a massive short position, the bots are having tough time lately pushing it up</Title><Username>zbc407</Username><Timestamp>1368034735961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the market strength that big boys are using for distribution. The overall market is going up with thin volume, which is perfect to walk it up for easy sells.</Msg><Username>hb5fa_2</Username><Timestamp>1368035902518</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368036029804-25</Id><Title>Short term market correction is coming if S&amp;P goes below 1625</Title><Msg>Taking up more short here.</Msg><Username>hb5fa_2</Username><Timestamp>1368036029804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:00:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368036372682-26</Id><Title>Channel Advisor predict AMZN revs MISS next quarter</Title><Msg>I'd post the u-r-l path but got b-locked by Yahoo 3 times already</Msg><Username>zbc407</Username><Timestamp>1368036372682</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:06:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368036773742-27</Id><Title>Could you imagine if the bots scanned for posts on the message boards...</Title><Msg>ruh roh buckwheat Frashaa's down ggggggggggg all would tell the bots what to do these comments of course, would be just as useful as anything else</Msg><Username>zbc407</Username><Timestamp>1368036773742</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:12:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368037399965-28</Id><Title>Paltry volumez..... Sniff sniff, whats that smell?</Title><Msg>Smellz like bots taking a massive dump in the swirling toilet we call the market.... That would lead to a phlash crash... Sure sure, the SEC would blame it on some poor traderz stinky unwashed phat finger that he had stuffed in a nasty #$%$ the night before, or some terrorists hack into twitter sending out nasty gramz about the pres.... But in the end we all know that smell iz really thoze HFTVrobots releiving themselvez at high speedz after a nasty constipation of bernanke bux.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368037399965</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:23:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368037507183-29</Id><Topic><Title>Someone must be building a massive short position, the bots are having tough time lately pushing it up</Title><Username>zbc407</Username><Timestamp>1368034735961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So is CalPers or others pensions just become bag holders again? I'll venture to say SMA 50 is where the selling will be begin. Black boxes are being primed for another dump.</Msg><Username>tung_5000</Username><Timestamp>1368037507183</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:25:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368037696466-30</Id><Title>Senate passes internet sales tax bill amid opposition from conservatives</Title><Msg>Screw the consumer. All it is is a grab for more tax money from the consumer so the government can have more of your money to spend. Hope AMZN takes a beating since they were in favor of this tax increase. I for one will no longer buy from Amazon on line, no siree.</Msg><Username>muksieatea</Username><Timestamp>1368037696466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:28:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368037717340-31</Id><Topic><Title>FPE of 80</Title><Username>lived666or12</Username><Timestamp>1367977551664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:45:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"after the 2008 debacle"...... The fed wont be able to step in and save anything.... Bernanke iz dirty harry, except in this movie he actually fired all 6 shots instead of 5.... Do you feel lucky, punk?</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368037717340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:28:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368037924341-32</Id><Topic><Title>Someone must be building a massive short position, the bots are having tough time lately pushing it up</Title><Username>zbc407</Username><Timestamp>1368034735961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All state pension funds in states where AMZN is not collecting taxes should simply withdraw all direct and indirect investment in Amazon until it collects taxes (and yes, that means pulling from funds that are invested in it). The financial community would hammer Amazon quickly until it conceded and the problem would be gone. Small internet retailers do not materially adversely affect employment and the velocity of money the way that Amazon does.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1368037924341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:32:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368037937377-33</Id><Topic><Title>Someone must be building a massive short position, the bots are having tough time lately pushing it up</Title><Username>zbc407</Username><Timestamp>1368034735961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup yup</Msg><Username>hb5fa_2</Username><Timestamp>1368037937377</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:32:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368038103016-34</Id><Title>Beautiful price actions</Title><Msg>Too bad I have an appointment and have to leave and cannot witness it happening. I have added to my position. Good luck to all. Peace.</Msg><Username>hb5fa_2</Username><Timestamp>1368038103016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:35:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368038727055-35</Id><Title>Morgan Stanly note hurting AMZN</Title><Msg>MS survey results: 11% of AMZN customers would never buy from AMZN again if they collected sales tax, and another 60% said they would spend less. Wow - 71% of AMZN customers would either spend less of go away .... ouch.</Msg><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1368038727055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:45:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368039117621-36</Id><Topic><Title>Morgan Stanly note hurting AMZN</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1368038727055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:45:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except those Prime customers who joined Prime basically for free video. They have limited resources and will continue their small size order with free two day shipping... And someday the analysts will correctly analyze the cost drivers for a mail order business that delivers directly to the door... Stacked loss leaders create interesting liabilities...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1368039117621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:51:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368040708906-37</Id><Topic><Title>Someone must be building a massive short position, the bots are having tough time lately pushing it up</Title><Username>zbc407</Username><Timestamp>1368034735961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Name starts with an E?</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1368040708906</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:18:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368040711800-38</Id><Title>Last ones in here get caught big time</Title><Msg>Like all massive pyramid schemes last ones in get left holding the massive losses. These games of greed never end with Wall Street.Blame the Federal Reserve for this with cheap money. It will destroy the whole system.</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1368040711800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:18:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368040830741-39</Id><Title>New Ernst &amp; Young Survey: many firms misrepresenting results to meet targets</Title><Msg>Of course Amazon isn't.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1368040830741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368041224280-40</Id><Topic><Title>Morgan Stanly note hurting AMZN</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1368038727055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:45:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tech - I was reading through Credit Suisse report where they missed the shipping expense line by 30% ($300M) and actually claimed to have nailed it. They put out a huge piece just prior to the Q announcement on how the new fulfillment centers would drive down shipping costs - boy were they wrong. Turns out that even though gas prices were down almost 2% Y/Y shipping expense once again outgew revenue (26% vs 21%). As we have discussed this is related to the ASP declines in the biz that swamp out any advantage the fulfillment centers may be offering. So, go spend $Billions on FC's, fact is the economics are like quick sand for AMZN and will eventually suffocate them.</Msg><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1368041224280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:27:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368041410093-41</Id><Topic><Title>Morgan Stanly note hurting AMZN</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1368038727055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:45:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The bounce back post the MS news proves this to be a trading scam. That news should have sent the stock down 5% at least. The price is not tied to the fundamentals at all. Tech - I hope you are close to blowing this thing up .. I have tried in other ways, but to no avail - scam is too powerful.</Msg><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1368041410093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:30:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368041469957-42</Id><Topic><Title>FPE of 80</Title><Username>lived666or12</Username><Timestamp>1367977551664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:45:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But, right now, it seems they are playing the infinite leverage takeout game that will only lead to destabilizing outcomes in time" This seems to be the case, people's greed knows no bounds, the guy with $1 billion, wants to make that $5 billion etc etc, good for him if he abides by tax rules, fair market principles but no, government needs to save us we are too big to go bankrupt offshore accounts, outright fraud etc etc</Msg><Username>kenji100</Username><Timestamp>1368041469957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:31:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368041557455-43</Id><Topic><Title>Morgan Stanly note hurting AMZN</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1368038727055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:45:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The analysts are the same people doing this stuff years and years and doesn't matter if they are wrong they keep doing the same job.</Msg><Username>kenji100</Username><Timestamp>1368041557455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:32:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368041763944-44</Id><Topic><Title>Senate passes internet sales tax bill amid opposition from conservatives</Title><Username>muksieatea</Username><Timestamp>1368037696466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:28:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you haven't been following the story. AMZN for years and years fought this tax regulation, but finally they saw that they would lose. What do you mean scew the consumer? Why is it ok to buy from Best buy and pay taxes, and buy from AMZN and not pay taxes, where is the logic in that??</Msg><Username>kenji100</Username><Timestamp>1368041763944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:36:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368043000198-45</Id><Title>Time to close out longz and scrrrrraaaape in $28k of gainz</Title><Msg>Status: FILLED at $8.84 Symbol: AA Description: ALCOA INC Action: Sell Quantity: 30000 Filled Quantity: 30000 Route:</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368043000198</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:56:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368043430721-46</Id><Topic><Title>Beautiful price actions</Title><Username>hb5fa_2</Username><Timestamp>1368038103016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:35:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nasdaq closed at high of day Amzn closed $1.61 below high of day It is weak, and getting weaker. Perhaps bots will throw in towel tomorrow</Msg><Username>zbc407</Username><Timestamp>1368043430721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:03:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368043480404-47</Id><Topic><Title>Time to close out longz and scrrrrraaaape in $28k of gainz</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368043000198</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:56:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Robots are walking the markets up the same way they did cmg in 2012.... Time to get outbefore we reach the top of the stair case and walk off into a 1000 point drop on the s&amp;p</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368043480404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368043481672-48</Id><Topic><Title>Someone must be building a massive short position, the bots are having tough time lately pushing it up</Title><Username>zbc407</Username><Timestamp>1368034735961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lol, Amazon used to have a legal map of 50 states showing which they should not set foot into due to tax and other employment issues. JB is some kinda guy.</Msg><Username>tung_5000</Username><Timestamp>1368043481672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:04:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368044896539-49</Id><Title>LION BROADCASTING WARNS RETAIL: BEZOS SALES TAX FRAUD LOOT BUBBLE GAME OVER , WHAT NEXT? CRASH AND BURN</Title><Msg>PAY DIVIDEND OR GO SINGLE DIGITS IN 2014 LEAP PUTS RECOMMENDED TO RETAIL FOR 2014/2015 ON THIS RETAIL HYPED BUBBLE MANIA TREAT THEM LIKE WMT/COST NEXT.... WHY NO DIVIDEND HERE??</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1368044896539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:28:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368046327057-50</Id><Title>Robots got crackhead optionz buyerz on a spit</Title><Msg>And are roasting them alive.... Theze poor slobz are getting painfully cooked.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368046327057</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:52:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368048584286-51</Id><Title>Yo tech, how those leaps hold'in up?</Title><Msg>Sybs did warn you about those fvck in thingz and URGED restraint and resistance to that high grade expensive crack.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368048584286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:29:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368048908824-52</Id><Title>The blood of optionz crackheadz haz sered az robot fuel since 2009</Title><Msg>Those poor slobz got thrown in a fvck in juicer with a banana and some yogurt</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368048908824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368050328647-53</Id><Title>Singhlion iz the internet equivalent of that homeless kook down the street from a manhattan coffee shop</Title><Msg>He'z been shouting at by passerz az they shuffle their way along the busy streets of the city, preaching that death and destruction iz upon us all and that we should REPENT before it iz too late and the death of a title wave struck by the Lord'z Hand iz upon us all since 2009. Don't worry singh, sybil will drop a buck in your hat on the way by and listen to a few wordz of your warningz. Fight the good fight , bro.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368050328647</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:58:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368064163458-54</Id><Title>No more 'cost advantage' for a flying pig that haz achieved its mission to become a world class loss leader</Title><Msg>Pay the tax! pay the tax! Tax ! Tax! Tax! Bezos stopped fighting the inevetible, but only few know that he cashed out billionz in free stok on the backs of bagz before thowing in the towel. He'z just fine, but what about the poor bagz and 401k's that hold this pos? When the markets TANK (notice 'when' rather than 'if'), this pig and the poor bagz that knowingly and unknowingly own it are gonna get painfully butchered with a butter knife .</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368064163458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:49:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368067217264-55</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN will test $300 in the next several days.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1367945135459</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:45:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your a joke</Msg><Username>xdon69</Username><Timestamp>1368067217264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:40:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368069138494-56</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN will test $300 in the next several days.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1367945135459</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:45:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If she doesn't test even $297.21 within the next several days, I will stop posting here." Geegee - 05/07/2013 One can only hope that this dope stayz true to hiz word</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1368069138494</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 23:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>