<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-09-15"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379232144689-1</Id><Topic><Title>Shop By Local: Find national brands, locally, with the worlds most relevant local search engine, Krillion</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1376825608369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 07:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why Shop by Local is more sustanainable than Yelp Do you use Yelp, if you had fund through Yelp an excellent restaurant, Yelp once more and more again? Do you use Yelp, if you had fund through Yelp an excellent hairdresser, Yelp once more and more again? I believe, I can stop my questions, because everybody is easy clear, that Yelp will be hurt from saturationseffects. But if you look for a buy of a new product with Sho by Local, you will ever do the same, if you look for a new product again. Saturationeffects like by Yelp don't exist. Less Very bad growth of Yelp: Only to 58-59 million it Q3/13 from 55 million in Q2/13 = only 6,9% - a joke for a company with more than 20-times-revenues. “The San Francisco-based local business reviewer said it lost 1 cent per share on $55 million in revenue for the second-quarter. For the third-quarter, Yelp expects sales to be between $58 million and $59 million.” Less</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1379232144689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-15 04:02:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379242554689-2</Id><Title>It's True America WAS a nation of immigrants, but NOW...</Title><Msg>It is the case of illegal immigrants, it is law breakers, criminals, gang thugs, drug runners and the occasional Jihadist. The Past does not equal the present, and Mr PresentIdiot oBOMBa is making one shinning sea to shinning sea GHETTO !!!</Msg><Username>rebelwithchemicals</Username><Timestamp>1379242554689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-15 06:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379243350374-3</Id><Topic><Title>Miss leading</Title><Username>rocketman2001ab</Username><Timestamp>1378995933609</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:25:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The insider monkey Motley fool deception report of 15.7 billion in earning was actually 7 million loss while Walmart made 6.86billion . Who is running who out of market. best buy earned 266 million</Msg><Username>rocketman2001ab</Username><Timestamp>1379243350374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-15 07:09:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379253998540-4</Id><Title>Well folks, our trusty US agencies have been kicking the can down the road for 5 solid yearz, the end of the road iz nearing quickly</Title><Msg>Fed Tapering of unsustainable QE forever iz inevitable. But alas, the economy haz 'recovered' justifying ben's inevitable announcement of The end of the easy money bond float program . Budget impass sits in front of the do nothing but take vacationz congress. Memberz of Congress, who inside trade without impunity, must sell their bitcoin stox as they take action to either cap the debt ceiling or raise it once again - the jig iz up come october with gietner gone last january, and bernanke leaving this january, the gods of unsustainable bailouts are bailing out leaving some other hack and the american economy to hold the bag. Finally, a bitcoin stok market that missed its window of opportunity for structual change iz well tread into the bubble with bit coin stox having all put in bubblicious highs of 10x and more off historic trend linez and north of 20x book valuez with ipos &amp; mega mergerz hitting a creceindo. Yes folks its been a fun float stuck inside the bubble while watching mystical pigz fly, but az with all good thingz - it must end, and End badly it will with high inflation, high unemployement, high bankruptcy, low markets, low wagez, and low government / muni services.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379253998540</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-15 10:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379284494140-5</Id><Title>stock futures go parabolic (S&amp;P up 17 , NDX up almost 35) ON Syrian agreement and Summers withdraw from Fed consideration</Title><Msg>Which means Janet Yellen, who's even more a a dove, money printer than Bernanke, has the insider track to be the next Federal Reserve Head. Techstrategy, your're a complete idiot to deny the connection b/t the Federal Reserve's ongoing QE actions and the stock market going to the moon. You've denied it forever and yet look at tonight's reaction. The market is going much higher by the looks of it with Yellen coming in.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1379284494140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-15 18:34:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379286026885-6</Id><Title>geee, why even bother askinga fraud like Sybil anything: the guy would be broke with the kind of move up we're seeing if real</Title><Msg>notice how he never talked about protecting his captial with stops, just unlimited shorts: that's just false b/c it's trading for dummies style. EVen XDON doesn't give specifics of how he trades. Just takes unlimited upside moves. Welll, there' s another big one tonight shorties without stops: you are fighting against the unlimited power of a printing press of dollars being thrown into the market. And Janet Yellen is coming next it looks like, valuations be damned: these people don't care about them: only mopping up with more liquidity when the hiccups come.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1379286026885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-15 19:00:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379289797043-7</Id><Topic><Title>stock futures go parabolic (S&amp;P up 17 , NDX up almost 35) ON Syrian agreement and Summers withdraw from Fed consideration</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1379284494140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-15 18:34:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nas, you mislead. I've never denied that WS TBTF/POMO/BB banks are using inlimited leverage in massively irresponsible ways. I've said that it hurts the real economy (and Amazon's actual performance). Technical trading based upon flows and not fundamentals eventually collapses and hard. This will too. Q3 comps not looking so good (last year got a big boost with full product line update). This is a trading scam without ANY fundamental support. If the large holders have any common sense, they will use this relief to unload as much as possiblr before earnings.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1379289797043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-15 20:03:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379291720221-8</Id><Title>Its a wonder that nascrack600 haznt worn hiz pud into a bloody nub yet</Title><Msg>The dude wastes hiz life away jerking off.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379291720221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-15 20:35:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379300217927-9</Id><Title>Because AMZN longs love roasting shorts.</Title><Msg>I've enjoyed riding the AMZN short roasting train for years, so I thought I'd mention a short busting that really started to take off on Friday. BTH is way upsidedown and looks like it's going to see some big fireworks this week. Have fun!</Msg><Username>cowboycrooner</Username><Timestamp>1379300217927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-15 22:56:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379300753821-10</Id><Title>By 9:47 a.m. EST tomorrow, we'll know . . .</Title><Msg>. . . if tomorrow is an up day or a down day. My gut feeling is that since I have no positions at all, AMZN can go up or down a lot.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1379300753821</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-15 23:05:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379301058947-11</Id><Title>Sybil and Techstrategy are both deranged.</Title><Msg>They've been dead wrong for over a year about AMZN and the market in general. Yet they still keep posting their same old "theories" after "theories" as if they know the best.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1379301058947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-15 23:10:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379301966638-12</Id><Topic><Title>geee, why even bother askinga fraud like Sybil anything: the guy would be broke with the kind of move up we're seeing if real</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1379286026885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-15 19:00:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nasdaq_6000_baby: "EVen XDON doesn't give specifics of how he trades. " Xdon69 is Sybil's minime. They have been both killed by NFLX and AMZN. (They don't admit, but they've been killed already.)</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1379301966638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-15 23:26:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>