<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-09-08"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378641637109-1</Id><Title>up $79k, advice please?</Title><Msg>I bought because of an alert on flash market research (google them) I locked in some profits. im up $79k realized but holding some freebie shares. considering locking in the rest because flash market research has a new pick coming out soon, their last pick went up 1300% which was insane - i need some advice, does anyone think I should hold or just lock all my profits in and wait for something fresh? thanks</Msg><Username>mandyschwarz9</Username><Timestamp>1378641637109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-08 08:00:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>92</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378649128221-2</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon to offer free smart phone....really</Title><Username>wuwuwu3</Username><Timestamp>1378505351000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-06 18:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>two CEOs in USA that need public hanging and their free loot seized are: JEFF BEZOS &amp; REED HASTINGS THESE CRIMINALS ARE PART OF HOME GROWN FINANCIAL ALQAEDA DESTROYING REAL BUSINESS BY RUNNING PONZI SCHEMES TO LOOT BILLIONS INTO POCKETS OF THEIR NEXUS SCAM GANGS ON FRAUD STREET CASINO IN USA “I believe that banking institutions are more dangerous to our liberties than standing armies.” – Thomas Jefferson If the American people ever allow private banks to control the issue of their currency, first by inflation, then by deflation, the banks…will deprive the people of all property until their children wake-up homeless on the continent their fathers conquered…. The issuing power should be taken from the banks and restored to the people, to whom it properly belongs. – Thomas Jefferson in the debate over the Re-charter of the Bank Bill (1809) Andrew Jackson : Gentlemen, I have had men watching you for a long time and I am convinced that you have used the funds of the bank to speculate in the breadstuffs of the country. When you won, you divided the profits amongst you, and when you lost, you charged it to the bank. You tell me that if I take the deposits from the bank and annul its charter, I shall ruin ten thousand families. That may be true, gentlemen, but that is your sin! Should I let you go on, you will ruin fifty thousand families, and that would be my sin! You are a den of vipers and thieves. DAVID STOCKMAN: We've Been Lied To, Robbed, And Misled</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1378649128221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-08 10:05:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378652277558-3</Id><Topic><Title>up $79k, advice please?</Title><Username>mandyschwarz9</Username><Timestamp>1378641637109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-08 08:00:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>su|cide?</Msg><Username>jagdeep_m2000</Username><Timestamp>1378652277558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-08 10:57:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378656014533-4</Id><Title>Free phones from Amazon</Title><Msg>Lets say they give away 1/10 as many phones as apple sold last year. That's about 15M they'd give away free. And let's say they are so bare bones that they cost only $100 to make. That's a cool $1.5B in losses. Compare that to last year's $39M in losses. Amzn shareholders should love that "opportunity". Oh, and what carrier is going to provide the cellular service for these free phones? Maybe Amzn will set up free wifi nationwide, that shouldn't cost much to provide. Bezo and Amzn will be BANKRUPT soon. With sales tax leveling the playing field and Amazon purchases having to pay for shipping and losing the instant gratification that brick n mortar buyers enjoy, this is doomed. For comparison look at Coborns Delivers, an on line grocery company that delivers your groceries. Their prices are way higher because their costs are. Amzn has only been able to survive this long due to its unfair sales tax advantage which it will lose soon making their overall price including shipping higher. Their "dumping" of product to take market share and drive competitors out of business should be prosecuted.</Msg><Username>thomasthecat69</Username><Timestamp>1378656014533</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-08 12:00:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378663587068-5</Id><Title>up $79k, advice please?</Title><Msg>I bought because of an alert on flash market research (google them) I locked in some profits. im up $79k realized but holding some freebie shares. considering locking in the rest because flash market research has a new pick coming out soon, their last pick went up 1300% which was insane - i need some advice, does anyone think I should hold or just lock all my profits in and wait for something fresh? opinions are appreciated thanks</Msg><Username>sheilawyche</Username><Timestamp>1378663587068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-08 14:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>91</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378664332400-6</Id><Topic><Title>up $79k, advice please?</Title><Username>mandyschwarz9</Username><Timestamp>1378641637109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-08 08:00:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you made that much on their pick i would just play their next one lock it in bro</Msg><Username>sharolynbaines</Username><Timestamp>1378664332400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-08 14:18:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378685867480-7</Id><Title>Bezos Criminal MF thug Backed off from a phone or this year:LOL</Title><Msg>Two crimianl CEO thugs in USA need Public Hanging Bezos Hastings</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1378685867480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-08 20:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378694829027-8</Id><Topic><Title>up $79k, advice please?</Title><Username>mandyschwarz9</Username><Timestamp>1378641637109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-08 08:00:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would lock it in if it were me.</Msg><Username>bullish1_2</Username><Timestamp>1378694829027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-08 22:47:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378695605060-9</Id><Title>external perception vs internal reality</Title><Msg>wait til the street figures it out</Msg><Username>metalz71</Username><Timestamp>1378695605060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-08 23:00:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378695964569-10</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon to offer free smart phone....really</Title><Username>wuwuwu3</Username><Timestamp>1378505351000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-06 18:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This post is SPOT ON.</Msg><Username>metalz71</Username><Timestamp>1378695964569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-08 23:06:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378698674146-11</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon to offer free smart phone....really</Title><Username>wuwuwu3</Username><Timestamp>1378505351000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-06 18:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shouldn't it be llyod blankfiend? and jamie diemon? the bankster cartels need to die first before amazon should if you are talking about moral high grounds. amazon is at least letting people have things cheaply which many appreciate. not so much for investors lol. but thanks. eventually I see amazon backstabbing us all but not yet. the food business is not good how the heck is amazon going to ship fresh food... yeah it doesn't work. food has to be local especially if it is fresh. but then again 90% of processed food = not fresh anyway. you can forget about fruits veg meat + fish only thing you will get are canned goods processed cereal etc #$%$ of the #$%$ and it is still more expensive from amazon since we cannot use coupons on them. which means much more expensive compared to shopping with coupons. if amazon lets us use them it would be perfect or amazon consistently provides it to us at coupon prices then it is fine. how they make money though.... smartphones I already laid out a plan for amazon to do it. but it will be a bandwidth hog if I know what amazon plans on doing hence they better pay for the service as well. this is essentially what google should be doing in the first place though as the content to be delivered you need huge amounts of bandwidth and for that to occur you need some cheap source of bandwidth for all the ads. as a result this means google and advertisers NEED to foot the bandwidth cost as they are a drain on the bandwidth more than users are. that is the main reason why ads fail on smartphones after all. bandwidth hogs yes we do not appreciate you making us use our min and then putting us over the cap and the service providers take money from users. thanks but no thanks. you will have to pay bandwidth to advertise srorry</Msg><Username>ryugo82</Username><Timestamp>1378698674146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-09-08 23:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>