<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373775990383-1</Id><Topic><Title>Time to sell, not necessarily short AMZN...</Title><Username>gomerpylegriffith</Username><Timestamp>1373761845520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 20:30:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly, their profits are not enough for paying those C*Os and directors, they then issue endless stock options. No insider reaaly buys even one share of AMZN from the market, but then exercise their optionsand then sell them at this overvalued prices .</Msg><Username>yakimariver</Username><Timestamp>1373775990383</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:26:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373782160493-2</Id><Title>AMAZON.COM-THIS STOCK GOING TO $350.00 PER SHARE READ MESSAGE BELOW</Title><Msg>Amazon stock going to $350.00 per share. Wipe most shorts out unless you have money to cover margin account. longs will start selling big profit that jeff bezos made for them. sweet if your long! stock will come down from longs selling. big profits for longs especially if bought couple of years ago. Part of big game played, like shell game in the wild west. trying to figure out of big money is made selling hardware like apple or services down road that amazon is promising with large volume of sales. so far amazon is almost non for profit business. can't see benefit becoming amazon prime member only if your using the e-commerce site daily. american funds gambling big with jeff bezos amazon.com</Msg><Username>smartybob569</Username><Timestamp>1373782160493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:09:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373783322910-3</Id><Topic><Title>Amzn $400 to $800 stock</Title><Username>getintoh20</Username><Timestamp>1373744705611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 15:45:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>longs will start to sell big profits being made. Bank some money, longs are scared to loosing profits back.</Msg><Username>smartybob569</Username><Timestamp>1373783322910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:28:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373802611006-4</Id><Topic><Title>AMAZON GOING TO BE DOWN 100+ POINTS AFTER EARNINGS</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373663924847</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 17:18:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>American Funds were also smart enough to dump the majority of their APPL stock much closer to their highs than their lows so that says something.</Msg><Username>sammsjohn99</Username><Timestamp>1373802611006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 07:50:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373802667560-5</Id><Topic><Title>140 Billion for a company that has an EPS of -0.19</Title><Username>mo_659</Username><Timestamp>1373729721465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 11:35:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"headwinds against what should not be good for AMZN" except that's worse for other retailers that rely on consumers to burn gas coming into stores and who have to send all kinds of stuff too and from warehouses. Kindle books and Instant Videos simply sidestep the whole fuel issue. Much bigger headwinds, these and DOJ case against Apple.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1373802667560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 07:51:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373804690876-6</Id><Topic><Title>I am inventing the AMZN Rule</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1373738088812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 13:54:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Instead, the earnings went down, stock more than doubled" Because the market liked the cause of the earnings difference: accelerated capex for extraordinary expansion. Too bad shorts do not understand these dynamics. Wouldn't they just be better off avoiding shorting stocks they don't understand?</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1373804690876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:24:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373805095663-7</Id><Topic><Title>Internet Groceries have mostly flopped</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1373752174867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 17:49:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Do you really trust some kid in a "fullfilment center" to pick out your lettuce, avocados and steaks?" Yeah, because you can probably send it back or get a refund if you don't like it and the kid will probably be fired if keeps doing that. Don't kids also pick the lettuce, avocados and other stuff in the back kitchens of MacDonald's where most Amazon shorts have been forced to feed due to their recent heavy losses, or even at finer establishments?</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1373805095663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:31:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373807460547-8</Id><Topic><Title>140 Billion for a company that has an EPS of -0.19</Title><Username>mo_659</Username><Timestamp>1373729721465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 11:35:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bought small number of 305 July 20th Puts Friday at the close. If I have to I will take a loss on Monday and wait for a better entry point. My Opinions: AMZN is a great company with a stock price that is way ahead of it's future earnings / cash flow prospects. Look what recently happened to AAPL. There is no arguing that the longs have been in control however stocks like AAPL had a lot more going for them before it took big hits. The desparation of shorts continues to rise and so does the overconfidence of longs. Who will win in the short-term is anyone's guess. Technically, AMZN is still incredibly strong however with an RSI at nosebleed levels and up ten days in row it triggered my purchase of Puts .</Msg><Username>sammsjohn99</Username><Timestamp>1373807460547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373808000504-9</Id><Topic><Title>140 Billion for a company that has an EPS of -0.19</Title><Username>mo_659</Username><Timestamp>1373729721465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 11:35:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So it's worse for other retailors and parabolic good for AMZN on the fact that oil is going up agressively: which is ac ost for all. What about interest rates going up ? I guess that's good also. Thanks for clearing it up: that helps explain continued parabolic upside happening right now with compeitors beig left in the dust.</Msg><Username>party_bistro</Username><Timestamp>1373808000504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:20:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373808172023-10</Id><Topic><Title>I am inventing the AMZN Rule</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1373738088812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 13:54:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much is capitalized of the accelerated capex vs expensed. Makes a big difference as earnings should be going up into balance sheet captialziation where you amortize/depreciate the spending over time.</Msg><Username>party_bistro</Username><Timestamp>1373808172023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:22:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373809190733-11</Id><Topic><Title>I am inventing the AMZN Rule</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1373738088812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 13:54:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably explains why they had to get bonds issued in December. "Reinvested" profits didn't cover spending.</Msg><Username>party_bistro</Username><Timestamp>1373809190733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:39:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373809657114-12</Id><Topic><Title>I am inventing the AMZN Rule</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1373738088812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 13:54:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very interesting, I'd noticed it but never linked a pattern together as you have. What I find scary about owning this stock at these levels is that a good case could be made that it was fairly (or even richly) valued at $207, not $307. It's a bit like NFLX, and there's a little too much voodoo in the valuation for me.</Msg><Username>waterlemon_cay</Username><Timestamp>1373809657114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:47:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373811748737-13</Id><Topic><Title>140 Billion for a company that has an EPS of -0.19</Title><Username>mo_659</Username><Timestamp>1373729721465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 11:35:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, since they used a lot of that capex build distibution centers much closer to consumers and to the extent they can now use their own trucks for deliveries cutting out middle men like UPS and FDX. "In 2011, Amazon changed its fulfillment strategy and began building new distribution warehouses closer to large, heavily populated areas such as Los Angeles and San Francisco. In the first quarter of 2013, Amazon's shipping costs were 4.7 percent of revenue, down from 5.1 percent a year earlier. "For a company the size of Amazon, that's a pretty big deal," said R.J. Hottovy, an equity analyst at Morningstar. "That could be potentially very disruptive to UPS and FedEx," he added."</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1373811748737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:22:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373812086001-14</Id><Topic><Title>140 Billion for a company that has an EPS of -0.19</Title><Username>mo_659</Username><Timestamp>1373729721465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 11:35:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Other retailers have not done as much as Amazon in reducing non-fuel price related shipping cost (using their own trucks, building centers closer to consumers). Interest rates? I guess they weight that risk against doing nothing and paying higher shipping expenses instead to UPS, FDX and over further distances like out of state distribution centers.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1373812086001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:28:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373812416706-15</Id><Topic><Title>I am inventing the AMZN Rule</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1373738088812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 13:54:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Depends on the discretionary choice of whether or not Amazon aggressively (rapidly) amortize them or not. Most shorts tend to only invest in Old World stocks like Walmart and so they assume Amazon amortizes at similar rates as a brick and mortar operation. They never bother to check this.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1373812416706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:33:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373812640693-16</Id><Topic><Title>I am inventing the AMZN Rule</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1373738088812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 13:54:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And look how much the market applauded the move by Amazon in ceasing the investment opportunity. How was it anything but a great idea, and how was it anything but a horrible, horrible nightmare if you were short?</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1373812640693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:37:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373813251211-17</Id><Title>AMZN is twice market cap of GS,</Title><Msg>same market cap as BAC 5x market cap of Yahoo Bigger than CSCO Do you really think an online shop who is so much subjective to taxes and not generating any profit should be at this point ?</Msg><Username>think_plan_act</Username><Timestamp>1373813251211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:47:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373813431875-18</Id><Topic><Title>I am inventing the AMZN Rule</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1373738088812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 13:54:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You misunderstand the short-term impact of expansion. Capex simply indicates some of the extent of an expansion which may have greater or lesser impact on the the Statement of Operations depending on rates of amortization. Short-term what happens is that you have lots of new centers operating at their lowest capacity with staff that are being trained and are also not operating optimally yet. As with previous cycles as optimization takes place over time returns become parabolic indeed such is in the several years subsequent to the last investment phase.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1373813431875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:50:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373813666673-19</Id><Topic><Title>140 Billion for a company that has an EPS of -0.19</Title><Username>mo_659</Username><Timestamp>1373729721465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 11:35:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting, AMZN is now adding on the hat of being a "shipping company" as well as a retailor, cloud computing, digital.media creator/deliverer etc.: DO have any timeframe in your head when the top line scale will start again to the bottom line with all this? I thought $64 billion might do it but not yet. Perhaps as long as the market merely keeps rewarding spending inititiatives as shown by driving the market cap higher and higher along with Bernankes' $85 billion a month, there will never be a need for profits anytime soon. Certainly WS and investors see the scale story still intact somewhere ahead to drop profits the botttoml line. A $10 earnings/shr drop,whenever it comes, puts AMZN at almost a 31 multiple today on that level. And that's almost a four bagger to record earnings in history. So the earnings when they come, are gonna be a sigth to see ahead. There's never been more confidence by the market and WS that's it's a slam dunk. somewhere ahead. You've been correct all along on the market assumptions of it all.. more intact than ever:congrats.</Msg><Username>party_bistro</Username><Timestamp>1373813666673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:54:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373814077672-20</Id><Topic><Title>I am inventing the AMZN Rule</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1373738088812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 13:54:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you're talking bottom line return optimization I would think: parabolic is an appropriate word as the stock is now almost a 9 bagger since $34.68 2008 Nove lows. No doubt investors see it ahead</Msg><Username>party_bistro</Username><Timestamp>1373814077672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:01:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373814230251-21</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN is twice market cap of GS,</Title><Username>think_plan_act</Username><Timestamp>1373813251211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:47:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you have to also remember that AMZN is now getting "present value" increases in its' other business: e-books, cloud computing,and I guess, the shipping part now. It's a rollup of more than physical internet retailor.</Msg><Username>party_bistro</Username><Timestamp>1373814230251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:03:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373814300270-22</Id><Title>Data Centers/Hosting -- Another Great Low-Margin Business</Title><Msg>Perfect complement to groceries and books...</Msg><Username>mitt_romney_will_win</Username><Timestamp>1373814300270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373814329199-23</Id><Topic><Title>I am inventing the AMZN Rule</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1373738088812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 13:54:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>9 bagger? Then I'd suggest the lows were simply too low. After all, the cause being artificial, a market crash having nothing to do with Amazon's performance or operations per se.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1373814329199</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:05:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373814487712-24</Id><Topic><Title>I am inventing the AMZN Rule</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1373738088812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 13:54:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Technology and content costs are expensed as incurred" This was accounted for the largest acceleration in all of the expense line items. And no, if you can read English you will note that it does not say "over time", it says "as incurred."</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1373814487712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373814628442-25</Id><Topic><Title>I am inventing the AMZN Rule</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1373738088812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 13:54:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when might it be too high or is that not possible? We are living under the umbrella of money printing to supess rates to 0 for 5 years now. That might have some impact as well there. Alittle.</Msg><Username>party_bistro</Username><Timestamp>1373814628442</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:10:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373814714474-26</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN is twice market cap of GS,</Title><Username>think_plan_act</Username><Timestamp>1373813251211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:47:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except what they did with shipping reduced their expenses. More than physical? How is relying on UPS's or FDX's physical assets any different? You just pay more to a middle man. I can see you do not have much of a head for business. You would rather pay more to a third party than pay less by foregoing them in order to claim you aren't reliant on your own physical assets.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1373814714474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:11:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373814992369-27</Id><Topic><Title>I am inventing the AMZN Rule</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1373738088812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 13:54:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I never had to worry about that. At $150 shorts told me it was too high but it wasn't and now it has doubled. I've done very well by reversing the short's "logic", so I guess that means until they start saying to buy I should stay long. The Fed has always printed money and will continue doing so until long after you are dead. Betting on them this changing is not a good way to prevent your getting your next margin call on an Amazon short.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1373814992369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:16:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373815334830-28</Id><Topic><Title>I am inventing the AMZN Rule</Title><Username>once_on</Username><Timestamp>1373738088812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 13:54:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>indeed, you haven't had to worry about profits and when they come. They'll never matter whether they will and when. Never. And the Fed has always kept rates at 0 % run rates. Thanks for the heads up whats' ahead.</Msg><Username>party_bistro</Username><Timestamp>1373815334830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:22:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373815802531-29</Id><Title>if all the bears ar right how come cr suisse- goldman- susq have target over 320????</Title><Msg>sjsdsdsdsds</Msg><Username>davekomives</Username><Timestamp>1373815802531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:30:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373816396404-30</Id><Topic><Title>if all the bears ar right how come cr suisse- goldman- susq have target over 320????</Title><Username>davekomives</Username><Timestamp>1373815802531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>were those targets set for next week? almost there. though some were for a year out, but they might be hit a couple weeks out from where some were set, and not even have to wait a year.</Msg><Username>party_bistro</Username><Timestamp>1373816396404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373816881672-31</Id><Title>maybe we'll see timberlane again now that Nemesis showed up, usually happens.</Title><Msg>I gotta admit: Nemesis has been right more than anyone else about the stock performance of AMZN, if not the timeing of profit growth.</Msg><Username>party_bistro</Username><Timestamp>1373816881672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:48:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373820445626-32</Id><Title>Insider Sales</Title><Msg>Insiders have sold 48k shares in May and 2500 in June. This is small by historical standards.</Msg><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373820445626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:47:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373820786030-33</Id><Topic><Title>Psychology of bag holding longz and pumperz drinking koolaid....</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1373717688163</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 08:14:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373820786030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:53:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373821752306-34</Id><Topic><Title>Insider Sales</Title><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373820445626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:47:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would like to see the data in July. I didn't see even one share they bought from the market yet.</Msg><Username>yakimariver</Username><Timestamp>1373821752306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373821940466-35</Id><Title>crack head optionz</Title><Msg>I did some analysis on the optionz that expire next friday. Here's what I got: There are a total of 40k call contracts and 30k are in the money. There are a total of 32k put contracts and 545 are in the money. If amzn closes at 307.55 next week, call contracts will payout 88.6 million... put contracts will payout 700k. Max Pain is at 280... calls would pay out 25 million and puts would payout at 13.3 million. If the optionz writers have any influence over the stock price, its hard to see amzn going up next week.</Msg><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373821940466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:12:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373822116496-36</Id><Topic><Title>Insider Sales</Title><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373820445626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:47:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to the data in yahoo, monthly insider sales look as follows: shares 7/1/2011 25000 8/1/2011 44986 9/1/2011 52700 10/1/2011 5000 11/1/2011 46308 12/1/2011 53955 1/1/2012 68 2/1/2012 49098 3/1/2012 4038 4/1/2012 10000 5/1/2012 25361 7/1/2012 1604 8/1/2012 62359 9/1/2012 45981 10/1/2012 4500 11/1/2012 818721 12/1/2012 1687 2/1/2013 242781 5/1/2013 48077 6/1/2013 2500</Msg><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373822116496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:15:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373822486953-37</Id><Topic><Title>Insider Sales</Title><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373820445626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:47:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" didn't see even one share they bought from the market yet." huh? When have you ever seen insider buying in AMZN stock? Don't hold your breath until you do. It won't happens. Nor does the insiders selling mean anything bad over the years: It's no indication at all to stock performance. In fact, more power to the insiders to take advantage of it, as someone keeps moving the stock higher and higher. We shold be so lucky to have that type of backing merely on their spending/buildout.</Msg><Username>party_bistro</Username><Timestamp>1373822486953</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:21:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373822900720-38</Id><Topic><Title>Insider Sales</Title><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373820445626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:47:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>party_bistro, i take it you're long. i, on the other hand am short, and last week really hurt. i'm not pointing out insider sales to bolster the argument that amzn is over-valued. the fundamentals do that. as a short, i'm actually a bit concerned to see insider sales decelerate. by historical standards, insider sales are very small. finally, i agree with you, insider sales in and of themselves have little meaning for a company that grants so many options. if i worked at a company that i thought had good prospects, i'd sell my options to diversify.</Msg><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373822900720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:28:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373825345288-39</Id><Topic><Title>crack head optionz</Title><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373821940466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:12:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Norges Bank is the central bank of Norway - check their US stock holdings per 3/31/2013 filing. just saying</Msg><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1373825345288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:09:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373826840155-40</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened To Sybil/Trannyboy Waiting Till 245 To Post Again??????</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1372176106859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:01:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well???????????????</Msg><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1373826840155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:34:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373827562145-41</Id><Topic><Title>crack head optionz</Title><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373821940466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:12:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good observation, and certainly a possible reason for some downward pressure. However, here's another way to look at look at all those calls: if a large number of them are naked sales, then those sellers will have to buy stock in the open market to be able to deliver on the calls. This scenario would provide some upward pressure on the stock until they have enough stock to deliver. A simplistic bit of info in a complex market with many other factors at work. Personally NP, got stopped out of last short.</Msg><Username>algaebb</Username><Timestamp>1373827562145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373827884505-42</Id><Topic><Title>crack head optionz</Title><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373821940466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:12:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would be nice to know who's writing all of those call contracts. Its hard for me to believe that they are mostly written by naked retail investors. It seems more likely that institutions are writing these contracts. Who knows?</Msg><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373827884505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:51:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373828635692-43</Id><Topic><Title>Sybs isn't just Sybs. SYB IS A D-YUSHHHH-BAG!</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1372633487815</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:04:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said.........</Msg><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1373828635692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:03:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373829250395-44</Id><Title>cumulative up days in a row</Title><Msg>amzn has never had more than 10 up days in a row. see histogram below: Up Days In A Row Count 1 2533 2 245 3 134 4 59 5 25 6 18 7 3 8 3 9 3 10 3 11 0</Msg><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373829250395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:14:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373829323125-45</Id><Topic><Title>140 Billion for a company that has an EPS of -0.19</Title><Username>mo_659</Username><Timestamp>1373729721465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 11:35:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>:except that's worse for other retailers that rely on consumers to burn gas coming into stores and who have to send all kinds of stuff too and from warehouses" AMZN doesn't burn gas? or pay for it? Guess that gives them an advantage to the 19 % rise in progress the last Month in the RBOB unleaded contract. In a month! That's gonna keep rolling out to retail and corporations on a 7-10 day lag as long as it keep going up. All retail has some effect of that. Maybe, AMZN alittle less b/c the customers are so rich with market gains right now.</Msg><Username>homeytheclown03</Username><Timestamp>1373829323125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:15:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373829723885-46</Id><Topic><Title>crack head optionz</Title><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373821940466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:12:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Traders are more sophisticated than that, it's unlikely that traders would write naked calls against AMZN. That's just asking for it...would you really take a chance on being assigned a short position with a stock as hot as AMZN. Much more likely they did what I did, they purchased calls out of the money and AMZN kept on moving up during the last month. Now, all of a sudden their calls are in the money. Looking at the coming week, it looks like GOOG will run-up to earnings on Thursday and possibly carry AMZN and the sector with them. So, I'll probably sell my calls during the early part of the week.</Msg><Username>chaolopez</Username><Timestamp>1373829723885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:22:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373829937520-47</Id><Topic><Title>140 Billion for a company that has an EPS of -0.19</Title><Username>mo_659</Username><Timestamp>1373729721465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 11:35:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and I guess if they are getting into the shipping end with transit, AMZN can also be part of the "Transports". Those values can be affected with the moves in energy. So far so good.</Msg><Username>homeytheclown03</Username><Timestamp>1373829937520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:25:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373834027351-48</Id><Topic><Title>Insider Sales</Title><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373820445626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:47:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, there are days set for options that can be exercised, and that can not, I believe. Anyway I would like to see the insider sales during the recent rally.</Msg><Username>yakimariver</Username><Timestamp>1373834027351</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373836837535-49</Id><Title>Sayyyy...anybody need insurance? Auto? Life? Homeowners? Renters?</Title><Msg>Just to talk to your ol' pal skiidady for some really good bargains! I'll even provide some free investing advice on the side for free.....</Msg><Username>skiidady6</Username><Timestamp>1373836837535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:20:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373837090114-50</Id><Topic><Title>Sybs isn't just Sybs. SYB IS A D-YUSHHHH-BAG!</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1372633487815</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:04:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said...........</Msg><Username>remo_luvs_boggies</Username><Timestamp>1373837090114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:24:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373840282888-51</Id><Topic><Title>Insider Sales</Title><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1373820445626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:47:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All those insiders that showed in the record are locked now due to near earning release date. I am sure some will sell after this Q earning is released.</Msg><Username>ling.chen</Username><Timestamp>1373840282888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:18:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373840687100-52</Id><Title>Sybil bashing peaks with market tops and market bottomz because.....</Title><Msg>At market tops sybs a short, and at market bottomz sybs a long. Sybil walks a lonely road, but makes TONZ of cake while doing so.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1373840687100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373841020359-53</Id><Title>Sybil iz now beyond 100% short nflx, amzn, and pcln - pig stox in pig markets</Title><Msg>Sybil iz MARGIN SHORT these playz eagerly awaiting the turn. Sybil haz theze three phat pigz POWER SHORTED in the Master Margin Power Trade Account at 70% equity and iz gonna push an arsload in on monday to 50% equity and then some, split equally amongst theze three pigz, with matbe a little extra weight thrown at pcln.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1373841020359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:30:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373842463642-54</Id><Topic><Title>Sybs isn't just Sybs. SYB IS A D-YUSHHHH-BAG!</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1372633487815</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:04:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On the subject of dooshbags, look it's the pizza flyer selling stalker/briar!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1373842463642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:54:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373849554287-55</Id><Topic><Title>140 Billion for a company that has an EPS of -0.19</Title><Username>mo_659</Username><Timestamp>1373729721465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 11:35:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah , however the difference here is that Amazon ACTUALLY delivers the desired product more often than not!</Msg><Username>davdddd</Username><Timestamp>1373849554287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373860351638-56</Id><Title>WAL-MART- COPY AMAZON BUSINESS MODEL</Title><Msg>Receive business from walmart on line and let third party users market there products and receive commission. walmart to be king of e-commerce</Msg><Username>smartybob569</Username><Timestamp>1373860351638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 23:52:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>