<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-10-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382933505073-1</Id><Topic><Title>FELLOW USA 99% GO AND SURROUND "SEC" HEAD QUARTERS WHERE THESE CRIMINALS GET ALL FRAUD WEAPONS TO SCAM/BANG/LOOT US ALL</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382716651223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 11:57:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have to explain you something u maybe unaware of (as far as financial experiment). All mortgage paper ends up at the FED these days and all promissory notes to repay have real property listed as the collateral. So, during the next round of foreclosures FED will simply own "the title" to the properties lost by the suckers of all kinds. Now, if you can only comprehend it :)))</Msg><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382933505073</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 00:11:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382934538484-2</Id><Topic><Title>Guess tommorow'z closing price</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382906652511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 16:44:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4oo! no seriously 381</Msg><Username>robbierobnj</Username><Timestamp>1382934538484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 00:28:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382937154092-3</Id><Title>Tech Co. v. Consumer Co. Apparently it is now a tech</Title><Msg>company. Being compared to Google in the most recent article. They deliver books and shoes. Calling that a tech company makes Dominoes Pizza a tech company!!!!</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382937154092</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 01:12:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382941551992-4</Id><Title>MMMW</Title><Msg>possible 10 bagger</Msg><Username>peteza777</Username><Timestamp>1382941551992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 02:25:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382942076761-5</Id><Title>AMZN could hit $400 soon. BUY at the open</Title><Msg>Easy money</Msg><Username>sbull1751</Username><Timestamp>1382942076761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 02:34:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382942584052-6</Id><Topic><Title>Local Corp is Master of Relevance in Mobile Shopping - And that’s the key: it has to be a relevant deal</Title><Username>fankenkoenig</Username><Timestamp>1382883998119</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Local Corporation’s Krillion® Platform Powers Shopping Channel for Pittsburgh Post-Gazette IRVINE, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- Local Corporation (NASDAQ: LOCM), a leading online local media company, today announced that it is powering a new local shopping channel for the Pittsburgh Post-Gazette through its online property. . Other well-known of the more than 1,600 members in the Network of Local Corp: The Gazette The Record Searchlight The State Journal-Register The Telegraph Treasure Coast Triangle411 Valley News Ventura County Star Vermont Today Washington Post Journal Star Knoxville News Sentinel LaCrosse Tribune NC Times Newsday Norwich Bulletin Observer-Reporter Orange County Register Pittsburgh Post-Gazette San Diego Union Tribune Santa Ynez Valley News Savannah Morning News St. Louis Post-Dispatch Star Banner The Arizona Republic The Augusta Chronicle The Commercial Appeal The Dispatch The Examiner The Florida Times Union Arizona Daily Star Arkansas News Boston Herald Columbia Daily Herald Cumberland Times News Daily Herald - Utah Daily Princetonian Daily Tarheel East Valley Tribune Honolulu Star Advertiser</Msg><Username>fankenkoenig</Username><Timestamp>1382942584052</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 02:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382948490236-7</Id><Title>put leaps</Title><Msg>would buying put leaps be a good strategy without owning the stock if you think the stock will correct in next 12 months...dont know if this is profitable stragety</Msg><Username>investorsandme</Username><Timestamp>1382948490236</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 04:21:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382949615535-8</Id><Title>Muddy Waters: AMZN "A Massive Fraud Business Model"</Title><Msg>"AMZN doesn't worth 166 billions". Rated Sell.</Msg><Username>trendking</Username><Timestamp>1382949615535</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 04:40:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382953127279-9</Id><Topic><Title>The fear hazn't even begun, ayahtolla</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382922305023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 21:05:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't disagree,but you've made your reasoning clear that we are in the midst of a parabolic up, which appear ready to continue today right into AAPLearnings, FB this week, and the FOMC you touched on., as we enter the strong season for the market, which dodged the Sept/Oct bad period by skying.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382953127279</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 05:38:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382955368225-10</Id><Topic><Title>I just had a thought about monopolies &amp; amazon</Title><Username>fbertital</Username><Timestamp>1382916087633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 19:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>name one company that Amazon has driven out of business, you ignorant clown!!!!!</Msg><Username>barite_warrior8</Username><Timestamp>1382955368225</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 06:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382958817108-11</Id><Topic><Title>FELLOW USA 99% GO AND SURROUND "SEC" HEAD QUARTERS WHERE THESE CRIMINALS GET ALL FRAUD WEAPONS TO SCAM/BANG/LOOT US ALL</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382716651223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 11:57:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And it provides the real asset underpinning to USD. I thought the Fed would increase mortgage purchases (which actually does help underpin the housing sector) to accelerate the rate at which it owns title to all real estate at the same time...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382958817108</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 07:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382958834495-12</Id><Title>MASSIVE ...SNTA CONFERENCE CALL 8AM...ITS GOING TO RUN MASSIVE SO MANY SHORTS GOT IT WRONG</Title><Msg>19 MILL SHORT /41 MILL FLOAT FUNDS 73%</Msg><Username>slimjim2005007</Username><Timestamp>1382958834495</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 07:13:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382959275825-13</Id><Title>Bandwaggon shorts are gonna have their balancez bashed so hard by december that their childrenz accounts will feel it</Title><Msg>It will happen so hard that they wont know what hit em. These staunch shorts are gettin kicked in the nuts by robots 3 different wayz: hard, fast, and repeatedly. Welcome to the glory of a parabola.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382959275825</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 07:21:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382961404466-14</Id><Topic><Title>Local Corp is Master of Relevance in Mobile Shopping - And that’s the key: it has to be a relevant deal</Title><Username>fankenkoenig</Username><Timestamp>1382883998119</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IP &amp; Technology of Local Corp 07:47 #5769 Proprietary platform and know-how - Real time business, product and services data integration - Large scale local/commercial content production and syndication - Very large scale CPC ad-serving and distribution - Web indexing and local search relevance - Very large scale SEO, SEM campaign expertise - Local display ad production and syndication - Web hosting and local/commercial domain name acquisition 12 patents issued, 7 pending Key patents - Local web indexing (for indexing local web sites across the web) - Pay per call for local and commercial searches via a mobile device (multiple patents) The billion dollar industry question: How do we monetize mobile? - Dynamic cascading menu search (for product search on tablets and smart phones) - Bulk domain registration Source: CORPORATE OVERVIEW | 3Q2013</Msg><Username>fankenkoenig</Username><Timestamp>1382961404466</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 07:56:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382961542060-15</Id><Topic><Title>I just had a thought about monopolies &amp; amazon</Title><Username>fbertital</Username><Timestamp>1382916087633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 19:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Quidsi play was that." Naive of you to say so. Walmart regularly prices items lower than brick and mortar competitors in order to gain some kind of advantage. The law is devised to protect the consumer, not to give false hopes to some poor schmuck who lacked a brain and went off shorting wrecking himself to kingdom come that his heavy loss"Quidsi play was that his already heavy losses will not mount further.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382961542060</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 07:59:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382963157243-16</Id><Topic><Title>I think Sybil's "Base Camp 4" analogy is proving to be very true here: you shorts have lost your minds</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382890116248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Baldsillie never squeezed me, Lampert never squeezed me, Icahn never squeezed me and Bozo won`t squeeze me either... I`m short and using derivatives when it`s time to hedge and (mostly) to get candies before the collapse......... Anyone who have enough free cash(not to heavily invested) will close that position with great profit.... I`m not here for peanuts.... But I can`t desagree with you,, the last parabolic pop is usually hurthing many short side traders.....</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1382963157243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 08:25:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382963452202-17</Id><Title>cr susise increase target to $433 from 330</Title><Msg>margins to get better</Msg><Username>maniamoron</Username><Timestamp>1382963452202</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 08:30:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382963642610-18</Id><Topic><Title>Future Headline: AMZN- Amazing Tulip Bubble of 2013</Title><Username>n59218</Username><Timestamp>1382900587279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 15:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMZN down in pre-market as expected. Do last week's 360+ buyers now have to wait 100 years to get back their moola, or forever? :-) Having a billion in hand right now is no guarantee of the future; Lookup: Brazil's Eike Batista: Former Billionaire's story! If the (real) billions can vanish like that, imagine the profitless-billions in the name of the revenue after being public for more than 16 years! LoL!</Msg><Username>n59218</Username><Timestamp>1382963642610</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 08:34:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382963665258-19</Id><Topic><Title>Muddy Waters: AMZN "A Massive Fraud Business Model"</Title><Username>trendking</Username><Timestamp>1382949615535</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 04:40:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We don't question AMZN CAPEX, but generating revenue thru selling merchandise for little or no profit is not only sustainable down the road, it is a massive fraud"</Msg><Username>trendking</Username><Timestamp>1382963665258</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 08:34:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382963842469-20</Id><Title>is icahn losing on amzn short?</Title><Msg>icahn claims hes up 30% fpr year but has some losers or would be up 50%</Msg><Username>maniamoron</Username><Timestamp>1382963842469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 08:37:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382963929521-21</Id><Title>DOWN PREMARKET - Check out NFLX few days ago to see what will happen today</Title><Msg>P/E insange, EQUITY BUBBLE</Msg><Username>spstaniec</Username><Timestamp>1382963929521</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 08:38:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382964225595-22</Id><Topic><Title>DOWN PREMARKET - Check out NFLX few days ago to see what will happen today</Title><Username>spstaniec</Username><Timestamp>1382963929521</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 08:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>insane</Msg><Username>spstaniec</Username><Timestamp>1382964225595</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 08:43:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382964656154-23</Id><Title>td ameritrade has cr suisse analysis of amzn with buy target of $433</Title><Msg>for those int--u can see their analysis on td amtd</Msg><Username>maniamoron</Username><Timestamp>1382964656154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 08:50:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382964742217-24</Id><Title>muddy waters is corrupt short selling scavenger firm</Title><Msg>they dont understand fropolop technogly</Msg><Username>maniamoron</Username><Timestamp>1382964742217</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 08:52:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382965045525-25</Id><Title>FINAL MESSAGE TO USA 99% RETAIL: DEPLOY LEAP PUTS ON FRAUD STREET CASINO AND DUMP ALL FRAUD MUTUAL FUNDS/ETF/TECH BUBBLE POOP WIPE PAPER ON</Title><Msg>FINAL MESSAGE TO USA 99% RETAIL: DEPLOY LEAP PUTS ON FRAUD STREET CASINO AND DUMP ALL FRAUD MUTUAL FUNDS/ETF/TECH BUBBLE POOP WIPE PAPER ON OCT 28, 2013 AND CRASH THE FRAUD STREET CASINO THIS WILL BRING BACK ALL LOOTED BLOOD SWEAT OUR SAVING BACK INTO OUR ACCOUNTS ONE SIMPLE WEAPON USA 99% CAN USE AND UNLEASH A REVOLUTION WITHOUT AN VIOLENCE IF ACT, WE WIN OR WE FACE MARTIAL LAW AND BRUTAL CIVIL UNREST IN 2014 IN OUR NATION ROME DID NOT BURN IN A DAY AMEN FRAUD FRAUD STREET CASINO AND ALL WATCH DOG AGENCIES WORKING AGAINST USA 99% HIGH TREASON CRIMINAL RULERS ALREADY SOLD USA 99% LIKE LAM &amp; SHEEP TRAPPED IN BANKSTER FINANCIAL SLAUGHTER HOUSE FOR FINAL SLAUGHTER NEXT “I believe that banking institutions are more dangerous to our liberties than standing armies.” – Thomas Jefferson If the American people ever allow private banks to control the issue of their currency, first by inflation, then by deflation, the banks…will deprive the people of all property until their children wake-up homeless on the continent their fathers conquered…. The issuing power should be taken from the banks and restored to the people, to whom it properly belongs. – Thomas Jefferson in the debate over the Re-charter of the Bank Bill (1809) Andrew Jackson : Gentlemen, I have had men watching you for a long time and I am convinced that you have used the funds of the bank to speculate in the breadstuffs of the country. When you won, you divided the profits amongst you, and when you lost, you charged it to the bank. You tell me that if I take the deposits from the bank and annul its charter, I shall ruin ten thousand families. That may be true, gentlemen, but that is your sin! Should I let you go on, you will ruin fifty thousand families, and that would be my sin! You are a den of vipers and thieves. DAVID STOCKMAN: We've Been Lied To, Robbed, And Misled FRAUD WEAPONS HANDED BY OUR HIGH TREASON CRIMINAL RULERS TO BANKSTERS &amp; CORPORATE THUGS TO LOOT USA 99% PENSIONS FREE STOCK OPTION GRANTS TO CEO'S BUY BACK COMPANY STOCK TO RAPE BALANCE SHEET &amp; ALLOWED TO USE DEBT TO BUY BACK TO CREATE EVEN BIGGER SCAM BUBBLES SO THEY BECOME BILLIONAIRES IN WEEKS OR MONTHS NOT YEARS....... OFF BALANCE SHEET COOK BOOK SCAM LEGAL FOR FRAUD HFT MACHINE GUNS TO CREATE FRAUD TRADING VOLUME AND MASSIVE PRICE DISTORTION TO RAPE RETAIL TRADERS AND SMALL FUNDS WEEKLY DERIVATIVES TO OPERATE PUMP/DUMP WEEKLY TO RAPE RETAIL IN DERIVATIVE MARKET IT IS NOT WALL STREET ANY MORE IN USA; PURE FRAUD STREET CASINO...... GLASS STEGAL ABOLISHED BY BILL CLINTON #$%$ FASB157 abolished by OBAMA #$%$ Today, all that is left of America is a deeply-indebted welfare state run by a corrupt cabal of tyrants who have no moral authority, no faith of the People and no solutions. America has devolved into a corrupt, bankrupt, incompetent government tyranny headed for imminent collapse. HERE WE HAVE FRAUD STREET CASINO OPERATED BY HOME GROWN FINANCIAL TERRORIST BANKSTERS LOOTING ALL 99% WORKING CLASS PENSIONS WITH THEIR FRAUD PONZI BUBBLE MANIA BUSINESS MODELS WITH #$%$" ACCOUNTING RULES AT "SEC'........ CORPORATE THUGS LIKE MF THUG GREED HASTINGS BECOMING BILLIONAIRES WITH ALL FRAUD SUPPORTED AND PROTECTED BY CRIMINALS AT "SEC'/BANKING COMMITTEE &amp; OBAMA/ERIC HOLDER CHICAGO MAFIA SHILLS IN WHITE HOUSE &amp; DOJ ===================== The day the U.S. government collapses in default is fast approaching Because an exponential rise in debt cannot be sustained, at some point the U.S. government will simply collapse into financial default. Soon after, Martial Law will have to be declared in every major U.S. city to quell the riots. Imagine 50 million Americans going hungry and realizing their welfare food credits aren’t going to be available anymore and you begin to get an idea of why cities will be nearly impossible to survive when the chaos hits. The impending failure of the federal government is now obvious to everyone. Even Ron Paul is now openly talking about the coming collapse of the U.S. empire, mirroring the overnight collapse of the Soviet empire in 1991, where that nation broke into twelve independent republics. Many people now believe the U.S. is headed for a similar outcome, and that such an outcome can happen virtually overnight. The crash of EBT cards could be the tumbling domino that sets this into action. Nearly every state already has a secessionist movement calling for independence, and the Tenth Amendment Center is leading the charge on state nullification of federal tyranny. Groups like the Oath Keepers are ready to step in and help establish local law and order in the short-term chaos that would follow a dissolution of the U.S. empire. ============================================= FRAUD GANG IS BUSINESS LOOTING WEEKLY DERIVATIVE PREMIUMS VIA BIGGEST FRAUD PRICE/VOLUME MANIPULATION SCAM EVER IN HISTORY OF USA WALL NOW PURE FRAUD STREET CASINO LION DEMAND ENTIRE TRADING RECORD OF THIS NEXUS SCAM GANG SINCE 2009 ROUND ONE LOOT SCAM GANG 2009-2012 ROUND TWO LOOT SCAM GANG 2012-2013 PROVEN FRAUD SINCE JULY 2011 BUT COVERED UP PROTECTION AT "SEC' CONTINUES FOR ROUND TWO L LOOT WITHOUT ZERO FEAR SHUT DOWN "SEC' AND HANG THEM ASAP ALONG WITH THIS MF THUG REED HASTINGS/GOLDMAN SACHS LED SCAM GANG</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382965045525</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 08:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382965235959-26</Id><Topic><Title>FINAL MESSAGE TO USA 99% RETAIL: DEPLOY LEAP PUTS ON FRAUD STREET CASINO AND DUMP ALL FRAUD MUTUAL FUNDS/ETF/TECH BUBBLE POOP WIPE PAPER ON</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382965045525</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 08:57:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>get cancer and die</Msg><Username>ibumpyou69</Username><Timestamp>1382965235959</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:00:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382966192783-27</Id><Topic><Title>FINAL MESSAGE TO USA 99% RETAIL: DEPLOY LEAP PUTS ON FRAUD STREET CASINO AND DUMP ALL FRAUD MUTUAL FUNDS/ETF/TECH BUBBLE POOP WIPE PAPER ON</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382965045525</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 08:57:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harsh reality not liked by your $ucked brain stuck up your scam $ss lol</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382966192783</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:16:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382966480906-28</Id><Topic><Title>Future Headline: AMZN- Amazing Tulip Bubble of 2013</Title><Username>n59218</Username><Timestamp>1382900587279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 15:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sybil, Have you looked at the short pct lately? There are barely any shorts left in this stock.</Msg><Username>ilikegold2003</Username><Timestamp>1382966480906</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:21:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382966789172-29</Id><Title>Another great day for AMZN and me.</Title><Msg>I love dips. They give me opportunities to buy calls at lower prices!</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382966789172</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:26:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382966980547-30</Id><Topic><Title>Future Headline: AMZN- Amazing Tulip Bubble of 2013</Title><Username>n59218</Username><Timestamp>1382900587279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 15:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why cnbc crimianl media shill don't bring bezos scam $ss fake laughs anymore??</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382966980547</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:29:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382967095127-31</Id><Title>Company deceptively attributes margin "gains" to services but 75% of sales gains came from Gen Merch and Elc Products</Title><Msg>Total sales rose 3286 while a simple review of the 10Q reveals media product sales fell from $2988 to $2760 mils QOQ.Media services rose from 1612 to 2273 ,almost ALL in North Americas (none I'ntl) Electronics and gen'l merch from 8558 to 11048, or 2490 of the 3286 gain, yet with this sales gain income falls flat. All AWS and credit card sales gain of a measly 352 mil came in North America All cash gains come from an increase in payables. If the company "re-invested" profits back into technology etc, they would report net income and an increase in assets on the bal. sheet. They dont b/c the expense is actually a one time cost of doing business and the losses are real. They will never make money no matter how large the sales grow. You can sell alot of merchandise at losses and ship it for nearly free to prime members. Thats why they lose one billion or so quarter on net shipping. One day investors will wake up and say, Hey! Who knew? The answer: Everyone who actually knows how to read a 10Q.clearly not the WS analyst shilld. And never Cramer et al.</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382967095127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:31:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382967166174-32</Id><Topic><Title>Muddy Waters: AMZN "A Massive Fraud Business Model"</Title><Username>trendking</Username><Timestamp>1382949615535</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 04:40:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A whistle blower! LoL</Msg><Username>polpounder5</Username><Timestamp>1382967166174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:32:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382967522173-33</Id><Topic><Title>Company deceptively attributes margin "gains" to services but 75% of sales gains came from Gen Merch and Elc Products</Title><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382967095127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:31:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHY NOT CALL THESE CRIMINALS AT "SEC' ENFORCEMENT DIVISION AT SEC:Manipulation is intentional conduct designed to deceive investors by controlling or artificially affecting the market for a security. Manipulation is intentional conduct designed to deceive investors by controlling or artificially affecting the market for a security. Manipulation can involve a number of techniques to affect the supply of, or demand for, a stock. They include: spreading false or misleading information about a company; improperly limiting the number of publicly-available shares; or rigging quotes, prices or trades to create a false or deceptive picture of the demand for a security. Those who engage in manipulation are subject to various civil and criminal sanctions. of a security's price or volume CALL THESE CRIMINALS AT "SEC' 202-551-2100 MARY JO WHITE 202-551-4500 GEORGE CANELLOS 202-551-5500 JOHN RAMSEY THESE 3 MUST BE ARRESTED ASAP AT "SEC' AND HANG THEM ASAP WITH LIVE BROADCAST IN USA AND WARN FRAUD STREET BANKSTERS &amp; HEDGE FUND MAFIA ALONG WITH MUTUAL FUND CRIMINAL TERRORISTS AND SCREAM , WE ARE COMING TO HANG YOU TOO ASK OUR ARMED FORCES TO ROUND UP ALL HIGH TREASON CRIMIANL RULERS IN WASHINGTON DC SEIZE ALL THE SCAM LOOT STOLEN FROM USA 99% AND RESTORE USA REPUBLIC</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382967522173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:38:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382967698744-34</Id><Topic><Title>FELLOW USA 99% GO AND SURROUND "SEC" HEAD QUARTERS WHERE THESE CRIMINALS GET ALL FRAUD WEAPONS TO SCAM/BANG/LOOT US ALL</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382716651223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 11:57:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FINAL MESSAGE TO USA 99% RETAIL: DEPLOY LEAP PUTS ON FRAUD STREET CASINO AND DUMP ALL FRAUD MUTUAL FUNDS/ETF/TECH BUBBLE POOP WIPE PAPER ON FINAL MESSAGE TO USA 99% RETAIL: DEPLOY LEAP PUTS ON FRAUD STREET CASINO AND DUMP ALL FRAUD MUTUAL FUNDS/ETF/TECH BUBBLE POOP WIPE PAPER ON OCT 28, 2013 AND CRASH THE FRAUD STREET CASINO THIS WILL BRING BACK ALL LOOTED BLOOD SWEAT OUR SAVING BACK INTO OUR ACCOUNTS ONE SIMPLE WEAPON USA 99% CAN USE AND UNLEASH A REVOLUTION WITHOUT AN VIOLENCE IF ACT, WE WIN OR WE FACE MARTIAL LAW AND BRUTAL CIVIL UNREST IN 2014 IN OUR NATION ROME DID NOT BURN IN A DAY AMEN FRAUD FRAUD STREET CASINO AND ALL WATCH DOG AGENCIES WORKING AGAINST USA 99% HIGH TREASON CRIMINAL RULERS ALREADY SOLD USA 99% LIKE LAM &amp; SHEEP TRAPPED IN BANKSTER FINANCIAL SLAUGHTER HOUSE FOR FINAL SLAUGHTER NEXT “I believe that banking institutions are more dangerous to our liberties than standing armies.” – Thomas Jefferson If the American people ever allow private banks to control the issue of their currency, first by inflation, then by deflation, the banks…will deprive the people of all property until their children wake-up homeless on the continent their fathers conquered…. The issuing power should be taken from the banks and restored to the people, to whom it properly belongs. – Thomas Jefferson in the debate over the Re-charter of the Bank Bill (1809) Andrew Jackson : Gentlemen, I have had men watching you for a long time and I am convinced that you have used the funds of the bank to speculate in the breadstuffs of the country. When you won, you divided the profits amongst you, and when you lost, you charged it to the bank. You tell me that if I take the deposits from the bank and annul its charter, I shall ruin ten thousand families. That may be true, gentlemen, but that is your sin! Should I let you go on, you will ruin fifty thousand families, and that would be my sin! You are a den of vipers and thieves. DAVID STOCKMAN: We've Been Lied To, Robbed, And Misled FRAUD WEAPONS HANDED BY OUR HIGH TREASON CRIMINAL RULERS TO BANKSTERS &amp; CORPORATE THUGS TO LOOT USA 99% PENSIONS FREE STOCK OPTION GRANTS TO CEO'S BUY BACK COMPANY STOCK TO RAPE BALANCE SHEET &amp; ALLOWED TO USE DEBT TO BUY BACK TO CREATE EVEN BIGGER SCAM BUBBLES SO THEY BECOME BILLIONAIRES IN WEEKS OR MONTHS NOT YEARS....... OFF BALANCE SHEET COOK BOOK SCAM LEGAL FOR FRAUD HFT MACHINE GUNS TO CREATE FRAUD TRADING VOLUME AND MASSIVE PRICE DISTORTION TO RAPE RETAIL TRADERS AND SMALL FUNDS WEEKLY DERIVATIVES TO OPERATE PUMP/DUMP WEEKLY TO RAPE RETAIL IN DERIVATIVE MARKET IT IS NOT WALL STREET ANY MORE IN USA; PURE FRAUD STREET CASINO...... GLASS STEGAL ABOLISHED BY BILL CLINTON #$%$ FASB157 abolished by OBAMA #$%$ Today, all that is left of America is a deeply-indebted welfare state run by a corrupt cabal of tyrants who have no moral authority, no faith of the People and no solutions. America has devolved into a corrupt, bankrupt, incompetent government tyranny headed for imminent collapse. HERE WE HAVE FRAUD STREET CASINO OPERATED BY HOME GROWN FINANCIAL TERRORIST BANKSTERS LOOTING ALL 99% WORKING CLASS PENSIONS WITH THEIR FRAUD PONZI BUBBLE MANIA BUSINESS MODELS WITH #$%$" ACCOUNTING RULES AT "SEC'........ CORPORATE THUGS LIKE MF THUG GREED HASTINGS BECOMING BILLIONAIRES WITH ALL FRAUD SUPPORTED AND PROTECTED BY CRIMINALS AT "SEC'/BANKING COMMITTEE &amp; OBAMA/ERIC HOLDER CHICAGO MAFIA SHILLS IN WHITE HOUSE &amp; DOJ ===================== The day the U.S. government collapses in default is fast approaching Because an exponential rise in debt cannot be sustained, at some point the U.S. government will simply collapse into financial default. Soon after, Martial Law will have to be declared in every major U.S. city to quell the riots. Imagine 50 million Americans going hungry and realizing their welfare food credits aren’t going to be available anymore and you begin to get an idea of why cities will be nearly impossible to survive when the chaos hits. The impending failure of the federal government is now obvious to everyone. Even Ron Paul is now openly talking about the coming collapse of the U.S. empire, mirroring the overnight collapse of the Soviet empire in 1991, where that nation broke into twelve independent republics. Many people now believe the U.S. is headed for a similar outcome, and that such an outcome can happen virtually overnight. The crash of EBT cards could be the tumbling domino that sets this into action. Nearly every state already has a secessionist movement calling for independence, and the Tenth Amendment Center is leading the charge on state nullification of federal tyranny. Groups like the Oath Keepers are ready to step in and help establish local law and order in the short-term chaos that would follow a dissolution of the U.S. empire. ============================================= FRAUD GANG IS BUSINESS LOOTING WEEKLY DERIVATIVE PREMIUMS VIA BIGGEST FRAUD PRICE/VOLUME MANIPULATION SCAM EVER IN HISTORY OF USA WALL NOW PURE FRAUD STREET CASINO LION DEMAND ENTIRE TRADING RECORD OF THIS NEXUS SCAM GANG SINCE 2009 ROUND ONE LOOT SCAM GANG 2009-2012 ROUND TWO LOOT SCAM GANG 2012-2013 PROVEN FRAUD SINCE JULY 2011 BUT COVERED UP PROTECTION AT "SEC' CONTINUES FOR ROUND TWO L LOOT WITHOUT ZERO FEAR SHUT DOWN "SEC' AND HANG THEM ASAP ALONG WITH THIS MF THUG REED HASTINGS/GOLDMAN SACHS LED SCAM GANG</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382967698744</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:41:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382968141697-35</Id><Topic><Title>Another great day for AMZN and me.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382966789172</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:26:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool. What are buying and when?</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382968141697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:49:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382968176020-36</Id><Title>See massive sell-off at least 2000 points here.</Title><Msg>Just money being thrown at everything to make it stick. Massive debt here and world wide will consume everything. No way any of it wil ever be paid. FEd just trying to hold up economy throwing money at anything everything. WE can never repay loans period They try to play interest tate game just to make it less expensive to finance our massive debt only. Wake up America.</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1382968176020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382968176237-37</Id><Title>Gradual descent.</Title><Msg>I'm still waiting. Not buying any calls yet.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382968176237</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382968539739-38</Id><Topic><Title>Gradual descent.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382968176237</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will piggyback your trade. I read youre the best tarder here so please let me piggyback your call option purchases. Thank you</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382968539739</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:55:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382968607827-39</Id><Title>thats right, big guys are realizing they were DUPED by the Wall st HEADLINE scammers and that karl d</Title><Msg>is right. they are not growing at 20%</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1382968607827</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:56:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382968620889-40</Id><Topic><Title>Muddy Waters: AMZN "A Massive Fraud Business Model"</Title><Username>trendking</Username><Timestamp>1382949615535</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 04:40:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone have link to Muddy Water report. I do not believe it.</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382968620889</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382968622579-41</Id><Title>$400 + target for all analysts now on AMZN.expect $400 by year end</Title><Msg>We will see a $400 push for AMZN soon .I expect a close above $375 today !</Msg><Username>justeastern</Username><Timestamp>1382968622579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382969196800-42</Id><Topic><Title>See massive sell-off at least 2000 points here.</Title><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1382968176020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My TS model just indicated $100 dump coming ahead in AMZN!</Msg><Username>n59218</Username><Timestamp>1382969196800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382969264522-43</Id><Topic><Title>Gradual descent.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382968176237</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gengeejar please give me price to buy call options. I cant wait and watch so I need to put my buy order in now. What is the lowest stock can go? What is the highest it can go? Do we buy for Christmas sales ?</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382969264522</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:07:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382969498517-44</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst Kool Aide Drinkers!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382732698989</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 16:24:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Newbies in growing Demographics are the food (-aka- fools) on which those upgrades feed on! They'll get their A-Double-Stars handed to them on silver platter real soon now! LoL!</Msg><Username>n59218</Username><Timestamp>1382969498517</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:11:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382969721572-45</Id><Title>Relax, shorts. As long as she remains below 361.25 . . .</Title><Msg>. . . she won't hit $370.1327 today.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382969721572</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382969938407-46</Id><Topic><Title>Relax, shorts. As long as she remains below 361.25 . . .</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382969721572</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:15:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its over that according to my broker.you are not helping and I need to go to work.Thanks Gengeejar</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382969938407</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382970515607-47</Id><Title>Shorts, if you don't place stops, she will keep falling . . .</Title><Msg>Can't you just stay put even for a couple of hours? Are you all girls?</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382970515607</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:28:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382970670497-48</Id><Topic><Title>Company deceptively attributes margin "gains" to services but 75% of sales gains came from Gen Merch and Elc Products</Title><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382967095127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:31:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“They dont b/c the expense is actually a one time cost of doing business and the losses are real.” No, the levels of depreciation vary and are a smaller percentage during expansion phases than otherwise. They’re also amortized in many cases at faster rate than with most companies so it never works out that all more even that much of it is “actually a one time cost of doing business”. You simply have not analyzed the ten year cycle appropriately. If you had I don't think you would have ever tried shorting the stock.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382970670497</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:31:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382970758516-49</Id><Topic><Title>Company deceptively attributes margin "gains" to services but 75% of sales gains came from Gen Merch and Elc Products</Title><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382967095127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:31:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"are a smaller percentage during expansion phases than otherwise." Sorry, larger not smaller.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382970758516</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:32:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382970783997-50</Id><Title>amazon is coming back down to</Title><Msg>the $335 range , and that's all there is to it ! accept it .</Msg><Username>adavidson_nyc</Username><Timestamp>1382970783997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:33:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382970893435-51</Id><Title>The bandwaggon of shorts are gonna get beat about the head and shoulderz by Uncle Ben tomorrow and wed at the fomc</Title><Msg>Then he'z gonna poke 'em in the ars.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382970893435</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:34:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382971062585-52</Id><Topic><Title>The bandwaggon of shorts are gonna get beat about the head and shoulderz by Uncle Ben tomorrow and wed at the fomc</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382970893435</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:34:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey MF criminal pumper shill Shut $the $uck up FRAUD STREET CASINO will go up in flames in 2014 Massive civil unrest in USA 2014</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382971062585</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382971124923-53</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare vs Amazon ironic</Title><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382895526418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 13:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamacare stole Christmas 2013 Amazon needed Christmas 2013</Msg><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382971124923</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:38:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382971204834-54</Id><Title>Bought some calls.</Title><Msg>Couldn't wait any longer. I had to get in.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382971204834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:40:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382971379282-55</Id><Topic><Title>LION BRODCAST VS FRAUD STREET BANKSTER FRAUD ANALYST TERRORIST: OUTRIGHT DUMP AND AVOID RATIUNG ON AMAZON ENFORCED</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382730679201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 15:51:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't Cry for me Amerintina "SONG" &amp; this song Gene Burnett - Jump You F*#kers (A Song For Wall Street) - YouTube “I believe that banking institutions are more dangerous to our liberties than standing armies.” – Thomas Jefferson If the American people ever allow private banks to control the issue of their currency, first by inflation, then by deflation, the banks…will deprive the people of all property until their children wake-up homeless on the continent their fathers conquered…. The issuing power should be taken from the banks and restored to the people, to whom it properly belongs. – Thomas Jefferson in the debate over the Re-charter of the Bank Bill (1809) Andrew Jackson : Gentlemen, I have had men watching you for a long time and I am convinced that you have used the funds of the bank to speculate in the breadstuffs of the country. When you won, you divided the profits amongst you, and when you lost, you charged it to the bank. You tell me that if I take the deposits from the bank and annul its charter, I shall ruin ten thousand families. That may be true, gentlemen, but that is your sin! Should I let you go on, you will ruin fifty thousand families, and that would be my sin! You are a den of vipers and thieves. DAVID STOCKMAN: We've Been Lied To, Robbed, And Misled FRAUD WEAPONS HANDED BY OUR HIGH TREASON CRIMINAL RULERS TO BANKSTERS &amp; CORPORATE THUGS TO LOOT USA 99% PENSIONS FREE STOCK OPTION GRANTS TO CEO'S BUY BACK COMPANY STOCK TO RAPE BALANCE SHEET &amp; ALLOWED TO USE DEBT TO BUY BACK TO CREATE EVEN BIGGER SCAM BUBBLES SO THEY BECOME BILLIONAIRES IN WEEKS OR MONTHS NOT YEARS....... OFF BALANCE SHEET COOK BOOK SCAM LEGAL FOR FRAUD HFT MACHINE GUNS TO CREATE FRAUD TRADING VOLUME AND MASSIVE PRICE DISTORTION TO RAPE RETAIL TRADERS AND SMALL FUNDS WEEKLY DERIVATIVES TO OPERATE PUMP/DUMP WEEKLY TO RAPE RETAIL IN DERIVATIVE MARKET IT IS NOT WALL STREET ANY MORE IN USA; PURE FRAUD STREET CASINO...... GLASS STEGAL ABOLISHED BY BILL CLINTON #$%$ FASB157 abolished by OBAMA #$%$</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382971379282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382971523275-56</Id><Title>Can this play break past $1?</Title><Msg>PRDL rockets 9,900% in 10 months. Will it breach 10,000%? Get the full PRDL profile at: creativework.asia/522868</Msg><Username>cunninghammichael852</Username><Timestamp>1382971523275</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:45:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382971525600-57</Id><Topic><Title>Company deceptively attributes margin "gains" to services but 75% of sales gains came from Gen Merch and Elc Products</Title><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382967095127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:31:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. You prove my point. The faster you amortize or depreciate a CAPEX "investment" you are just proving that it is NOT a long term re-investment of capital but merely a one time cost of doing business. Nothing in scalability will enhance profits and that has been PROVEN already quarter after quarter as revenues rise and net profits do not, but losses are consistent. One thing is assured.All those who believe in the "story" will wake up one day at 265 and say, "what a great buying opportunity" when in fact it will be the beginning of the end. Walmart shows gross margins of 25 % for decades and net profits after SGA etc of 6%. And that is on sales of 450 Billion. It sells at a p/s of .5. Amazon could potentially be afforded that valuation even if they cannot get a bottom line profit so at 200 billion in sales it could be worth 100 Billion.But then again, after dilution of ISOs etc, that would be just about 200 a share. I think 200 is aggressively overvaluing this, but time will tell when real sellers attempt to liquidate in a real bear market. Your analysis is pathetic.</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382971525600</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:45:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382971843560-58</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google Shopping gives lower prices than amazon too. Amazon structure is flawed to think they can compete longterm by shipping everything to a middleman warehouse and then ship to the consumer. That's never going to be profitable. Cut out the middleman. Amazon has only survived by selling for cost. Amazon will go out in a few years now that it's surrounded with advancing competition.</Msg><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382971843560</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382972053800-59</Id><Topic><Title>Bought some calls.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382971204834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Added more.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382972053800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:54:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382972153954-60</Id><Topic><Title>Bought some calls.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382971204834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What? which ones? You need to let me piggy back. Help please.</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382972153954</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382972330113-61</Id><Topic><Title>Bought some calls.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382971204834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok . Cool. I think stock price is around 360 so I can do better than you,otherwise I would be #$%$ at your selfish insensitivity.</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382972330113</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382972348276-62</Id><Title>This stock will down to 200</Title><Msg>This stock will down to 200</Msg><Username>yibang</Username><Timestamp>1382972348276</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:59:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382972348404-63</Id><Title>Get ready for the tech sell off....</Title><Msg>Market showing signs of cracking. Blow off tops all across the board in AMZN, GOOG, and PCLN is usually the sign we hit the top.</Msg><Username>tolllsname</Username><Timestamp>1382972348404</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:59:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382972825599-64</Id><Topic><Title>Bought some calls.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382971204834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Added more. Got enough for now.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382972825599</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:07:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382973474714-65</Id><Topic><Title>Bought some calls.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382971204834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got 80.</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382973474714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:17:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382974276311-66</Id><Title>Amazon retail is a non-value added middleman</Title><Msg>Google shopping finds lower prices than amazon and has greater selection. It's a free portal with no middleman. Amazon's retail structure is fundamentally flawed as being just a middleman. Cost to ship inventory to central warehouees, manage, repack and ship again is non value added operation and shipping costs. The ONLY reason it works at all is by passing through for no profit. if you think there are any future profits to be had, you are mistaken. This is commodity retail middleman people!! Middleman can be eliminated and has no market leverage. Amazon cannot and will not make profit.</Msg><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382974276311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:31:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382974564456-67</Id><Topic><Title>Get ready for the tech sell off....</Title><Username>tolllsname</Username><Timestamp>1382972348404</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Indeed, U could be right.... we' ll see.....</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1382974564456</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382974896286-68</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon retail is a non-value added middleman</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382974276311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:31:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Commodity retail middleman... what about the tablets? Last place tech will not survive either. Kindle is like blackberry. Pure readers are already dead. Just like blackberry got overtaken, Kindle Fire sales even at cost still aren't selling well, because they aren't as good as ipad, samsung or surface.</Msg><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382974896286</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:41:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382974993215-69</Id><Topic><Title>LION BRODCAST VS FRAUD STREET BANKSTER FRAUD ANALYST TERRORIST: OUTRIGHT DUMP AND AVOID RATIUNG ON AMAZON ENFORCED</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382730679201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 15:51:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3RD PART RESELLERS ..fraud by BEZOS against them Germany is going to chew Bezos scam $ss and other nations will follow next</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382974993215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382975025630-70</Id><Topic><Title>FELLOW USA 99% GO AND SURROUND "SEC" HEAD QUARTERS WHERE THESE CRIMINALS GET ALL FRAUD WEAPONS TO SCAM/BANG/LOOT US ALL</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382716651223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 11:57:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FRAUD IN NFLX SCAM TRADING PIT ?ZERO LIQUIDITY?????????? FRAUD TRADING BY NEXUS SCAM GANG ARE FRAUD MACHINES OPERATING OUT OF "SEC' TORA BORA CAVES? OR WHITE HOUSE? OR AT DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE? OR AT FBI HEAD QUARTER? BIGGEST FRAUD LOOT RECORD AND STILL GOING STRONG WITHOUT ZERO FEAR PROVEN FRAUD AND COVERED UP AT BY CRIMINALS AT "SEC' MARY SCHAPIRO/ROBERT KHUZAMI /ROBERT COOK SCAM GANG...........DICTATING INSTRUCTIONS FROM OUTSIDE TO THE SCAM GANG LEFT BEHIND AT "SEC" WHISTLE BLOWERS BEING THREATENED BY "SEC' CRIMINAL SCAM GANG ENFORCEMENT DIVISION AT SEC:Manipulation is intentional conduct designed to deceive investors by controlling or artificially affecting the market for a security. Manipulation is intentional conduct designed to deceive investors by controlling or artificially affecting the market for a security. Manipulation can involve a number of techniques to affect the supply of, or demand for, a stock. They include: spreading false or misleading information about a company; improperly limiting the number of publicly-available shares; or rigging quotes, prices or trades to create a false or deceptive picture of the demand for a security. Those who engage in manipulation are subject to various civil and criminal sanctions. of a security's price or volume CALL THESE CRIMINALS AT "SEC' 202-551-2100 MARY JO WHITE 202-551-4500 GEORGE CANELLOS 202-551-5500 JOHN RAMSEY THESE 3 MUST BE ARRESTED ASAP AT "SEC' AND HANG THEM ASAP WITH LIVE BROADCAST IN USA AND WARN FRAUD STREET BANKSTERS &amp; HEDGE FUND MAFIA ALONG WITH MUTUAL FUND CRIMINAL TERRORISTS AND SCREAM , WE ARE COMING TO HANG YOU TOO ASK OUR ARMED FORCES TO ROUND UP ALL HIGH TREASON CRIMIANL RULERS IN WASHINGTON DC SEIZE ALL THE SCAM LOOT STOLEN FROM USA 99% AND RESTORE</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382975025630</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:43:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382975335596-71</Id><Title>Shouldn't she be creeping up by now?</Title><Msg>I may be in trouble.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382975335596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:48:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382975468513-72</Id><Topic><Title>Shouldn't she be creeping up by now?</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382975335596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do not think that is funny. I am positive by .20 for 80 calls right now. If you sell you must tell me to sell too.</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382975468513</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:51:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382975471654-73</Id><Topic><Title>Shouldn't she be creeping up by now?</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382975335596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no u can't be. because it is not real</Msg><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382975471654</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382975729305-74</Id><Title>$358, I see 354 by the end of the day. Profit taking from the bigs.</Title><Msg>no upside short term.</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382975729305</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382975764827-75</Id><Topic><Title>Company deceptively attributes margin "gains" to services but 75% of sales gains came from Gen Merch and Elc Products</Title><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382967095127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:31:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SEC is run by lawyers who do not investigate accounting shams until investors loss money. Should they desire to contact people who can read the financial statements after the stock has fallen 60%, no one will help them for the same reason that they didnt respond when the stock was fabulously adored and overvalued. Cavaet emptor. SEC is a nonexistent body and can not/will not protect investors.</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382975764827</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:56:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382975811921-76</Id><Topic><Title>Shouldn't she be creeping up by now?</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382975335596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take care of yourself..... remember you`ve been completely washed washed out not so long ago.....</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1382975811921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:56:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382976082331-77</Id><Title>When will AMZN hit $383.12375?</Title><Msg>My bet is before the end of this week.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382976082331</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:01:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382976208489-78</Id><Topic><Title>When will AMZN hit $383.12375?</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382976082331</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:01:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm with you gengeejar. as long as we stay positive we win.If I lose,I will hate you and your name forever.</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382976208489</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:03:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382976266074-79</Id><Topic><Title>$358, I see 354 by the end of the day. Profit taking from the bigs.</Title><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382975729305</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:55:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>probably more like $346 or so .</Msg><Username>adavidson_nyc</Username><Timestamp>1382976266074</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:04:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382976609738-80</Id><Topic><Title>$358, I see 354 by the end of the day. Profit taking from the bigs.</Title><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382975729305</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:55:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just sold. The P/E was scary. Took major profits from the post-earnings boost.</Msg><Username>saurabh87prabhu</Username><Timestamp>1382976609738</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:10:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382976687591-81</Id><Topic><Title>Bought some calls.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382971204834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sold all calls for a descent profit! Is this a great country or what?</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382976687591</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:11:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382976882484-82</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon retail is a non-value added middleman</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382974276311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:31:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Kindle Fire sales even at cost still aren't selling well” Happy to here it. Shorts claim that Amazon loses money on each Fire sold so the fewer they sell the better for Amazon’s financials. But how does that help shorts?</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382976882484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:14:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382976942640-83</Id><Title>ALL THIS FRAUD SWITCH SPINS TO TURN PROFIT ARE FARCE FARTS COMING OUT OF MF CRIMINAL FINANCIAL TERRORIST JEFF BEZOS SCAM $SS</Title><Msg>All this fraud switch spins to turn profit are farce farts coming out of mf criminal financial terrorist jeff bezos scam $ss revenue ponzi scam will blow in smoke..... no dividend...........fraud loot by mf bezos scam gang in usa from usa 99% pensions fraud street casino is going up in flames in 2014 massive civil unrest in usa in 2014 usa hijacked by home grown financial al qaeda led by bankster financial terrorists high treason criminal rulers in pockets of home grown financial al qaeda</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382976942640</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382977074318-84</Id><Topic><Title>Company deceptively attributes margin "gains" to services but 75% of sales gains came from Gen Merch and Elc Products</Title><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382967095127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 09:31:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, it is a long-term investment. Amortizing timelines and the length of time the purchased asset is used are not necessarily the same thing, and with Amazon they seldom are.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382977074318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:17:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382977241853-85</Id><Topic><Title>Relax, shorts. As long as she remains below 361.25 . . .</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382969721572</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 10:15:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know what I mean, shorts? Bwahahahaha . . .</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382977241853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:20:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382977457032-86</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon retail is a non-value added middleman</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382974276311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:31:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a diminishing revenue stream. Profits aren't here, profits are not coming so the only thing left is revenue. Too many unsold HDX units would be a deathblow to the house of cards. At cost will become even "lower than cost" and less rev.</Msg><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382977457032</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:24:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382978748780-87</Id><Title>Geegee takes the prize for being the dumbest phvck on the board</Title><Msg>There'z some stiff competition for this infamous spot, but geegee sure takes the cake handz down.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382978748780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382978917363-88</Id><Title>Angry#$%$_woman iz philjoe</Title><Msg>He'z angry because he'z a broke tranny that repressez hiz home mo tendanciez. He likes to pop up on different uzer handlez to vent on sybil because he'z ashamed .</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382978917363</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382978929734-89</Id><Title>Shorts, I have a personal question.</Title><Msg>Are you stupid?</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382978929734</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:48:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382979062949-90</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon retail is a non-value added middleman</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382974276311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:31:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Profits aren't here, profits are not coming" Double talk. Shorts keep telling revenue doesn't matter. Only fundamentals. If this is so then selling fewer loss generating units improves Amazon's fundamentals and the effect on revenue does not matter at all. You can't have it both ways.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382979062949</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382980323387-91</Id><Title>Monday head fake down is done</Title><Msg>Time to buy kids, Markets only go up</Msg><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1382980323387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:12:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382980670955-92</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon retail is a non-value added middleman</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382974276311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:31:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not double-talk. Losing money now and losing money in the future is bad. A long believes they are investing now for bigger "future profit". If HDX fails, then it's not going to be that future profit realized. Cutting loses on a loser initiative and investing in something that will make money "could" work. In amazon's case, they are priced like a super tech giant, but they are no match for the superior competition. Kindle Fire is blackberry. A realized failure of Kindle Fire is the end of the road for revenue growth and the fantasy of future profits. To even stay in business, they need to be investing in winners. None of their off-shoots are winners and the core commodity retail middleman business will never realize the fantasy future profits either. This house of cards is built on revenue growth rates that aren't going to sustained and fantasy hypothetical future profits. HDX failure is one pin that can pop this bubble.</Msg><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382980670955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:17:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382981350903-93</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare vs Amazon ironic</Title><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382895526418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 13:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obamacare stole Christmas 2013" LOL Good One, probably true</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382981350903</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382981754546-94</Id><Topic><Title>When will AMZN hit $383.12375?</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382976082331</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:01:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, shorts here don't give it a rest. They're eager to buy now. I thought they were saying that $330 was insanely expensive. Why are they buying now? Strange people. Beyond me.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382981754546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:35:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382981937217-95</Id><Title>I'm going "Buy High, Sell Higher."</Title><Msg>Just kidding. I will stick with "Buy Low, Sell High." Unlike you, shorts, I'm a disciplined trader. I have my own rules and I stick with them.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382981937217</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:38:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382982033813-96</Id><Title>I'm back. I'm ready to trade again.</Title><Msg>I had a wonderful breakfast. My kitties and I enjoyed it immensely.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382982033813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:40:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382982126706-97</Id><Title>Amazon Holding Up Firm</Title><Msg>with Friday's huge gain. We don't need no stinkin earnings, we just need revenue!</Msg><Username>mtgfriendofman</Username><Timestamp>1382982126706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382982188762-98</Id><Title>AMZN should build electric cars!!! They are</Title><Msg>not in this market, and it seems like a great growth story!!!</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382982188762</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382982440275-99</Id><Title>UUP going up</Title><Msg>UUP reversed the trend and this AMZN will go down now in the afternoon!</Msg><Username>n59218</Username><Timestamp>1382982440275</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:47:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382982561695-100</Id><Title>So the new story is- AMZN will never show profits</Title><Msg>They will just put profits in to new businesses until they have every business cornered. From forbes: "The way to think of Amazon here is not as “a business” but as ” a series of businesses”. It just happens that the growth to profitability of each of these businesses and then the recycling of those profits into further new projects is happening inside the boundaries of one firm. Rather than, say, through a series of firms." Please do note that this is an analogy, it’s not a precise and exact guide to what is going on. But with this mental image we can then answer the question of whether there is a switch that can be flipped and Amazon starts making profits? Sure there is. And no, it’s not the bankruptcy of all other retail businesses so that Amazon can raise prices. Instead it’s simply that Amazon could stop investing in those new businesses and the profits it is already making from the mature ones would become apparent. Maybe the shareholders would like that to happen some day and maybe Bezos would or would not. But that’s all that has to happen for Amazon to start showing good profits. Just stop investing the ones it is already making in new lines of business."</Msg><Username>kenji100</Username><Timestamp>1382982561695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382982641149-101</Id><Topic><Title>I'm going "Buy High, Sell Higher."</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382981937217</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:38:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the stock is going higher. Low float 475,000,000 shares Bezos owns 85,000.000 and American funds owns a ton 80,000,000. Sell at costs until drive other companies out of business, then raise price, better gross margins. Like movie shawshack redemption escaping from a prison using a rock chisel. Another Andy. Jeff now owns Washington Post politics sales tax problem in his favor now. I shorted small amount lost money. Underestimated Bezos, smart man. Stock goes higher unless economy goes bad.</Msg><Username>smartybob569</Username><Timestamp>1382982641149</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:50:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382982827695-102</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN should build electric cars!!! They are</Title><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382982188762</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Might as well, they can sell electric cars at a loss as well.</Msg><Username>abatulis</Username><Timestamp>1382982827695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:53:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382983543019-103</Id><Topic><Title>So the new story is- AMZN will never show profits</Title><Username>kenji100</Username><Timestamp>1382982561695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The way to think of Amazon here is . . . ." Don't think. That's how you make money in the stock market.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382983543019</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 14:05:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382983639590-104</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN should build electric cars!!! They are</Title><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382982188762</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, it's more revenue and we all know that revenue is king in this stock. Next they'll be a direct seller of gold at a discount to the market. The question I have is what investment bank will be behind the next round of financing and what is their relationship with amazon at this time. They'll love it until they hate it.</Msg><Username>hapihammer</Username><Timestamp>1382983639590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 14:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382983748249-105</Id><Title>$357.50 somewhat critical today.</Title><Msg>If we get there today, I would buy puts. Once we get there, $352.82 is likely to be tested. Longs don't want to see $356.12.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382983748249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 14:09:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382983902576-106</Id><Topic><Title>I'm back. I'm ready to trade again.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382982033813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:40:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You a #$%$. I sold my call option and made 2 dollars no thanks to you. Hope you lose your money for not telling me what to do.</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382983902576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 14:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382984043992-107</Id><Title>The air is thin at this level...</Title><Msg>smart to take some profits. I can even understand the "let your profits run" case, but who is going to be buying at these levels? Answer is only momo players. And they will run for the hills at the first sign of the ice cracking.</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382984043992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 14:14:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382984266388-108</Id><Title>AMZN: the greatest stock in the Universe.</Title><Msg>She keeps letting me buy calls cheap over and over and over . . . . What more do I need from stocks?</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382984266388</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 14:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382984401938-109</Id><Topic><Title>UUP going up</Title><Username>n59218</Username><Timestamp>1382982440275</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:47:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Told you so. Went down in a snap!</Msg><Username>n59218</Username><Timestamp>1382984401938</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 14:20:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382986912483-110</Id><Title>Bandwaggon shorts are jammed up in this pig with no Carl Ican to save em</Title><Msg>He saved the pig flix bandwaggonerz by unphvckinloading hiz scam longz after pulling a 5x wealth transfer on it... Amzn bandwaggonerz are trapped until fido and cap world unload.... soon, but not quite yet. There's more pain</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382986912483</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:01:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382987302584-111</Id><Title>Carl Ichan Tweets Buys shares of JCP and OTHM</Title><Msg>Carl Ichan Tweets Buying Shares of JCP and OTHM</Msg><Username>t0psecret.leader</Username><Timestamp>1382987302584</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:08:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382987623821-112</Id><Title>The higher this pig goez, the more shorts that pile on the bandwaggon armed to the teeth</Title><Msg>Shen theze idiots shoot each other by covering higher and higher. And then sheeple wonder why its gone parabolic despite fundiez. This thing aint gonna drop until institutional robots that have been holding it for 3-5 yearz unload it. They wont do that until all the shorts are dead and/or bernanke stops qe and raisez intrest rates and/or the muni bond market failure hits the bank's books... Soon, but there'z more UP side left... And it dont take a lot of time to get killed by a fellow short trying to escape the pain of a parabola. Sybil nailed the call for this move we are currently in weeks ago... Sybil did right by covering amzn shorts to a conservative level in order to have fire power to short pigflix ah at 370 when they reported. Now sybs haz a tight stop on pigflix for 1/2 of the pigflix 370 shorts sybby took down. The only thing sybs haz done wrong on any of these pigz iz not going long the sybil parabola call, but alas, sybil iz merely a retail short trader - not a robot.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382987623821</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:13:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382988227576-113</Id><Title>OT: DNDN is running!</Title><Msg>DNDN actually has a cancer drug for treating Prostate cancer. I think there is a high probability that DNDN going into the $9-12 range in the next few week/months. Heck, that stock once traded from $5 to $24 in a week (on drug news)! in 2007.</Msg><Username>newmarketpro2002</Username><Timestamp>1382988227576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:23:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382988354637-114</Id><Topic><Title>$357.50 somewhat critical today.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382983748249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 14:09:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you only had a clue</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382988354637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:25:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382988688735-115</Id><Topic><Title>The air is thin at this level...</Title><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382984043992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 14:14:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The same was said at the 330 level.</Msg><Username>txbradley28</Username><Timestamp>1382988688735</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:31:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382988953348-116</Id><Topic><Title>The air is thin at this level...</Title><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382984043992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 14:14:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not by me, I am new to this POS. $166B market cap. hahahahaha. I could buy both MCD and GS for $166B.</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382988953348</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:35:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382989015876-117</Id><Title>Dead Money!!!</Title><Msg>ha, what a waste of $166B</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382989015876</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:36:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382989064409-118</Id><Topic><Title>Dead Money!!!</Title><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382989015876</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:36:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that was music to my ears :)</Msg><Username>poopyestpapa</Username><Timestamp>1382989064409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:37:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382989106512-119</Id><Topic><Title>Dead Money!!!</Title><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382989015876</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:36:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" dead money for years to come" ..</Msg><Username>poopyestpapa</Username><Timestamp>1382989106512</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:38:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382989537710-120</Id><Title>Let the Mass Exodus</Title><Msg>Begin. It's time for the evil ways to be thwarted. Calling on divine intervention for a $100 point drop.</Msg><Username>his_angel_in_the_snow</Username><Timestamp>1382989537710</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:45:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382990042814-121</Id><Topic><Title>So the new story is- AMZN will never show profits</Title><Username>kenji100</Username><Timestamp>1382982561695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean the same old story.</Msg><Username>brewsman2002</Username><Timestamp>1382990042814</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382990164990-122</Id><Title>Bought some calls again.</Title><Msg>Wish me luck!</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382990164990</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:56:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382990516146-123</Id><Topic><Title>Bought some calls again.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382990164990</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:56:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Am I the only one who doesnt have you on ignore?</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382990516146</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 16:01:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382990616082-124</Id><Title>Cross trading bots will not be able to hold this turkey in a correction</Title><Msg>they were determined to paint $358 today and volume remained low enough. In a real correction this $70 equity will have some willing to book profits for the next $100 down. Where is the SEC?</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1382990616082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 16:03:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382992031939-125</Id><Topic><Title>Geegee takes the prize for being the dumbest phvck on the board</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382978748780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 12:45:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whether I'm "the dumbest phvck on" this "board" or not, I made money today buying/selling calls on AMZN. When was the last time you made any money?</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382992031939</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 16:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382992151128-126</Id><Topic><Title>Monday head fake down is done</Title><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1382980323387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:12:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There will be one more dip tomorrow morning. If AMZN turns around then, she may really shoots up to test $380 . . . this week. Good luck to all.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382992151128</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 16:29:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382992181842-127</Id><Title>5 Disruptive Effects on Q4 Revenue</Title><Msg>1) Obamacare stole Christmas: The meat and potatoes (middle class) of the economy are getting pre-holiday sticker shock from their insurance situation. That's thousands of dollars each family. 2) 5% Food Stamps Reduction: EBT cards for 50M Amricans get an accross the board hit on Nov 1st. Although it's justified because of the massive fraud and federal budget constraints, it's also less "play" money for the foodstampers to use on their iPhones and such 3) Best Buy is Back in the game: For many years, Amazon benefited from vampiric sales from Best Buy. This season is different thanks largely to California sales tax (and other big states) new cost this year for online orders. Many pricey and easy to ship electronics will be had locally with a boom for BB. No more $50 sales tax advantage on that $500 item in California. 4) Walmart is the #2 largest ecommerce retailer (OK, it's a tie for #2, but not for long and up from 4th place this year passing Apple and now passing Staples): Amazon has had good growth for ecommerce, but there's one company with a bigger growth rate now than Amazon. #2 ecommerce retailer Walmart has only one thing in its sights.... guess who? 5) Kindle Fire HDX wimper - Unsold Units is ungained revenue. How much farther below cost to unload them? Kindle is blackberry and this is a big problem when planned growth doesn't pan out. How big will the loss be? Who cares right? Well, this is all disruption to revenue!</Msg><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382992181842</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 16:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382992439706-128</Id><Topic><Title>Bought some calls again.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382990164990</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:56:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stockvestigator: "Am I the only one who doesnt have you on ignore?" Many here listened to that deranged fellow named "techstrategy" and put me on ignore. If they didn't put me on ignore and bought calls each time I posted that I bought some calls, they would have made money . . . lots of money. Instead, they chose to keep listening to techstrategy and have lost more money. I must conclude that shorts here like to lose money.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382992439706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 16:33:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382992529231-129</Id><Title>AAPL falling in AH, they made too much money!! Not smart like Bezos</Title><Msg>Growing $70Billion in earnings at 25% is only going to work for a few years, revenue estimates WILL come down to the 10% range</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382992529231</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 16:35:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382992690744-130</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL falling in AH, they made too much money!! Not smart like Bezos</Title><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382992529231</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 16:35:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMZN ... 340, 330... 310, 280 ... now ... get the picture!</Msg><Username>n59218</Username><Timestamp>1382992690744</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 16:38:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382992770668-131</Id><Topic><Title>Bought some calls again.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382990164990</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 15:56:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know .I bought 80 call options and earned a profit of 2 dollars each but you did not tell me what to do like I asked. I got nervous when you didnt respond so I sold them. Maybe when the stock gets back to 352.53 I will buy again. i know you lost money on yours even though you said you didnt because the stock price was lower each time you posted except once. And I know you say you are long call options that you bought when the stock was 359 again and you dint sell them so hopefully you will not lose much more tomorrow.</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382992770668</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 16:39:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382992805502-132</Id><Topic><Title>So the new story is- AMZN will never show profits</Title><Username>kenji100</Username><Timestamp>1382982561695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This makes for a formidable stock. It can lose money and investors won't care. I sold out at 307 and have been hoping for a big correction so I could buy back, but it hasn't happened. I may have missed the train to 1000. But that's ok, I have my money. Unlike the shorts who lose and lose and lose.</Msg><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1382992805502</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 16:40:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382993349236-133</Id><Topic><Title>So the new story is- AMZN will never show profits</Title><Username>kenji100</Username><Timestamp>1382982561695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" I may have missed the train to 1000." Is this the comment of the day or the month? The stock is at 360 and its going to 1000 and you say you missed the train..huh? Interesting!</Msg><Username>dowto6k</Username><Timestamp>1382993349236</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 16:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382994143744-134</Id><Title>Geegee slamz hiz head off the glass of a special needz bus like a retread az he gets whipsawed in hiz weekliez</Title><Msg>He'z very stupid.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382994143744</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 17:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382995240930-135</Id><Title>Bandwaggon shorts are panting heavily az they eyeball the daily charts from a position of weakness</Title><Msg>They are stuck in a gap 'n trap with their fingurez crossed az aapl reports and the fed meets on the aniversary of the 1929.... Those stuck in house callz are due soon, and trapped with the prospect of another JUMP up - just to phvck em in their stuck position....</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382995240930</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 17:20:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382995862640-136</Id><Title>84 years ago, Tuesday--"Black Tuesday, 1929"--the biggest day of the crash of '29</Title><Msg>Will there be an echo? So much complacency &amp; bullish sentiment.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1382995862640</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 17:31:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382996034063-137</Id><Title>Wow, That singing lion fellow hates Sybil almost as much as PhilJoe</Title><Msg>I kind of side with Sybil here. SHOUTING &amp; RANTING is a loser.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1382996034063</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 17:33:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382996473393-138</Id><Topic><Title>84 years ago, Tuesday--"Black Tuesday, 1929"--the biggest day of the crash of '29</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1382995862640</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 17:31:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Oct 29th, 1929 drop on that day was about 12%. A 3-5% drop might qualify as an "echo". Wipe the smirk of the pumper faces.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1382996473393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 17:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382996590590-139</Id><Title>Singing Lion, why do you hate Sybil?</Title><Msg>Sybil is a kind hearted and full of good advice.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1382996590590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 17:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382996875631-140</Id><Title>We need an activst investor to demand more segment &amp; profitability information from AMZN..Calling Icahn</Title><Msg>I don't understand why a hedge fund activist doesn't start riding AMZN's Board and Exec. Mgmt. for not releasing more data. Afterall, isn't a company owned by its shareholders and shouldn't they have access to key segment and profitability information? I bet if an activist took on this role, this stock would plummet overnight.</Msg><Username>rxcount</Username><Timestamp>1382996875631</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 17:47:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382997040224-141</Id><Topic><Title>So the new story is- AMZN will never show profits</Title><Username>kenji100</Username><Timestamp>1382982561695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Revenues are growing slower. Which means that even if they can flip that switch they will have to trade sideways for 10 years to justify this market cap. And once they are big enough, yes then they can flip the switch. But if you chart the revenue growth it is an almost straight line for the last three years. 41% 31% 22% Which means next years growth may be a paltry 12%. Imagine how long it will take to justify the market capitalization if growth slows to 12%.</Msg><Username>it_all_goood</Username><Timestamp>1382997040224</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 17:50:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382997139232-142</Id><Title>SINGLE MOMS love AMZN 24% growth in revenue, when profit hits we will be 600-700 easily</Title><Msg>we are waiting for the moment.</Msg><Username>wforty</Username><Timestamp>1382997139232</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 17:52:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382997558829-143</Id><Topic><Title>We need an activst investor to demand more segment &amp; profitability information from AMZN..Calling Icahn</Title><Username>rxcount</Username><Timestamp>1382996875631</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 17:47:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody invested in Amazon would want that data out. It would cause the price to go down. Ignorance is bliss for momo players and institutional holders. They don't want the data. They just want to be out at the top before the collapse is all.</Msg><Username>one_smooth_stone</Username><Timestamp>1382997558829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 17:59:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382997676246-144</Id><Topic><Title>We need an activst investor to demand more segment &amp; profitability information from AMZN..Calling Icahn</Title><Username>rxcount</Username><Timestamp>1382996875631</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 17:47:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, just be happy we have arrived at the "unloading time". The data will come out after the collapse when Amazon has to explain what happened.</Msg><Username>one_smooth_stone</Username><Timestamp>1382997676246</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 18:01:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382997745314-145</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN should build electric cars!!! They are</Title><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382982188762</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Precisely. Enron, but the malfeasance if not fraud lies elsewhere....</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382997745314</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 18:02:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382997938245-146</Id><Topic><Title>5 Disruptive Effects on Q4 Revenue</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382992181842</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 16:29:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Q4 will be bad for retailers this year. Perhaps amazon will suffer most since they don't just need a profit like all the other retailers. Amazon needs growth or it's over and they're not going to get growth.</Msg><Username>one_smooth_stone</Username><Timestamp>1382997938245</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 18:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382998028908-147</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN should build electric cars!!! They are</Title><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382982188762</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we support it.</Msg><Username>wforty</Username><Timestamp>1382998028908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 18:07:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382998389003-148</Id><Title>Amazon smartphones coming?</Title><Msg>http://seekingalpha.com/article/1778972-some-free-amazon-smartphone-speculation</Msg><Username>nathanjamesbrooks</Username><Timestamp>1382998389003</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 18:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382998555776-149</Id><Topic><Title>So the new story is- AMZN will never show profits</Title><Username>kenji100</Username><Timestamp>1382982561695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll buy some if it dips below 300.</Msg><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1382998555776</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 18:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382998669439-150</Id><Topic><Title>Muddy Waters: AMZN "A Massive Fraud Business Model"</Title><Username>trendking</Username><Timestamp>1382949615535</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 04:40:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Search!</Msg><Username>polpounder5</Username><Timestamp>1382998669439</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382999079586-151</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon retail is a non-value added middleman</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382974276311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 11:31:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An improvement from steadily declining earnings isn't good enough when your are tading at hundreds of 2019 earnings that are based upon a much larger rev base. The upshot for Amazon is prop hardware is harder on its working capital, so the failure is a minor reprieve and might buy the IBs a little (very little) more time...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382999079586</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 18:24:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383000269328-152</Id><Title>Bottomline: Book the profits in AMZN now, or loose it all.</Title><Msg>The earning's day reaction was just created to get the big-boys off the upper-deck! Signs of distribution already started. Nothing to look fwd to here anymore on the long side, for a loooooooong time to come! IMHO!</Msg><Username>n59218</Username><Timestamp>1383000269328</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 18:44:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383000719958-153</Id><Topic><Title>5 Disruptive Effects on Q4 Revenue</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382992181842</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 16:29:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All those 5 items are guaranteed, but the risk is even worse to the downside... 1) Fed Taper "could" start, but not expected, but why is a $15B taper so feared? It's out there as a wildcard to start Q4. Pressure on Yellen's nomination might scrutinize why they don't try a taper. 2) Recession may start. We're on the edge. An acknowledgement of a coming recession may be unavoidable, so that would be another wildcard inter-twined 3) Effects of Obamacare might be more than just middleclass getting sticker shock. We're in the throws of upheaval on 16.7% of the eceonomy too 4) Iran is only "weeks" away they say. Is something going to happen or not?? 5) Disfunctional negotiations will continue in Washington right through Q4. They'll talk increased taxes and maybe an internet tax too all through Q4. It'll be crazy. So, there are plenty of additional wildcard Q4 downside risks that are heating up possible. Will these be disruptive to amazon's revenue growth? Yes. Who wants to buy or hold into a quarter that is going down?! The gig is up.</Msg><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1383000719958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 18:51:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383002011629-154</Id><Title>Hey sybil, what happened today ??</Title><Msg>closed down !!! will it repeat goog pattern, flat or so tomorrow and then another pop for a last attemp to squeeze retails.............. anyway, I`ll just increase my short position if it pops later this week.......</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1383002011629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 19:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383004318319-155</Id><Topic><Title>Muddy Waters: AMZN "A Massive Fraud Business Model"</Title><Username>trendking</Username><Timestamp>1382949615535</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 04:40:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does not exist</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1383004318319</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 19:51:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383004565953-156</Id><Topic><Title>I do not know.....</Title><Username>bensadri</Username><Timestamp>1382717545506</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 12:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But at least AMZN sells products, BB does not!</Msg><Username>berrytarder</Username><Timestamp>1383004565953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 19:56:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383005105869-157</Id><Topic><Title>Hey sybil, what happened today ??</Title><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1383002011629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 19:13:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" I`ll just increase my short position if it pops later this week......" OK, if you camm JUMPING from 315 to 358 closing "down" then have it your way, crack head. You MUST have shorted 363 or better to be so happy. Sybil will be shorting your panick buying going into dec. sybilz 1st shorts are just a few bux higher to start. This pig haz at least a 370 handle in it and if it gets saucey with bandwaggon shorts then its going to 420 to kill them. End of the month iz thursdayand there'z lots of robots that dont want to miss out on the "holiday run"</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1383005105869</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 20:05:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383005375067-158</Id><Topic><Title>Muddy Waters: AMZN "A Massive Fraud Business Model"</Title><Username>trendking</Username><Timestamp>1382949615535</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 04:40:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the blues guitarist? I thought he was dead.</Msg><Username>joeshmoe1234z</Username><Timestamp>1383005375067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 20:09:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383005445988-159</Id><Title>about the only big name tech stock that goes nowhere</Title><Msg>Amazon, Google, Netflix, Facebook, all flying high.</Msg><Username>joeshmoe1234z</Username><Timestamp>1383005445988</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 20:10:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383006452911-160</Id><Title>AMZN is the best with cheaper products.</Title><Msg>Whole America wants cheaper products. Pay less and get more. We may see all college grads making 8 bucks an hour. A new wind is blowing. AAPL, MSFT and INTC will all be like General Motor. Cheap America with cheaper products will have no place for innovators like AAPL. Go AMZN go.</Msg><Username>harveykoff</Username><Timestamp>1383006452911</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 20:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383006515100-161</Id><Topic><Title>So the new story is- AMZN will never show profits</Title><Username>kenji100</Username><Timestamp>1382982561695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Irrational Exuberance is showing it's ugly head again - 13 years after the first round. This time, AMZN is fooling investors in by building up volume and undercutting all peers by charging less for services and goods. If China was doing this they would be prosecuted under the anti-dumping rules. But AMZN can cleverly use this model and build up their gross income while losing money. How long can they keep this up without investors running out of patience? It's akin to a bubble gum being blown bigger and bigger - we're not sure when but at some point the bubble will burst with a big bang. Investors beware.</Msg><Username>future_is_fiber</Username><Timestamp>1383006515100</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 20:28:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383007326596-162</Id><Title>Hey kidz.... Sybil just looked at the charts and confirmed that Amzn iz going......</Title><Msg>Higher. 420 - 480 Ya better coooover.... Sybby aint shorting this pig yet.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1383007326596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 20:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383007584780-163</Id><Topic><Title>Hey kidz.... Sybil just looked at the charts and confirmed that Amzn iz going......</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1383007326596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 20:42:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry sybil got carried away.... 405-425.... Didnt mean to scare you with that 480 number.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1383007584780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 20:46:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383007695136-164</Id><Topic><Title>So the new story is- AMZN will never show profits</Title><Username>kenji100</Username><Timestamp>1382982561695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 13:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No true-er statement on these boards than that Geegee. No truer statement ever !</Msg><Username>zbc407</Username><Timestamp>1383007695136</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 20:48:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383012196278-165</Id><Title>Bezos Ponzi vs Madoff Ponzi</Title><Msg>Which scheme is better?</Msg><Username>fu_cowwwboy2</Username><Timestamp>1383012196278</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 22:03:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383013660765-166</Id><Topic><Title>Bezos Ponzi vs Madoff Ponzi</Title><Username>fu_cowwwboy2</Username><Timestamp>1383012196278</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 22:03:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All I know is: "Bezos Ponzi" still has a "Bozo" in it, while Madoff Ponzi has "Nomad Off" the scene now! :-) [Picking the letters created this marvelous coincidence! :-) ].</Msg><Username>n59218</Username><Timestamp>1383013660765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 22:27:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383013880790-167</Id><Topic><Title>Bezos Ponzi vs Madoff Ponzi</Title><Username>fu_cowwwboy2</Username><Timestamp>1383012196278</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 22:03:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that really hard to say they both worked so well</Msg><Username>xdon69</Username><Timestamp>1383013880790</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 22:31:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383016686435-168</Id><Title>I'm an AAPL investor- why do you guys here have such good luck?</Title><Msg>Insane p/e and all. Oh well.</Msg><Username>dereksjsu2002</Username><Timestamp>1383016686435</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-28 23:18:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>