<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-23"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361595648396-1</Id><Topic><Title>Treatment of options income in funds....</Title><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361578934155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:22:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil, You are right on with this. I hope you repeat this post sometime when it is not buried three levels deep in message board. When the massive collapse occurs, there will be many contracts that will not be honored, including insurance policies, pensions, FDIC, etc. People need to move into cash at the appropriate time.</Msg><Username>jeffpmpccea</Username><Timestamp>1361595648396</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 00:00:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361621020627-2</Id><Topic><Title>Treatment of options income in funds....</Title><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361578934155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:22:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is not correct. In each fund prospectus it outlines what managers can/cannot do, vast majority of funds exclude option activity. Some use covered call income (EXG/EOS for example) but the profit/loss is returned to the shareholders. Look at AMZN auto-callable securities issued by Morgan Stanley in Feb 2012. This was an option income security. Majority of weekly options are written by traders/market makers, taking the wider bid/ask and basically skimming theta and gamma, whilst managing delta.</Msg><Username>panichomo2</Username><Timestamp>1361621020627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 07:03:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361629359546-3</Id><Title>Reversal Time</Title><Msg>I have been following there recommendations on DIA, SPY and QQQQ and find them accurate and timely. Well done for a solid service. I want to tell you that I can't compare anyone to them in terms of the daily analysis. For someone like me, who is familiar with technical analysis and has used it for two decades, it is very rare to hear from anyone who will share their analysis like they do. Watch the daily video its free, and maybe it can help you like it has helped me. copy and paste and put info this link TECHNICAL-TRADER</Msg><Username>robinhenry939</Username><Timestamp>1361629359546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 09:22:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361629999607-4</Id><Topic><Title>Treatment of options income in funds....</Title><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361578934155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:22:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It didn't sound right to me. Having said that, I read an article that more mutuals funds (and many of the better performing ones are now selling options (trying to find it again), so that is changing. If so, I partially t explains the ever expanding divergence we are seeing in the market (multiples as a function of control of float moreso than earnings growth). That the scam moves up most on big POMO days already clarifies that said MM are using POMO money to keep this balloon inflated and extract trading profits. The Fed is supposedly printing to keep rates low and encourage investment in risk assets. But, the PD (also the MM) never put the money to work in risky assets. They simply use it to scalp and drive trading profits, undermining the "goal" of Fed printing as the money is kept out of the real economy so that the MM can make healthy profits and pay out bonuses that are multiples of the typical family income (since running the floam jam scam creates so much value for society). Anyone see the bloomberg article that the implicit subsidy of TBTF banks accounts for most of the profit at this banks? Wonder what the Fed printing enabled option scalping provides to them...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361629999607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 09:33:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361631386604-5</Id><Topic><Title>Treatment of options income in funds....</Title><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361578934155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:22:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tech, That whole issue has been gnawing away at me for a while. I assume Ben is a smart guy and could figure that out or have one of his people inform him of what's going on, but he continues to push his agenda. All that Fed printing isn't helping the people ( friends have been denied loans even with decent credit) nor small businesses. Only the people who causes the '09 mess in the first place get the benefit. I found it funny that in '09 they only people that got bailed out were the banks, the ones that caused the mess. GM, car industry didn't get sweet deals. And nothing has been done to control/regulate banks. Oh, ok, the sheep get to see their interest payments on their credit card statement....big deal. So getting to my point.....why would he allow this to happen or even continue? Is he just that idealistic or naive .....or (insert conspiracy theory here). I find it ironic that the some of the biggest contributors to both R and D campaigns are the very same banks. I stole this quote from Singlion2001: Andrew Jackson quotes: Gentlemen, I have had men watching you for a long time and I am convinced that you have used the funds of the bank to speculate in the bread stuffs of the country. When you won, you divided the profits amongst you, and when you lost, you charged it to the bank. You tell me that if I take the deposits from the bank and annul its charter, I shall ruin ten thousand families. That may be true, gentlemen, but that is your sin! Should I let you go on, you will ruin fifty thousand families, and that would be my sin! You are a den of vipers and thieves. Seems like things don't change but the integrity of our leaders has been diminished. - PJ</Msg><Username>pjlouie13</Username><Timestamp>1361631386604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 09:56:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361632361563-6</Id><Topic><Title>Treatment of options income in funds....</Title><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361578934155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:22:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whilst I agree with your sentiment regarding banks, don't think they are getting a totally free ride. Dodd Frank and Basel 2/3 are severely limiting their leverage/trading via capital requirements and position disclosure. The element not mentioned here is hedge funds and black box algos who are obviously "involved" in the casino called Amazon.</Msg><Username>panichomo2</Username><Timestamp>1361632361563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 10:12:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361636933918-7</Id><Topic><Title>Treatment of options income in funds....</Title><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361578934155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:22:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Panic: The constraints on financial sector leverage are prudent. The reality is that the financial sector took on way too much leverage in the past in order to drive up profit per capita and there is/has been massive moral hazard in the use of the leverage, particularly naked derivative contracts (soon you may see more on the subject in HBR). The banks are getting screwed on NIM because of ZIRP. But, the gov't cannot afford to have interest rates normalize. The reality is that financial sector compensation has to enter secular and structural decline until it is inline with the rest of the economy -- and it has a long way to go. That's the only realistic way to maintain banks profitability without amplifying systemic risk. Back to the subject here. I will be reading the prospectus of every MF company and fund holding over 2MM shares to see how they are using derivatives and treating profit streams from them. I have a hypothesis that they are doing something similar to loaning shares for shorting and deriving interest income, but that still creates a significant conflict of interest between shareholders of a fund and institutional (fund manager / company) IMHO. Only one way to find out and these btards have made it worth my while to keep digging deeper to understand the scam in its entirety...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361636933918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 11:28:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361637392980-8</Id><Topic><Title>Treatment of options income in funds....</Title><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361578934155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:22:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tech, mutual funds have charterz, many are limited to what they can do with optionz... Those that are limited are the baggie buy high dumping groundz and then sell low at the bottom funds like a fidelity 2030 funds. Those high net worth fundz that manipulate a stock to scrape optionz set forth a return target for their clients and pay their active fund managerz risk based compensation based upon their individual activities that exceed targets from their optionz scrapes. When the high net worth fundz are done with playing a stock such az FMR with nflx in 2011, they dump it into the markets and over to their baggie mutual fundz at the top.... Integrated brokerage house, underwriting, mutual fund family, market makerz, and hnw client black box trading desk companiez use each branch and in house live data feeds between the integrated branchez, and run real time bot statistics and probabilities to scalp money and move securitiez from one in house branch to another at the expense of the many. The solution would be to disintergrate inttergrated companiez so one couldnt play off another in house.... Its what iz going down dude, like it or not.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1361637392980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 11:36:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361637902992-9</Id><Topic><Title>Treatment of options income in funds....</Title><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361578934155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:22:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Panichomo (good handle btw), Fidelity, world cap, et al, were not part of the tbtf ers in 08 and have benefited well beyond the bac, c, and even gs of the world since.... They are no so buried in the scam market scalping now that they are indeed tbtf..... When the jig iz up then real baggie buy high mutual fund accounts will be left with the bag. Fidelity uz not a bank, it iz a financial institutional, how ever financial institutionz that begrudgingly became banks (like gs) fvcked themselvez under the lawz and microscopes of the dodd / frank rulez... Dod frank does not apply to fmr or financial companiez like it.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1361637902992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 11:45:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361638613836-10</Id><Topic><Title>Who iz gonna hold their tulip bulbz too long?</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1361396700569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:45:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you think shorting is better advice than buying long-dated puts? I understand you think options are a scam, but by this logic, isn't the whole market a scam? Individual investors are losing millions on options plays gone bad. But before they lost just as much on stocks. Even if options didn't exist, big money would still have the advantage and would still exercise a great deal of control over the market at the expense of the individual investor. But there are many things that cannot be predicted and cannot be controlled. In extreme situations big money can no longer control the market. It turns against them. That is when you are going to make money on AMZN going down, and when AMZN crashes you are going to make money whether you are holding puts or short of the underlying. The problem is no one knows exactly when it's going to happen. At the very least you need to know someone's financial situation and risk tolerance before you recommend they short AMZN. Not everyone has the capital to short a stock like this, or to keep shorting it until the known date when it crashes, and shorting exposes one to the possibility of infinite losses. With long-dated puts one's losses are limited to the premiums. If at the end of the contract, the option expires worthless, the buyer still lost more money than anyone who held onto a short position during that length of time. Conceivably at some point the short would have been forced to cover and possibly be pushed out of the market altogether as a result of the loss.</Msg><Username>newpikachu</Username><Timestamp>1361638613836</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 11:56:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361638749001-11</Id><Topic><Title>Who iz gonna hold their tulip bulbz too long?</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1361396700569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:45:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>corrections to the above... "the unknown date when it crashes" and "the buyer still lost less money than anyone who held onto a short position"</Msg><Username>newpikachu</Username><Timestamp>1361638749001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 11:59:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361645951548-12</Id><Topic><Title>Treatment of options income in funds....</Title><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361578934155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:22:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybs: I have access to nationally recognized expert in corp and securities law. Was discussing with one last night. There could be significant issues with what you are describing. More as due diligence proceeds. Anyone with examples/evidence of fund managers or management companies making returns on derivatives of the underlying that is not wholly shared with the underlying fund owning securities (the folks whose capital makes the extensive holdings and thus the large share of float possible) and its shareholders, please email my alias with said info anonymously if necessary.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361645951548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 13:59:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361647250337-13</Id><Topic><Title>Treatment of options income in funds....</Title><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361578934155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:22:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tech, You idiot.... Sybil doesn't have emparicle evidence of how exactly this iz done. Its only plainly obvious that it iz being done. Just like when you saw a no doc immigrant move into a 4500 square foot mcmansion in 2005, or an idiot handy man flipping housez like they were hamburgerz didnt pass the smell test in '05, no one knew the mechanics until nov 2008. Sheeple will only realize the true gamez being played AFTER THE DAMAGE IZ DONE, dummy.... But after it all panz out with the bogus bond repurchasing, qe over qe, and the gamez yhat robots played with leveraged liquidity anybody reading sybil posts will have a vague sense that 'sybil was on to something'. If sybil owned a robot with a MIT mathematician behind it and gobz of no hazard opmz then sybil would run the exact scamz that sybil iz outlining.... It would not be that hard to do.... That being said, when sybil querried sybs broker on optionz writing and trading within a trading desk as to where iz the money going the answer was "its compensation at risk for active fund managerz"..... Doez sybil have a recording? No.... Diez sybil have an employee name? No.... Did sybil understand the simplified answer that came out of a complex inquisition? Probably not.... But its going on, dude, az sheeple feed the optionz machine with scam leveraged etfs and straight out option buying without a clue....</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1361647250337</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 14:20:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361652539542-14</Id><Title>BOZO and his gang is dumping shares..</Title><Msg>Sale growth has slowed.. 3 years of producing nothing.. Heading to 150..</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361652539542</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 15:48:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361656799985-15</Id><Topic><Title>BOZO and his gang is dumping shares..</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361652539542</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 15:48:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While bezos and hiz crew are certainly masterz in the scamz of stock and option comp cashinz, theze guyz a quire boyz compared to hastingz and hiz crew at pig flix.... They must have went to the same school to learn how to get rich dycking baggiez in the ars....</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1361656799985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 16:59:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361657022757-16</Id><Topic><Title>Treatment of options income in funds....</Title><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361578934155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:22:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybs: Don't worry. I'm not relying on one anecdotal POV. I will now go out and dig into what is really happening. I know folks involved in the many fee/subadvisory fee suits taking place now (read about Hartford/Vanguard/Wellington to see what I am talking about). They'll probably have some visibility into this issue from that. And, maybe they'll be able to leverage their knowledge base and sunk cost to go after another abuse of trust...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361657022757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 17:03:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361659478866-17</Id><Title>Tech, what are u trying to prove here</Title><Msg>that al Capone has avoided paying taxes or something of thatr nature. u could learn marxism instead of wasting time on how US mafia operates. could it be you put was sold by the company that was doing buyback,, some option fund, mutual fund or some fancy index fund aka CDO we don't know about yet. in any case starting Feb 4 2013 SEC has implemented limit up down rule to reduce volatility (and kill the options premiums including long term ones, of course). so if scam is not up then it will be harder to take it down for sure. u are fighting the system called central bank and there is no way u can do something unless it is physical way.</Msg><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1361659478866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 17:44:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361660567849-18</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, what are u trying to prove here</Title><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1361659478866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 17:44:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it was central bank, then Apple doesn't drop 40% while Amazon increases 20%. This is a private scam being run with Fed money. It would be best for the longs to let the air out slowly so that limit up/down doesn't trigger as that will only draw more attention to how egregiouus this AAPL/AMZN scam has been...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361660567849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:02:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361661535900-19</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, what are u trying to prove here</Title><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1361659478866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 17:44:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm afraid that this will all end in violence if those running the scams don't wake the fvck up. That's not me. I try to point of the path that is right and just. Want to do what I can to make people aware of abuses to stop them before they trigger real conflict. Amazon is simply a clear case study of what is wrong with the capital markets and it is sufficiently visible and its downfall over the next 12 months sufficiently clear and inevitable that I will be here through it all (even if I lose all that I have riding on Amazon) to make sure all the shenanigans gets plenty of sunlight.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361661535900</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:18:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361662796618-20</Id><Topic><Title>BOZO and his gang is dumping shares..</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361652539542</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 15:48:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, sales have grown from 34b to 61b, an increase of 150%.</Msg><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1361662796618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:39:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361663082385-21</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, what are u trying to prove here</Title><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1361659478866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 17:44:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cash, It looks like old sybs haz got tech all fired up with a cause.... Pretty soon he'll be reduced to a stock board ranter like that crazy baaaaastaaaard singhlion .... That poor slob iz like a crazy dude preaching "repent - for doom And destruction iz upon us!" at passerbyz.... He's been at it since 2010 and sybs waiting for that guy'z head to explode....</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1361663082385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:44:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361663119641-22</Id><Topic><Title>It took a few yearz, but the optionz scam iz so blantantly obvious to retailerz that ....</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1361571970630</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:26:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tech, I don't know how options trading can effect the stock price, but I can understand how shorting a stock affects the price. When someone sells short, they "borrow" the shares, but who do they borrow them from? The brokers who are holding the shares for clients? Do the brokers get paid to loan the shares for shorting? Loaning a clients shares to a short seller is so outrageously against the clients interest, it should be illegal.</Msg><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1361663119641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:45:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361663128136-23</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, what are u trying to prove here</Title><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1361659478866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 17:44:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And mini option contracts are launching to create more flow from decay with smaller holders who are likely less sophisticated... They are doing everything they can to feed the best, but eventually they will have to eat each other...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361663128136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:45:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361663565906-24</Id><Title>Techstrategy"':I'm afraid that this will all end in violence if those running the scams don't wake the fvck up" LOL!</Title><Msg>You've turned into a 100 % bonafide nutbag my friend trying to explain why you got fleecedi in amzn.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1361663565906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:52:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361663634435-25</Id><Title>TECHSTARTEGY IS STARTING TO OVERTAKE SYBIL IN NUTBAG CONSPIRCACIES AND THAT'S TOUGHT TO DO: SYBIL IS A MORON!!</Title><Msg>So funny to watch the clowns start fight with each other</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1361663634435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:53:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361663735505-26</Id><Title>THIS IS HOW IT GOES" THE SHORT CLOWN LOSING START FIGHT WITH EACH OTHER:: "IT'S A CONSPIRACY THAT ENDS IN VIOLANCE!" LOL!!</Title><Msg>You've gotta be kidding me! by the way, sybil is still the biggest nutball clown wrong on these boards bar none despite techstrategy really starting to lose it now.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1361663735505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:55:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361663879366-27</Id><Title>YEAH SYBIL THE OPTIONS SCAMS WERE SO OBVIOUS TO YOU WITH AMZN YOU SHORTED AMZN AT 215 AND IT'S NOW 265 AND MONTHS LATER</Title><Msg>WHAT A FREAKING MONDAY MORINING QUARTERBACK</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1361663879366</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:57:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361663956066-28</Id><Title>I LOVE READING THE "MONDAY MORNING QB" TALK OF SYBIL NOW THAT HE'S CLEARLY BEEN REAR ENDED IN AMZN AGAIN AND AGAIN!</Title><Msg>Shorts always have to resort to explanations of why their scenarios didn't play out.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1361663956066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:59:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361668778314-29</Id><Topic><Title>Techstrategy"':I'm afraid that this will all end in violence if those running the scams don't wake the fvck up" LOL!</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1361663565906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:52:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That comment IS NOT directed at Amazon. That's a statement on the end result of Fed policies and banks/financial sector players continuing to pursue the same strategies that have failed and will continue to fail in an accelerating fashion. Trying to inflate our way out to preserve nominal asset prices simply harms those without large financial assets (most of the population) because necessities go up for everyone. The right answer is to write off bad debt and realize losses. Instead, the are slowly squeezing the majority of the country. I am afraid that the continual destruction of wealth and real standard of living except those at the very top of the financial food chain will eventually lead to instability.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361668778314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 20:19:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361669695403-30</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, what are u trying to prove here</Title><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1361659478866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 17:44:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybs: Not true. I've been tracking irregular activity on this stock for some time. I will continue to. I do believe that the rise of institutional long use of options to generate income has dramatically altered the behavior of the market and I can show statistically that multiple are increasingly a function of control of float rather than earnings/revenue growth. My analysis is clinical and factual. My comments on concern for how all this ends are directed to the ridiculous Fed measures which are taking place purely to prevent banks from realizing losses with the overlevered dervative mess at the expense of the general population. If it wants to do QE, do QE to the people rather than banks... Clearly, the posts conflated the topics in my posts. Amazon's failure will cause no major damage, except that it will serve as a case study of our dysunctional financial markets... This is a different scam. And, while the Fed reversing course may be impossible at this point, this company is headed for serious trouble on the fundamentals.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361669695403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 20:34:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361671173164-31</Id><Topic><Title>It took a few yearz, but the optionz scam iz so blantantly obvious to retailerz that ....</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1361571970630</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:26:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well Bruce, that is where we are headed. No shorts anywhere. And, when we get there, Amazon is hosed because only short squeezes and the option scam keep this levitating. Once they are gone, capital will migfrate to true investments rather than trading scams.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1361671173164</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 20:59:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361672476479-32</Id><Topic><Title>It took a few yearz, but the optionz scam iz so blantantly obvious to retailerz that ....</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1361571970630</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:26:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brucetheskinfluteguy, Sybil borrowed your dharez and sold them for you since youre too stupid to do it yourself. Sybs got them short sharz right on sybs table and they got a stamp on them that says "property of bruce" followed by an "IOU" right the fvck on them... Sybs promisez to return them back to you sub 100.... It shouldnt be too much longer now, dummy.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1361672476479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 21:21:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361672735215-33</Id><Title>sybil seez nasdaq_6000 beating hiz meat behind the veil of</Title><Msg>yahoo ignore..... What a dope.... No worriez that guy dissappearz when this pig goez down 50 cents.... It wont be long before he completely vanishez.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1361672735215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 21:25:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361678647380-34</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, what are u trying to prove here</Title><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1361659478866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 17:44:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are there any good articles dealing with how the limit up limit down rule will actually work in real world situations? Right now it is not clear to me that this rule will make long term options worthless. If there is strong buying or selling pressure in a stock, the stock will make a massive move to the up or downside in the short term. Rules like this cannot stop fear based selling or greed buying. As I understand it this mechanism will just stop massive price movements from taking place too rapidly--five minute periods. This is really just an emergency measure to stop total market collapse instituted at the level of individual securities; it won't stop volatile stocks from being more volatile. In fact if trading is halted due to price collapse in an equity during that time sell orders will continue piling up and will have to be executed when trading resumes. I don't know if all of this is totally correct, but this is understanding based on the information I have read which was released by the SEC. If you can provide reference to any good articles on the subject, I'd like to read them.</Msg><Username>newpikachu</Username><Timestamp>1361678647380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 23:04:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>