<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364648791203-1</Id><Topic><Title>Secret AMZN Info Revealed</Title><Username>josephharris479</Username><Timestamp>1363347722710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:42:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that very helpful</Msg><Username>ednamutchler</Username><Timestamp>1364648791203</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 09:06:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364648973552-2</Id><Topic><Title>Newz headlline readz: "Authors Guild head blasts Amazon buy of Goodreads"</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364596650622</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:37:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"He will undercut what authorz make by low balling them." Goodreads is just a place where readers discuss books. It has nothing to do with what authors make or don't make. "Bezos hasnt disclosed what he paid" News reports say it is about $160 million with some possible bonuses attached depending on whether the site meets certain targets putting the upper range around $200 million in total. "The web site haz 16 million 'subs'" So Amazon breaks even at about $10 per sub. Sounds like a pretty good deal. "but it will decline and errode, and will never make any money" Ha! Where will 16 million people go? Amazon already owns all the competing sites. People don't tend to move around that much, they tend to stay put in the communities they've gotten used to. Only some ignorant short would think that the goal is for the site to generate its own profits. Everyone else understands that these things merely generate more sales of books and that Amazon will make $billions in book profits in upcoming years.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1364648973552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 09:09:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364649932844-3</Id><Title>EXCITING NEWS ON AMZN CLOUD ALGOS--INCIDATE FROPOLOP TECH ATTRACTING NEW BUSINESS!</Title><Msg>DFSDFSDSD</Msg><Username>bachrachjeff</Username><Timestamp>1364649932844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 09:25:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364650729038-4</Id><Topic><Title>Secret AMZN Info Revealed</Title><Username>josephharris479</Username><Timestamp>1363347722710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:42:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very useful.</Msg><Username>wilma.castillo</Username><Timestamp>1364650729038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 09:38:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364653680354-5</Id><Topic><Title>Secret AMZN Info Revealed</Title><Username>josephharris479</Username><Timestamp>1363347722710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:42:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks you. That very useful.</Msg><Username>janetschmitd</Username><Timestamp>1364653680354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364655164447-6</Id><Title>Unfortunately, markets dont crash when everyone expects them to....</Title><Msg>Thats too bad, because sybs a h8r thats stuck bieing in agreement with the general consensus that the market iz a scam destined for a BIG crash thats right around the corner. The only thing that sybil hates more then scam stox in bernanke's manufactured big markets iz being in consensus with billionz of other dopes that are h8r's too. Sybil's got a new measure by which to scale and weigh a potential market top.... Az cruel az it sounds, sybs haz designed this metric around a posting pal's trading methods: techstrategy. Sybil callz it the TECH FACTOR. Here's how it works: Now sybs had a hunch for yearz that optionz on a grand scale are going to be one of several major components leading the boom / bust cycle that we are in. Tech haz been a BIG trader of 'quality' DITM , 6 month, 9 month and leap optionz all the way through this cycle; just Waiting for pig stox drop on puts and barking dogz to get up and run on callz..... Ok let sybs get to the point: When tech capitulates on optionz and sybs dumps scam bear etfs that ise optionz in disgust - that will be an indication of the top... Or if tech and sybs dont capitulate only to find that optionz contracts and etfs side bets will be liquidated to 0 without being honored due to 'black swan' market conditionz - that will be a sign that the crash iz in full effect.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364655164447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:52:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364655276899-7</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil haz an amazing prediction for todayz action</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364556669493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"whose IQ isn't close to any of the shorts on this board, including me." Since only someone with a zero IQ could think that his having started shorting Amazon at $180 and the stock being now over $260 to have been a "smart" move, then this would mean that G's IQ is well above your zero level. "competitive moves by Best Buy. Target, WalMart, Google; impact of gasoline/shipping costs and average order size on profitability, etc)." Yeah, Best Buy pricing products below cost is surely a sustainable strategy that shorts here can count on. And so is Target and Walmart's forcing shoppers to drive to stores to pick up items when gas is priced so highly. "The reality is that your strategy in fighting this scam has been much better than mine." Thanks for being honest here and alluding to the true failure of your "strategy" for once instead of trying to claim that having started shorting from $180 was anything but a dumb move.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1364655276899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:54:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364659772966-8</Id><Topic><Title>Secret AMZN Info Revealed</Title><Username>josephharris479</Username><Timestamp>1363347722710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:42:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice work!</Msg><Username>ronniem88a</Username><Timestamp>1364659772966</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 12:09:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364663548183-9</Id><Topic><Title>Secret AMZN Info Revealed</Title><Username>josephharris479</Username><Timestamp>1363347722710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:42:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thats it!</Msg><Username>burkejosh93</Username><Timestamp>1364663548183</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 13:12:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364669440653-10</Id><Topic><Title>Unfortunately, markets dont crash when everyone expects them to....</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364655164447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:52:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybs: The unexpected move is now for the markets to behave rationally and focus on quality earnings. We'll see. Tech</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1364669440653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 14:50:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364670185314-11</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil haz an amazing prediction for todayz action</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364556669493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazon bears the gas cost because it pays for the last mile. TGT and WMT do not. Further, consumers have plenty of TGT and WMT stores on existing travel routes. Incremental/marginal cost is limited. Amazon's economic model was well suited to high interest rates and low gas costs. We have the opposite and will continue to into the future. You've got the stock price argument (for now). But, on fundies you have nothing.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1364670185314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:03:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364680434213-12</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil haz an amazing prediction for todayz action</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364556669493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tech , Sybil takes everything back - we are both going to do great. Nemisis iz the ultimate contrain top picking clown pumper.... Hold your shorts and double down, its nothing but grey shiez for longz when this idiot showz on a board. If sybs were a long and nemisis showed up then sybs would be scared and angry.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364680434213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364680773265-13</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil haz an amazing prediction for todayz action</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364556669493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tech, Too much focus on fundiez. Fundiez dont matter - its all market mechanics ... Learn how to read charts, momentum, sentiment.... Fundiez are a waste of time because at the end of the day ALL common stox are an unsecured bot driven mechanism whose sole purpose iz to - well you know.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364680773265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:59:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364682162810-14</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil haz an amazing prediction for todayz action</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364556669493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eventually fundamentals matter sybs. You have to pay attention to fundamentals in order to identify what is rational and what is irrational because there are times the scripts get flipped and when they do I have little doubt that the momo scams will lead the way down.</Msg><Username>hapihammer</Username><Timestamp>1364682162810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 18:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364683804393-15</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil haz an amazing prediction for todayz action</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364556669493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except if it were true that incremental costs were limited TGT and WMT would not have been threatened by selling Kindles in their stores. Consumers have come to realize they bear a lot of TGT and WMT's last mile and with higher gas prices this becomes more an more transparent to them. These stores aren't really well located. To save on cost they are purposely located near the edges of cities, not centrally. You must live in a low rent area if you think this. And what ever advantage you described that they had in this, with the change in tax law, Amazon has now moved much closer to the consumer, and so their last mile has just gotten a whole lot shorter an cheaper to fulfill from. For now? I've always had stock price argument since you got here at $180. I'll have it at over $300 when your last crushing margin calls come as well.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1364683804393</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 18:50:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364684049637-16</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil haz an amazing prediction for todayz action</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364556669493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except if fundamentals matter from say the $350 level to say $315 then how does that help someone who is short from $265? Does it mean they get to lose $85 instead of $50? Shorts just don't see how banking on the "fundamentals" can be a losing strategy for them.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1364684049637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 18:54:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364684333582-17</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil haz an amazing prediction for todayz action</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364556669493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nemisis iz the ultimate contrain top picking blah, blah...Hold your shorts and double down, blah, blah..." Nope. I picked no top. Shorts here are the contrarians. They short at $180 and contrary to common sense, doubled down at $220 simply adding to their already huge losses. "when this blah, blah showz on a board." I showed up at $180 and the stock went over $260. When I show up, it is horrible news for shorts, just horrible!</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1364684333582</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 18:58:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364690081227-18</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil haz an amazing prediction for todayz action</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364556669493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The last mile just got a lot shorter" -- your intellect is truly dizzying... Amazon's moves to date do nothing to affect the last mile. It has greatly increased aggregate inventory, reduced inventory turns and reduced ROIC, but it has been unable to offset the rising shipping cost. (All, look at gross shipping as a percent of net sales... increasing. Only internal revenue transfers from Prime in 2012 reduced net and even then, it is higher than net shipping as a % of net sales in 2010, even after significant expansion of facilities... Nem doesn't like the let the facts get in the way of his story (he would fit well on the Amazon sell side). BTW, you must live on another planet claiming Target only locates outside major population centers and are inconvenient... Google Target IN Chicago... or NYC. Or choose your city. Moron. Unless a household is going to buy everything online (not so practical or cost effective), they will still travel to stores as part of life. Few evaluate the fuel cost and even those that do will simply make fewer, larger trips...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1364690081227</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 20:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364690490469-19</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil haz an amazing prediction for todayz action</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364556669493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nemisis you lieing bag of #$%$. You have shown up a the tops of many pumped up pigz .... Including nflx and crm... Sybs haz spanked you down many timez.... Sybs never even showed up here at 180, dummy..... Sybs 1st opening short position waz north of 240 and sybs haz swung this pig to the extent sybilz avg short sell basis iz 265 .... What an idiot.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364690490469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 20:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364690697410-20</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil haz an amazing prediction for todayz action</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364556669493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Except if fundamentals matter from say the $350 level to say $315". You koolaid drinking drunk.... This pig iz pressed to value at 25.00, dummy.... Just because mogan stanley wants to cash in their stock feez north of 300 on pumps in exchange for underwriting this trash doesnt make the fundiez improve, stupit.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364690697410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 20:44:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364691040780-21</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil haz an amazing prediction for todayz action</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364556669493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You have to pay attention to fundamentals in order to identify what is rational and what is irrational" Tech, it doesnt take slogging through a cash flow, balance sheets, and income statements to id a pig... A simple chart with a trend line tellz the whole story when you know what your looking at and understand market mechanics.... Sybil pulled down a 12% year in an up market az a short trader and iz positioned for 2 yearz of compounded 35% plus gainz without the 'story'. That being said, sybs knowz how to analyze fundiez, but people lie about the numberz all the time bro.... You gotta wake up dude.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364691040780</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 20:50:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364695923963-22</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil haz an amazing prediction for todayz action</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364556669493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That wasn't my comment sybs. But, true fundies will break this pig. Extraordinarily vulnerable now. No net cash with almost 50% of cash in Europe. The embedded economic trade off in the business model will continue to move against Scamazon. Gross/Net shipping over time(excluding Prime transfer mathemagic to fool analysts) breaks the story...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1364695923963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 22:12:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364700806872-23</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil haz an amazing prediction for todayz action</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1364556669493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ho clueless are you? If fundamentals matter for this one it won't be going from $350 to $315. Figure it out before you post anymore nonsense.</Msg><Username>hapihammer</Username><Timestamp>1364700806872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 23:33:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>