<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359781252175-1</Id><Topic><Title>At this very moment, sybs is down 8700.00 on a wopping 11300 sharez held short</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359749166741</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:06:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil: "At this very moment, sybs is down 8700.00 on a wopping 11300 sharez held short" Are you sad, Sybil? After waiting for months and getting into the red by almost $400,000, you are just getting closer to breaking even and you're sure this year is going to be your best year? Well, compared to losing so much every year, breaking even seems pretty good, huh?</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1359781252175</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 00:00:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359784799480-2</Id><Topic><Title>This the dumbest message board.</Title><Username>diggo_man</Username><Timestamp>1359668508945</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 16:41:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazon will be approaching $100 by EOY and I will make plenty. I invite all pumpers to stand in the way of it and keep adding. FMR and Capital World and 401Ks everywhere would appreciate it. The only way the markets ever regain the trust of retail investors is if the institutional longs let the MOMO scams die. I think they will recognize their own self interest in doing so...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1359784799480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 00:59:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359806505484-3</Id><Title>more pain for longs--jus beginning! id get out if i were u!</Title><Msg>stupid stock</Msg><Username>bachrachjeff</Username><Timestamp>1359806505484</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:01:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359807512281-4</Id><Title>Barron's is out with support for AMZN this weeked: says 3rd Party sales is the key driver in the future</Title><Msg>And AMZN will move toward being the infrastructure platform of these sales, and slowly diminish ther own % of the sales, thereby continueing to increase gross margins in the future. The story is by Tieran Ray and shown on the bottom of this page. FWIW.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359807512281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:18:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359807890837-5</Id><Title>Another Barron's article mentions AMZN as a top holding of the fund manager: at the bottom as well, bullish in Barron's this weekend.</Title><Msg>mentioned in 2 different places. : Second piece here like it for the Cloud as "icing on the cake."</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359807890837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:24:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359808982913-6</Id><Title>hbf5: I guess the idea would be if you play options game is to mimic the "sellers" around the max pain activiity</Title><Msg>and ride the back of what they are doing, if you play the options game, and never be a buyer of options. At least at the near month. Of course, as you say, that max pain number could float around b/t now and a couple weeks from now. Buying puts in AMZN has been the biggest losing game of all. At least the options call buyer get the support of WS for AMZN the stock, such as you see in Barron's in two different places this weekend.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359808982913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:43:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359809038897-7</Id><Topic><Title>Another Barron's article mentions AMZN as a top holding of the fund manager: at the bottom as well, bullish in Barron's this weekend.</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359807890837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:24:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If 33% mark up and original seller takes 20% 13% left for amzn to pay shipping charge and make a profit. splitting and small profit 2 ways</Msg><Username>rocketman2001ab</Username><Timestamp>1359809038897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:43:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359809337544-8</Id><Topic><Title>Another Barron's article mentions AMZN as a top holding of the fund manager: at the bottom as well, bullish in Barron's this weekend.</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359807890837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:24:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wonder if AMZN will ever get into being it's own shipper: via Natgas powered vehicles ahead for example, planes? Then they could control the front to end distribtuion system for themselves and the 3rd party sellers. A complete plaform of didstribution. interesting concept. You know they are looking at swithing to delivering via Natgas power as that would place less reliance on where oil goes to cost/fufillment pressures.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359809337544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:48:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359809451201-9</Id><Topic><Title>Barron's is out with support for AMZN this weeked: says 3rd Party sales is the key driver in the future</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359807512281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:18:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least to me, the improvement in gross margins this quarter was the key indicator that Bezos might pull off his master plan. That has not be ignored by the Street, this weeks price action was all about options and the put premiums were huge. This coming week should tell the real tale. With all the bearishness on this board, coupled with the fact that many higher flying momo oriented stocks were flat yesterday too, this week should see a nice bounce - if on volume it will be a move up - if for no other reason than to kill all the put premium . . .</Msg><Username>ajmanieri</Username><Timestamp>1359809451201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:50:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359810163198-10</Id><Title>makes no money based upon the last 4 quarters / yet worth billions and billions</Title><Msg>i think amazon is just over priced hulk of a machine</Msg><Username>creativeforce65</Username><Timestamp>1359810163198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 08:02:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359810347769-11</Id><Topic><Title>Barron's is out with support for AMZN this weeked: says 3rd Party sales is the key driver in the future</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359807512281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:18:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"At least to me, the improvemenit in gross margins this quarter was the key indicator that Bezos might pull off his master plan" that or WS has to move to the "gross margin" story as sale increases slow down so that story looks more flimsey. The gross margin story coveniently leaves out the more thatn offsetting fufullment expense increase: which could be a smorgasboard of stuff the might be clasified as "cost of goods sold" in their 3rd party business. More of an accounting of where expenses are placed then anyting else so far: as it allows the hype of the gross margin story. Bottom line: AMZN hasn't achieved the botttom line results that were expected off a couple years ago off the $2.52 peak base of earnings. Whether Bezos is pulling off a vision or WS is merely trying to keep the AMZN bull story intact, time will tell. Tapping the bond market shows they had troulbe funding themselves from internal operations. Option strikes, positions be damned.</Msg><Username>im_too_hipp</Username><Timestamp>1359810347769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 08:05:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359810944304-12</Id><Title>ur insane to buy this stock up here its worth about $30 at most</Title><Msg>scamazn</Msg><Username>bachrachjeff</Username><Timestamp>1359810944304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 08:15:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359812069040-13</Id><Topic><Title>makes no money based upon the last 4 quarters / yet worth billions and billions</Title><Username>creativeforce65</Username><Timestamp>1359810163198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 08:02:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Longs are convinced this will never go down, so it is definitely going to crash at some point in the near future. Not to mention this entire market hinges on trillions upon trillions of government intervention to keep our GDP up to around 2% take them away and we have a massive recession. QE infinity baby!</Msg><Username>pschkqitzsough</Username><Timestamp>1359812069040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 08:34:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359812406721-14</Id><Topic><Title>head and shoulders stock market analyst,</Title><Username>jamivelardifmon951</Username><Timestamp>1307106303000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2011-06-03 09:05:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice site.</Msg><Username>henryjoshep</Username><Timestamp>1359812406721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 08:40:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359814049155-15</Id><Title>Medical Marihuana Inc [Ticker MJNA]</Title><Msg>The stock has been on a tear with 1,100% revenue growth 60% margins and a P/E just under the it is a TRUE growth story.</Msg><Username>pschkqitzsough</Username><Timestamp>1359814049155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:07:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359814168296-16</Id><Topic><Title>Medical Marihuana Inc [Ticker MJNA]</Title><Username>pschkqitzsough</Username><Timestamp>1359814049155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:07:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should have said P/E under 30. 1 cent/share doesn't sound like much but that have 740 Million shares that's a lot of earnings for a company only valued at a quarter billion in a well over 100MM market in the US alone, they also have operations in Europe where the are growing thousands of acres of hemp, hemp is to GROW in the US and no other country in the world (industrial hemp has no THC and is NOT marihuana).</Msg><Username>pschkqitzsough</Username><Timestamp>1359814168296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:09:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359814484661-17</Id><Topic><Title>hbf5: I guess the idea would be if you play options game is to mimic the "sellers" around the max pain activiity</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359808982913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:43:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Re: hbf5: I guess the idea would be if you play options game is to mimic the " Robot Having institionz with statistically significant control of the float like FMR - Fidelity (fido) will buy theze put optionz underwritten by retailerz will buy these thingz up in drovez when retailerz start thinking that they can 'do it like the institutionz do' and sell put optionz... Upon loading up on these trash puts, they will promtly unload their underlying sharez that they have ridden up to the moon for 4.5 yearz solid post nov 2008 and take 0 loss in the selling frenzy az they are 'hedged' by their freshly minted puts underwritten in retailer'z blood... When will retailerz understand that fido can "see" in real time what is going on with the statistically significant portion of the float that they own the same data that takes months for a retailer to see in stale SEC reports.... Here are just a few thingz that Bot runnerz can see on their float control: Margin leverage to the long side from their 3 rd party trade accounts for which they can extrapolate to the universe of the stock float using basic statistics and probabilities Number of sharez loaned to their internal broker desks for shorting and the margin levelz of accounts held short for which they can extrapolate to the universe of the stock float using basic statistics and probabilities All open interest optionz data with nano second number crunching az the set the optimal bet line valuez for option greek variable valuez. And then to boot... Theze idiots managing the HNW client side (the real money for which FMR iz accountable by individual account ownerz and trustees) have a universe of no consequence 2030 "agressive growth" buy high baggie retirement funds that they can unload theze pigs too with one quick phone call to the manager of theze 'retirement funds' that have 0 accountability... retailer that have at least the capacities of fmr that sybs listed above with an armada of robots programmed by the phd that got laid off from nasa and trillionz of dollarz of other peoplez money should by all meanz play optionz... If not, then they should at least recognize that they are a patsy at the card table being dealt from the bottom of the deck. Retailerz that recognize that they would indeed be an option game patsie if they played dont play (ie sybil). Onez that do recognize this and play anyway are sworn crack addicts - they have a differwnt behavioral problem that goez beyond trading options... And ones that dont know they are patsies (ala playerz that tried 3 yearz ago) are broke or will be broke as they keep hitting the optionz crack pipe... Weekly optionz went into play 4 yearz ago, sybil tried them 2 x over that time with some small bets and immediately realized how gamed theze things were, and has been warning people since... They dont get it... Options are derivatives, and retailerz dobt have a chance unless they know how to perform liniear algebra and diff eq's, can control a few key variables with other peoples gun powder, and got A plusses in through 3 or 4 college courses of stats and probabilities at princeton or stamford, and have a MIT rocket scientist code writer input well researched and thought out algos into a bank of the fastest computers on the planet that are plugged directly into the nyse / euronext exchange to limit delay of data Good luck though... Sybs will be routing for you from the sidelines with a bag full of shorts without a time limit.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359814484661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:14:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359815841191-18</Id><Topic><Title>hbf5: I guess the idea would be if you play options game is to mimic the "sellers" around the max pain activiity</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359808982913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:43:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sybil forgot to mention a very important advantage that institutions have over retailerz that dare to play against them in both the stok and particularly the timed optionz areana: A complex communicationz network to the mass media for which to control giganic herdz of sheeples behavior to such a pervasive extreme that they can convince the public massez to buy with a smile at the very tops and sell while they are crying at the very bottoms of markets with a sense of relief that they did so - very powerful : influencing behavior. Couple that with the fact that they have the full backing of the fed as 'too big to fail' and the surety of bring bailed out when they get it wrong without 1 cent of 'moral hazard'. Again, unless you have all of these aformentioned capabilities and / or fully recognize that you dont then you should not play any component of the markets, particularly crack head optionz. Dealing options iz like strapping on a suicide vest, and then posting a video on utube telling the world the date time and place (strike price) that you will blow yourself up... Even a palestinian terrorist iz smarter then that, plus they get 21 virginz in the end where you just end up broke.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359815841191</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:37:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359816099084-19</Id><Topic><Title>Medical Marihuana Inc [Ticker MJNA]</Title><Username>pschkqitzsough</Username><Timestamp>1359814049155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:07:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All though sybs would be long nothing here, this iz a ticker that sybil would have loved to had had a private equity / venture capital stake in! Now this, sybs stoner freinds around the world, iz a 'growth' industry.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359816099084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:41:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359816313509-20</Id><Topic><Title>Medical Marihuana Inc [Ticker MJNA]</Title><Username>pschkqitzsough</Username><Timestamp>1359814049155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:07:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jazz this product up with a little lab generated amonia's and extra's that they put in a pack of camel lights... Through some mary jane c notes redeemable for your next pack, and a pink floyd esq logo and lable on them with a good cartoon characte, and you got yourself a mint... This wheel has already been invented, you dont have to even think about making money in this game - it will print its own.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359816313509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:45:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359816695233-21</Id><Title>Dow UP 149, AMZN DOWN</Title><Msg>I thought this was a premier stock. What happened? The DOW raced up by 149 Points and this DOG didn't move!!! I'm going to find some better stocks to invest.</Msg><Username>stock_selector1</Username><Timestamp>1359816695233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:51:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359817596868-22</Id><Title>AMZN Stock chart looks lousy</Title><Msg>It is pointing to a downtrend. It is going down to 245, where it will test support. Otherwise, it goes down to the next support level at 227. The selling may accelerate as investors rush to hold on to their 48% profit in the past 12 month period.</Msg><Username>bullish1_2</Username><Timestamp>1359817596868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 10:06:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359819948304-23</Id><Topic><Title>Dow UP 149, AMZN DOWN</Title><Username>stock_selector1</Username><Timestamp>1359816695233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like all other shorts here, you don't know what you're playing with. The DOW: Oct 12, 2007 14,016.34 14,101.77 14,013.74 14,093.08 1,787,400 14,093.08 AMZN: Oct 12, 2007 89.42 92.39 88.92 92.37 8,359,900 92.37 (October 12, 2007 was the last time the DOW finished above 14,000 before yesterday.) Good luck to all.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1359819948304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 10:45:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359820335222-24</Id><Topic><Title>The Contrarian Trader - Bearish Video on AMZN</Title><Username>ballnchain8002</Username><Timestamp>1359681792600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 20:23:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good video and refreshingly honest. So refreshing that I signed up. His video prediction in the members area are consistent to what has unfolded although he is carrying a loss on the short side but otherwise making big profits on his long calls.</Msg><Username>nastytrader6098</Username><Timestamp>1359820335222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 10:52:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359820586351-25</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN Stock chart looks lousy</Title><Username>bullish1_2</Username><Timestamp>1359817596868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 10:06:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are absolutely right but it must break 257 37 first.I bought the march 275 puts for 10.90 and im still in</Msg><Username>elbar56</Username><Timestamp>1359820586351</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 10:56:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359823168766-26</Id><Topic><Title>ur insane to buy this stock up here its worth about $30 at most</Title><Username>bachrachjeff</Username><Timestamp>1359810944304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 08:15:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I may make more money if I opened up at lemon aide stand</Msg><Username>rocketman2001ab</Username><Timestamp>1359823168766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 11:39:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359823717939-27</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN Stock chart looks lousy</Title><Username>bullish1_2</Username><Timestamp>1359817596868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 10:06:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>".I bought the march 275 puts for 10.90 and im still in" 265.90 break even, anything between 255.90 and 265.90 on the underlying, you lose on option time decay... You could have a crack at making money if we test the AH lows of 255, but your probably lose on the greeks as crackheadz buy the near the money puts with the 275's you own losing open interest volume increasez.... March may very well be the market peak az the orchestrated effort in the overall markets to get the bags 'in' on massive institutional distribution and to fry the shorts.... With all the scam factorz that go into optionz, sybil cant believe that idiot crack headz are still buying them... Why they simply dont trade the underlying without time or strike decay, worse - why they pay a premium to blow themselvez up, iz waaaaay beyond sybs comprehension... But alas understanding that would be to understand why a crack head usez knowing that its very addictive and unhealthy to do so.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359823717939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 11:48:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359824042744-28</Id><Topic><Title>Another Barron's article mentions AMZN as a top holding of the fund manager: at the bottom as well, bullish in Barron's this weekend.</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359807890837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:24:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After seeing this post think I will start loading up on puts. Do you really think they would have a chance against fdx/ups. NO</Msg><Username>pricewowens</Username><Timestamp>1359824042744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 11:54:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359824123369-29</Id><Topic><Title>Another Barron's article mentions AMZN as a top holding of the fund manager: at the bottom as well, bullish in Barron's this weekend.</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359807890837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:24:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They could also start mfg all the goods they sell too. They could control the world.</Msg><Username>pricewowens</Username><Timestamp>1359824123369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 11:55:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359824258495-30</Id><Title>Find it interesting that in FMR, LLC last 13F . . .</Title><Msg>they were dumping AAPL shares while adding AMZN shares, increased their AMZN holdings by over 600k shares . . . will be interesting to see what the next 13F will reveal . . .</Msg><Username>ajmanieri</Username><Timestamp>1359824258495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 11:57:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359824774795-31</Id><Topic><Title>At this very moment, sybs is down 8700.00 on a wopping 11300 sharez held short</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359749166741</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:06:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"At this very moment, sybs is down 8700.00 on a wopping 11300 sharez held short by sybil_lives . Feb 1, 2013 3:06 PM" Dear Sybil, AMZN's prices on February 1, 2013, around 3 p.m.: time open high low close 3:00 p.m.: 264.47 264.56 264.37 264.52 3:01 p.m.: 264.56 264.56 264.31 264.31 3:02 p.m.: 264.38 264.49 264.30 264.49 3:03 p.m.: 264.43 264.55 264.37 264.46 3:04 p.m.: 264.48 264.50 264.27 264.27 3:05 p.m.: 264.30 264.35 264.17 264.28 3:06 p.m.: 264.28 264.31 264.16 264.26 Assuming that "this very moment" you refer to in your post falls into the period between 3:00 p.m. and 3:06 p.m. (the time of your post's submission for publication), the best price and the worst price for you would have been $264.16 and $264.56, respectively. Let's take the average of these two prices, $264.36, as the price which yields your claimed loss, $8,700, at that "very moment." Then your average short-sell price must to be about $263.59. Even though, it's higher than my estimate of your average short-sell price, I take your word for it because we both know we are gentlemen. Have a nice weekend.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1359824774795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:06:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359827679499-32</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN Stock chart looks lousy</Title><Username>bullish1_2</Username><Timestamp>1359817596868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 10:06:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>im already up on those march puts 4.40 and i have 20 .my broker wants me to get out near 259 but i will get out on the next down day</Msg><Username>elbar56</Username><Timestamp>1359827679499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:54:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359827763951-33</Id><Topic><Title>At this very moment, sybs is down 8700.00 on a wopping 11300 sharez held short</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359749166741</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:06:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Geegee, You dummy... You like to waste time... If you simply read sybs posts then you'd know sybs avg of all shorts iz 264.... Even if this pig were to hit north of 300 all the way to 350 where sybs would only add to the short side and raise sybs short avg.... Try to Imagine the coin that will be accured in sybs Master Margin Trade Account az this pig hits 205, 180, 140, 120, 80, 50, 20... Off of which at any of these levelz except lower then 50, sybil will short any 30-40% rally with 'momo shorts' az this pig collidez with disaster.... Sybil will make a MIN of 30% if sybs decides to cover any shorts under poor timing... If the momo to the downside iz plade correctly by sybil then this will be a 300% er in the short trade .... Timing disaster is much tougher then timing a run up because distaerz happen 15-20x faster then momo trading climbs aza pig deflates and melts away in 3 -6 months what took 10 yearz to pump up.... Watch and learn dummy instead of out smartimg yourself... By the way - if you feel like making a calculation then do these: Last week you 'bought some callz' on wed and thurs. What strike price were your calls that you bought? How many contracts did you buy? How much did you pay per contract? When do they / did the expire? Sybs not clear , did you sell some or all of them? If so, how much did you sell them for? What were you commissions for each transaction that you made? If you can answer all of theze basic questionz then you can keep up with what sybil can do in a daily basis in sybs head with sybs own KISS short, hold and subtract on the rips method of trading pig stox in pig markets... You see - sybil doesnt try to out smart a robot, nor does sybil keep track of any onez but sybs own tradez...</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359827763951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:56:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359828104799-34</Id><Topic><Title>Find it interesting that in FMR, LLC last 13F . . .</Title><Username>ajmanieri</Username><Timestamp>1359824258495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 11:57:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats the report that gives you something useful... Too bad its up to 135 dayz stale, but nonetheless useful. Privately held secretive goliath Fidelity has the ball, watch them as closely as permissible by a retailer, and you have your tells... Sybil guesses that you will see some fmr dumping of this pig on the q4 report due out on or about 2/15, you can looc it up on the SEC website.... But sybs also imaginez that they have been dumping hard (distributing in dieckhead finance termz) from jan 15th and will continue to do so for the next 45 dayz... This data wont be made avalable until july 15th though... Capiche?</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359828104799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:01:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359828628849-35</Id><Topic><Title>Find it interesting that in FMR, LLC last 13F . . .</Title><Username>ajmanieri</Username><Timestamp>1359824258495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 11:57:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you sick logic is flawed . . . first, they are not going to increase their share count by nearly 4% when the stock is trading between 233 to 250 range only to dump near 260-265, chump change . . . second, they are not that short sighted and finally, they were dumping AAPL during the same period . . . what does that tell you? I am sure you will answer bearish to talk yourself into the fact that it will only go down . . . 262 range has been tested at least twice now . . . still in a upward channel . . . this week will give a better indicator if breaking down in short term or moving higher . . .</Msg><Username>ajmanieri</Username><Timestamp>1359828628849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:10:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359830213759-36</Id><Topic><Title>Medical Marihuana Inc [Ticker MJNA]</Title><Username>pschkqitzsough</Username><Timestamp>1359814049155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:07:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next thing ya know.... PBS will be airing "The Kitchen 'Pot' " ....Pastry chefs from around the world making gourmet snicky snacks sold legally on AMZN if you have a friend in Colorado.</Msg><Username>shlockheed</Username><Timestamp>1359830213759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:36:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359831101346-37</Id><Topic><Title>Morgan Stanley Issues $16MM of Securities that Bet on Amazon Move</Title><Username>americanuspublius</Username><Timestamp>1347933378126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:56:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's there, but you have to know how to look for it. It's not on the income statement. It's on the balance sheet. Cash is increased. The proceeds from the cash increases paid in capital in excess of par. You have to look at the retained earnings statement, which is usually in a footnote. That's where much of the $1 Billion increase in capital surplus may have come from. One of the reasons this is a popular technique for high tech companies (and others) to raise cash is that it is not required to be specifically disclosed by the SEC or by GAAP. Could AMZN raise $1 Billion from selling out of the market puts? YES, easily. The market capitalization of AMZN is about $120 billion and the stock trades over a million shares a day. AMZN has 454 million shares outstanding. The January 2014 200 puts sell for about $10, $1000 per 100 shares. Buying a million shares in the market today would cost $265 million. Selling away the right to have 1 million shares put to you at $200 a share would give you $10 million. If forced to buy the shares, the cost would be $210 million, instead of $265 million today. Most of the time out of the money puts expire worthless, so this could be done over and over. AMZN would not be doing this on an options exchange, though, but in an OTC transaction with a trading desk of an investment bank.</Msg><Username>friedlandjt</Username><Timestamp>1359831101346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:51:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359831201314-38</Id><Topic><Title>Morgan Stanley Issues $16MM of Securities that Bet on Amazon Move</Title><Username>americanuspublius</Username><Timestamp>1347933378126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:56:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO, AMZN is not speculating in its own stock. This technique of raising cash is done by tens of high tech firms. Its SOP.</Msg><Username>friedlandjt</Username><Timestamp>1359831201314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:53:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359831676612-39</Id><Topic><Title>Find it interesting that in FMR, LLC last 13F . . .</Title><Username>ajmanieri</Username><Timestamp>1359824258495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 11:57:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"first, they are not going to increase their share count by nearly 4% when the stock is trading between 233 to 250 range only to dump near 260-265, chump change . " Fidelity has owned this since 2003 when it was 20.00, they 'doubled down' in 08-09, the began selling weekliez in '09, and yes they did add in q3 during q2 most likely when it was between 180-205. Sybs gauranteez that fido hasn't spent more then 210 for this pig, save the internal transferz from FMR to the 2030 'agressive growth' 401k baggie fundz north of 250... All this being said this iz 10's of billionz of dollarz of gainz over a very long period, certainly not short term, certainly not 'chump change' "second, they are not that short sighted and finally, they were dumping AAPL during the same period . . . what does that tell you? I am sure you will answer bearish to talk yourself into the fact that it will only go down . . . 262 range has been tested at least twice now . . . still in a upward channel . . . this week will give a better indicator if breaking down in short term or moving higher . . ." It tells sybil that you are a fvck in idiot that iz relying on 135 day old stale data as if transactionz were recorded in real time to make a call... People didnt find out fido dumped a large portion of aapl from jul 1 - sept 30 until Nov 15th, dummy. Just az sheeple wont see what fido did last week until may 15th, from where this pig will collapse completely if fido iz seen az 'dumping' in a stale report. Considering all of the factorz comming to bare on the markets blowing off and the amount of foolz 'Getting in' you are short sighted to think this goez much higher even az the markets continue to run just before muzak stops abtuptly... In a nano second wprld of robot trading, this process doez take a while, but indeed the end iz almost here, dummy... Go ahead and take the baggie risk of 284+ and sybil will meet you down below 50...</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359831676612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 14:01:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359831817655-40</Id><Topic><Title>Medical Marihuana Inc [Ticker MJNA]</Title><Username>pschkqitzsough</Username><Timestamp>1359814049155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:07:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>can you buy smokes and booze tax free on scamazon? The ans no.... Dummy.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359831817655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 14:03:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359834354862-41</Id><Title>anybody else notice how fast gas prices are up lately</Title><Msg>the unleaded future contract for March is up from 2.60 area to close at 3.05 Friday . That's a huge move. Guess part of the price we are gonna pay for all the Fed reserve shananigans. Retail 87 unleaded regular went to a $4 handle today. Expect to start seeing headlines soon about gas prices so the Fed can have their stock bubble.</Msg><Username>im_too_hipp</Username><Timestamp>1359834354862</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 14:45:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359834661740-42</Id><Topic><Title>Morgan Stanley Issues $16MM of Securities that Bet on Amazon Move</Title><Username>americanuspublius</Username><Timestamp>1347933378126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:56:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What happens when the market turns down? Say, a mini 2008/2009. Wouldn't the company risk burning through its cash pile real quick? Leverage goes both way...seems dangerous practice to me. Also, would the practice induce companies to do whatever to keep share prices high? In other words, there is now a focus on share prices rather than the core business.</Msg><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1359834661740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 14:51:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359835040582-43</Id><Topic><Title>Morgan Stanley Issues $16MM of Securities that Bet on Amazon Move</Title><Username>americanuspublius</Username><Timestamp>1347933378126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:56:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please let me know if I am interpreting your comment correctly. I think your meaning is that major mutual fund managers like Fidelity have been selling publicly traded options, both puts and calls, over the past four years. They have sold out of the money puts with great success against passive income generators with thin trading volumes (low float) as the "pigz" moved up in price 6 times above their price at the bottom. They have made huge profits selling weekly puts and calls, most of which expire worthless, to speculators. When some of their holdings look like they will fall in price, they have profitably closed out their positions by buying back the naked puts they sold, sold covered calls against their stock, and opened new positions by buying naked puts sold to them by individual investors on options exchanges. Then, they bought back their covered calls at a profit, sold their stock at a profit, and because of the drop in price caused by the sale of their stock, sold the puts at a huge profit. Fidelity may have done all that with their investments/speculation in GMCR and NFLX. By pigz, do you mean utilities, master limited partnerships, and real estate investment trusts? ======================================================== Note that many mutual funds are structured so that the fund manager may earn revenue from stocks held in the fund by using derivatives and by loaning out the stock for short selling. The profits from those transactions belong ONLY to the fund manager, not to the mutual fund shareholders, unless the mutual fund indenture specifically states that such profits are to go to mutual fund shareholders. In most funds, in return for being allowed to make those profits, the mutual fund manager is obligated to indemnify the fund for losses from derivatives trading and from stock lending.</Msg><Username>friedlandjt</Username><Timestamp>1359835040582</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 14:57:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359836935910-44</Id><Topic><Title>more pain for longs--jus beginning! id get out if i were u!</Title><Username>bachrachjeff</Username><Timestamp>1359806505484</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:01:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you think this was the AAPL board? I've been long since 135, haven't had any pain yet! I sell the spikes, buy the dips, and doubled my mone in AMZN in 2012.</Msg><Username>brucetheparishiltonfan</Username><Timestamp>1359836935910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 15:28:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359837394034-45</Id><Topic><Title>Medical Marihuana Inc [Ticker MJNA]</Title><Username>pschkqitzsough</Username><Timestamp>1359814049155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:07:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, for the past 12 months MJNA has been my money printing machine :)</Msg><Username>pschkqitzsough</Username><Timestamp>1359837394034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 15:36:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359838266767-46</Id><Topic><Title>Morgan Stanley Issues $16MM of Securities that Bet on Amazon Move</Title><Username>americanuspublius</Username><Timestamp>1347933378126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:56:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reminds me of the Nikkei linked bonds in Tokyo in 1989 --- 5 x leveraged. Cant lose more than the principle. To structure this security, the buyers of the bond are effectively selling a put spread in size that is leveraged. The seller of the lower put (MS and other banks) can get hosed if the stock goes well south of 191.73 to bounce around the short put strike which I guess is around 140.... Long live derivatives and financial engineering! This structured ended badly for Bankers Trust and MS in Tokyo when the Nikkei collapsed in 1990. Makes me want to short AMZN.</Msg><Username>buyfreecashflow</Username><Timestamp>1359838266767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 15:51:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359838862017-47</Id><Topic><Title>Morgan Stanley Issues $16MM of Securities that Bet on Amazon Move</Title><Username>americanuspublius</Username><Timestamp>1347933378126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:56:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's so much to comment on here.... Pig stox are not nessesarily utility mlp's all the a shell game, more like the worthless onez trading on thin air, like nflx, crm, gmcr, cmg, amzn, and many more... " In most funds, in return for being allowed to make those profits, the mutual fund manager is obligated to indemnify the fund for losses from derivatives trading and from stock lending." Bull sheit... An 'agressive growth' mutual fund gainz 5% when the market iz up three and losez 8% when the market iz down 3 after absorbing all the risk and reaping marginal gainz relative to that risk... Then when the sheeple open their states on occasion and ask "why?" they are instructed to 'read the prospectus' and to 'consult their financial advisor'. Fidelity iz a multifacited behemouth that rotates stock for the high net worth gutz at tge expense of their retailerz and when they are done they dump the high priced stock from managed accounts back into the market slushfund on pumps and tge remainder of high priced sheit goez into baggie 401ks at tge top to be sold back in a panic at the market bottoms... Fidelity and the enormous bot runnerz are deemed implicitly too big to fail so when their private bets gone bad spill over into fund money for which there iz supposed 'fiduciary responsibility' they would be promptly bailed out without consequence or hazard... Thats the precident the fed haz set... Fidelity being privately held, is to 2013 as goldman which used to be privately held was to 1999... It will end badly for these clownz.... They will follow their own green line right into a PR nightmare soon enough, just like goldman did.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359838862017</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:01:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359839395916-48</Id><Topic><Title>Morgan Stanley Issues $16MM of Securities that Bet on Amazon Move</Title><Username>americanuspublius</Username><Timestamp>1347933378126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:56:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i recall asking u syb sometimes ago what is the average price basis the mutuals own this stock at. weekly option motel rentals are so profitable this scam can't be stopped unless all possible metrics start deteriorating. remove weeklies and this stock will collapse (together with every pig, of course)</Msg><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1359839395916</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:09:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359839750699-49</Id><Topic><Title>Medical Marihuana Inc [Ticker MJNA]</Title><Username>pschkqitzsough</Username><Timestamp>1359814049155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:07:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tax is a good thing. Dummy</Msg><Username>shlockheed</Username><Timestamp>1359839750699</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:15:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359839897080-50</Id><Topic><Title>Morgan Stanley Issues $16MM of Securities that Bet on Amazon Move</Title><Username>americanuspublius</Username><Timestamp>1347933378126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:56:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You want to short AMZN because the deal reflects MS negative sentiments of AMZN ?</Msg><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1359839897080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:18:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359840201125-51</Id><Topic><Title>Another Barron's article mentions AMZN as a top holding of the fund manager: at the bottom as well, bullish in Barron's this weekend.</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359807890837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:24:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Price: The way to #$%$ if capital investments are performing is not to look for a small increase in gross margin. It is to evaluate whether the ROIC is increasing significantly over time. For Amazon, it is dropping and hard. Why? Because Amazon makes less net profit per item sold on 3P versus 1P, yet is adding roughly the same amount of incremental CapEx to service FBA as it would have to internally (actually more, due to inventory optimization theory, but that is for another time...). Looking at gross margins including service revenues when those service revenues drive fulfillment costs but have no cost of product simply isn't intellectually honest. When including fulfillment, the improvement is much smaller (rather than an increase of 3.5%, it would be an increase of 2.4%. Net operating margins are still just 2.2% from 1.7%. Anchor on those numbers are let's hear all the analysts raving about higher margins at 2.2%... The other laughable claim is the massive savings in shipping cost. It isn't happening. Gross shipping cost as a % of revenue have actually increased to 8.45% from 8.41%. Net shipping cost have declined slightly to 4.5% of sales from 5.4% of sales because of revenue transfer from Prime in 2012 that didn't happen in 2011... The gross line is the one that cannot be manipulated (given Amazon's opacity, no one knows how it splits revenue recognition from Prime as far as I can tell). Just wait for the rest of the year to play out and follow these lines... They will get more interesting as time passes. Despite the rhetoric, the regional buildout is not providing the claimed leverage (fulfillment is GROWING as a % of net sales and GROSS shipping is also GROWING as a % of net sales).</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1359840201125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:23:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359840250610-52</Id><Topic><Title>Morgan Stanley Issues $16MM of Securities that Bet on Amazon Move</Title><Username>americanuspublius</Username><Timestamp>1347933378126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:56:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quite the opposite. The underwriters of the deal assume that stock can never get much below 190.... The underwriters are long the 190 and short 140s. Big short option strikes are like magnets... given the way short gamma affects trader behavior. But the deal is too small to matter given the daily volume of AMZN shares.</Msg><Username>buyfreecashflow</Username><Timestamp>1359840250610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:24:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359842055694-53</Id><Topic><Title>Medical Marihuana Inc [Ticker MJNA]</Title><Username>pschkqitzsough</Username><Timestamp>1359814049155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:07:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least learn how to spell marijuana stoner boy!!!</Msg><Username>arkie_golfer</Username><Timestamp>1359842055694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:54:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359842812200-54</Id><Title>Sybs is a fantasy freak</Title><Msg>No one holds a 3,000,000.00 position and talks on the fricking yahoo stock message board. Freak!!!</Msg><Username>arkie_golfer</Username><Timestamp>1359842812200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:06:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359843531038-55</Id><Topic><Title>Another Barron's article mentions AMZN as a top holding of the fund manager: at the bottom as well, bullish in Barron's this weekend.</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359807890837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:24:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nota bene: 1) All prime customers are not created equal. They are not equally profitable. A great analyst would ask how revenue (better yet incremental profit) per Prime customer is changing over time and ask for a cohort analysis of Prime customers as well... Mark this post. This will prove to be a real issue over the next few years... 2) Amazon's GROSS shipping cost as a percent of total revenues will grow this year rather than shrink and its net shipping cost will grow as a % of revenue versus Q4... If you work bottom up, you will see why... 3) Most importantly, the gross margin comp is going to get a lot harder next quarter and throughout the year. While GM sucked in Q42011, it was 24.8% for all of FY 2012... In other words, Q4 did not have magically improved margins from the rest of the year. Q4 was marginally better than the rest of the year. This was simply the one YOY comp that analysts could push to continue the pump and dump... The MM's can keep scaling options and playing financial games, but Amazon is up against fundamental economic constraints that are going to expose all the failings of the business model in 2013. Those who keep playing the game are going to have A LOT of explaining to do, because the flaws in Amazon's economic model are knowable with good DD, even with Amazon's amazing opacity. I am honestly FLOORED that large institutional holders allow Amazon to hide or omit material information (such as sales intensity in states where collecting tax versus those where it is not). I would think that responsible investors would demand vastly more transparency before accumulating a stock trading at north of 30X operating cash flow (operating cash flow which, by the way, only grew 7% in 2012, despite all the hype)... Unlike Bruce, large institutions cannot get out of their position without moving the market. The clock is running out of the scam. Margin comps will be much higher next quarter... They are running out of misplaced metrics to anchor people on... Have a good weekend...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1359843531038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:18:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359844351406-56</Id><Topic><Title>Sybs is a fantasy freak</Title><Username>arkie_golfer</Username><Timestamp>1359842812200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:06:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They do when they hold $3.5 mil marginable down to 40% on the short side 35 on the long, and a net worth of 12 mil, dummy.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359844351406</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:32:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359845483248-57</Id><Topic><Title>Sybs is a fantasy freak</Title><Username>arkie_golfer</Username><Timestamp>1359842812200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:06:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sybils how fast do u think amzn falls an where do u cover also do u see the markets correcting this week thanks</Msg><Username>xdon69</Username><Timestamp>1359845483248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:51:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359851011759-58</Id><Topic><Title>Sybs is a fantasy freak</Title><Username>arkie_golfer</Username><Timestamp>1359842812200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:06:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You probably have 3500.00 account like everyone else on these message boards, quit living in a fantasy world.</Msg><Username>arkie_golfer</Username><Timestamp>1359851011759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 19:23:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359854919949-59</Id><Topic><Title>Another Barron's article mentions AMZN as a top holding of the fund manager: at the bottom as well, bullish in Barron's this weekend.</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359807890837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:24:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMZN is protected. It can't go down. Safe money going to $700 to GOOG and AAPL level.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1359854919949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 20:28:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359855334991-60</Id><Topic><Title>Morgan Stanley Issues $16MM of Securities that Bet on Amazon Move</Title><Username>americanuspublius</Username><Timestamp>1347933378126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:56:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sybil_lives, thank you for your reply. You use so much slang and unique spellings, it takes me a lot of time to understand your meaning. Did what I wrote express what you meant? The fund managers who make profits on derivatives upon stocks held in their mutual funds, that also make good to the fund when they produce losses, are much smaller than Fidelity. I agree that many of the employees and managers of Fidelity have likely given into the temptations of making easy money from the accounts held with them.</Msg><Username>friedlandjt</Username><Timestamp>1359855334991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 20:35:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359855386827-61</Id><Topic><Title>Medical Marihuana Inc [Ticker MJNA]</Title><Username>pschkqitzsough</Username><Timestamp>1359814049155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:07:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo usually bleeps out the correct spelling which is why I use the alternate spelling. However, they have received thousands of complaints and may have changed that. And by the way, marihuana and marijuana are considered correct spellings.</Msg><Username>pschkqitzsough</Username><Timestamp>1359855386827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 20:36:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359855481125-62</Id><Topic><Title>Another Barron's article mentions AMZN as a top holding of the fund manager: at the bottom as well, bullish in Barron's this weekend.</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359807890837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:24:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, the math will work even better on that than Amazon's existing business... What everyone misses when talking about NG engines is the upfront ENERGY investment required in replacing fleets. UPS and FedEx should raise prices on Amazon to much higher levels. Amazon has ZERO choice but to use them (or risk its brand with the USPS...), but is trying to disintermediate them over the longer term. With retail matching prices, Amazon simply cannot afford delivery risk... Let Amazon raise $20B to build out its own delivery fleet.... I'm gonna enjoy watching Amazon get slammed from all sides. That's the problem with lack of focus and a zero profit strategy. It makes everyone your competitor or enemy...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1359855481125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 20:38:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359856144468-63</Id><Topic><Title>Another Barron's article mentions AMZN as a top holding of the fund manager: at the bottom as well, bullish in Barron's this weekend.</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359807890837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:24:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I'm gonna enjoy watching Amazon get slammed from all sides." Are you gonna just watch the show because you don't have any more money to buy puts? Hahaha . . .</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1359856144468</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 20:49:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359856698773-64</Id><Topic><Title>Sybs is a fantasy freak</Title><Username>arkie_golfer</Username><Timestamp>1359842812200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:06:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"sybils how fast do u think amzn falls an where do u cover also do u see the markets correcting this week thanks" Sybil and all other shorts here, including you, end up being AMZN's fertilizer. Sybil has been shorting from November 16 last year non-stop, starting from $220. Check his post. She's as clueless as any other shorts here.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1359856698773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 20:58:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359856917834-65</Id><Title>amazon puts 1 million people out of work</Title><Msg>and loses money, geeeez, The are everything wrong with america</Msg><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1359856917834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 21:01:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359857840632-66</Id><Topic><Title>Sybs is a fantasy freak</Title><Username>arkie_golfer</Username><Timestamp>1359842812200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:06:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil may cover a little, but iz already 1000 lightened in sybs original load from AH on bezos story telling day at 257. Sybil really doesnt plan on covering in any meaning until south of 180, and even then - only a nominal amount for a swing trade.... On that note, even though sybil wont trade it, sybs sees this thing bottoming in the upper 250's before trying to make a final bid at the pump... That being said, this pig could head south and not stop until 180... Thats why sybs in now hurry to attempt a swing trade for a couple og bux... Sybs done that in the past with too many shares on nflx and missed a big chunk of the drop 120 to 190 with sharez that sybil had to reshort .... 'Trading' sux, sybs target is 125 before covering in earnest, and 50-80 to walk away unless there was a pop like nflx just had.... Sybil just reupped nflx shorts 1500 base loaded at 165, and another 300 at 170....</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359857840632</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 21:17:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359857932932-67</Id><Topic><Title>amazon puts 1 million people out of work</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1359856917834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 21:01:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>John Deere put a lot more people out of work. A man with a tractor can farm 5 times as much land as a man without a tractor. All those farmer out of work! How terrible is that? We have plenty of food without having to work all day. That's so bad for America.</Msg><Username>brucetheparishiltonfan</Username><Timestamp>1359857932932</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 21:18:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359861794364-68</Id><Topic><Title>Another Barron's article mentions AMZN as a top holding of the fund manager: at the bottom as well, bullish in Barron's this weekend.</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359807890837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:24:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep laughing. You'll be served soon...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1359861794364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 22:23:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359862851347-69</Id><Title>PLEASE DO NOT CHASE..OVERVALUED</Title><Msg>on every metric</Msg><Username>biglefthook_00</Username><Timestamp>1359862851347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 22:40:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359863439302-70</Id><Title>Welcome to new shorts here.</Title><Msg>Thank you for coming over willingly to become the next batch of organic fertilizer for AMZN, the greatest stock in the Universe. She needs lots of fertilizer to sustain her steady growth. Shorts, you're the backbone of America. Thank you.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1359863439302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 22:50:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359864298540-71</Id><Title>living social</Title><Msg>is driving the stock price tell me i am wrong</Msg><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1359864298540</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:04:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359864705019-72</Id><Topic><Title>Welcome to new shorts here.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1359863439302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 22:50:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Geege, You must be aware that for every new share shorted, an additional long share is "created". For each short share, two people will show a long position in their account for that share; the person from whom the share was borrowed (to lend to the short seller) and the person who bought the share from the short seller. Therefore, two people think they own that share, and each brokerage account will reflect that they own the share. Therefore, for each shorted share, there are two potential share owners (who could decide to sell). Therefore a squeeze is just as likely to occur in either direction, depending on who has the upper hand that day.</Msg><Username>jeffpmpccea</Username><Timestamp>1359864705019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:11:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359867179015-73</Id><Title>AMZN should be downgraded</Title><Msg>The ways they upgraded AMZN after earning was so funny, I was in disbelieved. Many analysts rushed to discount all misses but talked so highly on operating margin. The true is AMZN not that great company and it should not deserve to be this price. I shorted AMZN, and I will hold on to it for the next few months.</Msg><Username>tt_hongloan203</Username><Timestamp>1359867179015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:52:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359867576398-74</Id><Topic><Title>Welcome to new shorts here.</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1359863439302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 22:50:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't you have to do some pushups for your young ladyfriend?</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1359867576398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:59:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>