<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-09-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379156735639-1</Id><Topic><Title>Shop By Local: Find national brands, locally, with the worlds most relevant local search engine, Krillion</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1376825608369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 07:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Message from Local Corp to Retailers: Increase visibility and reach more local shoppers Now you can promote your products across a vast network of high-quality, location-based publishers and partners by including your national and local store assortment in the Krillion® localization engine. Engage highly motivated local shoppers online! Optimize Your Advertising: Reach a more qualified local buyer through our network of local and national partners, and drive both online and in-store purchases. Drive More Qualified Sales: Capture online shoppers who are ready to buy with our real-time StockCheck™ technology. Increase In-Store Traffic: Direct buyers to local stores that have the products they’re looking for in stock.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1379156735639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 07:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379161748211-2</Id><Title>Hello, kidz - sybs here after a bit of an absense from the scamazon community of board basherz and short traderz</Title><Msg>Sybs been working the pigflix and high fly-in travling piggy pcln boardz for a bit. Sybil will also have you know that sybby haz been VERY busy working in this BOOMING economic bernanke bubble recovery. After more study of bit coin stok markets, the fed plan, and bezos the man sybil haz come to the following conclusion: All three match the great albert einsteinz definition of insanity which iz az followz: Repeating the same mistakes while expecting a different outcome. Bit coin stok markets: use the same debt leverage, derivitavez, and pumped up algos that led to the the crash of 2000 and 2008 will not result in an putcome any different then any other crash beit 1929 bucket shops, 2000 ipo's of worthless stox, or 2008's realestate hops. The fed induced bubble: at no point in history haz government intervention been proven to 'fix' the markets, in fact they have made subsequent crashez more pronounced and severe, beit the early 70's comming off the gold standard bit coin , greenspanz 'irrational exhuberance bubble', and now the fed induced bernanke bubble that iz pouring gasoline on the fire pyre built by hiz predecessorz. And finally, bezos the man: repeating the EXACT same mistake az 1995-2000 - revenue growth at all cost and without profit at the expense of putting ligit business out of business, never to make earningz for share holderz and wasting hiz money (which should be the share holderz money) on stupid sideline venturez . This led to the amzn stok collapse from 100 to 5 in 2000, never to turn a profit, hurting the consumer economy, while wasting personal wealth on space travel and print newz paperz. Conclusion: short scamazon, short the bit coin markets, subtract the rips, and cover the crash bottom of 2015.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379161748211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 08:29:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379167300420-3</Id><Topic><Title>Hello, kidz - sybs here after a bit of an absense from the scamazon community of board basherz and short traderz</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379161748211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 08:29:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil: "Conclusion: short scamazon, short the bit coin markets, subtract the rips, and cover the crash bottom of 2015." But you were saying earlier last year (2012), the entire market (and AMZN) would collapse this year (2013)!</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1379167300420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 10:01:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379172694637-4</Id><Title>Anyone now gettting daily sales email from AMAN</Title><Msg>Never before have I gotten a daily email promotion from Amazon, until the last 3 weeks or so. (Sure before I might get an email when I clicked on a product that took me to the site from somewhere else....) And early this week they send me a promo for laptop sales that included free 12 month financing. Am I just new to this aspect of marketing or is everyone now getting this.......did Amazon just start this marketing invention or are they trying to drive sales harder in this week quarter?? Would be interesting to know</Msg><Username>bnmcpa</Username><Timestamp>1379172694637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 11:31:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379176512647-5</Id><Topic><Title>Time to sell AMZN regardless your cost, seriously.</Title><Username>leland_chen</Username><Timestamp>1367428782648</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMZN: May 1, 2013 253.90 254.20 245.75 248.23 4,391,400 248.23</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1379176512647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 12:35:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379176858689-6</Id><Title>AMZN may start sagging for the next few days.</Title><Msg>I think breaking $298 yesterday was bad. I'll be monitoring this interesting situation carefully.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1379176858689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 12:40:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379180092060-7</Id><Title>Ahhhhh yes. What would the scamazon boardz be without sybil H8erz and sybil basherz</Title><Msg>Geegee and casback quick with to reply back responsez az they exhibit utter frustation with getting whipsawed in the piggy markets. Theze poor slobz couldnt call white az white or black az black on their best dayz, so understanding shadez of gray iz nearly an impossibility for theze retreadz. Sybil haz consistantly stated time and again, that 'timing' the market, particularly with crackhead suicide optionz iz a foolz game, yet they still attempt to do exactly this, and get beat like bongoz. Sybil haz said repeatedly that a market top iz a "process" by which bitcoin stox are converted back to bernanke bux of the many by the few who were rich and became richer az moral hazard waz tossef out the window while implicit and explicit bailouts were ushered through the front door. In response, all theze knuckleheadz can say iz "sybil, you said 284 wouls be the top for amazon, you lost , you were wrong, we are broke, we hate you sybil." Geegee and cashback, Sybil understandz your frustration, but you must take ownership of your own stupidity and lossez without lashing out at otherz and projecting your self created misery into a wish for sybby'z demise ... The down fall of sybil, the losing of sybs housez, the margin callz sybil would get are mere figments of your imaginationz and a reflection of your own pain. Its ashame what bit coin markets that operate without moral hazard do az they transfer the wealth of the many to the few by proxy of worthless digital stox . Az can be seen with geegee and cashback's posts, the bitcoin markets are a net negative on society az a whole az people that lack forsight, education and intelligence degrade and become angry, broke, and beligerent.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379180092060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 13:34:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379184181852-8</Id><Topic><Title>Hello, kidz - sybs here after a bit of an absense from the scamazon community of board basherz and short traderz</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379161748211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 08:29:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Considering the 10 yr T bill JUMPED from 1.91% to 2.91% in a matter of 5 weeks time from may st to june 15th and have been stuck there since with no hope for would be borrowerz of ever going back to "historic lowz " in our lifetimez, yes 15% interest rates on mortgagez and car loanz secured with leinz on the hard assets iz not out of the question - that will be 2018.... 10 yr t bill Interest rates will waffle and continue to rise from 2.19-8% between now and 2016 az the markets crash, and once the crash due to leverage and money printing iz done , those 10 year rates will SHOOT up to 12-15% or higher in a NASTY bout of stagflation az we CRAWL out of a fed induced depression that lasts for YEARZ to come. This sermon iz over, go in peace stupid. Amen.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379184181852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 14:43:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379192814724-9</Id><Topic><Title>Sybby just shorted a TRUCK LOAD of this trash at 285</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1376920563107</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 09:56:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil: "Giddy the fvck up! This pig iz going in the TANK - FINALLY!" Define "FINALLY," please, Sybil. It's been almost a month since you posted the above. Now, don't tell us that you don't time the market because if you're not timing the market, you wouldn't be shorting anything ever.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1379192814724</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 17:06:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379193287137-10</Id><Topic><Title>Those that laugh last, laugh the hardest of all fvck erz</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1377287020992</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-23 15:43:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil, what did you do with these 2,500 shares of NFLX you shorted on August 23, 2013? This past week, weren't you telling people on the NFLX message board that NFLX is going much higher and you will short after the shorts there get killed?</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1379193287137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 17:14:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379196198787-11</Id><Title>On terrible dayz sybil likes to "help" idiots that are getting killed and sitting beside themselvez</Title><Msg>You'll often find sybby pouring verbal gasoline on a fire by shouting "COVER. YOU MUST COVER BEFORE YOUR BROKERZ DO IT FOR YOU" On a short squuuuueeeeze run. But more often then not sybby iz shorting while otherz are covering and buying when otherz are selling. Sybil iz short GOBZ of pig flix and pcln az of last week , highest shorts being 310 and 883, respectively.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379196198787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 18:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379197824840-12</Id><Topic><Title>On terrible dayz sybil likes to "help" idiots that are getting killed and sitting beside themselvez</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379196198787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 18:03:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil, what's the average selling price of your AMZN short now? And how big is your AMZN short GOBZ?</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1379197824840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 18:30:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379198154912-13</Id><Title>Why do you ask geegee?</Title><Msg>Do have a little dieock complex are you broke, or both?</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379198154912</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 18:35:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379202639067-14</Id><Topic><Title>Why do you ask geegee?</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379198154912</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 18:35:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil: "Why do you ask geegee?" Why don't you answer, Sybil? You used to be eager to post such information as the size of position and the average cost, without being asked by anybody.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1379202639067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-14 19:50:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>