<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-29"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372520533689-1</Id><Title>Cramer: DuPont Is The MOST INNOVATIVE COMPANY He Knows??!</Title><Msg>Percussive Pint-Sized Performer Continues To Fawn Over &amp; Cheer Ms. Kullman, DuPont Chieftess THE WEAK IN REVIEW Readers, the louder this elfin entertainer on CNBC screeches to promote Ellen J. Kullman, the less credibility he has. All week long, he clattered and battered his audience with outright misleading, if not dishonestly deceptive praises for this shriveled chemical and seeds conglomerate based in the dwarf state of Delaware. Yesterday, Friday June 28, 2013, he air-horned investors with this incredible hype: "It's [DuPont] become the single most innovative company I know of. The corporate culture is all about using science to tackle some of the toughest challenges out there and transform society." Come on! More "innovative" than Apple? More "innovative" than Amazon"? More "innovative" in seeds than Monsanto? BASF in chemicals? This T.V. faker is abetting Ms. Kullman &amp; her mediocre TEAM of circa 100 DuPont Presidents and Vice Presidents in downplaying and covering up the sheer magnitude of their colossal FAILURES in "Innovation": The ongoing multi-$billion losses from tree-killing DuPont Imprelis, from DuPont OptimumGAP, a GM seed trait flop. A truly "innovative" company does not produce and hide the largest, most costly new product failure in 21st century corporate America. Imprelis, Tell Us! And the Harvard-educated Mr. Cramer surely knows this! Merely THE WEAK IN REVIEW digitally penned by one individual retail investor, who is determined not to hide a damn thing when it comes to this faltering and failing, shrinking and sinking Delaware conglomerate...funfun..</Msg><Username>funfundvierzig</Username><Timestamp>1372520533689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:42:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372522608397-2</Id><Title>Biggest Divergence on Nasdaq</Title><Msg>flankenking flankenking • Jun 14, 2013 5:37 AM Flag0 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 0 Reply Local Corp’s (market-cap = 38 million) development of Unique Visitors on the flagshipsite (Souce: Siteanalytics) Local Corp’s development of Unique Visitors on the flagshipsite (Souce: Siteanalytics) Local Corp’s development of Unique Visitors: 11/2012: 18,745,842 Monthly Unique Visitors 12/2012: 22,738,206 Monthly Unique Visitors 01/2013: 26,410,927 Monthly Unique Visitors 02/2013: 24,017,605 Monthly Unique Visitors 03/2013: 24,427,755 Monthly Unique Visitors 04/2013: 23,785,928 Monthly Unique Visitors 05/2013: 27,804,187 Monthly Unique Visitors And there are additional more than 12 million Monthly Unique Visitors from the Network, which are not part of the numbers above) = together about 40 million Monthly Unique Visitors in May.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372522608397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:16:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372525234502-3</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Divergence on Nasdaq</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372522608397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why the valuation of Local Corp with lower than 40 million is one of the biggest jokes the Nasdaq had ever seen The Inflection Point of Local Corp is Now • Five material challenges in 24 months withstood »Significant cost to the company in revenue and earnings • Highest revenue per employee ever »Projected growth to about $900k per employee EOY »Running lean! • Returning to profit »Significant cost savings starting 1Q13 »Achieved 1Q13 Positive Adjusted EBITDA »Achieved positive cash from operations from 1Q13 Reuters: Local Corp Issues FY 2013 Guidance; Revenue Guidance In Line With Analysts' Estimates Local Corp Issues FY 2013 Guidance; Revenue Guidance In Line With Analysts' Estimates Thursday, 9 May 2013 04:15pm EDT Local Corp announced that for fiscal 2013, it expects revenue of between $93 million and $95 million and adjusted EBITDA to be at least $5 million. According to I/B/E/S Estimates, analysts are expecting the Company to report revenue of $95 million and EBITDA of $5.80 million for fiscal 2013.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372525234502</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:00:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372525597558-4</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Divergence on Nasdaq</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372522608397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Patents and Patent Applications of Local Corp Owner* Short Title Country Status Application/ Issuance Number Filing Date Inventors Searches Assisted by Multi-Level Menus Issued 7,062,453 08/31/2000 Heath B. Clarke Search Selections with Supplier Information Issued 7,890,378 12/14/2005 Heath B. Clarke Rewarding User For Search Selections Pending 12/985,277 01/05/2011 Heath B. Clarke Dynamic adjustment of Telephone Listings Issued 7,596,218 05/30/2003 William A. Montemer Dynamic adjustment of Telephone Listings Issued 8,306,208 08/07/2009 William A. Montemer Dynamic adjustment of Telephone Listings Pending 13/669,870 11/06/2012 William A. Montemer Directory assistance using keywords Issued 7,200,413 07/30/2003 William A. Montemer, Heath B. Clarke Bidding for directory assistance Issued 7,715,857 03/23/2006 William A. Montemer, Heath B. Clarke Bidding for Directory Assistance Issued 8,359,049 03/25/2010 William A. Montemer, Heath B. Clarke Using Rules to Influence Search Results Pending 11/302,506 12/12/2005 William Bertovich, Stephen Ely, Heath B. Clarke Determining A Search Center Pending 11/302,412 12/12/2005 William Bertovich, Stephen Ely Advertising based on Semantical Keywords Pending 11/452,607 06/13/2006 Ian Harcourt Niles, Heath B. Clarke Bulk Web Domain Generation Issued 8,312,125 03/12/2010 Adam Rioux Bulk Web Domain Generation Pending 3/675,340 11/13/2012 Adam Rioux Geocoding related Webpages Issued 7,231,405 01/10/2005 Sam Xia Indexing Found Geocodes with Webpages Issued 7,822,705 06/11/2007 Sam Xia Indexing Found Geocodes with Webpages Issued 8,176,082 09/22/2010 Sam Xia Search Engine Indexing Techniques Pending 13/438,339 04/03/2012 Sam Xia Provision Of Localized Shopping Based On Geocodes Issued 8,032,427 04/03/2007 Roger Spreen System for Providing Localized Shopping Information Pending 13/238,489 09/21/2011 Roger Spreen Methods and Sy</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372525597558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372525905093-5</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened To Sybil/Trannyboy Waiting Till 245 To Post Again??????</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1372176106859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:01:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes stinky, tell him............</Msg><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1372525905093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:11:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372529804666-6</Id><Title>AMZN = Ponzi scheme, using a better name as "business",</Title><Msg>so long as it can hold others' hope that it will be making lots of money, this Ponzi scheme can keep going for a long long time! even grocery business is used to grow its top line, which is the only thing AMZN has been consistently growing for years. I believe AMZN is going to get into automobile dealer business soon, THAT will really grow its BUSINESS!! based in Seattle, why not getting into selling Boeing 787?!</Msg><Username>bc66620</Username><Timestamp>1372529804666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:16:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372532573797-7</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened To Sybil/Trannyboy Waiting Till 245 To Post Again??????</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1372176106859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:01:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh no, stalker/briar timeout....................</Msg><Username>skiidady7</Username><Timestamp>1372532573797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:02:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372533731039-8</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Divergence on Nasdaq</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372522608397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lori Chavez comes from Local Corp Debunking 4 Local Advertising Myths 6/21/2013 - MediaPost by Lori Chavez Fact or fiction – local advertising is a waste of online marketing dollars? If you answered fact, you could be missing a potential $38 billion market opportunity. The challenge is how do brands take advantage of deploying the right tools to reach and engage local consumers. Not everyone gets it right. Of all the misconceptions brand marketers have about ad networks and local advertising, perhaps the most critical is that it can’t be done well. In reality, it’s been something of an after-thought. As a result, some brands don’t embrace the nuanced approach necessary to target those markets in a way that drives desired results. Today, it’s essential to debunk some of the long-standing myths that are holding local advertisers back from success in their local market. Here are four brands need to know to avoid the pitfalls of misinformation</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372533731039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372534270957-9</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer: DuPont Is The MOST INNOVATIVE COMPANY He Knows??!</Title><Username>funfundvierzig</Username><Timestamp>1372520533689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:42:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cramer likes it that means sell</Msg><Username>xdon69</Username><Timestamp>1372534270957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:31:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372535719442-10</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Divergence on Nasdaq</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372522608397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EBTIDA will increase to 2.5 million in Q2/2013 from 0.6 million in Q1/2013 Why? Read the both threads “Lower expenses in Q2 (and in the following quarte) through a non-recurring of $900,000” and and “The revenues in Q2/2013 will increase to about 24 million from 21.755 million in Q1/2013”!</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372535719442</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372535778433-11</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Divergence on Nasdaq</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372522608397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The result is on a yearly base of P/E of idiotic low 3.8.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372535778433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:56:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372536091614-12</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer: DuPont Is The MOST INNOVATIVE COMPANY He Knows??!</Title><Username>funfundvierzig</Username><Timestamp>1372520533689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:42:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>xdon, Sell, indeed! Jim Cramer Celebrates Coach Kullman! Obnoxious Non-Stop Gushing Distorts and Deceives Unsuspecting Investors! Good Afternoon, Bonsoir, Guten Abend, Readers, in follow-up crowing late yesterday morning, "Top CEOs Talk Success With Cramer", June 28, 2013, CNBC's elfin entertainer gushes that CEOs like Ellen "you-know, you-know" Kullman should be celebrated like coaches. Coaches "set the tone", he proclaims. Well, if that is the case, DuPont's Head Coach, the one who has been calling all the big plays for the past four years, should be sacked for going with DuPont Imprelis. Never once does the silly Cramer mention his American Idol has commanded and directed the most disastrous, most costly new product failure in 21st century corporate America. DuPont Imprelis is nothing short of a multi-$billion consumer FRAUD. Why the sneaky cover-up, misleading and deceptive to viewers and listeners? $Billions in cogent claims of fraud and massive losses are a matter of public record in numerous federal and state courts across the land. To read more, GOOGLE "DuPont Imprelis Litigation" or "DuPont Imprelis Fraud". "Mad Money" should be renamed, "Bad Money", for there is no integrity of journalism on this pop stock show. Merely the afternoon comments and opining of one independently-speaking investor and long-time student of the conning DuPont conglomerate...funfun..</Msg><Username>funfundvierzig</Username><Timestamp>1372536091614</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 16:01:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372539180749-13</Id><Title>Skiidady and geegee are off to the alter today after the supreme court decided in favor of same-sex marriage</Title><Msg>They are gonna celebrate with a quite wedding, dumpster dive behind taco bell for a reception, and then sneak back to geegee's LA ghetto tenament for a wild night of circle jerking.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1372539180749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 16:53:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372556033857-14</Id><Title>Skiidady iz a pitcher while geegee lovingly catchez</Title><Msg>Neither admits their inner desirez, therefor they lashout at otherz in frustration and anger.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1372556033857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>