<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367149585959-1</Id><Topic><Title>Would one of you optionz crackheadz on the board help 'ol sybil out with a quick question?</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1366891118384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:58:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't speak for all crackheads... I typically trade puts pre-earnings. My thought process is I can limit my downside to the option premium and hope for a big downward move off earnings. So Sybil, maybe you can enlighten me. Do you really think that institutions would invest billions so they could manipulate the stock price in a effort to keep a few $$$ in premiums? Seems far fetched to me.</Msg><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1367149585959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 07:46:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367150700458-2</Id><Title>I can't fully express how happy I am</Title><Msg>to see the market begin to come to its sense regarding the value of this low-margin distributor. There's just no way this company should be trading where it is. More like $40 - 60 per share and even at that level it's a speculative bet on the future.</Msg><Username>radar_the_kat</Username><Timestamp>1367150700458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367153618547-3</Id><Title>Help me God, help AMZN go to 274</Title><Msg>it has been a torture....down 7% in a day</Msg><Username>kotharivk</Username><Timestamp>1367153618547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:53:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367154754361-4</Id><Title>do not lose your heart</Title><Msg>amzn is not going down; it will come back up; 16 billion in sales in a quarter</Msg><Username>kotharivk</Username><Timestamp>1367154754361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 09:12:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367155012377-5</Id><Title>amzn is best</Title><Msg>buy when it is down it is going to go up above 300</Msg><Username>kotharivk</Username><Timestamp>1367155012377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 09:16:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367157219500-6</Id><Title>AMZN will fall below $100/share</Title><Msg>in the next 2 years. This is the just the beginning of the decline. Make sure you have your STOP orders in place. A loss of 8% is recoverable, but a loss of 70% will put you in a hole that is extremely difficult to get out of.</Msg><Username>stock_selector1</Username><Timestamp>1367157219500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 09:53:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367157277689-7</Id><Topic><Title>amzn is best</Title><Username>kotharivk</Username><Timestamp>1367155012377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 09:16:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet it hits $200 before it hits $300!</Msg><Username>jackiejones569</Username><Timestamp>1367157277689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 09:54:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367157492028-8</Id><Topic><Title>I can't fully express how happy I am</Title><Username>radar_the_kat</Username><Timestamp>1367150700458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I share the same opinion. AMZN has been OVERPRICED for quite a few years. Investors are just realizing it... As the price decline accelerates, more investors will join the ones who harbor a NEGATIVE sentiment with respect to this stock. Just look at Apple - investors and analysts LOVED it at 700/share, raising some estimates to over 1000. Now that it has fallen to 390, they are ALL negative and hate the stock. This is what is going to happen to Amazon. Just wait and see...</Msg><Username>bullish1_2</Username><Timestamp>1367157492028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 09:58:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367159035724-9</Id><Topic><Title>I can't fully express how happy I am</Title><Username>radar_the_kat</Username><Timestamp>1367150700458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMZN = hope of a rosy future, far far down the road. Want proof? Earning has been on the decline for the last two years. The company has been in operation for 25 years and still cannot pay a dividend because it did not make any money in 2012. At 255/sh, there are still a lot of believers out there...of one day going to paradise to enjoy 1000 virgins!</Msg><Username>nje457</Username><Timestamp>1367159035724</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 10:23:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367159507591-10</Id><Topic><Title>I can't fully express how happy I am</Title><Username>radar_the_kat</Username><Timestamp>1367150700458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When companies that PRINT money like Apple are in decline, imagine how strained the patience of big investors is on AMZN. They have some very profitable business units, yet a number are very unprofitiable. The two cancel one another out. They intend to spend even MORE money on unprofitable ventures, so the profitable sector, which is merchandise sales, will eventually see competition. Imagine if EBAY chooses to create an international warehousing of goods to copy Amazon? It will destroy Amazon, and if its not EBAY, it will be Google or someone else.</Msg><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1367159507591</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 10:31:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367159603577-11</Id><Title>May 3 Puts at 255 can be bought very cheaply</Title><Msg>Invest $4 to make $30 this week. Amazon will touch 220 at some point this coming week.</Msg><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1367159603577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 10:33:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367161217230-12</Id><Title>Big Deals of Competitor Spreebird</Title><Msg>Scrunchy Butt Bikinis $19 for Two Scrunchy Butt Bikinis ($80 Value) Over 30 Styles to Choose From! Time Remaining 4 days, 13 hrs, 34 mins 112 Bought Top of the Notch Restaurant $19 -- Mt. Baldy: Unlimited Breakfast w/Lift Ride, Reg. $40 Time Remaining 8 days, 5 hrs, 36 mins 1,212 Bought Deal Partner Travelzoo Clarisonic Facial Brush Heads $25 for Two Clarisonic Replacement Facial Brush Heads ($60 Value) Time Remaining 13 hrs, 33 mins, 38 secs 262 Bought Deo Juvante Yacht Charters $45 -- Newport: Sunset Yacht Cruise for 2 w/Drinks &amp; Apps Value $140 Time Remaining 4 days, 2 hrs, 53 mins 288 Bought Deal Partner Travelzoo From You Flowers $15 for $30 of Flowers, Balloon Bouquets &amp; More with From You Flowers Time Remaining 5 days, 10 hrs, 52 mins 81 Bought Limited Quantity Available OC Foodies and Fashionistas Event $25 -- OC Food, Wine &amp; Fashion Launch Event Ticket, Half Off Time Remaining 2 hrs, 51 mins, 6 secs 138 Bought Deal Partner Travelzoo</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1367161217230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367164671462-13</Id><Topic><Title>amzn is best</Title><Username>kotharivk</Username><Timestamp>1367155012377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 09:16:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just dont bet the farm.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1367164671462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 11:57:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367164732968-14</Id><Topic><Title>amzn is best</Title><Username>kotharivk</Username><Timestamp>1367155012377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 09:16:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"buy when it is down it is going to go up above 300" All righty then.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1367164732968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 11:58:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367164859122-15</Id><Topic><Title>Help me God, help AMZN go to 274</Title><Username>kotharivk</Username><Timestamp>1367153618547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:53:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"it has been a torture....down 7% in a day" Unfortunately the pain haz yet to begin. That pain that you feel now iz merely the needle in the injection site for the truth serum you just got to help you along the way to finding your religion.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1367164859122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 12:00:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367165206553-16</Id><Topic><Title>Would one of you optionz crackheadz on the board help 'ol sybil out with a quick question?</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1366891118384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:58:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Do you really think that institutions would invest billions so they could manipulate the stock price in a effort to keep a few $$$ in premiums?" Multiply 1.5 - 3 million / week x 48 weeks timez 4 yearz - thats the money robots make off optionz. Now add (250- 105) * 15 million sharez. Thats the cap gainz for the robots on the undwrlying in entering and swing trading sharez for 4 yearz at a 105 entry and 250 exit. You tell sybs - haz systemically writing and killing paid off for the robots?</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1367165206553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 12:06:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367165809383-17</Id><Topic><Title>I can't fully express how happy I am</Title><Username>radar_the_kat</Username><Timestamp>1367150700458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I share the same opinion. AMZN has been OVERPRICED for quite a few years. Investors are just realizing it..." Correction: robots aren't 'investorz'. They are robots. The just happened to stick the money that bernanke printed for them in this and a few other picks, but theze picks could just az well be tulip bulbz or bitcoin. Who knowz... Rare tulips are indeed pretty, and internet vendorz are accepting bitcoin, so maybe amzn stok iz a scad over priced because it aint pretty like a tulip, and you cant really exchange it for goodz or servicez.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1367165809383</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 12:16:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367165825688-18</Id><Topic><Title>Help me God, help AMZN go to 274</Title><Username>kotharivk</Username><Timestamp>1367153618547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:53:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The sentiment on the board is all of the shorts/puts buyer beating their chests. If that's the overall sentiment the crooks may be up to something. Should it go down further. Yes, it always should because by any valuation metric this thing is overvalued by a ton. Warning, this obviously has been a favorite of funds, hedge funds with their HFT algos and the like so don't be surprised if this goes up early in this week. If and when it closes below it's 200DMA which appears to be just above $250 then the party might get started. Before that we could see some weird action. Ideally if the market is not totally cracking we will see the rotation out of here into modestly valued companies such as AAPL. If the overall market is about to crack as we go into May (not convinced since there is lots of money coming in), then I propose that Amazon carry the red flag out front since it is the longest running scam in this market and should take the pounding it's more than due. But alas folks, let it play out and don't go all in.</Msg><Username>hapihammer</Username><Timestamp>1367165825688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 12:17:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367172994816-19</Id><Topic><Title>Would one of you optionz crackheadz on the board help 'ol sybil out with a quick question?</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1366891118384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:58:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you get to 1.5 to 3 million per week? Is this an assumption?</Msg><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1367172994816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 14:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367175502470-20</Id><Title>FAIR VALUE IS BELOW $50 PER SHARE</Title><Msg>we will get there</Msg><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1367175502470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 14:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367180291680-21</Id><Title>FAIR VALUE IS NOT BELOW 50</Title><Msg>It is 75</Msg><Username>penystoc</Username><Timestamp>1367180291680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 16:18:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367187109883-22</Id><Topic><Title>I had no idea this was so overpriced</Title><Username>iztheman2002</Username><Timestamp>1367180479714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 16:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now you know.... This iz what robots do when you stuff them full of benanke bux....</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1367187109883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 18:11:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367189861382-23</Id><Title>Why build their own settop box whe they can buy ARRS"s new box</Title><Msg>and have the very best box ans software avaliable!!</Msg><Username>rpc356</Username><Timestamp>1367189861382</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 18:57:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367191305606-24</Id><Topic><Title>Would one of you optionz crackheadz on the board help 'ol sybil out with a quick question?</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1366891118384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:58:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5000-8000 open interest contracts x 100 x 1.50 = 750k - 1.2 mil... More on an active week, and more money when volitility premiumz rise. Considering these are typically taken by crack headz at the current money they buy theze weaponz of mass destruction, run them across a 20.00 range for the week to draw in the bulk of crackheadz. Then the momo bots will float the underlying through the entire range throughout the week to murder everyone at one point or another. None of this factorz in monthlies or leaps. Theze are just the weekliez. Look dont listen to sybs, best if you try em yourself. You'll figure it out sooner or later.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1367191305606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 19:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367193610947-25</Id><Topic><Title>Would one of you optionz crackheadz on the board help 'ol sybil out with a quick question?</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1366891118384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:58:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybs, sometimes I fantasize about purchasing an option on expiry day to catch a 10-30+ bagger. Is that possible in reality, me thinks it is just a fantasy? But there are many big mid-day reversals that occur. For example, Google last week the day after earnings, and Amzn on Friday there were puts that were selling under 25 cents in the morning that were $3.00 later in the day.!!!</Msg><Username>zbc407</Username><Timestamp>1367193610947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 20:00:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367195216732-26</Id><Topic><Title>Would one of you optionz crackheadz on the board help 'ol sybil out with a quick question?</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1366891118384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:58:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil, I'm still having a hard time. Institutions own a little less than 70% of amzn... which is more than $70 billion. Are you saying that these folks are risking that money for 1.2 million a week? Seems like a big risk to own a bloated pig to get a return of 1.2 million. Also, are you assuming that all open contracts are written by institutions? I've written contracts before and I know other retail investors have as well. Finally, do any of these positions go against the institutions or are they bullet proof? Do they only write options that end up out of the money?</Msg><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1367195216732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 20:26:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367195494807-27</Id><Title>2 questions for crackheadz option traderz</Title><Msg>On Yahoo (http://finance.yahoo.com/q/op?s=AMZN&amp;m=2014-01) , there are two PUT options for AMZN with strike price 225 expiring on Jan 17 2014: AMZN140118P00225000 and AMZN7140118P00225000. I guess I have two questions: 1. shouldn't there be only one PUT option with that underlying / strike / expiryt date? 2. what is the difference between these two PUT options? Thanks!</Msg><Username>singe_delir</Username><Timestamp>1367195494807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 20:31:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367196123667-28</Id><Topic><Title>I think by tomorrow morning we will get the direction it's going...</Title><Username>pjlouie13</Username><Timestamp>1366933308639</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:41:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My two cents.... My favourite "statistic" is that AMZN has at times in the past several years outperformed AAPL or at least kept pace with AAPL stock since the iPhone, iPad and Kindle have been released! Meanwhile, Apple's PE just kept dropping while AMZN PE kept increasing. Although, AMZN may be only trading at 2X revs. My short on LNKD last year, taught me a few things about this 'new' equity market we live in. I started shorting LNKD in Feb 2012 and added to the position through the year, only to give up and close the short completely around the end of Dec. Looking at my trading summary, I probably could have made it work for me if traded back and forth instead of just holding a bigger and bigger position. The other thing I learned is that trend trading combined with HTF leaves no room for fundamentals anymore, imho. They are thrown completely out the window. The time may be now to start looking at shorting AMZN but I will be super careful to watch the TA more now so then ever. Apple is a good case in point, between Cook's handling of the constant attacks (he was about a quarter behind with his mini-Tarp for the shareholders), and the talking heads calling for $375, all combined with trend trading HFTs, the damn stock could barely get two consecutive green days, it was god awful. There was a post by Syb trying to calculate how much is riding and how much in profits the option trading brings in every week. And how many decades has this been going on? Perhaps the better question to ask is how many people are being supported by the option trading in AMZN, and how many firms, and what percentage of their profits too?</Msg><Username>zbc407</Username><Timestamp>1367196123667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 20:42:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367196467712-29</Id><Title>All you crackheadz with 20 questionz for sybz are like 5 year oldz asking "but why?" Tell you what....</Title><Msg>Sybs telling you the stove iz fvck in hot . Dont touch it. But you still feel the need to do so, so please go ahead - reach out with both #$%$ hands and grab the fvck in heating element with the toghtest grip that you can. Okay? Just stop asking sybs questionz , you'll figure out: 1. Optionz are a waste of money 2. Just when they should pay off BIG, they wont because when the markets crash in circuit breaker fashion, honoring derivativez will be the last consideration. They were honored in 2008 circa aig, and gs getting paid from bear and lehmanz, but they wont be honored come the next crash . Derivativez, swaps, levered etfs, and many other financially engineered worthles peoce of paper with a pronuse to make good will fail miserably. Headz you lose, tailz you lose. But hit the crack pipe by all meanz.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1367196467712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 20:47:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367196782207-30</Id><Topic><Title>All you crackheadz with 20 questionz for sybz are like 5 year oldz asking "but why?" Tell you what....</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1367196467712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 20:47:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suppose that answers my question about trying to pick a bottom/top on options expiry in hope of a monster reversal by afternoon! I should know better. But Sybs the heating element just looks so tempting to grab.</Msg><Username>zbc407</Username><Timestamp>1367196782207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 20:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367201250960-31</Id><Topic><Title>I can't fully express how happy I am</Title><Username>radar_the_kat</Username><Timestamp>1367150700458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Enjoy your short. I will remind you to cover when this hits 300.</Msg><Username>ejinecer</Username><Timestamp>1367201250960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 22:07:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367204042417-32</Id><Topic><Title>I can't fully express how happy I am</Title><Username>radar_the_kat</Username><Timestamp>1367150700458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. That's not happening this quarter bub, Better strap yourself in, this going down. Quickly.</Msg><Username>greymattermatters</Username><Timestamp>1367204042417</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 22:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367207964776-33</Id><Title>Growth Questioned</Title><Msg>Quite a few analysts are starting to question the AMZN growth and profitability story. When folks start to question your strategy, when the benefit of doubt disappears, companies, such as AMZN, with obscene valuations will drop like a rock. Here is basic math. Data are from YHOO: 1. AMZN did ~64B in revenue. 2. In order to grow 20% this year, AMZN will need to pull in an extra 12.8B next year for a total of: 76.8. 3. In order to growh 20% next year, AMZN will need to pull in 15.36B. See the trend? That's called the law of the large number. And, in order to pull off 12.8B extra in revenues, AMZN needs to spend A LOT of money on the infrastructure to support that extra 12.8B. Well, how much would AMZN need to spend to support yet 15.36B on top of that? AMZN has been losing money head of heels and if they have not been able to master the management "economies"of scale" to be profitable with 64B in revenues, what make you think AMZN will be able to master the economies of scale when revenues go to 76.8B and beyond? All well-managed business are profitable at any given revenue point. That's why they call in "well-managed". Sane businesses make money. Insane businesses lose money. ANYONE can sell a buck for 99 cents.</Msg><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1367207964776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 23:59:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>