<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358572822939-1</Id><Topic><Title>Q4 Earnings Announcement and stock reaction</Title><Username>stkguy</Username><Timestamp>1358554606328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 19:16:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uhhhhhhmmmmm, tech - You open up with : "I base nothing on the market being rigged. " Yet you directly observe a worthless pig that hasnt met earningz expectationz in 7 quarterz, and tcome the 30 th it will be 8 th, trading in the 270's. And then you close with: "The market is badly broken because of all the volatility selling. " Make up your mind. Are the markets fair and healthy, or are they broken and rigged. This Az your ditm (at least at the time you roll into them they were ditm and very expensive) put option leap strategy gets slaughtered year over year month over month. Which goez to directly to sybils argument: 1. The market haz been rigged 'for an extended period of time' and continuez to be now more than ever absolutely fvck in rigged 2. The blood of the Optionz crackheadz, even the userz of the good sheit (ditm puts), have driven theze pigz to absolute lofty levelz to kill optionz premoumz that will never ever be recovered. For az long az optionz are weaponized, crack headz will use them and destroy themselvez with collateral damage. Good luck tech, your optionz are about ready to get devoured by robots.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358572822939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 00:20:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358573149836-2</Id><Topic><Title>Q4 Earnings Announcement and stock reaction</Title><Username>stkguy</Username><Timestamp>1358554606328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 19:16:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If sybil made kick ars pizza and sold it for 2 bux a pie with free delivery from main to texas, then sybs could make lots of revenue. Dont ya think? Actually amzn's model iz to buy the pizza from a pizza maker for 18 bux, and then sell it for 2 bux with free delivery and then pay tax. Go figure! Amzn doesnt make pizza, they dont make any thing. Its amzn dot BOMB. Isnt this tune a classic from the march 2000 era? Ahhhh yes, sybil lovez the oldiez.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358573149836</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 00:25:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358573765973-3</Id><Topic><Title>DO NOT UNDERSTAND WHY THIS IS WORTH 125 BILLION,</Title><Username>trader5632</Username><Timestamp>1358558871913</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 20:27:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Facebook is "worth" $64 billion, Amazon at $123 billion is ridiculously cheap! You can see that, can't you?</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1358573765973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 00:36:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358592021759-4</Id><Topic><Title>I have never seen a stock get a 'valuation hall pass' like this POS.</Title><Username>fig_plucker</Username><Timestamp>1358543408521</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 16:10:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True. Wall Street has to be on drugs.</Msg><Username>stock_selector1</Username><Timestamp>1358592021759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 05:40:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358598866130-5</Id><Title>Sybil - A crackhead needs your help</Title><Msg>Sybil, for the sake of argument, let's assume that amzn goes into its earning call with its stock priced around $270. Would I be taking a huge hit off the pipe if loaded up on puts that expire the following Friday? OR... would I be an investor who is taking a calculated risk and has a nice chance for a nice asymmetrical return?</Msg><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358598866130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:34:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358599169774-6</Id><Title>"in fact sybs was scad short of aapl at 720 and unfortunately covered way too soon at 650. " one thing Sybil</Title><Msg>AAPL NEVER GOT TO 720! ANOTHER LIE IN A LONG LIST OF THEM BY THIS CLOWN! Folks, you are being duped bigtime by this guy and the 100's of messages of ex-golbug that say the same thing over and over while worhsipping this Sybil, who is lieing. Tempted to send his trade tickets to the SEC and this guy is over the tops on his fraud.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358599169774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:39:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358599443094-7</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil - A crackhead needs your help</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358598866130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:34:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why would you ask a guy who's proven that he puts up lies about where he got into stock prices and out? Also you ever question the validity of his trading tickets. Do what you want on trades, but I'd very careful following thie pied piper in all seriousness. He's likely to ditch and run if AMZN goes much higher. Thats' my call of what happens to this clown. Do your own due dilegence without listening to a clown like Sybil or me, for that matter.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358599443094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:44:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358599594093-8</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil - A crackhead needs your help</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358598866130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:34:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trust me on this one... I make my own decisions when it comes to my $$$. I think Sybil is funny and am looking forward to the response.</Msg><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358599594093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:46:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358599713799-9</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil - A crackhead needs your help</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358598866130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:34:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and remember: I don't make stock price predcitons on the price of AMZN or where it goes: this guy does over and over, and all have been wrong: He is facing going into earnings of AMZN with what he says are 12,000-15,000 shorts on a yahoo board with naked shorts: if AMZN gaps up huge: he'll a half million dollars off the bat perhaps. Completely reckless. Just remember: you're shorting a low float stock tightly controlled by the big boys where they know exactly what to do if the short side gets crowded against the shorts shares they lend out. The only thinkg he's right about is buying puts is a losers game. I suggest you look back on this clown predicitons: he's gonna disappear if this goes much higher as my thoughts are that his postion is completely BS or he's completely reckless where others here can't be. Now good luck whatever you do. Do your own DD.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358599713799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:48:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358599938536-10</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil - A crackhead needs your help</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358598866130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:34:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fair enough. Maybe he's funny but I 'd question what he's doing based off predcitions never coming true yet perpetually add to shorts for 50 points against him. The fact he throws out 720 AAPL short when AAPL only reached 705 should tell you something. It's amazing to see the worship on this board of some short loser if true perpetually shorting a stock that preys on people shortinng it on their perceived valuation of it. That's been a loseer trade for about 14 years now.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358599938536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:52:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358600616384-11</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil - A crackhead needs your help</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358598866130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:34:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>john, if you use optionz then you are a crack head. If you were to do what your hypothetical scenario spellz out, then your trade would be found to be correct the monday foloowing the friday you were found made insolvant with optionz that expired absolutely worthless. You will be OD and found dead, no pulse, on monday, after OD ing from a crack optionz binge. The funny part of it all iz that az people stop using these crack head optionz, the stock will TANK to the put side, leaving the still living and gaunt crack headz with a feeling that they 'lost' or 'missed out' on an 'opportunity', not realizing that their lack of blood donating optionz use iz precisely the reason why the stock TANKS. Its like the roullette player that runz out of money at a rigged casino where the number 21 they've been betting all night comez up on the spin they dont bet, only because the dealer moved the reversed magnet from 21 Spot that forced the rigged ball out of the spot all night long.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358600616384</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:03:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358600973435-12</Id><Topic><Title>"in fact sybs was scad short of aapl at 720 and unfortunately covered way too soon at 650. " one thing Sybil</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358599169774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:39:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sybil iz not allowed a typo, immediaty followed by a correction with reason for the typo before a guy like nasdaq_6000 jumps out of the bushez in the dark with nothing but a rain coat on.... He rips it open and starts jerk ing off yelling "SYBIL SYBIL SYBIL" in all caps az this creep chasez poor unsuspecting strangerz down the street.... He iz a lunatic and the asylum really should have tighter security.... Nasdaq_6000 should not have access to the public, he'z dangerous.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358600973435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:09:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358601451190-13</Id><Topic><Title>"in fact sybs was scad short of aapl at 720 and unfortunately covered way too soon at 650. " one thing Sybil</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358599169774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:39:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and the 720 wasn't a type: it was you talking out of you butt along with all your predictions. the only thing your right about is probably staying away from options. But you never address your reckless naked shorting into the float control for 50 points now. Are other people supposed to follow you into being 12,000-15,0000 short into earnings when it could gap up to 300 or beyond. Your predictions of its demise have been wrong since you came here at 215 afterall. If you have that postion , you could be down a half milliton just there before you know it. If AMZN isn't trading on earnings, nobody can say it can't but you say after 14 years it ends. Your'e idiots and you know it. That or a complerte fraud telling people to do what you do. I'm telling them in all serous to do their own DD. That's not reckless, that's smart. Especially with a proven idiot like you,</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358601451190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:17:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358601594191-14</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil - A crackhead needs your help</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358598866130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:34:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Crack headz wanting to be admitted to Sybilz 12 Step program to living clean and healthy iz encouraging. Sybil can help them, but they must prepare to tread a long hard road. The optionz crack head must self enroll into Sybils 12 Step Program on a voluntary basis. It iz important that the self enroll for Step 1 of Sybils Program iz to: 1. Admit there iz a problem This fellow haz crossed an important threshold to coming clean by admitting that he haz a crack problem and asking for advice. Sybil's program offerz a large support network for new patience to use and share their experiencez Open up son, without fear of being picked on. Welcome to sybilz program. Folks this iz John, he haz a problem with using optionz crack..... Please welcome him into the fold. "Hi John."</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358601594191</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:19:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358601869379-15</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil - A crackhead needs your help</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358598866130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:34:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil, have to disagree with regarding options driving the valuation of amzn. How could options drive this company to have a $120+ billion valuation? As far as I can tell, there are 2 things driving the price: 1) positive feedback... as the stock price increases, more people jump into the stock, which perpetuates further increases and 2) many investors believe that amzn will be able to continue to increase rev while increasing margins, thus its pe will decline because the "e" is going to go up. Once sales growth misses, or eps misses and investors come to believe that amzn won't be able to deliver earnings, amzn will crack. Anyone who buys puts (or calls) before the next earnings call will not influence the stock price. AMZN's results will impact price. AMZN reports on a Tuesday. My guess is AMZN misses eps by a mile and hits the rev estimate. I hope the puts pay off.</Msg><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358601869379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:24:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358602637732-16</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil - A crackhead needs your help</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358598866130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:34:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nas, there is no question that the institutions and insiders own AMZN and they are responsible for its valuation. As far as I can tell, AMZN's value is more story driven, than fundamental driven. The very smart folks that run these funds believe that amzn will continue to increase rev and eventually increase margin, thus justifying its current value. I don't for a second believe that there is some kind of conspiracy among the big institutions to drive up the stock price. I think Bezos has created a company that is great at satisfying customers and has woven an incredible story that institutions believe. I also think that it has had a long time to deliver on its promises and that the fundamentals should drive its value. If fundamentals did, AMZN would crack. We will see. By the way, I'm am not listening to Sybil for investing advice. However, even you have to admit, he's funny as hell!</Msg><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358602637732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:37:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358603034522-17</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil - A crackhead needs your help</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358598866130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:34:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK Sybil... The problem is the option crack is so goooooddddddd!!!! I don't think I can resist getting a big fix of puts a few hours before the next earnings call.... I probably need to hit rock bottom before enrolling.</Msg><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358603034522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:43:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358603349100-18</Id><Title>John,</Title><Msg>dont stray from the hard road that you must travel by 'rationalizing' crack addict optionz use az temting az it may be. Sybil will try to explain and wish you well along the difficult, but rewarding journey to comming clean. You see, amzn started out at a run of the mill oversold short squeeze in 2010 az it pressed the 120 range which waz an astronomical valuation even at that price, but thats what short squeezez do. At the same time, bot having institutionz teamed up with the CBOE to lobby, legalize, and institute use of weekly optionz crack, which sheila baird gladly rubber stamped az an 'INVESTMENT VEHICLE' for this nflx, crm and many, many other pjgz. Bot runnerz quickly realized the addictive nature of this form of 'cheap' crack, and understood that with access to realtime data and control of a statistically significant portion of the underlying low float stox like amzn that their money in a normal short squeeze waz no longer dead money at the top of the squeeze... Bot runnerz realized that they could price and sell this weaponized drug to crack headz and kill them like clock work and get paid weekly on what otherwize would have been 'dead money' at the top of a squeeze. Much like in the movie batman, the dark night risez, They found that if they lowered crackheadz into a deep pit and allowed them to see the light of day that they would hold hope of escape and move on to freedom and richez. Needless to say many many many have died, and the few that survive and (the antagonist and batman himeself) were either permanantly damaged social psychopaths or had the powerz of a super hero. (ie a robot running institution could very well at some point buy optionz crack from a 'smart' retail seller of them and then un fvck in load their underlying holdingz and cash in the crack puts, putting the retailer seller to the option and destroying him). The length of detail addressing your attemt to rationalize option use would require much much more time and space. Sybil will try to help you in small dosez. That iz all you get for today. Moving to fast can confuse and discourage a former user and lead them a stray. Stay strong john. Stay strong. Be clean be proud. One day at a time. One foot in front of the other.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358603349100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:49:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358603963146-19</Id><Title>Interesting post from last night : looks like it's wrtiten in "Sybil" language with the "z" but forgot to change the "ID" lol!</Title><Msg>looks like Sybil was arguing with himself last night here. I'd be careful what this clown is tellin' ya. 24/7 here with ID's yet millions. singingrapter = sybil? lol! "" am a student of history and have done mucho market research.... 'singingraptor by singingraptor . Jan 16, 2013 10:57 PM . Permalink After reading of bull markets, bear markets, hyper inflationz, and massive depressionz in ... After reading of bull markets, bear markets, hyper inflationz, and massive depressionz in markets around the world, The singing lion haz drawn the following general conclusion that can be best summed up az followz: At no point in history, nor in any market that the singing lion haz read of have stok markets been so high and so hated concurrently. In bull markets stox are highly valued, but loved - so loved. In bear markets stox are assigned low valuez, while being absolutely despised. In this market stox are at record highs, above the 20 year parabola from 1980-2000 even, while simultaneously they are despised and hated by way of massive government intervention. How can this be? Where will this take us? this dynamic haz never been in play, ever looking at markets dating back to the tulipo mania. Bubble - the 1st on record. Interesting to say the least - nice job tim and ben...."" Evn a gullible guy like techstrategy could reason Sybil writing this. wow.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358603963146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:59:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358604209391-20</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil - A crackhead needs your help</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358598866130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:34:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"By the way, I'm am not listening to Sybil for investing advice" good, you shouldn't form him, me, or anyone on a yahoo message board. I think your premise may not be wrong but the stock is in the hands of higher powered people who seem to be able to keep it up again and again. Scam or not at times: timing an ending of a 14 year run is difficult especially when you see AAPL crack and AMZN not. Fundmentals are one thing , having the support of the money on the street is another. And the Fed is supporting the street bigtime. good luck with what ever you do. Sybil's a con artist. Might be funny to read yes, but I'm not sure there's some that don't follow what he pleads with his "tickets" of trade.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358604209391</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:03:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358604441331-21</Id><Topic><Title>Do u have Nasdaq6 cell number, I`d like to ordera burger...</Title><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1358524091287</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 10:48:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If so I'll order an all dressed berger with a frie... for 12h15pm this monday... well once in a while junk food isn't that bad... and if you're on time, I'll give you an extra $.50 as tip.....</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1358604441331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:07:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358604699571-22</Id><Topic><Title>John,</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358603349100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:49:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil, you are both funny and, in some cases, insightful. Thx for trying to help this crackhead. I am confused though... you write that the bots have run up the price. how exactly do bots run up amzn from the low hundreds to 270 in a couple of years. I don't get it? Secondly, when amzn reports, how can the options influence the price more than the results of the report? BTW, the more I think of your crack analogy, the more I see the connection to options. The possibility of buying a few dollar option that can turn into much, much more is powerful (at least to me). And, when I have lost the premium I've paid in the past, it hasn't been pleasant. I recognize there may be some truth in your analogy.</Msg><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358604699571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:11:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358605391986-23</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting post from last night : looks like it's wrtiten in "Sybil" language with the "z" but forgot to change the "ID" lol!</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358603963146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:59:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in fact in sounds like Sybil = Singhlion : a guy who's been here shorting since about 50 AMZN stock price. wow.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358605391986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:23:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358609162064-24</Id><Title>Nas - Question</Title><Msg>Nas, you have been a committed bull, and over the last couple of months, you've seen a $50+ rise in the stock price. If you're long, good for you!!! As far as I can tell, your basis for being a bull is 1) institutions control amzn and they won't let it go do and 2) technical project it will go up. What happens to the stock price if they miss eps by a mile??? And if they miss rev growth targets??? Will the stock price hold, let alone continue to increase. BTW, there are many reasons to think there will miss eps by a mile. They have been well documented on the board...</Msg><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358609162064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:26:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610092684-25</Id><Topic><Title>Nas - Question</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358609162064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:26:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nas has been an AMZN bull for at least a couple of years. It doesn't matter if AMZN misses eps by a mile. It's happened before, and the stock has gone up in response. BTW, there are many reasons, documented on this board, to believe AMZN will fall to under $50. Of course its all bs.</Msg><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1358610092684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:41:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358610215776-26</Id><Title>What top line revenue number does AMZN need . . .</Title><Msg>to post say - 27% yoy - quarterly revenue growth, anyone know? tough stock to game as many know, kinda like CRM - all revenue no margins - but heavily held and all about the future and growth. the new normal, transports to the roof, basic materials stuck in the mud for almost 2yrs., infrastructure crumbling, but consumer still consuming and boxes still being delivered . . . maybe need a few bridges collapsing before the new normal adjusts . . . can't believe this has a beta under 1 either . . .</Msg><Username>ajmanieri</Username><Timestamp>1358610215776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:43:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610313714-27</Id><Topic><Title>I have never seen a stock get a 'valuation hall pass' like this POS.</Title><Username>fig_plucker</Username><Timestamp>1358543408521</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 16:10:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the last 8 years Amazon has had the highest customer satisfaction rating of all internet companies. What value should this be worth? It's not on the balance sheet. It takes more than calculating the PE to be able sucessfully trade amzn.</Msg><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1358610313714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:45:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610600992-28</Id><Topic><Title>Nas - Question</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358609162064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:26:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bruce, how can you say that earnings don't matter??? AMZN's valuation has been story driven so far... meaning that folks are investing in rev growth (which has been incredible) and banking on AMZN being able to increase margins in the future. At some point, AMZN will have to show earnings. And if they miss by a mile, they will have negative earnings for CY2012. Share price will drop if that comes true. Just because the stock price has risen in the past doesn't mean it will rise in the future. Fundamentals will matter sooner or later. I bet sooner.</Msg><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358610600992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:50:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610914987-29</Id><Topic><Title>What top line revenue number does AMZN need . . .</Title><Username>ajmanieri</Username><Timestamp>1358610215776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:43:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On the summary page, you'll see a link to financials. Look at the income statements and go to the quarterly view. There you'll see that AMZN's 2011q4 rev was $17.4 billion. A 27% increase puts 2012q4 rev at $22.1 billion. If they miss this, watch out.</Msg><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358610914987</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:55:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358611147068-30</Id><Topic><Title>Nas - Question</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358609162064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:26:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>John , I'm not sure it matters. You see AMZN numbers get walked down into reporting every qtr to where they don't miss anyway. If you read the upgrades of the last two weeks, you see not any of them have expectations of earnings, so there's not a downside number that mattters to me nor has there been for the last year or so. And I don't think there's much of a change that they miss topline. They never have by any material amount. Bigger than that, it's about the spin and support to whatever AMZN reports and that is usulaly overwhelmingly bullish no matter what. That's why I call AMZN the most loved and supported stock in the Universe. If valuation, meant anything,probably would see it go from 40 to 300 to 1000 to 3000 PE that all keep shoritng against. How is one to say when or how that's gonna stop? Now? Why? Just saying. It's one of the "chosen ones" on WS right now and has been for 14 years. Sure it get pullbacks from time time , even some like to 170 from 246. But usally the get bought up while shorts time shorinting into the overavaluation argument. It's more about the reaction to the numbers with AMZN than what the numbers are themselves. And most times, those reactions are quite postiive again and again. Don't let me stop you if you wanna take a flyer but .... but know the hisotry of how the stock ticks. To see AAPL crack, while AMZN ticks on tells you the story is more that about sales and earnings numbers in my book, especially on a quarterly basis. . Best of luck on whatever you do.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358611147068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:59:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358612011816-31</Id><Topic><Title>Nas - Question</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358609162064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:26:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the "PE" of AMZN has gone from 40 to 50 to 100 to 300 to 500 to 1000 to 3000 so far. It night even get to 'N/a'. And the stock is still well supported at alltime highs levels by the big money where the funds plus the founder own 89 % of the oustanding stock. That's why they love to "lend" it out on the "its' gotta go down sometime, GMCR and CMG or some other other one did....." Sure they did, but not on anyone's timeline, it's on the big money's timeline perhaps. That's my view on the meaningless of earnings in regard to AMZN or the number in general right now. Someday, yest, they will be pressured to show profits promised. But throw the dart guessing. It's always had a premium prices and a story to tell. More than ever today.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358612011816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:13:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358612038877-32</Id><Topic><Title>Nas - Question</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358609162064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:26:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have been right so far, no question... I can't help but believe that if AMZN misses eps by a mile, folks are going to realize that their business model can 1) deliver incredible rev growth and 2) no profits. If they hit $0.27 eps in q4, they will have negative earnings for 2012! If they miss by a mile, the story turns much uglier. They will have missed several quarters in a row and their 2012 earnings will be very negative. Assume for the sake of argument that they miss eps... how can AMZN maintain its current price?</Msg><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358612038877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:13:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358612763046-33</Id><Topic><Title>Nas - Question</Title><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358609162064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:26:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Assume for the sake of argument that they miss eps... how can AMZN maintain its current price?" I don't know... maybe by merely reacting like the last few misses to the botttom forbecasted, by having a blip down and then a grind back up to highs of AH, then going up the whole next day. There's no why or how to it in explaining it in terms of ripping apart quarterly numbers. YOu don't get to where PE doesn't matter if it did no? Go ahead and buy puts or short it if you think it's time that it will. The reactions havn't favored that since maybe one I've seen when it was 246 and corrected to about 168. I know this report there's "earningless" expectations. THat's what anlaysts have said. What if it's a one way street: they make money and the hype in media is laid on thick? Lol! it happens day in and day out with AMZN stock and documented here. And the shorts still are mystyfied. I'll say this: it'll matter when it matters. And its' all a guess. That's my view on how numbers mean nothing in the history of it: shorts have decided that they should into big money saying no again and again. I guess for you : have your number comparisons ready, see what they are, see how the stock reacts, and watch the support and spin to them. Gotta go now.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358612763046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:26:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358612841156-34</Id><Topic><Title>Apple has a $50/share earning to support the fall - What does this PIG have?</Title><Username>mallumazter</Username><Timestamp>1358526188647</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 11:23:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Buy AAPL, if you want to lose your money. They may never see $500 again. They're toast. Amazon is still in start up mode, beloved by their customers and associates." Yes, it's a dumb post, and I'm a dumb hillbilly. But I'm long AMZN, my cost per share is $43. What about you?</Msg><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1358612841156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:27:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358613404380-35</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon's Low-Profit Margin Model Is Key To Future Growth</Title><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1358263383578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:23:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo message boards are misleading. When you post, you click "long-term sentiment disclosure", but when it displays it just says "sentiment". Strong buy is my LONG TERM sentiment. My current sentiment of hold is because I already sold some at 260. Had I not sold any, I'd sell some now at 270. I would not buy at this price, I never buy at the all time high.</Msg><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1358613404380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:36:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358613675904-36</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon's Low-Profit Margin Model Is Key To Future Growth</Title><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1358263383578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:23:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, after all, we are in agreement...AMZN is simply too pricey at this level...despite all future promises. I tell you what, if AMZN blows away earnings and guidance goes up, I'd buy with both hands ;)</Msg><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1358613675904</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:41:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358614057451-37</Id><Topic><Title>What top line revenue number does AMZN need . . .</Title><Username>ajmanieri</Username><Timestamp>1358610215776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:43:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's interesting to note that GOOG "soft pedal" on their revenues and EBAY provided a cautious outlook. With taxes going up, uncertainties abound, and a year of big revenue growth, I think the law of the large numbers will kick in and AMZN will provide a tepid guidance even if they beat the odds last quarter. All around me, folks are moving away from shopping on AMZN due to sales taxes. I know for sure that's the case for us. There are plenty of great online places without sales taxes. There is no need for AMZN for us.</Msg><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1358614057451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:47:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358615309085-38</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting post from last night : looks like it's wrtiten in "Sybil" language with the "z" but forgot to change the "ID" lol!</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358603963146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:59:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blow sybilz virtual corpse douchbag..</Msg><Username>singingraptor</Username><Timestamp>1358615309085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:08:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358626774455-39</Id><Topic><Title>John,</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358603349100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:49:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Syb, you are correct in most things, and I mostly agree with you about avoiding weekly options. HOWEVER, I think option spreads are a sometimes useful way to profit from directional moves and they carry less risk than being long or shor a stock, if used carefully. Other than that, we're on the same page.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1358626774455</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:19:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358626918552-40</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting post from last night : looks like it's wrtiten in "Sybil" language with the "z" but forgot to change the "ID" lol!</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358603963146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:59:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Comparing Sybil to "singlion" is like comparing a Mercedes to a Yugo. Not the same. if you make that mistake, what other mistakes are you making?</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1358626918552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:21:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358627179244-41</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting post from last night : looks like it's wrtiten in "Sybil" language with the "z" but forgot to change the "ID" lol!</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358603963146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:59:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mistaking the two shows the lack of correct thought processes in your brain. How can anyone mistake thoughtful Sybil for Singlion? Boggles the mind.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1358627179244</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:26:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358628235642-42</Id><Title>AMZN Revenu</Title><Msg>Let's hear all the data points that may help us understand AMZN upcoming report for the past quarter and guidance for the next? We've seen quite a few data points that point to a challenging quarter for AMZN. Has anyone seen anything that points to a great quarter? Btw, I found a report from around 11/29 that says that AMZN S3 (one of their cloud services) lowered pricing by 24-28% ...that's huge</Msg><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1358628235642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:43:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358628469000-43</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN Revenu</Title><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1358628235642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Comscore estimates yoy online commerce increased 13.8%, which is obviously lower than what amzn is expected to grow. Not sure if this # includes mobile commerce though.</Msg><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358628469000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:47:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358629010625-44</Id><Topic><Title>John,</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358603349100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:49:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I am confused though... you write that the bots have run up the price. how exactly do bots run up amzn from the low hundreds to 270 in a couple of years. I don't get it?" Answer: by way of 'accomodative fed policy' of an extraodinary levelz through in the following order talf, tarp, qe 1, qe2, operation twist, qe 3 with operation twist, and now qe monthly for an 'extended period of time'. Banks and bot runnerz do not use their own money they use tax payer dollarz and credit bubblez that have since been monitized into the greatest, and unpayable, bond bubble of all time. A bond bubble where a non money making company like amzn scorez 3 billion dollarz of 2% 'high grade' bond money with a single page application and no verifiable meanz of paying back the 1st installment due in 2015. The underwriterz ( ms and gs ) that are now pumping the stock they recieved in fee for underwriting will soon become bashing bond bulliez taking ownership of amzn realestate assets for 40 cents on the dollar.... Amzn to the 2012 bond market bubble az iz the no doc immigrant landscaper that financed a no doc loan to the 2007 credit market bubble. Bernanke printed a new high at the mutitrillion expense of the bond market with the publics money and created an environment for the too big to failerz that no have less moral hazard then ever before... In fact in 1999 and 2006, theze idiot looked like quire boyz that the preist molested compared to what they have become now. But you have amzn at 270.00, the sheeple drinking koolaid and everything iz 'all better', a 'return to normal' if you will. "Secondly, when amzn reports, how can the options influence the price more than the results of the report?" Easy answer: it iz obvious that fundementalz are currently disjointed from stock price (thats putting it nicely), so the stock floats in the 270 range and possibly a small bump to do a final ringing out of weak handed shorts, and definitly a mass killing of optionz crackheadz for easy money az the bots unload into the final ring out. If you "invest" 2k in a stok and lose 50% of it iz iz unusual, if you buy 2k worth of crackhead optionz and lose 70% of it then it iz normal. Thats all sybs has to say about your last comment. Travel the hard road, john stay clean. If you do not have the gun powder to trade the underlying security of a pig stok like amzn, then move on to a cheaper pig like crm.... In todayz markets there are lots of pugs to be short, or to go long on if you are stupid enough to az the market tops out before rolling over, that you dont have to trade the big dogz. Simpy put (no pun intended), crackhead optionz are not the way.... They are the quickest way to lose 70-100% of principal on a bet that sybs knows of.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358629010625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:56:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358629430511-45</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting post from last night : looks like it's wrtiten in "Sybil" language with the "z" but forgot to change the "ID" lol!</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1358603963146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:59:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And it looks like amzn's inflated stock price iz directly proportion to the amount nasdaq_6000 beats hiz meat, and inversly proportional to the intellegence of hiz posts. Interesting obsevationz made by sybs. Sybs wonderz what those relationships look like when graphed against an rsi and macd az leading indicatorz of direction change.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358629430511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:03:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358629543120-46</Id><Title>Sybil iz sybil folks, alwayz declaring az such - nothing to hide under psuedo handlez</Title><Msg>All otherz are copy cats, and there are lots of them.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358629543120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:05:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358632024882-47</Id><Title>Screaming short</Title><Msg>I wish we could get a few big time shorts like Chanos, Ackman, or Einhorn to jump on board and see what is so obvious to everyone. Looks like barring the miraculous, AMZN will have 3 straight years of declining free cash flow...there is no plausible explanation for a company with that staggering of a PE to have declining free cash flow...</Msg><Username>budfox20001</Username><Timestamp>1358632024882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:47:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358632111324-48</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil iz sybil folks, alwayz declaring az such - nothing to hide under psuedo handlez</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358629543120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:05:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>blah blah blah. You didn't do a very good job on calling last week's movement skeezix</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358632111324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:48:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358632396649-49</Id><Title>Yo Tech....... You Really Need To</Title><Msg>Check out AZO. I think its a big bloated pig.</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358632396649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:53:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358632439934-50</Id><Topic><Title>John,</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358603349100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:49:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok Sybil, you make some good points. Problem is I still don't get it. It must be all those put crack hits I've done. They have shaved IQ points off my intelligence. In fact, I've gotten to the point where I've even dealt call crack and lost $$$. How many dealers do you know lose $$$? Back to the confusion... the first point you address is an asset bubble caused by easy fed money. The fed has flushed the system full of $$$ and that $$$ has to go somewhere. In this case some of the easy money has went to amzn. But I still don't see any relationship between option trading and the run up in amzn. If the run up is due to easy monetary policy, then the collapse will be swift, and I want to own puts when that happens (see the put crack addict is always chasing). Second, rather than options driving stock price, I think that amzn will miss eps by a mile and may even miss on rev. If this is the case, watch out below. Institutions will not be able to keep this thing up. You'll have hedge funds jump in short, you some institutions realizes its time to head for the exist and you'll see down-grades. If they just miss eps, I will keep a close eye on it. There are plenty of instances where an eps miss has caused a swift drop followed by reversion to its old price. Of course, this may be the delusional hope of a put option crack addict. We will see.</Msg><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358632439934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:53:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358632514340-51</Id><Topic><Title>Yo Tech....... You Really Need To</Title><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358632396649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:53:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have nothing against Eddie Lampert, but he epitomizes everything you KNOW. If he touches it.... well, check out RSH and/or SHLD.</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358632514340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:55:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358632586992-52</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil iz sybil folks, alwayz declaring az such - nothing to hide under psuedo handlez</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358629543120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:05:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll give ya the benefit of the doubt. In my benevolence.</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358632586992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:56:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358635762116-53</Id><Title>amazon bankrupcty</Title><Msg>i am betting very big that amazon will file for bankruptcy in the next 5 years.remember this post</Msg><Username>akarmatz</Username><Timestamp>1358635762116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:49:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358636153771-54</Id><Topic><Title>amazon bankrupcty</Title><Username>akarmatz</Username><Timestamp>1358635762116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:49:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$5B can desappear with only few bad qters..... Bags don't realize that with such thin margins, big lossses could happen in ant qters.... and when it will begin... it won't stop....</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1358636153771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:55:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358636352016-55</Id><Title>THIN MARGINS , NO PROFIT, ONLY $5B CASH, = DESASTER COMING IS OBVIOUS..</Title><Msg>Gee... SO OBVIOUS...... $272 and keep shorting..... will increase my position as long as it takes.... Anyway, see you, WAY LOWER...................</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1358636352016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:59:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358636522326-56</Id><Title>Is Sybil A Scam?</Title><Msg>A Yahoo shill. ??????????????????</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358636522326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:02:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358636613748-57</Id><Topic><Title>Yo Tech....... You Really Need To</Title><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358632396649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:53:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I ain't checked my email lately. Did you call?</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358636613748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:03:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358636780779-58</Id><Title>How Dare Sybil Post</Title><Msg>Whilst ignoring direct inquiries.</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358636780779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:06:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358636839211-59</Id><Topic><Title>amazon bankrupcty</Title><Username>akarmatz</Username><Timestamp>1358635762116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:49:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>highly unlikely that amzn goes bk... they call always raise prices. sure there rev growth will go bye-bye and stock price will tank... but they will be profitable. look, i think amzn is way over-valued, but give it some credit. it has a large customer base that is happy. they won't all disappear if amzn raises prices across the board.</Msg><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358636839211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:07:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358636859507-60</Id><Topic><Title>Yo Tech....... You Really Need To</Title><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358632396649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:53:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nahhhhhhhhhhhh. oh well.........</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358636859507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:07:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358636990927-61</Id><Topic><Title>Is Sybil A Scam?</Title><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358636522326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:02:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil iz not a scam or a yahoo shill. Sybil iz the Master of the Trade who iz respects the powerful trading gods and stands in good gracez before them. Sybil haz been known to dine with them on occasion.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358636990927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:09:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358637115632-62</Id><Topic><Title>Screaming short</Title><Username>budfox20001</Username><Timestamp>1358632024882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:47:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ackman has hid hands full with his foolish long in JCP and probably costly short in HLF, so I doubt he'd get involved. However, Einhorn and Chanos might. Einhorn has made very negative comments about Amazon, and Chanos surely knows about grossly overvalued and overhyped stocks. So it wouldn't surprise me ONE BIT if ether announced they have taken a short position in Amazon. Not one bit.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1358637115632</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:11:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358637172323-63</Id><Topic><Title>Screaming short</Title><Username>budfox20001</Username><Timestamp>1358632024882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:47:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>best not to play</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358637172323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:12:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358637216453-64</Id><Topic><Title>Yo Tech....... You Really Need To</Title><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358632396649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:53:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eddie is a clown but shld is heading to $50.... bought at $40 ONLY for the squeeze....he sold most of his azo shares so he has a lot of liquidity..... AZO is just an accounting fraud, building a big short position since almost a year...... heading sub $250.....</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1358637216453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:13:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358637280210-65</Id><Title>Buy DAL Below Eleven</Title><Msg>test....................</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358637280210</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:14:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358637301742-66</Id><Topic><Title>Screaming short</Title><Username>budfox20001</Username><Timestamp>1358632024882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:47:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"and probably costly short in HLF" huhhhh LOL</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1358637301742</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:15:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358637464522-67</Id><Topic><Title>Screaming short</Title><Username>budfox20001</Username><Timestamp>1358632024882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:47:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what's hlf?</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358637464522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:17:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358637576633-68</Id><Topic><Title>Screaming short</Title><Username>budfox20001</Username><Timestamp>1358632024882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:47:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ackan is still in deep green with his short position......</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1358637576633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:19:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358637591071-69</Id><Topic><Title>amazon bankrupcty</Title><Username>akarmatz</Username><Timestamp>1358635762116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:49:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Five yearz may be too generous, sybil subtracts 3 yearz and sayz that amzn along with many many companiez, munis, and counties, will be filing bankruptcy in record defaults by way of bond easy money void of moral hazard bond debt default.... Why? unsustainable debt loads masked by massive qe that carries no care or consideration because it will be faceless public money that iz defaulted on. If a credit crisis of private wealth can generate an occurance like that of 2008 with a fed that iz able to respond then imagine what can happen with a bond crisis of faceless public money with a weakened fed unable to respond? This iz the heavy price thst could be paid for what sybil viewz az irresponsible money printing continued 'for extended periodz of time'. There are no free lunchez, you can eat like a pig for a while but eventually the waitress showz up with the bill, and if you dont pay it then you get fvck ed up by the cookbthat ownz the dive.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358637591071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:19:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358637824887-70</Id><Topic><Title>Is Sybil A Scam?</Title><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358636522326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:02:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do trading godz dine on? angel-food?</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358637824887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:23:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358637904282-71</Id><Topic><Title>Is Sybil A Scam?</Title><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358636522326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:02:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or dog pooo?</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358637904282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:25:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358638124096-72</Id><Title>AMZN=AAPL=$350 in coming months..just remember me and my experience of shorting shorted AAPL $680</Title><Msg>and now long AMZN $220.</Msg><Username>checking_here</Username><Timestamp>1358638124096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:28:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358638159870-73</Id><Topic><Title>Is Sybil A Scam?</Title><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358636522326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:02:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ambrosia...... That's the word I was looking for. Angel-food,</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358638159870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:29:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358638409329-74</Id><Topic><Title>John,</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358603349100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:49:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How many dealers do you know lose $$$?" Only the dealerz that do not control a statistically significant portion of the float with nano second robots capable of crunching massive amounts of real time data to set pricing for the greek variablez, track sharez loaned, track leverage in real time, etc make out ahead of the game to the point where it iz very lucrative. You dont have to own a majority of the float, but syble estimates that 8 to 15% of the float needz to be under your control before writing optionz for .8 to 1.5% of what you control. This iz enough to run the statistics and calculate the probabilitiez of consistantly winning. This iz what you wont read in finra and cboe disclaimerz that "trading optionz entailz risk. Some or all of a pincipal balance can be lost. It iz advised that a financial planner be consulted before trading optionz. " add another 14 pagez of legal ease mumbo jumbo, followed by a choice: "I have read and understand the termz and conditionz for trading optionz" ACCEPT DECLINE</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358638409329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:33:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358638700795-75</Id><Topic><Title>amazon bankrupcty</Title><Username>akarmatz</Username><Timestamp>1358635762116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:49:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting...I had not paid much attention to the scenario where if economy stalls a bit, retails drop (higher taxes this year for everyone and uncertainties) , and with AMZN having no real cushion. I guess AMZN could head south in a real hurry if retail takes a dip this year. They do have massive fixed cost now...much different from when they were just a book seller.</Msg><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1358638700795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:38:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358638919086-76</Id><Topic><Title>Is Sybil A Scam?</Title><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358636522326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:02:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beware The Middle East. Dow 18K</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358638919086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:41:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358638933593-77</Id><Topic><Title>amazon bankrupcty</Title><Username>akarmatz</Username><Timestamp>1358635762116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:49:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem is once the sharks sense a weakness, they will want to feast on AMZN (or anyone else for that matter), one way or another. If AMZN does not have enough cash, they will be feasted. I'm sure AMZN contracts contain material adverse clauses, and they get triggered and cause a situation to snowball out of control...</Msg><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1358638933593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:42:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358639050282-78</Id><Topic><Title>amazon bankrupcty</Title><Username>akarmatz</Username><Timestamp>1358635762116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:49:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Best not to play.</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358639050282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:44:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358639319429-79</Id><Topic><Title>John,</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358603349100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:49:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The most boring thread of all time. But heah,! its sybs Far be it from him to talk to himself. But he is a genius. Maedame C knows all.</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358639319429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:48:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358639333370-80</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN=AAPL=$350 in coming months..just remember me and my experience of shorting shorted AAPL $680</Title><Username>checking_here</Username><Timestamp>1358638124096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:28:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you don't get AMZN.</Msg><Username>checking_here</Username><Timestamp>1358639333370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:48:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358639395384-81</Id><Topic><Title>John,</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358603349100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:49:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Madame.</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358639395384</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:49:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358639493149-82</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN=AAPL=$350 in coming months..just remember me and my experience of shorting shorted AAPL $680</Title><Username>checking_here</Username><Timestamp>1358638124096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:28:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're comparing apples to avacados</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358639493149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:51:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358639640359-83</Id><Topic><Title>John,</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358603349100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:49:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Madame C 2 U</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358639640359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:54:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358639966961-84</Id><Topic><Title>amazon bankrupcty</Title><Username>akarmatz</Username><Timestamp>1358635762116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:49:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hear it tons of time on azo at $380+....</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1358639966961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:59:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358640164792-85</Id><Topic><Title>How Dare Sybil Post</Title><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358636780779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:06:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're doin' better. Start thinking more long term oh brainy one.</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358640164792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:02:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358640425208-86</Id><Title>I've built my AZO short since a year... heard longs(now they're bags) that were laughing</Title><Msg>trying to explain why it was impossible for such a co to drop....ALL analysts had a target many points above $400...... Thanks god it didn't begin to drop sooner..... CAUSE NOW MY SHORT POSITION IS WAY BIGGER...... Novice longs here can't have vision..... I'm doing same thig here.... same thing as I did on rimm,kkd, jdsu,nt, fnm etc..... the longer it will tke to make money the more I'll make... as simple as that.... I'll let peanuts to bags at this level.... it's funny that someone like nasdaq saying he's longs since a very long time but has to flip burgers on lunche time to buy stocks !!!!!! Gee, I guess its part of their long learning process.... THEY JUST CAN'T SEE PROBLEMS AHEAD......</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1358640425208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:07:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358640629147-87</Id><Topic><Title>John,</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358603349100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:49:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey douchbag, john haz enrolled in sybilz 12 step program for going clean and sober... Do not torque sybil up when trying to help a crackhead lest you feel the full fury of the trading gods az the slap Clamidea around like the #$%$ that she iz ...... If sybil can save one crackhead at a time, then that iz one more straw on this pig's back towardz its collapse.... If more people listened to sybil 3.5 yearz ago az they came out with theze weekly crackhead optionz then the markets just may be a more friendly place (but probably not). That being said, if it werent for the blood of dead crackheadz and the kindness of tge trading gods then sybil would not have an account full of OUTSTANDING shorts for sybil to enjoy 'for an extended period of time'.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358640629147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:10:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358640804018-88</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN Revenu</Title><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1358628235642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>November 1-December 31 $37,170 $42,286 14% So, correct me if I'm wrong, but total retail sales went up 5B. AMZN last year rev was 17.43B. For them to hit 22.5B in rev this year, they would have to essentially grabbed essentially all the growth reported by Comscore and everyone else stay stagnant? Considering BBY reported gains in a number of places and ChannelAdvisor reported AMZN CA (lots of folks) spending dipped during a critical shopping period along with the fact they had to cut their cloud services (growth driver) by some 20-28%, I think the thesis that AMZN will missed revenue estimates is correct. Factor in that Bezos said AMZN does not optimize for margin, that means profits probably took a serious hit too...just to not lose sales somewhat? If AMZN revenues come in anywhere near 21B and with EPS almost certainly in the dump, I think we will be looking at a stock price below 200.</Msg><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1358640804018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:13:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358640953512-89</Id><Topic><Title>Is Sybil A Scam?</Title><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358636522326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:02:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What do trading godz dine on? " Poached eggs, caviar, leg of lamb, and the trade accounts of the disrespectful.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358640953512</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:15:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358640970469-90</Id><Topic><Title>I've built my AZO short since a year... heard longs(now they're bags) that were laughing</Title><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1358640425208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:07:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey dude, I'll give ya credit. I played AZO a long time ago.... up and down, and I probably lost. My new soap box is because of one of your posts I read a few weeks ago. But I got a feeling on this pig. Talk about empty flippin stores. And over built cannibalization.... however though, they can really leverage the Bollshete with "anythingautodatc0m" Internet used auto part sales, are gonna explode. It was a sharp move buying them. Give credit where credit is due.</Msg><Username>misterlockheed2u</Username><Timestamp>1358640970469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:16:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358641612918-91</Id><Topic><Title>I've built my AZO short since a year... heard longs(now they're bags) that were laughing</Title><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1358640425208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:07:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Way to late.. eddie has moved most of his money... Azo's exec bozos just CAN'T borrow more money/increase debts, that was the trick to pocket billions.... growth in this sector is about over.... debt are now hudge , insiders have cashed....their credit rating is going to be downgraded in 2013, interest on notes and others are going to pop..... etc etc etc..... $250 med term..... I've written so mmany options on it that my average short price is higher than the all time high.... I'm doing the same thing with amzn... Btw, I would like to see a pop in amzn next week, I'll keep writing calls.....</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1358641612918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:26:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358642041416-92</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN Revenu</Title><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1358628235642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think there is a good chance amzn misses rev too and I've done the same exercise you've done... Only I use a couple of different assumptions... First, the Comscore figure is for the US only. AMZN doesn't have get all of its incremental rev for the US market. Second, I think the Comscore figure is for people how buy through a pc, not a mobile device. If so, mobile $$$ isn't included in the comscore data. Also, they have fast growing non-retail businesses. This is a small piece of the total pie, but it will boost rev nonetheless. Clearly, amzn has a big hill to climb on the rev front. I hope they miss as I plan on holding a boat load of puts going into the earnings call. I'm much more confident they will miss eps by a wide margin. We will see.</Msg><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358642041416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:34:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358642814727-93</Id><Title>Only question for er, Are number cooked and by how much ? it's so easy to work numbers</Title><Msg>to get a last squeeze helping the distribution pattern......... I'm sure FMR and some other big dudes are in close contact with BOZO... They'll choose the best ratio to work with... and push big BS on it.........</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1358642814727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:46:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358643374312-94</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN Revenu</Title><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1358628235642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I hope they miss as I plan on holding a boat load of puts going into the earnings call." You have been booted from sybilz 12 step program for becoming clean and sober.... Free of crack optionz... You may renter when you are ready, unless the robots gun you down first. Sybil simply cannot allow a new candidate in the support group that will put the otherz who wish to recover at risk. Do not be discouraged for many have strayed from the hard road that must be followed. What you will find after earningz iz that you will be correct the monday following the friday after your put optionz explode like a suicide bomberz vest. You willingly strap this vest on with the certainty that this pig will TANK in the time frame of your optionz expiry.... You will pay a heavy price along with millionz of other crackheadz that are going to pay expensive premiumz to employ the same 'stratedgy'. Bots shall feed on your intestinez az they scrap you off the street and buildingz where you self detonate. But good luck anyway. Sybil will simply sit short and wait it out without worry of 'when' ....</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1358643374312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:56:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358644144646-95</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN Revenu</Title><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1358628235642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMZN already gave a sandbagged guidance range: They indicated they will generate sales of $20.25 billion to $22.75 million and earn a $490 million loss to a $310 million profit ( consensus estimate 27 cents). You know they are going to forecast a number they can easily beat...They understand the game of underpromising in order to overdeliver. Look for AMZN to reach sales of $24 billion and earnings of 54 cents.</Msg><Username>bluebloodedtrader</Username><Timestamp>1358644144646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:09:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358644804648-96</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN Revenu</Title><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1358628235642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil, I really think you're way to much anti-options !!! I'm usually a writer, however I remember a trade on goog that someone did, but I didn't.... He invested 20k(that was a tiny part of its portfolio) in a put way otm on goog just before earning release... wonder how he made.... about a million..... So yes most of the time buyers are crushed, but sometimes it worth it.... I'm trading tons of options to work my short positions... that's why I never had been squeezed.....(I've been squeezing long time ago, when I was a novice.... So you're making way to much with the option thing......</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1358644804648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:20:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358645593269-97</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN Revenu</Title><Username>stock_lol</Username><Timestamp>1358628235642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what's the basis for your expected monster beat on eps? there is ample reason to believe they will fail badly on the eps front. the last 4 esp results: Dec 11 = 0.38 Mar 12 = 0.28 Jun 12 = 0.01 Sep 12 = -0.60 notice a trend??? how exactly are they going to hit 0.54??? Other reasons they won't: 1) operating and net margins are declining 2) they started to collect sales tax in CA, PA and TX 3) the holiday season has widely been reported as disappointing 4) competition has offered to match prices 5) yoy online sales growth is 14% --- amzn is expected to increase yoy rev by 27% 6) their rev growth is decelerating 7) the unit rev per shipment is declining while unit shipping costs are flat to up... thus negatively impacting margins 8) they have droped prices on their cloud services shall I go on??? the consensus eps opinion for the upcoming report is 0.27 (which is a yoy from of 0.11) they will miss the 0.27 as well. one more thing... even if they hit the 0.27 eps they will have negative earnings for the year.</Msg><Username>johnalexgordon</Username><Timestamp>1358645593269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:33:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358650494170-98</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN=AAPL=$350 in coming months..just remember me and my experience of shorting shorted AAPL $680</Title><Username>checking_here</Username><Timestamp>1358638124096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:28:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IMO, Avacados are better for health than apples.</Msg><Username>checking_here</Username><Timestamp>1358650494170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:54:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358653316261-99</Id><Title>SYBIL=SINGHLION=EXGOLDBUG=OTHER ID'S</Title><Msg>OH YEA.</Msg><Username>tigers.james</Username><Timestamp>1358653316261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 22:41:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>