<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-10-26"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382765437853-1</Id><Title>Amazon is the largest turd on Wall Street.</Title><Msg>Plop</Msg><Username>madaelpha</Username><Timestamp>1382765437853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 01:30:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382767713368-2</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is something unethical about pulling $400 price targets out of your #$%$.</Msg><Username>one_smooth_stone</Username><Timestamp>1382767713368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 02:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382772907489-3</Id><Title>2008 on $100 and Friday in 1 day + $ 30.</Title><Msg>New record. Where will this end. I see $ 1.000 in the air.</Msg><Username>ruudkrul</Username><Timestamp>1382772907489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 03:35:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382773871848-4</Id><Title>Market cap unsustainable without increased free cash flow</Title><Msg>They are in the market cap neighborhood with some big names... for Christ's sake they are near the top 20 largest companies in the US. The law of large numbers will catch up to them. You cannot grow $100Billion at 25% for very long. after 7 years, you would need to INCREASE revenues by $97Billion. It's unsustainable! Company already seems a bit desperate for their growth, they are all over the place, delivering eggs, to kindles, what's next? I hear people say they "could be profitable" if they wanted to but "reinvesting" into the business. How come others can grow and be profitable? I don't even care about net income... just show us so free cash flow!!!</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382773871848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 03:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382773929078-5</Id><Topic><Title>Market cap unsustainable without increased free cash flow</Title><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382773871848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 03:51:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Disclosure I JUST shorted this stock today!!!</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382773929078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 03:52:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382784933147-6</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Walmart can kill amazon in just 1 quarter any time they want to." No, they couldn't. They do not have the appropriate infrastructure. Pick and pack of individual orders requires a radically different fulfillment operation. Also, Walmart doesn't carry a fraction of the SKUs so has only a very narrow offering of selection.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382784933147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 06:55:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382786380138-7</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon is the largest turd on Wall Street.</Title><Username>madaelpha</Username><Timestamp>1382765437853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 01:30:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>moron</Msg><Username>g99sim</Username><Timestamp>1382786380138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 07:19:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382786967088-8</Id><Topic><Title>Bezos to discuss new business initiatives on the cmoing CC</Title><Username>newmarketpro2002</Username><Timestamp>1382552966500</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-23 14:29:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"but never short it" Why not? lol!! why don't you tell the board about where you shorted from, your losses to here, and that might be a good reason to in itself. no? Seems your the only one who it didn't register with. Put it this way, a crash wouldn't even help you get out of you losses you've had in AMZN. Isn't that right?</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382786967088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 07:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382787193162-9</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts, if you cover now you can save yourselvez an additional 10% next week</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382756047958</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 22:54:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I hope they try to run it fast and hard. Works for me." How does it work for you? You've been short into this run before it happend: longterm, medium term and short term. That's the "works for you" that keeps on giving? come on man.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382787193162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 07:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382787364933-10</Id><Title>ok , techstrategy? since AMZN going up "works for you" at what level , does it not work for you?</Title><Msg>I sold almost all AMZN at $308, but I'm just wondering what a short mindset on that statement is as I'm curious. If I was another short thinking of shorting out there, I wouldn't short until all of you who have been dead wrong are gone. But I guess you'll short until AMZN is at 1000, 2000, 3000... defining risk in action on this board.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382787364933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 07:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382787383546-11</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ethical unethical, sophisticated unsophisticated - who cares about this nonsense? it will end when this country realizes that the only way to reduce the labor costs is to place millions of useless blood suckers (financial sector must go there first) into concentration camps and have them work.</Msg><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382787383546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 07:36:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382787493970-12</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe you should care more than you stupid post says, as those are the guys backed by serious power money, or havn't you learned that yet? you're another stupid idiot.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382787493970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 07:38:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382788428921-13</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am seeing u as their little #$%$ in that camp when history repeats. eat chyt and die, no one would notice</Msg><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382788428921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 07:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382791015961-14</Id><Topic><Title>ok , techstrategy? since AMZN going up "works for you" at what level , does it not work for you?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382787364933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 07:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sold all your inconsequential position at $308. Fund managers cannot do the same. Which is why they play these behavioral investing games on float jams scams because they understand that by anchoring on a #360 valuation, they'll be able to exit much more by $200 than if they never ran the float jam scam from $200 last Fall. But, it will fall back to $100 or below. And none of it, up or down, will have created any value. Just one giant skimming operation because it is all about trading liquid assets rather than investing in productive ones. The financial system is going to have a giant reset and the catalyst will be fundamentals/reality. The "wealth" most have accumulated will be wiped away rather quickly and those in the sector will find they are ill equipped for productive work required in the future.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382791015961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 08:36:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382791980506-15</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somewhat correct, but misleading. Most "selection" is value destroying. Some call it Pareto principle. But, eBay has more "selection" than Amazon. COST is better positoned for the future with its cost structure than Amazon. Besides, Amazon is doing a fine job of killing Amazon. It has levered up into another fast approaching deleveraging cycle and has consumed all its cash in doing so. Has blown through the NWC proceeds from Q4's offering already. A shock (which is all fairly likely given speculative leverage everywhere, record student loan delinquencies and defaults, sub prime auto lending, etc) reverses the benefit of the cash conversion cycle while having all those unearned revenues get claimed. I just want to see which fund managers are going to put new cash to work in the next offering, because they will become the poster children for moral hazard for a generation or two...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382791980506</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 08:53:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382792082857-16</Id><Topic><Title>ok , techstrategy? since AMZN going up "works for you" at what level , does it not work for you?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382787364933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 07:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>um... if it was your postion, it would be consequential right? Turning the stock from $50 to over $300 wasn't consequential at all for me. I see you won't answer the question as to where you strikes and dates were going into the lastest up AMZN run. I don't blame you for keeping that information to yourself: as that makes your whiole trading thesis and timing in AMZN stock look bad. I''m locked in, but still interested in the mind of a short seller in a stock like AMZN in fhe face of the Fed still providing, along with all the other banks of the world, tons of fuel for more rally. It's one thing to sell gains, it's another to be short into what has proven to be a steam roller and it has been for all you shorts.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382792082857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 08:54:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382792134013-17</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're an idiot not really worth having much of a conversation with. You and Sybil spell and talk on the same level. Both idiots.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382792134013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 08:55:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382792202979-18</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>though I guess inconsequential is all relative: such as to the gains of someone like Carl icahn and his recent gains in NFLX: near a billion I'm reading.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382792202979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 08:56:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382792739898-19</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but i wasn't looking to converse with u, it is u who need to feed the little ego just like the recent bunch of old trolls that crawled out of their holes on cmg board after long absence as they claimed they "sold' at 350 or 325 or 300 whatever. u monkeys have no life if u don't throw feces around yourselves. same traits.</Msg><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382792739898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:05:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382792827694-20</Id><Topic><Title>ok , techstrategy? since AMZN going up "works for you" at what level , does it not work for you?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382787364933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 07:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>labor camps will fix u</Msg><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382792827694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382792860324-21</Id><Title>Staunch Bandwaggon shorts will end up thowing in the towel within 15% of the top most likely next week</Title><Msg>At 425+ there will be few retail shorts left.... Once robots pile on there will be no sharez available for retailerz to short. We will hit the top at the mid - end of december. What a run!!! Sybby sure missed that one in a big way.... Although sybby covered to mucho cash a while back, sybby just couldnt muster up the courage to squuuueeeeze worthless bitcoin on the long side... Unfortunate.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382792860324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:07:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382793292433-22</Id><Topic><Title>Staunch Bandwaggon shorts will end up thowing in the towel within 15% of the top most likely next week</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382792860324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:07:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So how are you going to add to your short when there are none available Sybs? I suspect insitutions will stop lending shares short (here) and when the markets start falling, there wil be a broader short ban, which will only accelerate the drop here because others (INTC) have massive short interest that will become forced buyers...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382793292433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:14:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382793395626-23</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>except I didn't just crawl out here you dumb, ignorant, nasty short. I've been here since 50 when you just started slobbering all over our messy self in shortville. Your a freaking idiot, and angry about it? Yeah, you're a short, and anyone right in the market needs to go to labor camps. You,re also even a bigger idiot comparing CMG to the power of AMZN stock. Face it, you're a complete idiot along with complete ignorance. Blame yourself. Now I'm in YOUR FACE conversing with you whether you like it or not. Keep it going.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382793395626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:16:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382793541945-24</Id><Title>cashback,you idiot, i've been here since AMZN was a lower two digit stock, I just don't live on this board</Title><Msg>like you dumbells trying to figure out why AMZN keeps going up against you losing short postions. But I'm more amazed that none of you use trailing stops into force fed POMO's everyday. That's idiotic. And you still all talk about your CMG conquests. Face it, you all lost more than that in shorting AMZN. All of you.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382793541945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:19:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382793737921-25</Id><Topic><Title>Staunch Bandwaggon shorts will end up thowing in the towel within 15% of the top most likely next week</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382792860324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:07:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil you dumbarse, you quickly went back to calling long stupid at the first drop from the 313 highs at the end of last Summer. Your like a smelly fart that can change aromas in the wind. No conviction idiot. lol!</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382793737921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:22:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382794404091-26</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unlike AMZN, CMG at least has attractive fundamental economics and a structural cost/throughput advantage to its peers. Amazon doesn't. You are one of the most pathetic people I've come across on the board... Obviously, I meant market moving. I'm sure you have a million plus $ tucked away from your succeessful trading over the years. Yet, none of it will matter because it is denominated in an asset whose value depends upon trust that is being destroyed daily (and is levered at what 60 to 1)? Enjoy your gains. I'm playing a different game long productive assets and short financial ones and my horizon isn't a trade or a year. It is a generation...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382794404091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:33:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382794481744-27</Id><Topic><Title>cashback,you idiot, i've been here since AMZN was a lower two digit stock, I just don't live on this board</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382793541945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:19:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks like nasdaq found himself a new friend to talk to on the internet. just like skidady. get a life d ckless clown. get a life. no one will show u the trading edge</Msg><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382794481744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382794617789-28</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but unlike CMG,AMZN taught alot of you shorts, that it's not easy to time your preconceived notions of when a stock is "doomed." Isn't that right? I think it is. Alot of you came over here together and been completely obliterated shorting AMZN in one manner or another. And all begging and hoping for a reprieve. That's the facts not an opinion.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382794617789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:36:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382794627027-29</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382794627027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:37:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382794710072-30</Id><Topic><Title>cashback,you idiot, i've been here since AMZN was a lower two digit stock, I just don't live on this board</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382793541945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:19:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even better, though he mainly talks to/ praises himself...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382794710072</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:38:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382794712716-31</Id><Topic><Title>cashback,you idiot, i've been here since AMZN was a lower two digit stock, I just don't live on this board</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382793541945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:19:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, show me a trading edge cashback? your'e so enlightening to holding to the "key" of how I can make money. I warned every damn one of you CMG d-bags last year and it's all on this board to see. And you're still , expecially you, a bunch of d-bags!!</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382794712716</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382794781373-32</Id><Topic><Title>cashback,you idiot, i've been here since AMZN was a lower two digit stock, I just don't live on this board</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382793541945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:19:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and I feel bad for some, but not a d-bag like yourself. You deserve it.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382794781373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:39:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382794887319-33</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Well said." said one idiot shot to another. classic.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382794887319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:41:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382794968810-34</Id><Title>bring it shorts, I've got some time this am to hear the same thesis you've been barking about for 16 months, and 150 points</Title><Msg>mind boggling to watch you all justify staying in growing losing postiions.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382794968810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:42:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382795122591-35</Id><Title>"no one will show u the trading edge" what? like losing 100-250 points without placing stops b/c "it must go down?"</Title><Msg>that's one of the dumbest trading edge strategies ever. Perhaps making some to understand the situation more. Bring it you vile shorts, not all of you, i got it coming back right at ya.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382795122591</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:45:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382795234455-36</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. AMZN taught that Banksters moral hazard has extended TBTF to AMZN, so they need the shock excuse to let reality set in...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382795234455</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382795317136-37</Id><Title>ok, give a thumbdowns for all my post plese, b/c I tell you all the truth and you can't take it:</Title><Msg>I hope I get about 50, which means your all stuck short in a stock with limitied float, going up daily on neverending POMO money into the strongest part of the Season for a stock like AMZN, the Holiday Season lol!! Yeah "any minute now" it's gonna crash. Like I said long ago: "your fellow short, is your enemy is AMZN stock." some of you are pretty dense not to know that. ironically, Sybil may be giving you all the proper warning here. We'll see.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382795317136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382796083866-38</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>where's your strikes, how much have you lost in AMZN, and for how long: that's a pertinent question anyone taking you at full value: just like Paulo Santo: your thesis has led you to lose alot of money. Try to skip around those question for the 100 th time. I don't think you have a clue how WS works I worked there, you worked for Mckinsey. big difference. big big difference. Hard to analyze something you know so little about and bigtime inflexible on. And that cost you.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382796083866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:01:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382796190742-39</Id><Topic><Title>ok, give a thumbdowns for all my post plese, b/c I tell you all the truth and you can't take it:</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382795317136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. A corrupt system that is overrun with predatory trading using asymmetric information (co-location, quote stuffing fantaseconds) to essentially steal from actual investors in the greatest skimming operation of all time is the enemy. Fellow shorts are bit players...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382796190742</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:03:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382796496364-40</Id><Topic><Title>ok, give a thumbdowns for all my post plese, b/c I tell you all the truth and you can't take it:</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382795317136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no, a corrupt system b/c you were on the wrong side of what you thought. Let me clue you in: alot, who are out working hard the world, don't think it's corrupt to see their 401 k's skyrocketing and making real welath on the gains You sound like a whining baby , you really do. You get beat on something you didn't understand. Part of it was stepped up QE, which you completely denied when it happened that it would help the market to even higher heights. You've bee dead wrong....period. And that needs to be pointed out if you're gonna pontificate here endlessly as if you know what's going on, you havn't shown you do. nothing but a Monday morning QB trying to explain why your losses added up. A whining baby.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382796496364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:08:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382796725226-41</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I remember when AMZN went from 240 to 170..he claimed to have double his position first and then when the stock kept dropping he claimed to have sold it all. ohh yea...he also claims that he bought at $2. He is beyond help!</Msg><Username>dowto6k</Username><Timestamp>1382796725226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:12:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382796881256-42</Id><Topic><Title>ok, give a thumbdowns for all my post plese, b/c I tell you all the truth and you can't take it:</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382795317136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much did you lose in 2007-08? Or you sold back then as well? What did the people say about their 401ks? You have no clue.</Msg><Username>dowto6k</Username><Timestamp>1382796881256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:14:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382797091853-43</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, McKinsey had values... (even if Gupta f'd up and tarnished the brand). And McKinsey actually helps companies become more productive and profitable (though we too got caught up in "asset light strategies"... one of my biggest arguments in the first was me calling BS on "value creation" from off BS financing for chem/biotech player and fortunately the DCS agreed with me). Fundamentals are fundamentals. Success is determined over the long haul. We are approaching a one in a cnetury phase transition and the assets that will have value are very different than those of today. More importantly, the skill sets that will capture the ongoing flow of value in the future are very different. I'm playing for what you cannot see because you are simply another egocentric trader who cannot see anything beyond onesself or in the longer term. You are inconsequential from the future's POV...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382797091853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:18:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382797166279-44</Id><Topic><Title>ok, give a thumbdowns for all my post plese, b/c I tell you all the truth and you can't take it:</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382795317136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dowto6k, I lost nothing in 2007-9, and gained over 300 % since 2008-9? how about you? no wonder you're such a bitter man. You probably shorted the market starting in end of 2008-9? You sound like that type of idiot. And by the way, show me a post where I sold 170 and see where I really sold which I wish I handn't. I know all you BS makes you feel better, but I deal with reality here, not your bitter spin to try to make a loser like you feel better duriong the greatest bull market of our lifetime. 331 short is just you latest debacle in AMZN in a long line of them. And you still ask newmarket, why not short AMZN? You're proof of why not. There's still idiots like you out there for the big money to fleece more out of who didn't give up, despite 100-250 run against them. You're on the high side of that number which makes you maybe the biggest idiot of all in the short world. You know it, and I know it. Because I've seen you morph I'D's here b/c of it.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382797166279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:19:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382797332915-45</Id><Topic><Title>ok, give a thumbdowns for all my post plese, b/c I tell you all the truth and you can't take it:</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382795317136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fed isn't doing anybody any favors creating bubbles and crashes over and over.</Msg><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382797332915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:22:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382797370397-46</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You are inconsequential from the future's POV" yeah, of course it has to be the "future" b/c anyone looking back at 16 months conversation with you, will know damn well I've been right compared to you about the past: and that's documented here. No spin to be made to that. And I'm locked in to the gain of what I said as well. Which burns people like down26000 to no end.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382797370397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:22:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382797507198-47</Id><Topic><Title>bring it shorts, I've got some time this am to hear the same thesis you've been barking about for 16 months, and 150 points</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382794968810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:42:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>S300 of AMZN's stock price is already based on future wild speculation.</Msg><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382797507198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:25:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382797515310-48</Id><Topic><Title>ok, give a thumbdowns for all my post plese, b/c I tell you all the truth and you can't take it:</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382795317136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The fed isn't doing anybody any favors creating bubbles and crashes over and over." especially to the ones shorting into this. Big difference here is the Fed still is giving $85 billion a moths to this, they were RAISING rates into the last period of crashes that I believe you are referring to. Big big big difference.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382797515310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:25:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382797830321-49</Id><Title>Optionz buyerz are like methhead Tuco in Breaking Bad</Title><Msg>SNNNNNOOOOOOOORRRRRRRT: "oooooooooooooooo TIGHT TIGHT TIGHT!" It didnt end well for Tuco either.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382797830321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:30:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382797841233-50</Id><Title>Even if this ended in a crash, the key is staying solvent to benefit from that condition no?</Title><Msg>there's a famous Galbraith quote to that s,ubject. To each his own, especially one's finances, and decisions. Don't blame decicsions made by/for yourself on someone else. If anyone of you ever were to catch a crash, I guess with your persistance then you were to deserve it. Good luck</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382797841233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382798030900-51</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>by the way tech,let me clue you in, there were lifetime type gains made in some of these issues since 2008 that's gonna be LT helping. Crticizie me all you want b/c I saw the writing of them as a ST trader. lol! It' was over 5 years. A ST trader is more someone like you or Sybil going against the trends in place.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382798030900</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:33:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382798334741-52</Id><Title>saturday morning</Title><Msg>and I already got this psychotic monkey all worked up. hopefully by noon it gets heart attack and finita.</Msg><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382798334741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:38:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382798337943-53</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A ST trader is more someone like you" Yes! It is only LT if his has a $100 per share on his short.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382798337943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:38:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382798864155-54</Id><Topic><Title>By the way, techstrategy? let me clue you in on analysts: they upgrade near tops, and downgrade near bottoms</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382740840443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" just like Paulo Santo: your thesis has led you to lose alot of money." Yes, my name for his thesis is "wreckstrategy".</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382798864155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:47:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382799923824-55</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Most "selection" is value destroying." No, it is what drives growth. Amazon is a growth stock at this stage. Limiting selection destroys growth. This is why you have misjudged Amazon, you are ignorant of growth investing, and so are saddled with a $100 per share loss on your "value" biased short. "But, eBay has more "selection" " So what? It is an auction model which means limited revenue as most consumers do not wish to wait around or fuss with auctions. "COST is better positoned blah, blah..." COST offers a tiny fraction of selection. "Besides, Amazon is doing a fine job of killing Amazon." No, they are killing your wreckstrategy $240 short, down nearly $100 per share and counting.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382799923824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 11:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382800003829-56</Id><Title>Negative profit margins, negative return on equity, and negative PE RATIO.</Title><Msg>Bernie Madoff would be so proud.</Msg><Username>fig_plucker</Username><Timestamp>1382800003829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 11:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382800191243-57</Id><Topic><Title>Negative profit margins, negative return on equity, and negative PE RATIO.</Title><Username>fig_plucker</Username><Timestamp>1382800003829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 11:06:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget the boys at Enron, They are jumping with joy seeing that their 'model' is still alive and well:)</Msg><Username>shortstack_now</Username><Timestamp>1382800191243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 11:09:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382800394250-58</Id><Topic><Title>Negative profit margins, negative return on equity, and negative PE RATIO.</Title><Username>fig_plucker</Username><Timestamp>1382800003829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 11:06:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And lets not forget the buy side analyst jumping up and down pounding the table here. They probably have pictures of Blodgett and meeker hung on their walls. One must have a role models you know:)</Msg><Username>fig_plucker</Username><Timestamp>1382800394250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 11:13:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382800733829-59</Id><Topic><Title>LION BRODCAST VS FRAUD STREET BANKSTER FRAUD ANALYST TERRORIST: OUTRIGHT DUMP AND AVOID RATIUNG ON AMAZON ENFORCED</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382730679201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 15:51:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today, all that is left of America is a deeply-indebted welfare state run by a corrupt cabal of tyrants who have no moral authority, no faith of the People and no solutions. America has devolved into a corrupt, bankrupt, incompetent government tyranny headed for imminent collapse. HERE WE HAVE FRAUD STREET CASINO OPERATED BY HOME GROWN FINANCIAL TERRORIST BANKSTERS LOOTING ALL 99% WORKING CLASS PENSIONS WITH THEIR FRAUD PONZI BUBBLE MANIA BUSINESS MODELS WITH #$%$" ACCOUNTING RULES AT "SEC'........ CORPORATE THUGS LIKE MF THUG GREED HASTINGS BECOMING BILLIONAIRES WITH ALL FRAUD SUPPORTED AND PROTECTED BY CRIMINALS AT "SEC'/BANKING COMMITTEE &amp; OBAMA/ERIC HOLDER CHICAGO MAFIA SHILLS IN WHITE HOUSE &amp; DOJ ===================== The day the U.S. government collapses in default is fast approaching Because an exponential rise in debt cannot be sustained, at some point the U.S. government will simply collapse into financial default. Soon after, Martial Law will have to be declared in every major U.S. city to quell the riots. Imagine 50 million Americans going hungry and realizing their welfare food credits aren’t going to be available anymore and you begin to get an idea of why cities will be nearly impossible to survive when the chaos hits. The impending failure of the federal government is now obvious to everyone. Even Ron Paul is now openly talking about the coming collapse of the U.S. empire, mirroring the overnight collapse of the Soviet empire in 1991, where that nation broke into twelve independent republics. Many people now believe the U.S. is headed for a similar outcome, and that such an outcome can happen virtually overnight. The crash of EBT cards could be the tumbling domino that sets this into action. Nearly every state already has a secessionist movement calling for independence, and the Tenth Amendment Center is leading the charge on state nullification of federal tyranny. Groups like the Oath Keepers are ready to step in and help establish local law and order in the short-term chaos that would follow a dissolution of the U.S. empire. “I believe that banking institutions are more dangerous to our liberties than standing armies.” – Thomas Jefferson If the American people ever allow private banks to control the issue of their currency, first by inflation, then by deflation, the banks…will deprive the people of all property until their children wake-up homeless on the continent their fathers conquered…. The issuing power should be taken from the banks and restored to the people, to whom it properly belongs. – Thomas Jefferson in the debate over the Re-charter of the Bank Bill (1809) Andrew Jackson : Gentlemen, I have had men watching you for a long time and I am convinced that you have used the funds of the bank to speculate in the breadstuffs of the country. When you won, you divided the profits amongst you, and when you lost, you charged it to the bank. You tell me that if I take the deposits from the bank and annul its charter, I shall ruin ten thousand families. That may be true, gentlemen, but that is your sin! Should I let you go on, you will ruin fifty thousand families, and that would be my sin! You are a den of vipers and thieves. DAVID STOCKMAN: We've Been Lied To, Robbed, And Misled</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382800733829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 11:18:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382800791906-60</Id><Topic><Title>FELLOW USA 99% GO AND SURROUND "SEC" HEAD QUARTERS WHERE THESE CRIMINALS GET ALL FRAUD WEAPONS TO SCAM/BANG/LOOT US ALL</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382716651223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 11:57:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“I believe that banking institutions are more dangerous to our liberties than standing armies.” – Thomas Jefferson If the American people ever allow private banks to control the issue of their currency, first by inflation, then by deflation, the banks…will deprive the people of all property until their children wake-up homeless on the continent their fathers conquered…. The issuing power should be taken from the banks and restored to the people, to whom it properly belongs. – Thomas Jefferson in the debate over the Re-charter of the Bank Bill (1809) Andrew Jackson : Gentlemen, I have had men watching you for a long time and I am convinced that you have used the funds of the bank to speculate in the breadstuffs of the country. When you won, you divided the profits amongst you, and when you lost, you charged it to the bank. You tell me that if I take the deposits from the bank and annul its charter, I shall ruin ten thousand families. That may be true, gentlemen, but that is your sin! Should I let you go on, you will ruin fifty thousand families, and that would be my sin! You are a den of vipers and thieves. DAVID STOCKMAN: We've Been Lied To, Robbed, And Misled</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382800791906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 11:19:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382801705037-61</Id><Title>LESS THAN 3% SHORT ON AMZN......THERE IS NO SQUEEZE...</Title><Msg>This blow off top in all stocks will end in a crash across the board....get ready...everyone ginned up for a christmas run into the end of the year and a correction next year......i love it when "everyone" is on board.........................giiit ready you pigs the knives are sharpening not only here but across the board.........</Msg><Username>lemmeknow23</Username><Timestamp>1382801705037</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 11:35:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382802800939-62</Id><Topic><Title>FELLOW USA 99% GO AND SURROUND "SEC" HEAD QUARTERS WHERE THESE CRIMINALS GET ALL FRAUD WEAPONS TO SCAM/BANG/LOOT US ALL</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382716651223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 11:57:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WALL STREET SLUMLORDS PILLAGING RENTERS AFTER DESTROYING OWNERS1 commentPosted on 26th October 2013 by Administrator in Economy |Politics |Social Issues Blackstone, buy to rent, Foreclosure, fraud, Mike Krieger, mortgages, rodents, #$%$, slime, Wall street bankers Does anyone else see a common theme regarding what is happening in this country? Wall Street banks created the largest housing bubble in history with the help of their puppets at the Federal Reserve through a massive control fraud based upon fraudulent mortgage products, the packaging of these fraudulent loans into derivatives, below market interest rates, fraud in the inducement, and outright lies and deceit. They then held the American taxpayer hostage to bail them out from their criminal conspiracy when it all blew up in their faces. After being bailed out, they proceeded to conduct a massive foreclosure fraud by faking millions of legal contracts and destroying the lives of millions of homeowners. They then colluded with the government, Fannie and Freddie to purposefully create an artificial shortage of housing by sitting on millions of foreclosed homes and creating a new “asset class” of buy to rent homes. These Wall Street #$%$bags have bought hundreds of thousands of homes across the country, driving prices skyward and eliminating any chance that young families could buy at a reasonable price. Their master plan has been to drive prices up and then dump these properties when their Ivy League MBA created models tell them to dump. They care nothing for the tenants they have lured into these “investments”. With home prices having peaked this past summer and higher mortgage rates making affordability impossible for an average family, these Wall Street rodents are scampering for the gangway. Meanwhile, the families they destroyed in 2008/2009 are getting #$%$ again in 2013 as they rent from the same slimeballs that lured them into buying eight years ago. When will people wake up and realize who the true enemy is?</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382802800939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 11:53:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382802893459-63</Id><Topic><Title>FELLOW USA 99% GO AND SURROUND "SEC" HEAD QUARTERS WHERE THESE CRIMINALS GET ALL FRAUD WEAPONS TO SCAM/BANG/LOOT US ALL</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382716651223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 11:57:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not shocking, saw this one coming when Ob ama announced the gubment was going to fund the new “rent to own” scheme to “keep ‘murkins in their homes.” Now the next step will be for this to fester for a couple more years, then when the bottom is falling out of the market – again – the gubment will swoop in and enact sweeping legislation to “control and protect” the renters, which will end up being ANOTHER funding from ‘murkins to the elite at the heads of these companies. Of course, just like the lead law, the rubber tariffs, the “Food Safety Act,” etc., etc., the gubment’s “help and protection” will equate to running the small, family, landlords out of business while increasing the profit margins of these parasites. Doubt it? Check out Mattel’s profits and sales pre-lead law and after. There sales “shot up” by 30% (so did their prices, that was NEVER reported), and their profits SURGED while small, American toy and kids’ clothing companies were run out of business. It’s for the children ya’ know. The same children that we continuously shove toxic chemicals into while bullying parents into their consent and backing. The same children that we are feeding horrific, processed, NAME BRAND, poisons, calling them “healthy” because they only contain FAKE FAT and “whole grains.” The people in this country that continue to trust these #$%$ with their lives, and very health, and mandate that my family trust them too, deserve the pain, suffering, illness and poverty headed their way. Too bad the rest of us will all still have to pay for it. Until the day we figure out going Galt isn’t a horror, but our saving grace. I’m betting the numbers going Galt will EXPLODE once the market crashes and millions that think they have done the right thing and sweated and saved to have “security” figure out that between outright taxes, hidden taxes, and Obamacare expenses, they have no other choice. Dad always said you can’t get blood from a turnip, looks like our country as a whole is going to be figuring this out soon.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382802893459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 11:54:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382803262890-64</Id><Title>THE NEW NORMAL IN USA?HELLO USA 99% ZOMBIES: CAN YOU FIX BRAINS TO ABSORB HARSH REALITY FACTS AKA TRUTH OR FRAUD PROPAGANDA $UCKED BRAINS CAN NOT BE REPROGRAMMED?</Title><Msg>THE NEW NORMAL IN USA?HELLO USA 99% ZOMBIES: CAN YOU FIX BRAINS TO ABSORB HARSH REALITY FACTS AKA TRUTH OR FRAUD PROPAGANDA $UCKED BRAINS CAN NOT BE REPROGRAMMED? Our government and financial “leaders” tell us that things are back to normal and we are well on our way to economic recovery. They report rising GDP, declining unemployment, and record corporate profits. The legacy media propaganda machines, controlled by corporations dependent upon the government and Wall Street to funnel them advertising dollars in return for reporting falsehoods and mistruths, have been informing the masses that all is well. Just go back to staring at your iGadgets and tweeting your every thought to your followers, because the best and brightest in D.C. and Wall Street have it all figured out. The new normal is here to stay. I guess my interpretation of normal deviates slightly from our glorious leaders’ definition. During the long-term bond bull market, from 1982 until 2007 the 10 Year Treasury steadily declined from 16% to 5%. This was normal because inflation declined at the same rate. Inflation declined from 13% to 3% over this same time frame according to the BLS. In reality, measuring inflation as it was measured in the 80′s and early 90′s would have yielded an inflation rate closer to 6% in 2007. During the decade prior to 2007, which consisted of supposedly strong economic growth, the 10 Year Treasury ranged between 4% and 7%. Even during the 2001 recession, it never dropped below 3.5%. In a normal world an investor in a 10 Year Treasury bond would require a yield 2% to 3% above the rate of inflation. If the yield was below the rate of inflation they would be guaranteed to lose money. Only a fool, Federal Reserve chairman, or a CNBC bubble headed #$%$ would buy a bond yielding less than the inflation rate. The BLS reported inflation rate has been between 2.1% and 3.2% over the last two years. Over this time frame, the 10 Year Treasury yielded 2% or below until the threat of tapering reared its ugly head this past summer. Would this happen in a normal free market? If things are back to normal, why aren’t supposedly free markets acting normal? The Chinese and Japanese reacted normally. They stopped buying Treasuries with a real negative yield. The only fool willing to buy negative yielding Treasuries is none other than Ben Bernanke. He thinks they are the investment of a lifetime. He is so sure they are a can’t miss investment, he buys $2.5 billion of them per day, which just so happens to be the government deficit per day. Ben now has $3.8 trillion of bonds on his books, versus $900 billion in 2008. His balance sheet is leveraged 60 to 1, versus the 30 to 1 of Lehman and Bear Stearns prior to their implosions. When even the hint of reducing bond purchases from $85 billion per month to $75 billion per month caused 10 Year rates to jump from 1.5% to 3% in a matter of weeks, you realize how “normal” our economy and financial system is functioning. If our financial system was functioning normally and free market capitalism was allowed to operate according to true supply and demand, the 10 Year Treasury would be yielding 4% to 5% and 30 year mortgage rates would be 6% to 7%. Think about that for a minute. This scenario was normal from 2002 through 2007. That is what normal looks like. Now open your eyes and observe what your owners are telling you is normal. The slight increase in mortgage rates from 3.5% to 4.5% has brought the Wall Street buy and rent housing recovery scheme to it knees. Imagine if mortgage rates were allowed to rise to their true market rate. Housing would collapse in a heap.Allowing Treasury rates to adjust to a true market rate, based on true inflation, would double or triple the annual interest expense on the $17 trillion national debt and blow a gigantic hole in Obama’s already disastrous $1 trillion annual deficits. Does this sound like “normal” to a rational thinking human being with the ability to understand simple math? Luckily, there are very few rational thinking Americans left and even fewer with the ability to understand simple math. We have been programmed to believe rather than think. As long as the stock market continue to rise, then everything is normal. Do you think Ben Bernanke and his cohorts at the Federal Reserve worry about the average person who doesn’t own stocks, has to fill up their gas tank, feed their kids, make the mortgage, auto, and credit card payments, and figure out Obamacare, while working two part time jobs? Quantitative Easing (MONEY PRINTING) has one purpose and one purpose only – to further enrich the owners of the Federal Reserve – Wall Street banks. The .1% own most of the stocks in this country and their greed and avarice can never be satisfied.This artificial prosperity plan for Wall Street has the added benefit of allowing the captured politicians in Washington D.C. to continue their $1 trillion per year deficit spending with no consequences for their squandering of future generations’ wealth. Bernanke and Yellen will never taper, because they can’t. The Fed balance sheet will continue to grow by at least $1 trillion per year until they crash the financial system again. Except this time, there will be no money printing solution. We are all trapped like rats in this monetary experiment being conducted by evil mad scientists. No one will get out alive. Welcome to the new normal. Now eat your cheese.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382803262890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 12:01:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382803350074-65</Id><Topic><Title>THE NEW NORMAL IN USA?HELLO USA 99% ZOMBIES: CAN YOU FIX BRAINS TO ABSORB HARSH REALITY FACTS AKA TRUTH OR FRAUD PROPAGANDA $UCKED BRAINS CAN NOT BE REPROGRAMMED?</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382803262890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 12:01:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Close Look at the Decrepit World of Wall Street Rental Homes Posted on October 25, 2013 by Michael Krieger This new incursion by hedge funds and private equity groups into the American single-family home rental market is unprecedented, and is proving disastrous for many of the tens of thousands of families who are moving into these newly converted rental homes. In recent weeks, HuffPost spoke with more than a dozen current tenants, along with former employees who recently left the real estate companies. Though it’s not uncommon for tenants to complain about their landlords, many who had rented before described their current experience as the worst they’ve ever had. A former inspector for American Homes 4 Rent who worked in the Dallas office said he routinely examined homes just prior to rental that were not habitable. Though it wasn’t his job to answer complaints, he said he fielded “hundreds of calls” from irate tenants. - From the Huffington Post’s excellent article: Here’s What Happens When Wall Street Builds A Rental Empire This is a topic that I have been writing extensively on since the beginning of the year. In fact, I don’t think there’s another topic I have focused so intently on in the whole of 2013, with the exception of the NSA revelations. It all started back in January with my post titled, America Meet Your New Slumlord: Wall Street, which received a huge amount of attention in the alternative media world. I knew from the start that this whole “buy-to-rent” thing would be a disaster. Over the last decade or so, everything that Wall Street touched has turned into a scheme primarily focused on parasitically funneling wealth and resources away from society at large to itself. This is no different. They call it a “new asset class.” I call it Wall Street serfdom. What makes this article even more interesting is that it’s not simply greed, it is also obvious that these Wall Street firms have no idea what the #$%$ they are doing. For example: Former employees of the companies, who spoke on condition of anonymity because they worry about jeopardizing their careers, said their former colleagues can’t keep up with the volume of complaints. The rush to buy up as many homes as possible has stretched resources to the point of breaking, these people said. My advice to people out there in the rental market, is they should try to avoid Wall Street rentals. The three main companies highlighted in this article are: Invitation Homes (owned by Blackstone), Colony American and American Homes 4 Rent. Unfortunately, it appears these companies may try to hide their presence in certain markets so you may have to do additional digging. For example, WRI Property Management is the local agent of Colony American in Georgia. More from the Huffington Post: There’s no escaping the stench of raw sewage in Mindy Culpepper’s Atlanta-area rental home. The odor greets her before she turns into her driveway each evening as she returns from work. It’s there when she prepares dinner, and only diminishes when she and her husband hunker down in their bedroom, where they now eat their meals. For the $1,225 a month she pays for the three-bedroom house in the quiet suburb of Lilburn, Culpepper thinks it isn’t too much to expect that her landlord, Colony American Homes, make the necessary plumbing repairs to eliminate the smell. But her complaints have gone unanswered, she said. Short of buying a plane ticket to visit the company’s office in Scottsdale, Ariz., she is out of ideas. “You can not get in touch with them, you can’t get them on the phone, you can’t get them to respond to an email,” said Culpepper, whose family has lived with the problem since the day they moved in five months ago. “My certified letters, they don’t get answered.” Most rental houses in the U.S. are owned by individuals, or small, local businesses. Culpepper’s landlord is part of a new breed: a Wall Street-backed investment company with billions of dollars at its disposal. Over the past two years, Colony American and its two biggest competitors, Invitation Homes and American Homes 4 Rent, have spent more than $12 billion buying and renovating at least 75,000 homes in order to rent them out. Most who spoke with HuffPost said they moved into their rental homes only to find that renovations they were assured were comprehensive amounted to little more than a fresh coat of paint and new carpeting. Tenants said they immediately discovered major mechanical and plumbing problems: broken water heaters and air conditioners, broken toilets and in some cases even vermin infestations, including fleas, silverfish and rodents. Several weeks after Rosemary moved into the Raleigh, N.C., house she’s renting from American Homes 4 Rent, her hot water tank exploded. Rosemary, who declined to use her last name for fear of losing her security deposit, said she couldn’t shower for days. It took constant calls and emails to the rental company before they sent someone to replace the tank. Former employees of the companies, who spoke on condition of anonymity because they worry about jeopardizing their careers, said their former colleagues can’t keep up with the volume of complaints. The rush to buy up as many homes as possible has stretched resources to the point of breaking, these people said. A former inspector for American Homes 4 Rent who worked in the Dallas office said he routinely examined homes just prior to rental that were not habitable. Though it wasn’t his job to answer complaints, he said he fielded “hundreds of calls” from irate tenants. “It’s just a slumlord,” Culpepper said of Colony American. “A huge, billion-dollar slumlord.” Indeed, and it shouldn’t be a surprise to anyone.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382803350074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 12:02:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382803478426-66</Id><Topic><Title>THE NEW NORMAL IN USA?HELLO USA 99% ZOMBIES: CAN YOU FIX BRAINS TO ABSORB HARSH REALITY FACTS AKA TRUTH OR FRAUD PROPAGANDA $UCKED BRAINS CAN NOT BE REPROGRAMMED?</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382803262890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 12:01:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“The really dangerous American fascist… is the man who wants to do in the United States in an American way what Hitler did in Germany in a Prussian way. The American fascist would prefer not to use violence. His method is to poison the channels of public information. With a fascist the problem is never how best to present the truth to the public but how best to use the news to deceive the public into giving the fascist and his group more money or more power… They claim to be super-patriots, but they would destroy every liberty guaranteed by the Constitution. They demand free enterprise, but are the spokesmen for monopoly and vested interest. Their final objective, toward which all their deceit is directed, is to capture political power so that, using the power of the state and the power of the market simultaneously, they may keep the common man in eternal subjection. ~quoted in the New York Times, April 9, 1944” ― Henry A. Wallace “Still another danger is represented by those who, paying lip service to democracy and the common welfare, in their insatiable greed for money and the power which money gives, do not hesitate surreptitiously to evade the laws designed to safeguard the public from monopolistic extortion. They are patriotic in time of war because it is to their interest to be so, but in time of peace they follow power and the dollar wherever they may lead.” ― Henry A. Wallace “If we define an American fascist as one who in case of conflict puts money and power ahead of human beings, then there are undoubtedly several million fascists in the United States.” ― Henry A. Wallace “The American fascists are most easily recognized by their deliberate perversion of truth and fact.” ― Henry A. Wallace “In an effort to eliminate the possibility of any rival growing up, some monopolists would sacrifice democracy itself.” ― Henry A. Wallace</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382803478426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 12:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382803867464-67</Id><Topic><Title>how about making this prediction techstrategy? how high does AMZN stock go today?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382706883468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 09:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So the strategy has changed from DITM LT puts to OOM LT puts. Good move, you'll bleed out much slower.</Msg><Username>skiidady1</Username><Timestamp>1382803867464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 12:11:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382804065875-68</Id><Title>@ singhlion</Title><Msg>you post on these boards but the people who participate in these boards by reading and posting are the best and the smartest 10% of the population or even less. or some are useless paid shills. majority are as dumb as piece of wood. they have no clue what is fed or what is stock or god forbid weekly option casino, so you are wasting your time and energy. there will be no revolution by the poor until they become majority of the population and for now they are still protected class. please listen to George Carlin again and again.</Msg><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382804065875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 12:14:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382805157507-69</Id><Topic><Title>2008 on $100 and Friday in 1 day + $ 30.</Title><Username>ruudkrul</Username><Timestamp>1382772907489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 03:35:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>about 3 years on on day +$ 100. On 1 day +$ 30 is unbelievable. How strong is a dollar?</Msg><Username>ruudkrul</Username><Timestamp>1382805157507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 12:32:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382805187984-70</Id><Topic><Title>saturday morning</Title><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382798334741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:38:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't insult the other d'ckless clowns in rural Seattle by mentioning "skiidady"</Msg><Username>bionic_ironic</Username><Timestamp>1382805187984</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 12:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382805579507-71</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a sweetspot for "selection". Walmart has it. More SKUs above is more overhead on lowest volume. Growth in super low volume items isn't desirable, but that's what amazon has done with "more" SKUs. It'll always cost them more money is the only accomplishment there... a negative.</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382805579507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 12:39:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382806048026-72</Id><Topic><Title>how about making this prediction techstrategy? how high does AMZN stock go today?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382706883468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 09:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I let the parabola run right through my strikes. But, I won't bleed out -- I'll be here for it to run right back through them to the downside. And, the more they push the BS, the more negligently divergent "analyst" targets and communication I accumlate and document. Also, having fun watching Cap'ns'crew (Q4/Q1 quants that entered to run this low volume float scam to the final collapse). Hope they get a forensic review of the consolidated tape someday for the AAPLtrage and the algo/option manipulation.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382806048026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 12:47:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382806868037-73</Id><Topic><Title>saturday morning</Title><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382798334741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:38:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The psychotic monkey has NO position whatsoever. He claims to have made a few million dollars in AMZN alone and he here all day 24/7..go figure!</Msg><Username>dowto6k</Username><Timestamp>1382806868037</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:01:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382806896019-74</Id><Topic><Title>What shorts are forgetting</Title><Username>cospringboard</Username><Timestamp>1382701143301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 07:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree to the extent that the initiatives that they are currently involved in do not come to fruition. Yes, as an investor (which I am as I bought in at 128) I would like to see positive cash flow. However, we are also watching them diversify in to many different areas. This costs a great deal of money. My biggest concern is actually not the cash flow but the multitude of somewhat seemingly unrelated business ventures that they are getting in to. For example, why Tenmarks? If this is all dependent on the success of the Kindle then even more worrisome. However, I am betting on the fact that at least some of these (like the video/programming) become wildly successful and eventually generate revenue in their own right. I buy so many of my items from Amazon that I am taking the Peter Lynch view of the stock. However, in this environment where the big tend to get bigger I am buy into the story. I agree at some point they will have to stop dumping money in to data centers, distribution centers and video and it will need to be profitable. They are in all the right areas though and far be it from me to know when the market starts to valuate them in traditional terms. When it happens though, I believe that we will have plenty of warning and by then I would hope that they are profitable andor I expect that the stock will be higher than it is today.</Msg><Username>cospringboard</Username><Timestamp>1382806896019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:01:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382806957751-75</Id><Topic><Title>saturday morning</Title><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382798334741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 10:38:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't insult the people in Seattle by mentioning this d'ckless clown in the same sentence with Seattle. We disown him.</Msg><Username>dowto6k</Username><Timestamp>1382806957751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382807362398-76</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst Kool Aide Drinkers!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382732698989</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 16:24:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMZN is cornered now in a poor position. 1) losing the tablet war against AAPL MSFT &amp; SAMSUNG. They all have superior product with better sales and deeper pockets. Competitive advantages owned by the competition. 2) losing the online retail war against WMT. Walmart ecommerce growth rate is already higher than AMZN. Walmart is luring away IT talent and is improving it's website. It's investing billions now. Already price matching and can go lower price than AMZN can ever go. Competitive advantages all owned by the competition. 3) losing the content war. NFLX, AAPL, ETC. everyody is encroaching, but everybody else has found competitive advantage. 4) losing the Best Buy war. AMZN was making all its traction by beating Best Buy, but BB is finally turning the tide. AMZN doesn't win on price anymore for DVDs or computer gadgets. So, people aren't browsing BB and then buying on amazon anymore. AMZN finds itself in a SHTF corner now. Costs up, no way to make money, running out of cash and no competitive advantage to turn to. Q4 will be a loss too obviously, but also with revenue growth stalled out due to a poor holiday season, poor HDX sales, and the competition advancing on every front. Accounting tricks won't even be able to save them either.</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382807362398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:09:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382807702538-77</Id><Topic><Title>What shorts are forgetting</Title><Username>cospringboard</Username><Timestamp>1382701143301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 07:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"see microsoft, dell and apple" How can you mention Microsoft, Dell without even complete knowledge about the company itself. You do realize by the Microsoft was making billions and had billions and billions in cash.</Msg><Username>dowto6k</Username><Timestamp>1382807702538</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:15:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382809032967-78</Id><Topic><Title>What shorts are forgetting</Title><Username>cospringboard</Username><Timestamp>1382701143301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 07:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Economies of scale has not been reached with nearly $70Billion in revenues. 20%+ growth rate is going to be extremely hard to achieve with such large numbers. The law of large numbers catches up to them. The company already seems a bit desperate to achieve this growth. Absolutely no focus. Positive Cash Flow is a must. and to justify a $160 billion market cap, it has to be a lot of cash! Strange to see a company give poor guidance for their most important quarter and see the stock rise 10%. Company's top end is for a $500mm profit, lets double it and call it a billion. That is not impressive when you are valued at $160 Billion.</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382809032967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:37:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382809160208-79</Id><Title>The Game</Title><Msg>Stocks like this, CMG, PCLN, NFLX that rise in use % in one day is a sign that analysts severely miscalculated AND that the companies misstate their earnings expectations. Add in the FED free money, and there you have it. You can, in my opinion, battle this by buying both calls and puts.</Msg><Username>llpinter</Username><Timestamp>1382809160208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:39:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382809515647-80</Id><Title>Very high probability of price peak in AMZN stock at 366</Title><Msg>Low was 166. Mid point retrace support line in sand is 265 (for highly skilled tech analysts). Measured move is 363-66. Should retrace for a while from here down to 345 or lower.</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382809515647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382809690504-81</Id><Title>They keep doubling down!!!!</Title><Msg>I bet $1000 on a football game and win!! Yea, but then go and bet $2000 on the next game! AND I WIN now I got $4000... hmmm But I am going good, going to bet $4000 on the evening game. AND I WIN!!! I now have $8000 and bet $8000 on MNF... At some point a smart gambler takes his profits and goes back to betting $1000, and puts $7000 in the bank You haven't won anything until you take profits!</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382809690504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382810287326-82</Id><Topic><Title>Very high probability of price peak in AMZN stock at 366</Title><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382809515647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe the move yesterday was highly exaggerated. I know enough about TA to be dangerous so thank you for your input. But this move after, what was really a report that was in line with estimates, with mediocre guidance. This isn't some small cap stock. It added ~$15B in Market cap. That is an incredible move and unjustified. With $70B in revenues, economy of scale should have been reached, net income should be coming in and FREE CASH FLOW SHOULD BE PLENTIFUL.</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382810287326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:58:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382810479382-83</Id><Topic><Title>What shorts are forgetting</Title><Username>cospringboard</Username><Timestamp>1382701143301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 07:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you born after the clicks mania? big Rev with no profit can be disaster if sells will drop....</Msg><Username>emanuel_dabah</Username><Timestamp>1382810479382</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 14:01:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382810928985-84</Id><Title>google it is AMZON the cheapest place to shop</Title><Msg>you will be surprise what you will find ifehacker site yahoo do not allow to post it the conclusion is WMT cheaper 15%1!!!!</Msg><Username>emanuel_dabah</Username><Timestamp>1382810928985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 14:08:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382811819603-85</Id><Title>How much of growth is organic?</Title><Msg>They are getting more and more desperate. It gets harder and harder to achieve such growth with so $70B in revenues. How much of the growth is organic? How much is being bought? Is the growth increasing margins or decreasing margins? I have so many questions. Are there any real answers? Just a lot of smoke and mirrors.</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382811819603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 14:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382812152551-86</Id><Topic><Title>What shorts are forgetting</Title><Username>cospringboard</Username><Timestamp>1382701143301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 07:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Analyst profit estimates for Q4 are to take high-end of guidance range and triple that! Kool Aide drinkers!!</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382812152551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 14:29:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382812275690-87</Id><Topic><Title>google it is AMZON the cheapest place to shop</Title><Username>emanuel_dabah</Username><Timestamp>1382810928985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 14:08:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I googled it. Amazon is not cheapest on anything. They are either price matched or it's cheaper elsewhere.</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382812275690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 14:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382813129048-88</Id><Title>Deworsification!!!! best description ever!</Title><Msg>This company is so desperate for growth that they are throwing darts at everything hoping something sticks! This POS is lost. They deliver eggs? hahaha</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382813129048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 14:45:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382814801823-89</Id><Topic><Title>how about making this prediction techstrategy? how high does AMZN stock go today?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382706883468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 09:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I let the parabola run right through my strikes" correct me if I'm wrong, doesn't that mean you have had "puts" that expired worthless? You wouldn't be the only one who has had that happen over and over in AMZN.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382814801823</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 15:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382814809982-90</Id><Topic><Title>What shorts are forgetting</Title><Username>cospringboard</Username><Timestamp>1382701143301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 07:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First:The short interest is less than 3%... Second: Amazon has been a public company for 17 years and have generated less than 2.5 BILLION IN PROFITS for its shareholders...AAPL does this 2.5 billion in the first month of any given quarter for the last 5 years and is spending copious amounts of cash on expansion globally...... Third: Operating margins have been declining for over 3 years and are currently around 1%...Even IF THOSE MARGINS HEAD TO 4% OR 5% THIS COMPANY is still over valued by 175 points.... Fourth: Collusion between Wall Street and Amzn have proven to be the catalyst for this fraud we know as Amazon.... Fifth: Amzn balance sheet is riddled with holes...Their intangibles are piling up and they had to borrow money for expansion...Borrowing money in a business with 1% operating margins with 17 billion in revenues is simply a bad joke and unacceptable.... Before ya start chiding me as a " SHORT" STOP....I hold no position as of yet however I will be watching very closely in the coming days.........Not only is Amzn going down, the whole market is on the edge of a CRASH not just a "correction"....Good Luck...Any long will need it in the coming months.........Especially those on MARGIN WHICH THERE IS A BOATLOAD...</Msg><Username>lemmeknow23</Username><Timestamp>1382814809982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 15:13:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382814971746-91</Id><Topic><Title>how about making this prediction techstrategy? how high does AMZN stock go today?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382706883468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 09:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>alot of premium and time decay on your strategy is you way out on them.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382814971746</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 15:16:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382815017662-92</Id><Topic><Title>What shorts are forgetting</Title><Username>cospringboard</Username><Timestamp>1382701143301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 07:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cospringboard, your point is well taken. I am like many on this board as I have a negative view on amzn and have lost $$$ as a result. Let me tell you, if you value a company based on earnings, amzn is a very fustrating company to try to understand. 100% agree... 17 billion is a big deal. My problem is i've shorted amzn based on valuation rather than rev growth. I stand firm on the beleif that amzn is wildly over valued. But I will learn from this experience. I am going to start 1) looking for a signal that amzn rev growth is slowing or 2) the market starts to value amzn based on earnings.</Msg><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1382815017662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 15:16:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382815329662-93</Id><Topic><Title>What shorts are forgetting</Title><Username>cospringboard</Username><Timestamp>1382701143301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 07:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hopefully you don't believe your drivel....17 Billion with operating margins of less than 2% is nothing but a supermarket...A supermarket has a multiple of 12 if they are lucky...Amazon hasn't been able to produce more than 4 % operating margins since inception and that was in early 2000.... If I sell you something for a dollar and it costs me 99 cents Ive made a penny profit howver how much did it cost me to procure the product and pass that product to you? Well I will tell you for a fact it cost me more than a penny of energy and time..THAT IS A FACT....If you listen to the pundits and especially CRAMER THE PIG about how revenues are GROWING YOU ARE A FOOL...................REREAD THE EXAMPLE ABOVE AND PONDER IT.........</Msg><Username>lemmeknow23</Username><Timestamp>1382815329662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 15:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382815537936-94</Id><Title>THIS PIG BOZOS NEEDS TO START BREAKING OUT HIS SALES ON KINDLES AND OTHER PRODUCTS..</Title><Msg>This shyster is propogating this scam stock...sec needs to step in here and stop this fraud..... we need an activist at the helm actively shorting this fraud until the company comes clean on the intangibles and their actual losses.... ever wonder why these crooks dont break down the sales of hardware???hardware that needs to be upgraded every 2 or 3 years.....</Msg><Username>likballs22</Username><Timestamp>1382815537936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 15:25:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382816188008-95</Id><Topic><Title>What shorts are forgetting</Title><Username>cospringboard</Username><Timestamp>1382701143301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 07:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lemmeknow, first, we both agree that amzn is wildly over valued. I don't know about you, but I've lost money as a result of this belief. What if the market isn't valueing amzn based on earnings, but instead they are bidding it up on strong rev growth. What good would it do to short it? Finally, I was very fustrated by the markets reaction to the er as well. I made the same argument that amzn is showing rev growth by buying market share. Heck bezos has been quoted as saying "your margin is my opportunity". The market obviosly doesn't care at the moment.</Msg><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1382816188008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 15:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382816239046-96</Id><Topic><Title>THIS PIG BOZOS NEEDS TO START BREAKING OUT HIS SALES ON KINDLES AND OTHER PRODUCTS..</Title><Username>likballs22</Username><Timestamp>1382815537936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 15:25:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stock Compensation, Capex v. Opex? $70 billion in revenues and there is very little FCF. Yesterday's stock move is totally unjustified!</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382816239046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 15:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382816914982-97</Id><Topic><Title>What shorts are forgetting</Title><Username>cospringboard</Username><Timestamp>1382701143301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 07:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I haven't shorted Amazon for over 4 years....I made money on the drop to 45 a few years back....I covered and went long to around 85 and sold out....never looked back....Sure I missed out on a move to 360 however there are other solidly run companies that had actual fundies to support their "growth"....I am back now and will watch very carefully in the coming days... Watch the overseas markets for a true tell where we are going...They are about to experience something that hasn't happened since 1997 around this time of the year...Look it up and realize that is whats coming in the coming weeks..........................Think leverage, margin, and bullish momo and then look at oct 97................................</Msg><Username>lemmeknow23</Username><Timestamp>1382816914982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 15:48:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382816988618-98</Id><Title>Wall Street and the SEC are using CNBC to try and bring down the frothy</Title><Msg>stocks before it causes another major collapse in the market. Who wants to invest in the market when this type of thing is going on. The TSLAs, AMZN, NFLX etc, etc need to go away soon. Big money has always controlled the market but this is getting crazy. Almost every hr CNBC said something neg about TSLA on FRi</Msg><Username>nazawall</Username><Timestamp>1382816988618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 15:49:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382817566653-99</Id><Topic><Title>Very high probability of price peak in AMZN stock at 366</Title><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382809515647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My fundamental by the numbers research straight from the 10Q actually show DECREASING margins on gen merch sales and cash flow funded not from ops but from stock sales on option exercise and increase in payables. They increased gen merch products sales by 2.2 billion, about 20%, but increased net margin on those sales from 291 mil to only 295 mil, a drop is GM%. There are no true analysts looking at this stock only WS shills. I will reveal this all soon,maybe by Monday.</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382817566653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 15:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382818104551-100</Id><Title>Fundamentals deteriorating; Yahoo deletes my topic</Title><Msg>When they cry Who Knew? Enron Me.</Msg><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382818104551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 16:08:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382818310795-101</Id><Topic><Title>Very high probability of price peak in AMZN stock at 366</Title><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382809515647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree I added at 366 short I think 330 next week or so then 250 before new year</Msg><Username>xdon69</Username><Timestamp>1382818310795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 16:11:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382818574787-102</Id><Title>A look at the 1995 WMT annual report</Title><Msg>is a real interesting comparison. the company grew revenues by 22% from $67B to $82B. They spent $~4B reinvesting back into the company, which wiped out all of the cash flow from operations for future growth (sound familiar). But they reported EPS of $1.17 up 16% from $1.02. The Biggest difference I can find is Wal-Mart had a market cap of only $56Billion!!!! one third of Amazon's current valuation.</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382818574787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 16:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382818902748-103</Id><Topic><Title>Very high probability of price peak in AMZN stock at 366</Title><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382809515647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please Do! This stuff drives me crazy. I have been doing a comparison, looking at 1995 WMT annual report. Very similar revenue, CFO, FCF to AMZN. The only difference is the existence of EPS and even a dividend.</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382818902748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 16:21:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382818923837-104</Id><Title>Sybs predicts that pigz like amzn nflx goog pcln cmg tsla crm et al will crash with the markets when......</Title><Msg>Singhlion drops dead in the middle of a rant by way of a brain hemorage from that vein popping out of hiz thick crazy skull.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382818923837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 16:22:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382820084089-105</Id><Title>Lots of chatter in the middle of a squuuuuuuueeeeze</Title><Msg>One would only have to monitor the volume and sentiment of posts to tell what a stock iz doing without ever needing a chart. There'z more squeeze left, kidz. Sybil's unique Board Rant Volume &amp; Sentiment indicator hasnt peaked yet. You know when it peaks when volume of rants fallz low and the remaining sentiment iz pnly positive.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382820084089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 16:41:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382820225859-106</Id><Title>Crack head optionz buyerz are like Pooky in the movie New Jack City</Title><Msg>They just cant stay away from the bad stuff and it endz badly.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382820225859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 16:43:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382822380140-107</Id><Title>1995 WMT $80B in Sales with a $56B market cap growing rev at 22%.</Title><Msg>At that time they were pouring all of CFO back into the company, investing $4.5B for continued 20%+ growth AND at the same time they had EPS of $1.17, paid a dividend, and had a Market Cap of ONLY $56Billion This pig is overvalued by $50B at the very least.</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382822380140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 17:19:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382822820630-108</Id><Title>Sybilz unique sentiment indicator hazn't peaked yet... This stok iz going higher</Title><Msg>The indicator iz the Yahoo Posting Board Rant Ratio. Its a funny indicator - here'z how it works: Az a squuuueeeeze kicks in the volume of posting board rants skyrockets driving the price ever higher. It indicates a top when it goez divergent, meaning that az the price continuez to rise the rants become less and less az the squeeeeze killz all the negativity. The top iz in when rants dry up to nothing az ranterz are murdered, and the board haz one or two lonely posts per day - one from a get rich quick troll bot and the other from some insane pumper with time and no money. We are nowhere near divergence in sybby's Rant Indicator.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382822820630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 17:27:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382823422727-109</Id><Topic><Title>Sybilz unique sentiment indicator hazn't peaked yet... This stok iz going higher</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382822820630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 17:27:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seems to me you do alot of ranting so you must have no money? You spent weekends here ranting and raving. So you must have no money.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382823422727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 17:37:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382823512342-110</Id><Topic><Title>Very high probability of price peak in AMZN stock at 366</Title><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382809515647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when do you stop making stupid predction calls: they have been god awful.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382823512342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 17:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382823522732-111</Id><Title>Retail bandwaggon shorts comiserate together in the virtual world of posting boardz</Title><Msg>In the virtual world they find commonality and bond together, however in the trading world they willfully shoot each other in a bloody massacre to see who can cover lower then the other az a botcoin stok goez up up up and away. The tippity top of a bitcoin stok price parabola typically iznt picked off by some retail bag holder, its 99.999% of the time that the top price scored on a pig in a parabola by some poor slob that theew in the towel with a "buy to cover" market order.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382823522732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 17:38:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382823665263-112</Id><Title>Sybil, you do your share of ranting and raving yourself: saying the same thing? what does that say for you time and money?</Title><Msg>since you catagorize others here doing the same thing you do without money, then maybe YOU have no money.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382823665263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 17:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382824688841-113</Id><Title>AMZN LOST 41 MIL THIS Q. ITHAS NOR MADE ONE PENNY YET. ZERO CASH. BIG EXPANSIONS AND LOSSES</Title><Msg>Even though losses are down to 41 mil this quarter, amzn can never make 147 bil in cash like aapl. They will be lucky if they make 2 millions in net profit a quarter. Amzn should be priced at 50 dollars</Msg><Username>tamermous</Username><Timestamp>1382824688841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 17:58:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382825377769-114</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil, you do your share of ranting and raving yourself: saying the same thing? what does that say for you time and money?</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382823665263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 17:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's broke</Msg><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1382825377769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 18:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382825674030-115</Id><Topic><Title>Very high probability of price peak in AMZN stock at 366</Title><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382809515647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do anticipate at least 1/3 of the Friday's gain (closing price uptick) to be lost within days (as early as Monday's closing). That's roughly $10+ down from current closing of $363.39. So $353 is quite possible. Now from there to $345 and lower would depend highly on profit taking and some heavy selling by MMs, retail investors etc. Upside from current level at least in short term is very limited, if any at all.</Msg><Username>s_haliz</Username><Timestamp>1382825674030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 18:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382826094957-116</Id><Topic><Title>Retail bandwaggon shorts comiserate together in the virtual world of posting boardz</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382823522732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 17:38:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Youll get you day in the gallows hangin from a sharp utensil along with the collusive shadows coordinating this scam!!!!! Enjoy........</Msg><Username>likballs22</Username><Timestamp>1382826094957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 18:21:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382826370527-117</Id><Topic><Title>What shorts are forgetting</Title><Username>cospringboard</Username><Timestamp>1382701143301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 07:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually short interest is only 1.88% as of 10/15. Which means not many shorts needed to cover their shorts (I am sure most would have already covered this Friday). So if it starts a little bit of downturn from current level (very likely), shorts may not act as a buffer to prevent downfall (by covering). Your arguments are all valid. Just look at the authors/analysts and others who are writing "bullish" comments and inflated targets. They all owned it long. Easy from them to praise...Isn't it? Don't get me wrong. This is a great company for consumers but not for shareholders. Profit margin of a "penny"???? Even if you conquer 1/2 the world, how can you make enough money???</Msg><Username>s_haliz</Username><Timestamp>1382826370527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 18:26:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382827123268-118</Id><Title>1995 the FED did not print money !!</Title><Msg>the FED is the reason for this bubble</Msg><Username>emanuel_dabah</Username><Timestamp>1382827123268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 18:38:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382827176264-119</Id><Title>NEVER SHORT AMZN! $500 by Dec.</Title><Msg>Valuation does not matter here.</Msg><Username>sbull1751</Username><Timestamp>1382827176264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 18:39:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382827296265-120</Id><Topic><Title>What shorts are forgetting</Title><Username>cospringboard</Username><Timestamp>1382701143301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 07:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can assure you short interest stats from over two weeks ago are obsolete. It is quite simple to see just from the sudden appearance on this board of so many newbie shorts that there has been plenty of short rocket fuel newly added and ripe to burn.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382827296265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 18:41:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382827659302-121</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN LOST 41 MIL THIS Q. ITHAS NOR MADE ONE PENNY YET. ZERO CASH. BIG EXPANSIONS AND LOSSES</Title><Username>tamermous</Username><Timestamp>1382824688841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 17:58:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cash and net income are not the same thing. GAAP expenses include many non-cash I.e. stock-based compensation or one-time non-cash losses such as the share of Living Social's startup losses.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382827659302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 18:47:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382828376683-122</Id><Title>Mayday!</Title><Msg>New 24x7 help support system for Kindle Fire. That costs extra money on a loss leader product that still isn't selling well. 109K employees and adding tens of thousands more for the holidays. Stalling growth, plus added cost, plus no profit = Q4 Cash ...will ...burn! Mayday!</Msg><Username>one_smooth_stone</Username><Timestamp>1382828376683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 18:59:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382828399344-123</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except Amazon is growing faster than Walmart which disproves your theory. Overhead is a short-term value investor's concern, it does not matter in the short term to growth investors focused on revenue growth.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382828399344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 18:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382828627102-124</Id><Title>On pace</Title><Msg>to completely dominate in multiple categories. Also on pace to get crushed in the coming bear market.</Msg><Username>penystoc</Username><Timestamp>1382828627102</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 19:03:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382829626574-125</Id><Topic><Title>Very high probability of price peak in AMZN stock at 366</Title><Username>stockvestigator</Username><Timestamp>1382809515647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 13:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've already posted this and the facts that disprove the buildout narrative (look at gross shipping cost as a % of revenue), along with fulfillment cost growing as a % of sales (not really a good fact for those arguing scale economies). The fundies are f'd. Yes, the Scamalysts are all shills outside of Gillis.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382829626574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 19:20:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382829670232-126</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street and the SEC are using CNBC to try and bring down the frothy</Title><Username>nazawall</Username><Timestamp>1382816988618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 15:49:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still pumping Scamazon. See Cramer....</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382829670232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 19:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382830103951-127</Id><Topic><Title>how about making this prediction techstrategy? how high does AMZN stock go today?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382706883468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 09:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have. And, I have rolled others... I've lost money here. More than offset my CMG gains. But, there is a bigger point for me and I will see it through. Scamalysts must have feet held to fire (what I am trying to do) before someone else puts them on the firing line...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382830103951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 19:28:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382831207861-128</Id><Title>Its much easier to stay calm while sitting on a boat load of cash after covering 65.00 ago.....</Title><Msg>Sybby's not broke, sybs iz not a komokazi, that's just tailrisk and several other bandwaggon shorts. They scoffed at sybil for raising the spector to 360. They'll scoff again az sybil now sayz this pig iz going to 4 t-t-t-twenty. They project their misery onto sybil, but sybby stayz calm, out of the spray of bullets az shorts shoot each other, and waits pateintly for their demise.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382831207861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 19:46:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382831362744-129</Id><Title>Tech, you should never commit to a trade on principle at the detriment of all your principal.</Title><Msg>Sybby learned that long ago. Markets can stay insane MUCH longer then the sane can stay solvent.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382831362744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 19:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382832417314-130</Id><Title>Here's a bigger scam then amzn and other bernanke bubble flying pigz - and they alwayz mark the end iz near.....</Title><Msg>The good ol fashioned tried and true super hype of IPO after IPO.... Yes the IPO's, particularly listing on bernie madoff's beloved nasdaq exchange, are FLYING off the shelf.... Twitter amongst many iz the big Dog IPO. The IPO caps the tops of markets and they simply represent rich dudez turning their illiquid private equity into bountiful USD's. they list their "valuable" privately held companiez into the open armz of the public that are frothing at the mouth to get a 'peice of the action'. Yes indeedy - theze companiez are SOOOO valuable that rich dudez just cant WAIT to sell 'em to the public being the generous benefactorz that they are. They are not smiling when they hit that closing bell on the exchange, they are crying tearz of sadness az they sell their equity stake of a beloved money making company.... Yes thank goodness for the IPO, what a country, what a market..... Now, that being said, before you idiots all run out and short the market, understand this - there are 30 and 60 day holding periodz for theze rich dudez before they can unload, and market pump masterz work the bit coin into the biggest hype possible so the rich dudez can cash in. Sybby's got this market pegged to run hard and fast and top in DEC..... If you think you can ballz to the wall short a pig and survive the runnup, then think again chumps. Sybil haz seen this broken record played time and againover the last 30 yearz..... Thats why sybby iz not stooopit... You want to short the top and/or on the way down not before it. If you get wiped out just remember its your fault for not listening to sybil and heeding the call to bow down before the parabola, cover, and recognize its awesome power.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382832417314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 20:06:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382832791308-131</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WMT REvenue 2012 +23 Billion over 2011 AMZN Revenue 2012 +13 Billion over 2011 Sorry, even revenue is growing faster on a gross basis at Walmart,not even talking about profits or dividends. The reason no one has stepped up to undercut AMZN pricing yet, is because they are not profitable, and in the the real world businesses need profits. AMZN doesn't operate in the real world, which is why it's in the news. Every business Amazon is in has a profitable competitor- Rackspace in Cloud, Ebay/Overstock/WMT in retail, Apple in hardware,etc. Yet a 17 year old company, unable (or as they claim unwilling) to turn a profit is priced richer than all of them. Whoever runs this scam realizes that at this point if the stock price collapses the jig is up, because all those engineers they've paid with stock will up and leave as there will be no need to wait for their restricted options to vest and then they will be left with 80000 box packers doing what they've always done, selling at a loss.</Msg><Username>felix_urman</Username><Timestamp>1382832791308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 20:13:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382833450373-132</Id><Title>Thaaaaats right you poor slobz - just keep lieing to yourselvez</Title><Msg>Lie # 1: amzn will tank before the parabolic move breaks you in your dare devil short on fundiez Lie # 2: sybil iz broke We'll see how that works out for you and how it works out for sybby.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382833450373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 20:24:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382836303239-133</Id><Topic><Title>FELLOW USA 99% GO AND SURROUND "SEC" HEAD QUARTERS WHERE THESE CRIMINALS GET ALL FRAUD WEAPONS TO SCAM/BANG/LOOT US ALL</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382716651223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 11:57:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THE NEW NORMAL IN USA?HELLO USA 99% ZOMBIES: CAN YOU FIX BRAINS TO ABSORB HARSH REALITY FACTS AKA TRUTH OR FRAUD PROPAGANDA $UCKED BRAINS CAN NOT BE REPROGRAMMED? THE NEW NORMAL IN USA?HELLO USA 99% ZOMBIES: CAN YOU FIX BRAINS TO ABSORB HARSH REALITY FACTS AKA TRUTH OR FRAUD PROPAGANDA $UCKED BRAINS CAN NOT BE REPROGRAMMED? Our government and financial “leaders” tell us that things are back to normal and we are well on our way to economic recovery. They report rising GDP, declining unemployment, and record corporate profits. The legacy media propaganda machines, controlled by corporations dependent upon the government and Wall Street to funnel them advertising dollars in return for reporting falsehoods and mistruths, have been informing the masses that all is well. Just go back to staring at your iGadgets and tweeting your every thought to your followers, because the best and brightest in D.C. and Wall Street have it all figured out. The new normal is here to stay. I guess my interpretation of normal deviates slightly from our glorious leaders’ definition. During the long-term bond bull market, from 1982 until 2007 the 10 Year Treasury steadily declined from 16% to 5%. This was normal because inflation declined at the same rate. Inflation declined from 13% to 3% over this same time frame according to the BLS. In reality, measuring inflation as it was measured in the 80′s and early 90′s would have yielded an inflation rate closer to 6% in 2007. During the decade prior to 2007, which consisted of supposedly strong economic growth, the 10 Year Treasury ranged between 4% and 7%. Even during the 2001 recession, it never dropped below 3.5%. In a normal world an investor in a 10 Year Treasury bond would require a yield 2% to 3% above the rate of inflation. If the yield was below the rate of inflation they would be guaranteed to lose money. Only a fool, Federal Reserve chairman, or a CNBC bubble headed #$%$ would buy a bond yielding less than the inflation rate. The BLS reported inflation rate has been between 2.1% and 3.2% over the last two years. Over this time frame, the 10 Year Treasury yielded 2% or below until the threat of tapering reared its ugly head this past summer. Would this happen in a normal free market? If things are back to normal, why aren’t supposedly free markets acting normal? The Chinese and Japanese reacted normally. They stopped buying Treasuries with a real negative yield. The only fool willing to buy negative yielding Treasuries is none other than Ben Bernanke. He thinks they are the investment of a lifetime. He is so sure they are a can’t miss investment, he buys $2.5 billion of them per day, which just so happens to be the government deficit per day. Ben now has $3.8 trillion of bonds on his books, versus $900 billion in 2008. His balance sheet is leveraged 60 to 1, versus the 30 to 1 of Lehman and Bear Stearns prior to their implosions. When even the hint of reducing bond purchases from $85 billion per month to $75 billion per month caused 10 Year rates to jump from 1.5% to 3% in a matter of weeks, you realize how “normal” our economy and financial system is functioning. If our financial system was functioning normally and free market capitalism was allowed to operate according to true supply and demand, the 10 Year Treasury would be yielding 4% to 5% and 30 year mortgage rates would be 6% to 7%. Think about that for a minute. This scenario was normal from 2002 through 2007. That is what normal looks like. Now open your eyes and observe what your owners are telling you is normal. The slight increase in mortgage rates from 3.5% to 4.5% has brought the Wall Street buy and rent housing recovery scheme to it knees. Imagine if mortgage rates were allowed to rise to their true market rate. Housing would collapse in a heap.Allowing Treasury rates to adjust to a true market rate, based on true inflation, would double or triple the annual interest expense on the $17 trillion national debt and blow a gigantic hole in Obama’s already disastrous $1 trillion annual deficits. Does this sound like “normal” to a rational thinking human being with the ability to understand simple math? Luckily, there are very few rational thinking Americans left and even fewer with the ability to understand simple math. We have been programmed to believe rather than think. As long as the stock market continue to rise, then everything is normal. Do you think Ben Bernanke and his cohorts at the Federal Reserve worry about the average person who doesn’t own stocks, has to fill up their gas tank, feed their kids, make the mortgage, auto, and credit card payments, and figure out Obamacare, while working two part time jobs? Quantitative Easing (MONEY PRINTING) has one purpose and one purpose only – to further enrich the owners of the Federal Reserve – Wall Street banks. The .1% own most of the stocks in this country and their greed and avarice can never be satisfied.This artificial prosperity plan for Wall Street has the added benefit of allowing the captured politicians in Washington D.C. to continue their $1 trillion per year deficit spending with no consequences for their squandering of future generations’ wealth. Bernanke and Yellen will never taper, because they can’t. The Fed balance sheet will continue to grow by at least $1 trillion per year until they crash the financial system again. Except this time, there will be no money printing solution. We are all trapped like rats in this monetary experiment being conducted by evil mad scientists. No one will get out alive. Welcome to the new normal. Now eat your cheese.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382836303239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 21:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382836338819-134</Id><Topic><Title>LION BRODCAST VS FRAUD STREET BANKSTER FRAUD ANALYST TERRORIST: OUTRIGHT DUMP AND AVOID RATIUNG ON AMAZON ENFORCED</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382730679201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 15:51:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“The really dangerous American fascist… is the man who wants to do in the United States in an American way what Hitler did in Germany in a Prussian way. The American fascist would prefer not to use violence. His method is to poison the channels of public information. With a fascist the problem is never how best to present the truth to the public but how best to use the news to deceive the public into giving the fascist and his group more money or more power… They claim to be super-patriots, but they would destroy every liberty guaranteed by the Constitution. They demand free enterprise, but are the spokesmen for monopoly and vested interest. Their final objective, toward which all their deceit is directed, is to capture political power so that, using the power of the state and the power of the market simultaneously, they may keep the common man in eternal subjection. ~quoted in the New York Times, April 9, 1944” ― Henry A. Wallace “Still another danger is represented by those who, paying lip service to democracy and the common welfare, in their insatiable greed for money and the power which money gives, do not hesitate surreptitiously to evade the laws designed to safeguard the public from monopolistic extortion. They are patriotic in time of war because it is to their interest to be so, but in time of peace they follow power and the dollar wherever they may lead.” ― Henry A. Wallace “If we define an American fascist as one who in case of conflict puts money and power ahead of human beings, then there are undoubtedly several million fascists in the United States.” ― Henry A. Wallace “The American fascists are most easily recognized by their deliberate perversion of truth and fact.” ― Henry A. Wallace “In an effort to eliminate the possibility of any rival growing up, some monopolists would sacrifice democracy itself.” ― Henry A. Wallace Less</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382836338819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 21:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382836393508-135</Id><Topic><Title>THE NEW NORMAL IN USA?HELLO USA 99% ZOMBIES: CAN YOU FIX BRAINS TO ABSORB HARSH REALITY FACTS AKA TRUTH OR FRAUD PROPAGANDA $UCKED BRAINS CAN NOT BE REPROGRAMMED?</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382803262890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 12:01:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you know these Banksters have introduced mini option contracts on AMAZON this week? now 1 mini contract equals 10 shares not 100. I discovered it yesterday while placing an order and had to call Schwab to find out why Cash balance still high after placing the trade and they explained it it had AMZN7 option chain for mini option contracts..lol These crooks have become desperate to loot USA retail with more commissions by introducing mini option contracts and retail has very little cash left and all are now using derivatives and WALL STREET is wiping them all out with is new fraud weapon "WEEKLY DERIVATIVES" &amp; "HFT" FRAUD WASH SALE VOLUME scam It is has been discovered and Bart Chilton at CFTC has acknowledged it and screamed that it must be investigated. Sir Bart Chilton, I am spinning my brain after listening to your comments on "HFT" scam Trading Wash Sales and your book"Ponzimonium: How Scam Artists are Ripping Off America. You are commissioner at CFTC and you had and have the power to stop this fraud loot of USA 99% but I find very disturbing about your comments vs actions to stop this fraud weapons? Why were weekly derivatives introduced after 2008 Market crash and for what purpose? Can you enlighten us Sir on these weekly derivatives, when Warren Buffet was already screaming these derivatives are nuke of Financial Destruction? Dr. Paul Craig Roberts is right on: AMERICANS are history without Revolution &amp; USA is a Failed State. I am forwarding my email which I have been emailing to all watch dog agencies in USA and I have open challenge in USA to debate NETFLIX nexus scam gang ongoing unstoppable free loot in $10's of billions with new fraud weapons handed by FINRA/SEC/CFTC. I have open challenge to debate this scam with all Watch Dog agencies, High Treason criminal Rulers and academia in USA and I invite you to accept my challenge too. All your fraud weapons are in use in NETFLIX $60B+ loot Scam..</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382836393508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 21:13:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382837438441-136</Id><Title>amzn will keep going up on monday./</Title><Msg>just like goog ,the second day run up ........</Msg><Username>dkatakmo</Username><Timestamp>1382837438441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 21:30:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382837730005-137</Id><Topic><Title>how about making this prediction techstrategy? how high does AMZN stock go today?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382706883468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 09:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know most people will think I'm joking but did anybody else write the SEC about the e-publishing change that was not reported on an apples to apples basis and barely acknowledged by Amazon management? It's probably all for naught but I figure if enough people get in their ear and annoy them with it, what do you have to lose. If the impact was $600M-700M the actual apples to apples revenue was $16.-4-$16.5M and a clear miss of estimates. This increased revenue by 3.6%-4.3% most likely which is very far from immaterial. These people need their feet held to the fire. I feel like I'm on a mission here much like of some of you. I do think there will be profits to be made, although I admit to losing money in Amazon this year but I feel a bit like tech, it's beyond money at this point. It's about the corrupt and collusive action on Wall Street in this semi scam. If you haven't written them I encourage you to jam their in box with emails.</Msg><Username>hapihammer</Username><Timestamp>1382837730005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 21:35:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382841241504-138</Id><Topic><Title>how about making this prediction techstrategy? how high does AMZN stock go today?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382706883468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 09:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you delusional short kooks are hilarious.............</Msg><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1382841241504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 22:34:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382841915710-139</Id><Topic><Title>amzn will keep going up on monday./</Title><Username>dkatakmo</Username><Timestamp>1382837438441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 21:30:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But the chart says GOOG went down on the second day?</Msg><Username>one_smooth_stone</Username><Timestamp>1382841915710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 22:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382842121311-140</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Their online and store prices must stay close. That's Walmarts downfall. Amazon doesnt' have that anchor. Unbeatable, world domination...no question.</Msg><Username>g99sim</Username><Timestamp>1382842121311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 22:48:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382842136930-141</Id><Title>What can $166B buy? Lets start with buying</Title><Msg>Goldman Sachs for $74B Transocean for $18B Nordstrom's for $12B Dupont for $57B and we still have $5Billion to buy lots of cocaine and #$%$!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382842136930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 22:48:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382842757781-142</Id><Topic><Title>amzn will keep going up on monday./</Title><Username>dkatakmo</Username><Timestamp>1382837438441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 21:30:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correct. $6 down on the second day and another $10 down on third day. Total $16 down from Oct. 23 closing of $1,031.41. So it gained $24 and gave it back $16. Now do the math for AMZN.</Msg><Username>s_haliz</Username><Timestamp>1382842757781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 22:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382843256666-143</Id><Topic><Title>how about making this prediction techstrategy? how high does AMZN stock go today?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382706883468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 09:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, it's YOU, the d'ckless clown, who is hilarious.....you don't even have to use your lame attempts at HS humor to achieve that distinction.....it comes with being "skiidady" the d'ckless clown. Get a f'kg life, d'ckless</Msg><Username>bionic_ironic</Username><Timestamp>1382843256666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 23:07:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382843416346-144</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're mistaken. Amazon's operating cost plus shipping cost to the company is higher than Walmart. Walmart can go lower than AMZN every time. AMZN is already negative earnings, going lower burns cash. Amazon cannot compete with Walmart. If you believe that, you've bought a lie. The "anchor" is a profitable store in every city. Site-to-store is free ship for Walmart on trucks already moving anyway. That's a competitive advantage for Walmart when comparing shipping cost to the company.</Msg><Username>one_smooth_stone</Username><Timestamp>1382843416346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 23:10:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382843675712-145</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another thing you don't understand is that even Best Buy can beat Amazon now that state tax is collected. The days of browse at Best Buy, but then order amazon are over. The old advantage of skipping state tax is gone. The new advantage is browse and get it now at Best Buy for the same price.</Msg><Username>one_smooth_stone</Username><Timestamp>1382843675712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 23:14:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382843908674-146</Id><Topic><Title>amzn will keep going up on monday./</Title><Username>dkatakmo</Username><Timestamp>1382837438441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 21:30:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMZN math is pretty fuzzy.</Msg><Username>one_smooth_stone</Username><Timestamp>1382843908674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 23:18:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382844289942-147</Id><Topic><Title>amzn will keep going up on monday./</Title><Username>dkatakmo</Username><Timestamp>1382837438441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 21:30:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100% down closing guaranteed on Monday than Friday's closing no matter how fuzzy the math is for AMZN.</Msg><Username>s_haliz</Username><Timestamp>1382844289942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 23:24:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382845711046-148</Id><Title>44 Analyst follow AMZN... How many upgrades?</Title><Msg>The news is that a couple of analysts upgraded this POS. The real news is how many didn't change a thing. Short this above 360 and make a ton of money for cocaine and #$%$.</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382845711046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 23:48:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382846293928-149</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst Kool Aide Drinkers!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382732698989</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 16:24:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazon's fulfillment centers are not a superior structure to Walmart. As Walmart is on the move to invest more in ecommerce, they will improve the website and compliment distribution. Walmart is king of logistics and already worldwide. Amazon is a push over to beat for Walmart.</Msg><Username>one_smooth_stone</Username><Timestamp>1382846293928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 23:58:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>