<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-10-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382848077058-1</Id><Topic><Title>ok, give a thumbdowns for all my post plese, b/c I tell you all the truth and you can't take it:</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382795317136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. A corrupt system that purports to be investing people's 401K savings when it is actually just a speculative trading (and skimming) operation. You have have avoided the 2008 crash, but those 401K's didn't and they won't this time either. Meanwhile, those asset managers skim a few % off of bubbles valuations, take it off the table and then let the bubble pop. That's a corrupt system. Nothing less. The market is broken. Unless and until people start investing in illiquid productive assets (while illiquid, safe from HFT induced manipulation and false liquidity flash crashes), our future prospects will continue to degrade.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382848077058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 00:27:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382849262473-2</Id><Topic><Title>how about making this prediction techstrategy? how high does AMZN stock go today?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382706883468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 09:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hapi: We should all take different approaches. The path that will hit is their wallets. Every state pension fund should divest any direct or indirect investment in Amazon until it collects taxes across the board. I'm no HuffPost guy, but get the left on that message (state pension funds enabling artificially low cost of capital for corporate tax evader that is killing local jobs, state tax revenues and LT pension viability) and Amazon has IR problems... The real SEC opportunity will be with disclosures (and omissions) in the upcoming offering. Amazon's current NWC isn't good and trend is awful. A significant shock could lead to insolvency. Question is it debt or equity? Bigtime agency/moral hazard because whoever is buying certainly won't be putting much of their own capital in (but will be taking the fees!)...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382849262473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 00:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382852013885-3</Id><Topic><Title>ok, give a thumbdowns for all my post plese, b/c I tell you all the truth and you can't take it:</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382795317136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>techyboy, take your meds and go to bed. Stop obsessing about a message board........</Msg><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1382852013885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 01:33:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382854909406-4</Id><Title>Only 400 times this year's earnings</Title><Msg>Talk about a bargain!</Msg><Username>bobwins_o_phile</Username><Timestamp>1382854909406</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 02:21:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382864605871-5</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You display your ignorance about how Growth RATE is measured: WMT Revenue Growth 3Q13: 2.3% AMZN Revenue Growth 3Q13: 23.0% “not even talking about profits or dividends.” In Growth investing one makes a (temporary) trade off between these other considerations in order to maximize REVENUE growth. So “not even talking about” them here is appropriate. “in the the real world businesses need profits.” This is the real world, and depending on the timeframe and objectives there is no rule about needing “profits”. If the objective is to maximize growth profit will not be the objective. If a company has sufficient access to capital, profit is not a requirement for that time. Also, profit and cash are not the same thing. Not all the charges made to operations are cash expenses. “a 17 year old company, unable (or as they claim unwilling) to turn a profit” Actually they have produced a number of profitable years. They simply choose to maximize growth opportunities at this time.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382864605871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 05:03:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382865095725-6</Id><Topic><Title>how about making this prediction techstrategy? how high does AMZN stock go today?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382706883468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 09:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"And, I have rolled others... I've lost money here. More than offset my CMG gains." Your losses on your Amazon shorts are great illustrations of the (short) wreckstrategy at work. "But, there is a bigger point for me and I will see it through..." Readers interested in this phenomenon should read Shiller's (he just won the Nobel Prize in Economics) "Animal Spirits". Data from neural economics using brain imagining technologies reveal when many financial decisions get made (often ill-advised ones) the area of the brain stimulated is similar to that associated with vengence. This poster wreckstrategy must be attempting to stubbornly but hopelessly get his revenge on those on WS who he blames for his own follies.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382865095725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 05:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382876654093-7</Id><Topic><Title>ok, give a thumbdowns for all my post plese, b/c I tell you all the truth and you can't take it:</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382795317136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 09:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Stop obsessing about a message board........" And, hence, the d'ckless clown "speaks" of a subject that controls his whole "life" GET a f'kg life, d'ckless.....crpping on Yahoo message boards for securities you never have had or never will can only be worse that trying to sell insurance from a failed storefront in rural Seattle.....something you know all about.</Msg><Username>c_h_11l</Username><Timestamp>1382876654093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 08:24:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382876851153-8</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I get the percentage growth rates. But if you owned a real business, you would choose the own that is profitable, and growing profits. Yes Amazon has access to funding that no other business has. That is what TPTB seem to want. They pay their people with stock which has obviously allowed them to minimize real cash requirements and still be able to compete. No other business has that luxury. Yes Amazon was profitable in the past, but barely so relative to their share price. They are also extremely vulnerable to any number of disruptions as their cash on hand is far less than their 60 days accounts payable. A slowdown in demand, even temporary, will send them scrambling for cash unlike much cheaper tech companies which also show large revenue AND profit growth i.e Google, Ebay, etc.</Msg><Username>felix_urman</Username><Timestamp>1382876851153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 08:27:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382876924202-9</Id><Topic><Title>how about making this prediction techstrategy? how high does AMZN stock go today?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382706883468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 09:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, the research shows that decisions made on emotion, fear, greed or anger, can all lead to very bad outcomes. That's the point of shills like yourself and factless bashers on these boards. To move the thought process away from clinical, fact based logical areas of the brain. Further, behavioral economics (and investing) has shown the power of anchoring, affirmation and many other cognitive biases. These have an are being employed to lead lambs to the slaughter. The herding effect has been remarkable, especially with the unholy alliance between TBTF, FED and financial propaganda (I mean media) armed with the optimism bias. It remains the case that none of it is sustainable, even as remarkably lower levels. The barbell strategies have been employed into the wrong "growth sectors" because in a closed system, there's only 1 path to come back into balance and it ain't good for Scamazon.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382876924202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 08:28:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382877048332-10</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, He is framing the growth in absolate terms which should be reflective of abolute growth in market cap.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382877048332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 08:30:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382877802914-11</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have a winner... Even with the negative cash conversion cycle (AP 75 days, upfront/earlier collection), Amazon has seen its NWC drop over the years, despite being aided by a $1.8B net of HQ infusion in Q4 last year. It's NWC is now below that infusion meaning it would have been negative without it. In a shock, the rate of payable outflows exceed revenue inflows, so even with the NCCC, cash will be consumed. And, inventory drops in value.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382877802914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 08:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382878269196-12</Id><Title>The Bandwaggon of shorts are lising their sensez az the hike in the thin air of high altitudez without supplimental oxygen</Title><Msg>Many extreme hikerz go mad and talk themselvez out of the fact that they are going to die.... Now the bandwaggon of shorts are back to discussing "fundementalz" endlessly debating - WMT vs AMZN. The truth iz simple between the two: Both are businessez that sell retail goodz - thats where the commonality endz. Publicly traded stox are entirely divorced of the businessez that they represent, they are simply a meanz to transfer wealth from the many to the few.... The ticker amzn could just az well "TULP", the ticker for nflx could just az well be "BULB", and the ticker for wmt could just az well be "BUST". But shorts caught in a parabola are like hikerz caught at high altitudez of a dangerous mountain climb. 1st they lose thier mind, then they lose their livez in bouts of insanity Sybil stayed safely at base camp 4 opting not to attempt to summit - it just didnt feel right. Sybil will wait a while to see if an survivorz make it back, and hop on a pig stock for the fast and fun ride back down</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382878269196</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 08:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382878657104-13</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WMT's ecommerce growth rate is higher. That will be the comparable number. Since WMT is investing, it will accelerate and WMT's growth rate will be higher especially since smaller numbers are easier to make big percentage gains. WMT will win ecommerce now that it wants to play. :) Amazon's past year's small profits wouldn't translate today. They have expanded into areas that won't be profitable for them. They're trying to compete with AAPL &amp; Samsung by bringing late and inferior products. That's not going to win.</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382878657104</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 08:57:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382879090737-14</Id><Title>Tech - markets capatolizing the greed of making money and the fear of losing it will never change for that iz how wealth iz transfered</Title><Msg>Chatting (arguing) with omnipresent board pumperz that have no money at stake iz pointless. To deny human emotion in your case would be lieing to yourself az this bubble proceedz to break the 'toughest' of the bandwaggon of shorts. Report back in 6 to 8 weeks from amzn 420+, possibly 500, az it makes dramatic movez through the parabola, murdering shorts az it goez.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382879090737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382879397596-15</Id><Title>AMAZON: THE GREAT MONEY LOSING SCAM</Title><Msg>One day books will be written about the greatest retail stock scam in the history of the equity market. The company is a mature company that can't make money even with the unfair advantage of not charging sales tax in most states. It also has no retail brick and mortar infrastructure. Boso's knows that the muppetts in the stock market is only concerned with revenue growth so he continues to sell everything and anything even if he has to sell it at a loss -- which he ofter does. They can't make money on Kindles even though they give them away at cost. Even thought the market has inexplicably given Google a free pass for non-performance for 10+ years, eventually the shoe will drop and people will race for the exits. Eventually people will have to pay sales tax on orders in ALL 50 states as political pressure to do so continues to rise. When the shoe drops it will squash longs like a bug when they least expect it. It is only a matter of time.</Msg><Username>alphashort</Username><Timestamp>1382879397596</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:09:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382879492879-16</Id><Title>Amazon attacked iPad.....</Title><Msg>I love Amazon service and all. ....... but only companies with inferior products attack competing products by name. Compare the Kindle to the iPad head to head in the hands of customers and iPad will win hands down. The Kindle is 20% lighter because it is a cheap plastic compared to the aluminum iPad. Plus Amazon sells each Kindle at a loss .....which shows up in their quarterly loss. Will Amazon ever get making money? Will the stock tank some day to a reasonable P/E ? Sooner or later analysts will base there targets on real world earnings rather than their hopes. I would not want to own Amazon stock when it happens.</Msg><Username>marketsagame</Username><Timestamp>1382879492879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:11:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382879874798-17</Id><Title>Accepting, recognizing, and managing fear and greed az a part of trading can save your capital and make you more</Title><Msg>Fear iz useful az it iz a protective mode that drivez the fight or flight mode.... The fast and skiddish deer will survive being devoured by a pack of wolvez where the onez without fear will find themselvez devoured after being caught in the open with the greedy hopes of finding better grass to eat instead of bark. Greed iz useful in that it assurez itself the strength to survive - the greedy wolf that will fight off otherz gets to eat more of the freshly killed deer. Sybil iz a fearful deer dreased in a greedy wolf's disguize. Not being a true wolf - sybil waz incapable of covering shorts and then going long, but when the time iz right sybil will greedily canabalize the deer that lacked a sense of survival fear.... Sybs figurez this from a much higher level - many weeks out.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382879874798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:17:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382880908234-18</Id><Title>Wal-Mart Is the Next Big Tech Company</Title><Msg>While investors haggle over whether to invest in Apple or Google, the real star of the online retail space has been streaking ahead of both companies.  Apple is currently the third largest online retailer, but by the end of 2013, Wal-Mart will surpass Apple in online retail sales. This will make Wal-Mart the third largest online retailer -- behind only Amazon (NASDAQ: AMZN) and Staples.  Search for and read... Wal-Mart Is the Next Big Tech Company By Sean Sullivan</Msg><Username>marthor7</Username><Timestamp>1382880908234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382881018258-19</Id><Topic><Title>Tech - markets capatolizing the greed of making money and the fear of losing it will never change for that iz how wealth iz transfered</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382879090737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:04:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll be here Sybil. But, many others that actually look at the fundamentals and dive deeper are coming. That may provide short fuel, but it will vastly increase the visibility of this scam and the scrutiny that it gets. Hapi, is now writing SEC. Maybe it gets noticed. I'd love to see all shorts write the Scamalysts certified mail documenting the "divergence between PROJECTED 3-5 year earnings and price targets". Get them on record. Setup some personal liability and brand risk for their role in this. The general public is getting very frustrated with the wealth effect game. What they haven't pieced together is that it is a wealth and income effect for the financial sector, which takes a constant tax on AUM (a wealth tax, unlike the gov't) and so these bubbles enable them to skim our wealth as their income along the way. Then, it crashes (we bail them out) and they use what they took off the table to buy in post crash, thereby concentrating over time. When people really viewed WS as a wealth tax (it is), its secular decline will be a given...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382881018258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:36:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382881841883-20</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon attacked iPad.....</Title><Username>marketsagame</Username><Timestamp>1382879492879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:11:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even at a cheaper price, the fire is selling poorly. Everybody knows it's the last place option. Amazon is not special. Even future earnings expectations have to be somewhat realistic. In a few years, Amazon will be bleeding even more red is more realistic. Without a competitive advantage, the future of the company is completely in doubt. Any profit for even Q4 is unlikely. Future profit is even worse outlook. Amazon is not special or unique where they don't need to make money. Amazon cannot make money.</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382881841883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:50:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382882490914-21</Id><Topic><Title>Wal-Mart Is the Next Big Tech Company</Title><Username>marthor7</Username><Timestamp>1382880908234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WalMart's brick and mortar stores will also price-match ads from local grocers. Show the cashier the ads and the item purchased will be discounted per the ads. Instead of driving around town to save money at various stores, one can shop at WalMart or WalMart Neighborhood stores to obtain all the available discounts, plus WalMart's everyday low prices.</Msg><Username>nje457</Username><Timestamp>1382882490914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:01:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382882937606-22</Id><Topic><Title>AMAZON: THE GREAT MONEY LOSING SCAM</Title><Username>alphashort</Username><Timestamp>1382879397596</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:09:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A lot of the bigger states have the online tax now, so it's already 50%. This has helped Best Buy directly, so it's not browse at BB and then order amazon to avoid tax. That is over and Best Buy is starting to recover. Amazon has a little venture going to sell tax help to small online retailers. That's small potatoes though. Amazon cannot make money now or in the future. Walmart will pass them over as a bigger online retailer in a few years. Amazon's viability as a company is in doubt.</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382882937606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382883244959-23</Id><Title>Hapihammer - please let the board know how that letter to the SEC works out for you</Title><Msg>Good luck with that one! (Uuuuummmmmmm. Sybs being a little fasicious here ) Hopefully you do not remain short while you await a computer generated reply.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382883244959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:14:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382883336841-24</Id><Topic><Title>Wal-Mart Is the Next Big Tech Company</Title><Username>marthor7</Username><Timestamp>1382880908234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Walmart is being innovative to blend online with local shopping. Walmart has a far superior structure to win against amazon. “Ecommerce is the next growth engine for Wal-Mart,” Ashe said at a Barclays Capital conference on Wednesday. “We have global leverage, not just in cost and capital investment, but innovation leverage.”</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382883336841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:15:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382883450842-25</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is not growth investing then, it is value investing, the kind of thesis that resulted in your $100 per share losses, your (short) wreckstrategy. Growth investing is based on the RATE of revenue growth, not absolute dollars.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382883450842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382883544126-26</Id><Title>walmart is ghetto</Title><Msg>case closed for walmart on amazon board. besides those low basis wmt stock holders from early 90's are dead or cashed out. on the other side amzn is cool weekly options casino where funds like sands can SAFELY write enormous premiums EVERY WEEK. and it is the only excitement in this boring crop company</Msg><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382883544126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:19:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382883667830-27</Id><Topic><Title>how about making this prediction techstrategy? how high does AMZN stock go today?</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382706883468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 09:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"decisions made on emotion, fear, greed or anger, can all lead to very bad outcomes" Illustrate by your short wreckstrategy indeed one of the worst outcomes on these board to be heard about on these boards, those precise emotions demonstrated every time you call others who do not agree with you shills, get angry about WS or spout about the unholy.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382883667830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:21:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382883955654-28</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"if you owned a real business, you would choose the own that is profitable, and growing profits." Tell that line to the WMT shareholders whose shares have only risen only $1 per year on avg. since 1999.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382883955654</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:25:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382883998119-29</Id><Title>Local Corp is Master of Relevance in Mobile Shopping - And that’s the key: it has to be a relevant deal</Title><Msg>During all stages of the Mobile Shopping Life Cycle, consumers have the ability to tap into their mobile phones to find products and check pricing and availability based on where they are at the moment. This is where those ping alert type apps come in, such as when a consumer is driving or walking by a store they receive an alert of relevance. And that’s the key: it has to be a relevant deal.</Msg><Username>fankenkoenig</Username><Timestamp>1382883998119</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:26:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382884084226-30</Id><Title>nemesis doesn't own any real business</Title><Msg>he is big time putz</Msg><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382884084226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:28:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382884251033-31</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Modern "growth" investing is not investing. It is at best momentum trading, a ponzi in the sense of being wholly dependent upon the greater fool (and tacit collusion).</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382884251033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:30:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382884283962-32</Id><Topic><Title>walmart is ghetto</Title><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382883544126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:19:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazon's Fire is ghetto of tablets. Meanwhile Walmart has mobile shopping that works on any mobile device. That's first class innovation in ecommerce. Largest retailer becoming largest e-retailer too.</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382884283962</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:31:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382884963251-33</Id><Topic><Title>Wal-Mart Is the Next Big Tech Company</Title><Username>marthor7</Username><Timestamp>1382880908234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not sure if wal-mart is the king or not, but earnings have proved that Amazon is NOT!</Msg><Username>dowto6k</Username><Timestamp>1382884963251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:42:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382885526442-34</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for reiterating your anti-growth investing stance. It explains why your own short wreckstrategy has resulted in such heavy ($100 per share) losses for you.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382885526442</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:52:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382885529231-35</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Plus dividends too and it'll also still be here whereas Amazon is doing a blackberry in the future, running out of cash and no one wants to buy the carcass.</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382885529231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:52:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382885704326-36</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except when the myth of profit disappears, then growth stocks crash.</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382885704326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:55:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382885736058-37</Id><Topic><Title>Wal-Mart Is the Next Big Tech Company</Title><Username>marthor7</Username><Timestamp>1382880908234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If a short like short wreckstrategy has a $100 loss per share on his short what does that make him? King of Losers? King of Failed Investment strategies?</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382885736058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:55:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382886609279-38</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My anti-greater fool predatory trading stance that values assets purely on how they trade rather than the underlying value they create and capture. Yes, the momentum trading scam is doing real dmagae to the real economy from distorted "market" signals that encourage value destorying malinvestment. Real growth investing is investing in productive assets, instead most of our "capital" in on deposit in banks being used for prop trading profits rather than productive investment. The damage that will be done to the 401Ks of the "growth funds" was real in 2008 and will be greater this time. The wealth that will have been skimmed via AUM fees is real. Unlike you and NAS, those funds are too big to sit on one seat in the game of musical chairs. The moral hazard and misalignment of incentives is pushing the system to the brink.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382886609279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:10:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382886797906-39</Id><Topic><Title>nemesis doesn't own any real business</Title><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382884084226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:28:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he is b s rationalizator on yahoo board these people should be helpful in the labor camps</Msg><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382886797906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:13:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382886804329-40</Id><Topic><Title>Wal-Mart Is the Next Big Tech Company</Title><Username>marthor7</Username><Timestamp>1382880908234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cash, wasn't it Nem that displayed his utter lack of understanding of basic accounting a month or so ago? Or was that Nas? I think it was Nem. Do you remember? Maybe I should dig up that classic thread....</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382886804329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:13:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382886908390-41</Id><Title>If A Bucketfull Of Obsessive Compulsive Short Wierdos Posted Around The Clock Mindless Bashing</Title><Msg>Would it change the PPS?????? Techyboy and the rest of the gibbering short idiots seem to think so!!!!! Take a day off you mindless cretins.(Techyboy, time to get back on the OCD meds)...........</Msg><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1382886908390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:15:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382887510638-42</Id><Topic><Title>If A Bucketfull Of Obsessive Compulsive Short Wierdos Posted Around The Clock Mindless Bashing</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1382886908390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:15:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's humorous to see you, Nas, Nem and Geeg work so hard to attack and belittle me. The aggregate of pumper postings attacking me far exceeds that which I write... Pathetic that you all are so shallow and insecure that you feel compelled to spend all your time attacking others on a message board. I focus on facts and fundamentals, not personal attacks...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382887510638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:25:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382887578564-43</Id><Topic><Title>If A Bucketfull Of Obsessive Compulsive Short Wierdos Posted Around The Clock Mindless Bashing</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1382886908390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:15:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Truth that amazon's future is doomed and they can never make money again. Q4 will be a loss. FY14 will be a loss. ..the vapors of growth will disapate soon. Fake accounting trick propped up this quater. Without it, they missed. True!</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382887578564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:26:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382887784378-44</Id><Title>"... a charitable organization being run by elements of the investment community for the benefit of consumers."</Title><Msg>Please post opinions on Slate's Matthew Yglesias's quote. Does he make a valid point and if so what sort of correction would shake out such elements? Is the stock now at a level that it is venerable to a significant 20% + correction that could get such elements off sides and initiate a multi year contraction in PE? It may sound counter intuitive given the upward momentum; however, now that a significant gap reversal is possible, arguably it could become a momentum stock for years in the downward direction. Please post opinions that dispute this concern.</Msg><Username>call_bs</Username><Timestamp>1382887784378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:29:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382887815706-45</Id><Topic><Title>If A Bucketfull Of Obsessive Compulsive Short Wierdos Posted Around The Clock Mindless Bashing</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1382886908390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:15:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" I focus on facts and fundamentals, not personal attacks" How about the facts that your ignorance of growth investing has led to fundamental losses on your Amazon short of over $120 per share?</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382887815706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:30:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382887886283-46</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually the most of the stuff on Amazon website are now selling for Much cheaper prices or similar prices in our neighborhood stores. For examples, the Outdoorman sporty knifes, Steel mixing pots, etc are at much cheaper prices at Harry's Hardwares stores. The 16 Oz Boscoli Italian Olive Salad is $5.99 in Fresh Market, but Amazon's price is $9.35+5.29 shipping. The 8.5Oz Organic Kalamata Olive Spread is 3.99-4.99 in Fresh Market, but Amazon's price is $6.45 plus shipping. ... But hi, I just threw all the fundamentals out of the windows and bought lots of calls and sold lots of puts before the earning and it paid me. I bought more longer term calls on Friday with my profit.</Msg><Username>venturing_out_4me</Username><Timestamp>1382887886283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:31:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382888006715-47</Id><Topic><Title>If A Bucketfull Of Obsessive Compulsive Short Wierdos Posted Around The Clock Mindless Bashing</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1382886908390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:15:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's humorous to see you blah, blah..." And It's humorous to see you cherry pick selective financials and an ignorance of growth investing that has resulted in heavy losses for you.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382888006715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:33:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382888176416-48</Id><Topic><Title>If A Bucketfull Of Obsessive Compulsive Short Wierdos Posted Around The Clock Mindless Bashing</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1382886908390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:15:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The vapors of shorts will disapate as usual as they cover for losses and go away to be replaced by other newbie shorts to repeat the cycle.</Msg><Username>nemesis_editor_2007</Username><Timestamp>1382888176416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:36:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382888259116-49</Id><Title>Q3 accounting trick for fake beat</Title><Msg>The loss was real, but the revenue number was fake. They started booking ebooks as 100% revenue instead of just the 30% commission. So, that tripled revenue on paper. Only on paper. Without it, they missed revenue too. AMZN dodges questions and hides data breakouts to keep the ruse going.</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382888259116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:37:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382888393346-50</Id><Title>One day is one day</Title><Msg>This cr-p is not worth 20 billion</Msg><Username>unmarkeddrains</Username><Timestamp>1382888393346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:39:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382888815610-51</Id><Topic><Title>Tech - markets capatolizing the greed of making money and the fear of losing it will never change for that iz how wealth iz transfered</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382879090737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:04:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Hapi, is now writing SEC. " you really think the SEC is on your side? In this bull market, the FED, SEC, US government itself, have shown that they think creating bubbles is the norm for the USA and of National Security. You are so misplaced and righteous about all this. There's nowhere to turn to when the perpetraters are at the highest levels b/c it benefits them, the 1 %. WAKE UP!!!!</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382888815610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:46:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382888976861-52</Id><Topic><Title>nemesis doesn't own any real business</Title><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382884084226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:28:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes he does. He's been here and owned AMZN since it was single digits Why don't you speak about what you know before opening you yap, b/c you merely sound jealous of his knowledge and being on the right side.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382888976861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382889069203-53</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart Web-prices Exactly Match Amazon!! Automated price matching!</Title><Username>jaywishman</Username><Timestamp>1382741599196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think this guy Sybil is right about , you went from Base Camp 4 trying to climb to the top of MT.Everest, and the oxygen depletion is getting to your brain. You should take a step back, and a step down, to clear your mind to what has happened to you.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382889069203</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382889138780-54</Id><Topic><Title>Local Corp is Master of Relevance in Mobile Shopping - And that’s the key: it has to be a relevant deal</Title><Username>fankenkoenig</Username><Timestamp>1382883998119</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Platform - Patented Local Shopping Technology Powered by Krillion®, Krillion delivers the most robust and accurate location-based product search data available. Our solutions provide dynamic, up-to-the minute information about where specific branded products are sold, and which retailers have them in stock the instant shoppers are ready to buy. Our patented Krillion® localization engine provides aggregated and structured local product shopping data to our business customers and channel partners. We pioneered local shopping search and are committed to the continuous growth of our dynamic platform that supports multi-channel retailers and brands looking to engage consumers wherever they research products and where to buy. As a result, our patented data normalization platform offers the most comprehensive cleansing and distribution capabilities in the available today.</Msg><Username>fankenkoenig</Username><Timestamp>1382889138780</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382889239835-55</Id><Topic><Title>Wal-Mart Is the Next Big Tech Company</Title><Username>marthor7</Username><Timestamp>1382880908234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Cash, wasn't it Nem that displayed his utter lack of understanding of basic accounting a month or so ago? Or was that Nas? I think it was Nem. Do you remember? Maybe I should dig up that classic thread...." what doesn't he understand that you do? He's been long the stock since single digits. What the hell is wrong with you people?</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382889239835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:53:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382889297204-56</Id><Topic><Title>Q3 accounting trick for fake beat</Title><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382888259116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>true lots of bagholder long</Msg><Username>xdon69</Username><Timestamp>1382889297204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:54:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382889349798-57</Id><Topic><Title>If A Bucketfull Of Obsessive Compulsive Short Wierdos Posted Around The Clock Mindless Bashing</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1382886908390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:15:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as a bystander seeing it all, I'd say they have been right, and you wrong, to now. In Nemesis case, he's probably the most knowledgable longterm entity on this board, and not kidding, he's owned the stock since single digits. The others I can't say.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382889349798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:55:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382889523282-58</Id><Topic><Title>Q3 accounting trick for fake beat</Title><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382888259116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"true lots of bagholder long" what ? you have been a prediction maker, bagholding short in looking at your posting history. You have huge losses in both AMZN and NFLX, with your shorting while you keep making predctions. There's no bagholding longs when a stock makes or is near alltime highs: none.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382889523282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382889653019-59</Id><Topic><Title>walmart is ghetto</Title><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382883544126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:19:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all of retail is hurting so is amzn revenue is fake #</Msg><Username>xdon69</Username><Timestamp>1382889653019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:00:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382889744570-60</Id><Topic><Title>walmart is ghetto</Title><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382883544126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:19:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"all of retail is hurting so is amzn revenue is fake #' but does that make short losses fake? expecailly for those who have been shorting for a long time? no, the losses for shorts is not fake!!!</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382889744570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:02:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382889760091-61</Id><Title>amzn is cooking the books</Title><Msg>Enron in process gov better look into this or heads will roll</Msg><Username>xdon69</Username><Timestamp>1382889760091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:02:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382890116248-62</Id><Title>I think Sybil's "Base Camp 4" analogy is proving to be very true here: you shorts have lost your minds</Title><Msg>And you have no idea how long it might take or high it is from Base Camp 4 to the Peak 5. And it Peak 5 may not even be the top. You're all guessing and losing, with it accelerating.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382890116248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:08:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382890826013-63</Id><Topic><Title>Q3 accounting trick for fake beat</Title><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382888259116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bagholding longs are the ones who buy at the top.</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382890826013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:20:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382890974767-64</Id><Title>NIKE has revenues of</Title><Msg>nike has revenues approaching 35 billion... i.e. about half of AMZN... so by the same metric that AMZN is valued at... shouldn't NIKE be priced at around $ 180 per share ?? AND NKE makes tonnes of PROFITS AND FREE CASH FLOW !!! why not dump AMZN and BUY BUY BUY NIKE ???</Msg><Username>radmok</Username><Timestamp>1382890974767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382891085880-65</Id><Title>Bingo Tax</Title><Msg>AMZN will now book the tax as revenue and bingo pop in sales. Don't they can't because they will</Msg><Username>penystoc</Username><Timestamp>1382891085880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:24:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382891117388-66</Id><Topic><Title>Q3 accounting trick for fake beat</Title><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382888259116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Bagholding longs are the ones who buy at the top." that statement has been said at every juncture AMZN makes new alltime highs, you are speculating about this being the top. That statement has been proven false each and every time before: turning the bagholders on the shorts trying to GUESS THE TOP. What we do know is the only bagholders in AMZN are shorts, and that's forever. Buying long AMZN has since it's inception, made buyers millionaires and shorts go to the poor house no matter how they try to justify it. Facts not speculative statements is what I'm basing this post on.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382891117388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:25:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382891416603-67</Id><Topic><Title>I think Sybil's "Base Camp 4" analogy is proving to be very true here: you shorts have lost your minds</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382890116248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We need Nurse Cratchett to hand out the medication around here!!!!! I particularly enjoy Techyboy's ramblings about being an IPO launching entrepreneur. My guess is he's a public employee with too much time on his hands.................</Msg><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1382891416603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:30:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382891431521-68</Id><Topic><Title>Q3 accounting trick for fake beat</Title><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382888259116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup. I think there was a slight impact in q2, maybe a month or less but Q3 was the first full quarter of impact and likely artificially increased revenue by $600M-$700M but of course if you ask Amazon management they pull the Schultz defense, i.e. they know nothing. Bvll$hit.</Msg><Username>hapihammer</Username><Timestamp>1382891431521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:30:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382891464097-69</Id><Topic><Title>2008 on $100 and Friday in 1 day + $ 30.</Title><Username>ruudkrul</Username><Timestamp>1382772907489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 03:35:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does Amazon pay dividend? Can somebody let this know. thanks.</Msg><Username>ruudkrul</Username><Timestamp>1382891464097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:31:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382891590240-70</Id><Topic><Title>nemesis doesn't own any real business</Title><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382884084226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 10:28:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nemesis doesn't own any real business. u retarhds with mooslim ids can't read it appears. my determinations are being made based on the statements made by nemesis on this board.</Msg><Username>cashback_7</Username><Timestamp>1382891590240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:33:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382891661485-71</Id><Topic><Title>Tech - markets capatolizing the greed of making money and the fear of losing it will never change for that iz how wealth iz transfered</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382879090737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:04:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ayahtolla2003 I basically agree with what you are saying but I will exercise my right to have the truth told. I think the last thing the Fed and probably most of the government would want at this critical juncture of this Ponzi economy is to have any dirt thrown on this perceived "great American company" but the heck with them. Someone at some point will tell the truth.</Msg><Username>hapihammer</Username><Timestamp>1382891661485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:34:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382892091345-72</Id><Topic><Title>Tech - markets capatolizing the greed of making money and the fear of losing it will never change for that iz how wealth iz transfered</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382879090737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 09:04:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and I would fight for you right to do it, but what I am observing, is that the gov't is condoning this excess speculative behavior outright. So not only are they turining their head to it, they are PROMOTING it. But good luck if it comes to anything. Our leadership does appear to have morphed into a gambling casino type economy to fight any downswings like 2008. And that's sad, and also dangerous. So far for the short side. Every asset class is getting blown out here in all G7 Countries.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382892091345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:41:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382892331849-73</Id><Topic><Title>I think Sybil's "Base Camp 4" analogy is proving to be very true here: you shorts have lost your minds</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382890116248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mountain climbing is probably more like regular investing. Growth investing is more like flying. There is an upper limit to the atmosphere and they always, always end up back on the ground. :)</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382892331849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:45:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382893998503-74</Id><Topic><Title>I think Sybil's "Base Camp 4" analogy is proving to be very true here: you shorts have lost your minds</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382890116248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Considering that Amazon is so far beyond any possible realistic possibility of ever achieving this "value" in the longterm, it's gotten into the sure thing range of going significantly down from here. It's in those thin air upper limits and gas is limited. Even with growth investing, it has to he plausible to make money "in the future". Amazon cannot and will not make money. It's an easily replaced retail portal. The things they are expanding in are not money-makers. No competitive advantages.</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382893998503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 13:13:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382894048015-75</Id><Topic><Title>Q3 accounting trick for fake beat</Title><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382888259116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Bagholding longs are the ones who buy at the top." False. The tippity top, when it iz indeed hit will be nailed by some poor slob short that will throw in the towel with a: Market Order - Buy to Cover That short will then immediately expire with no note left behind after a suicide mission. He will be found with a bloody hand clutched to hiz mouse and blood and guts sprayed across the computer screen. The screen in front will be layered with "MARKET ORDER FILLED @ $xxx.xx". Behind that screen will read "SEC Margin Maintenance Exchange Call - please deposit cash or reduce holdingz to meet SEC and HOUSE Margin Maintenance Requirements by 3:00PM EST" The time of death will be found to be 2:59PM EST and also found to be the all time high of the stock run. Thats how these thingz work - its that simple.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382894048015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 13:14:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382894469296-76</Id><Topic><Title>NIKE has revenues of</Title><Username>radmok</Username><Timestamp>1382890974767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:22:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sounds good</Msg><Username>xdon69</Username><Timestamp>1382894469296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 13:21:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382894666585-77</Id><Title>Tech, nasdaq_6000, nemisis, and geegee attack you on a board from a position of no cash</Title><Msg>None have any money, and they are distracting you from Rule #1 of course Investment 101: 1. LIMIT YOUR LOSSES TO PRESERVE NEEDED CAPITAL Get your head in the game, your judgement iz clouded, but if you presist it will be made vwry clear that you are on the wrong side of the meltup washout and will be made insolvent before ever enjoying being on the right side of it. Sybil can still be bearish without going broke, you should consider the same. Change your wayz or find yourself burnt at the stake like Joan of Arc. Except you wont be made a saint after you are dead.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382894666585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 13:24:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382894687374-78</Id><Topic><Title>Bezos to discuss new business initiatives on the cmoing CC</Title><Username>newmarketpro2002</Username><Timestamp>1382552966500</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-23 14:29:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lol. You should't be allowed in the market, for your own sake. “Don't buy, don't short, sell it if you have a large position in this stock" was a genuine advice I gave at this point. I follow this company and stock and investors's behavior because it's our business. The herd mentality and complete complacency is at maximum display so it is very dangerous for all parties.</Msg><Username>newmarketpro2002</Username><Timestamp>1382894687374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 13:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382894923718-79</Id><Topic><Title>Q3 accounting trick for fake beat</Title><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382888259116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A short cover is not a bagholder. A bagholder is all the longs who bought too high at the top and are left holding the bag like the game hot potato. How long can AMZN hold the 300s when growth is stalling now and it's so far ahead of itself. The music is about to stop playing.</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382894923718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 13:28:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382895526418-80</Id><Title>Obamacare vs Amazon ironic</Title><Msg>Obamacare website sux and available selection sux has no competition has a future Amazon website awesome and lots of selection has superior competition has no future</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382895526418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 13:38:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382896537848-81</Id><Topic><Title>44 Analyst follow AMZN... How many upgrades?</Title><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382845711046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 23:48:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today's headlines are a perfect example of the #$%$ that is going on... "Analyst Raises Estimates" sounds so good, but the article basically said this pig is fully priced for years to come!</Msg><Username>jaypaulseattle</Username><Timestamp>1382896537848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 13:55:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382898756259-82</Id><Title>Wedbush $330 PT... at 50X 2019 EPS!!! Sell this bloated PIG.</Title><Msg>They are "neutral" on the stock, but PT is 10% below current levels... Neutral is analyst speak for "Sell this pig" NO transparency in the numbers. If management thinks they can just not answer the difficult questions, they have a another thing coming.</Msg><Username>jaypaulseattle</Username><Timestamp>1382898756259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 14:32:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382899516589-83</Id><Topic><Title>Wedbush $330 PT... at 50X 2019 EPS!!! Sell this bloated PIG.</Title><Username>jaypaulseattle</Username><Timestamp>1382898756259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 14:32:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even funnier is "hypothetical" 2019 eps which are inflated. How inflated? They lowered Q4 to .89 profit estimate. AMZN guided .25 to (.25) or zero for Q4. So, hypothetical extremely inflated 50x 2019 numbers gives a price target today of 330. LOL I guarantee Walmart ecommerce will have passed AMZN by 2019 and it's quite possible amazon is out of cash and gone by then. Which anlysts are even more frothy than this?</Msg><Username>one_smooth_stone</Username><Timestamp>1382899516589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 14:45:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382900587279-84</Id><Title>Future Headline: AMZN- Amazing Tulip Bubble of 2013</Title><Msg>Look up 20 best reasons, to sell and/or short AMZN paper now at this 363 level,over the Net and report it here!</Msg><Username>n59218</Username><Timestamp>1382900587279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 15:03:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382900963601-85</Id><Topic><Title>I think Sybil's "Base Camp 4" analogy is proving to be very true here: you shorts have lost your minds</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382890116248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont miss understand sybil here. Sybil iznt waiting at base camp for for the pig to fly down to get on the long side expecting it to ride back up. B sybs gonna attempt 2 daring feats with this pig: 1. Sybby's gonna eventually booster rocket up to this pigz altitude and short it with a tight stop loss If that doesnt work az picking off the top of a parabola iz tough to do: 2. Sybby's gonna slide back down to base camp 4 pack up a bacpack full of rocks and then jump on this pig on its way down az its passing by base camp 4 in a tail spin, again with a tight stop loss.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382900963601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 15:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382900965277-86</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare vs Amazon ironic</Title><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382895526418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 13:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Obamacare website can be fixed, but that's not the real problem. Amazon website is great, but that's not a real competative advantage.</Msg><Username>one_smooth_stone</Username><Timestamp>1382900965277</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 15:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382906652511-87</Id><Title>Guess tommorow'z closing price</Title><Msg>378 This iz awayz a fun game.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382906652511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 16:44:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382906719735-88</Id><Topic><Title>Guess tommorow'z closing price</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382906652511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 16:44:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>345 This pig is bloated!!!!</Msg><Username>jaypaulseattle</Username><Timestamp>1382906719735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 16:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382907008136-89</Id><Topic><Title>Future Headline: AMZN- Amazing Tulip Bubble of 2013</Title><Username>n59218</Username><Timestamp>1382900587279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 15:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this print will come out at a level of 420+ in december.... From now until then you will only here the drumbeat of upgradez and "buy, buy, buy". This stock iz going higher, and trapped shorts will be lucky to see a $15 retracement from its current 363 level before it peaks north of 420. Guessing where this pig will peak iz a fool'z errand.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382907008136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 16:50:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382907657968-90</Id><Topic><Title>I think Sybil's "Base Camp 4" analogy is proving to be very true here: you shorts have lost your minds</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382890116248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"and short it with a tight stop loss" Gee you`re became so effraid, maybe time for you to step to short term bond investment ??!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! If you`re going to short it for a real ride, why would you care to use stop loss at those level ??!!!!! Just build your position and don`t worry about pop up.... You``re rather talking like a daytrader ot like a trader that can only take ONE position at one price....... Geeeeeeeee, you almost become girly...........</Msg><Username>optionstrader008</Username><Timestamp>1382907657968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 17:00:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382908182297-91</Id><Title>What's next for AMZN</Title><Msg>Probable prices for tomorrow (10/28) would be around High: $359.50 Low: $347.89 Close: $351.36</Msg><Username>s_haliz</Username><Timestamp>1382908182297</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 17:09:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382909472332-92</Id><Topic><Title>Guess tommorow'z closing price</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382906652511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 16:44:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>348 close tomorrow</Msg><Username>one_smooth_stone</Username><Timestamp>1382909472332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 17:31:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382910584237-93</Id><Topic><Title>What's next for AMZN</Title><Username>s_haliz</Username><Timestamp>1382908182297</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 17:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>High 375 Low 357 Close 370</Msg><Username>timlawp</Username><Timestamp>1382910584237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 17:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382912029241-94</Id><Topic><Title>Q3 accounting trick for fake beat</Title><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382888259116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree..and cramer is still pumping. he refuses to look at the facts because he is a bilderberg shill. this company is not growing like everyone says. Karl D covered it on marketticker...the analysts, everyone are in a massive bubble. how much market cap did the stock go up on this so called rev beat? its a complete JOKE</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1382912029241</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 18:13:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382912231646-95</Id><Title>Cramer pumping the top and chiding bears on realmoney. he refuses to look at the Accounting trick Amazon used</Title><Msg>to once again cause a fake short squeeze of no liquidity......karl denniger has covered this on his site and guys like cramer who pump for Bilderbergs like bezos won't talk about for you morons, the only reason amazon has gotten so many free passes is 1. its a bubble. 2. bezos is a bilderberg. period 3. amazon was part of their plan to help destroy loads of shopkeeper/small business retail the last 15 years. wake up. they make NO MONEY. if they actually didn't have a bubble stock that was supported by these pricks they would never be here math doesn't lie in the end.</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1382912231646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 18:17:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382913168090-96</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer pumping the top and chiding bears on realmoney. he refuses to look at the Accounting trick Amazon used</Title><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1382912231646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 18:17:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trips, Doez this suprise you??? Cramer alwayz pumps the tops and panick sellz the bottomz - he'z done it for 16 yearz. You should rejoice in that knowledge. Anybody listening to cramer iz a moron. That being said , just az cramer waz saying "GET OUT" in '08 wasnt the exact bottom and him pumping the dop doez not preclude pigz stuck in a parabola tacking on another 20-30%.... Even a contrain call of isiot cramer cannot pick exact tops and bottomz - nothing really can.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382913168090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 18:32:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382913467959-97</Id><Topic><Title>I think Sybil's "Base Camp 4" analogy is proving to be very true here: you shorts have lost your minds</Title><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382890116248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 12:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Gee you`re became so effraid, maybe time for you to step to short term bond investment ??!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!" Ohhhh there's a difference between sybil being 'afraid' of a parabolic move and respwcting the parabola- sybil bowz down before the awesome might of a parabola and would advise any sane short to do the same , stupid.... If sybil were 'afraid' then sybby would be entirely out and cowering on a corner - this iz simply the wrong though process by a strung out crack head optionz trader</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382913467959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 18:37:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382916087633-98</Id><Title>I just had a thought about monopolies &amp; amazon</Title><Msg>Amazon has driven so many companies out of business, they may be the first co. never to make profit to be sued by the Justice department under the antitrust laws .</Msg><Username>fbertital</Username><Timestamp>1382916087633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 19:21:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382917923098-99</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer pumping the top and chiding bears on realmoney. he refuses to look at the Accounting trick Amazon used</Title><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1382912231646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 18:17:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cramer's recommendation of a stock at it's all time high is usually a kiss of death for the stock.Usually not right at at the time but shortly afterward.I've seen it happen many times.</Msg><Username>fester6346</Username><Timestamp>1382917923098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 19:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382918109680-100</Id><Topic><Title>THE NEW NORMAL IN USA?HELLO USA 99% ZOMBIES: CAN YOU FIX BRAINS TO ABSORB HARSH REALITY FACTS AKA TRUTH OR FRAUD PROPAGANDA $UCKED BRAINS CAN NOT BE REPROGRAMMED?</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382803262890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 12:01:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Detroit Pensioners Face Miserable 16 Cent On The Dollar Recovery If there is ever a case study about people who built up their reputation and then squandered it for first being right for all the wrong reasons, and then being wrong for the right ones, then Meredith Whitney certainly heads the list of eligible candidates. After "predicting" the great financial crisis back in 2007 by looking at some deteriorating credit trends at Citigroup, a process that many had engaged beforehand and had come to a far more dire -and just as correct - conclusion, Whitney rose to stardom for merely regurgitating a well-known meme, however since her trumpeted call was the one closest to the Lehman-Day event when it all came crashing down, it afforded her a 5 year very lucrative stint as an advisor. Said stint has now been shuttered. The main reason for the shuttering, of course, is that in 2010 she also called an imminent "muni" cataclysm, staking her reputation once again not only on what is fundamentally obvious, but locking in a time frame: 2011. Alas, this time her "timing" luck ran out and her call was dead wrong, leading people to question her abilities, and ultimately to give up on her "advisory" services altogether. Which in some ways is a shame because Whitney was and is quite correct about the municipal default tidal wave, as Detroit and ever more municipalities have shown, and the only question is the timing. However, as Citi's Matt King recent showed, when it comes to stepwise, quantum leap repricings of widely held credits, the revelation is usually a very painful, sudden and very dramatic one. This can be seen nowhere better than in the default of Lehman brothers, where while the firm's equity was slow to admit defeat it was nothing in comparison to the abject case study in denial that the Lehman bonds put in. However, as can be seen in the chart below, when it finally came, and when bondholders realized they are screwed the morning of Monday, Septembr 15 when the Lehman bankruptcy filing was fact, the move from 80 cents on the dollar to under 10 cents took place in a heartbeat. It is the same kind of violent and anguished repricing that all unsecrued creditors in the coming wave of heretofore "denialed" municipal bankruptcy filings will have to undergo. Starting with Detroit, where as Reuters reports, the recovery to pensioners, retirees and all other unsecured creditors will be.... 16 cents on the dollar!... or less than what Greek bondholders got in the country's latest (and certainly not final) bankruptcy. From Reuters: On Friday, city financial consultant Kenneth Buckfire said he did not have to recommend to Orr that pensions for the city's retirees be cut as a way to help Detroit navigate through debts and liabilities that total $18.5 billion. Buckfire said it was clear that the city did not have the funds to pay the unsecured pension payouts without cutting them. "It was a function of the mathematics," said Buckfire, who said he did not think it was necessary for him or anyone else to recommend pension cuts to Orr. "Are you saying it was so self-evident that no one had to say it?" asked Claude Montgomery, attorney for a committee of retirees that was created by Rhodes. "Yes," Buckfire answered. Buckfire, a Detroit native and investment banker with restructuring experience, later told the court the city plans to pay unsecured creditors, including the city's pensioners, 16 cents on the dollar. There are about 23,500 city retirees. One wonders by how many cents on the dollar the recovery to pensioners would increase if the New York-based Miller Buckfire were to cut their advisory fee, but that is not the point of this post (it will be of a subsequent). What is the point, is that creditors across all products, aided and abetted by the greatest credit bubble of all time blown by Benny and the Inkjets, will find the kind of violent repricings that Lehman showed take place whenever hope dies, increasingly more prevalent. And since retirees and pensioners are ultimately creditors, this is perhaps the fastest, if certainly most brutal way, to make sure that the United Welfare States of America is finally on a path of sustainability. The only question is how will those same retirees who have just undergone an 84 cent haircut, take it. One hopes: peacefully. Because among those whose incentive to work effectively has just been cut to zero, is also the local police force. In which case if hope once again fails, it is perhaps better not to contemplate the consequences. For both Meredith Whitney, who will eventually be proven right, and for everyone else.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382918109680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 19:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382918142401-101</Id><Title>"Analyst: Raises estimates on Amazon" What a bunch of bull</Title><Msg>The headline sounds so bullish. The article tells you to sell! more attempted spinning of this stock. This POS will break. I hope it starts tomorrow.</Msg><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382918142401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 19:55:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382919267151-102</Id><Topic><Title>"Analyst: Raises estimates on Amazon" What a bunch of bull</Title><Username>xom_bull</Username><Timestamp>1382918142401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 19:55:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PE on 2018 earnings?!? $330 price target on 5 years out?!?</Msg><Username>jmgerh</Username><Timestamp>1382919267151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 20:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382920099212-103</Id><Title>my question to Sybil: why do you keep beating the same drum here with 100 posts saying the same thing?</Title><Msg>ok you say 420, isn't that enough now? and I'm not even short. Seems like you have alternative motives in the amount of posts that say the same thing? don't you have any hobbies? just saying and observing. You've gotten the fear ,monger for higher prices out now: ok? It's clear.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1382920099212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 20:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382920576684-104</Id><Topic><Title>Guess tommorow'z closing price</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382906652511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 16:44:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$354</Msg><Username>california_is_greece</Username><Timestamp>1382920576684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 20:36:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382921703533-105</Id><Topic><Title>Guess tommorow'z closing price</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382906652511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 16:44:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THIS MF IS GONE CRAZY HERE LOL</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382921703533</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 20:55:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382921990293-106</Id><Topic><Title>Guess tommorow'z closing price</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382906652511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 16:44:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$351</Msg><Username>s_haliz</Username><Timestamp>1382921990293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 20:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382922305023-107</Id><Title>The fear hazn't even begun, ayahtolla</Title><Msg>There iz much fear to come.... Panick buying first, followd by the biggest panick sell you've ever witnessed... Wait 'till uncle ben comez on the horn at the fomc meeting with low 'no change to qe due to 'low inflation and slow job growth' and with 'caution iz warrented allowing for continuation of low inetrest rates for an extended period of time'.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382922305023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 21:05:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382925347220-108</Id><Topic><Title>The lowered their losses!!</Title><Username>moody.brent16</Username><Timestamp>1382749696380</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 21:08:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, I totally agree with you, a 10% pop on a loss is, lets see, I am at a loss of words, "death"?</Msg><Username>al_cool_1999</Username><Timestamp>1382925347220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 21:55:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382926643770-109</Id><Topic><Title>Guess tommorow'z closing price</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382906652511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 16:44:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>384</Msg><Username>caseus_865656</Username><Timestamp>1382926643770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 22:17:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382927754704-110</Id><Topic><Title>I just had a thought about monopolies &amp; amazon</Title><Username>fbertital</Username><Timestamp>1382916087633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 19:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One need not make a profit to engage in anti-competitive behavior. Without question, the Quidsi play was that. Targeting weak "gazelle" publishers (insteaad DOJ is going after Apple leveling the playing field...). Amazon will almost certainly be an anti-trust target over the next few years, as it should be.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382927754704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 22:35:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382927846167-111</Id><Topic><Title>Q3 accounting trick for fake beat</Title><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382888259116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 11:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess by a severa, hundred times the amount of the revenue beat... Rather fascinating math these days...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382927846167</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 22:37:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382928001210-112</Id><Title>Island reversal would be priceless...</Title><Msg>Let the pumpers load up for another day and then unload unlimited amounts at scam valuations when Fed cannot stop printing, but the impact of printing hurts Amazon.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382928001210</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 22:40:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382928496213-113</Id><Topic><Title>I just had a thought about monopolies &amp; amazon</Title><Username>fbertital</Username><Timestamp>1382916087633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 19:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMZN is no monopoly. AMZN could be 100% gone and you can still get everything elsewhere online.</Msg><Username>bloop2456</Username><Timestamp>1382928496213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 22:48:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382929345948-114</Id><Topic><Title>I just had a thought about monopolies &amp; amazon</Title><Username>fbertital</Username><Timestamp>1382916087633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 19:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL ERIC HOLDER SCAM GANG AT DOJ?LOL</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382929345948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 23:02:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382930987918-115</Id><Topic><Title>Island reversal would be priceless...</Title><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382928001210</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 22:40:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leave Sybil etc. stranded at $363 like on some pillar at Monument Valley. That would be nice. Almost happened with Netflix.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1382930987918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 23:29:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382931364856-116</Id><Topic><Title>FELLOW USA 99% GO AND SURROUND "SEC" HEAD QUARTERS WHERE THESE CRIMINALS GET ALL FRAUD WEAPONS TO SCAM/BANG/LOOT US ALL</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382716651223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 11:57:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An Introduction: Code Red When Lehman Brothers went bankrupt and AIG was taken over by the US government in the fall of 2008, the world almost came to an end. Over the next few weeks, stock markets went into free fall as trillions of dollars of wealth were wiped out. However, even more disturbing were the real-world effects on trade and businesses. A strange silence descended on the hubs of global commerce. As international trade froze, ships stood empty near ports around the world because banks would no longer issue letters of credit. Factories shut and millions of workers were laid off as commercial paper and money market funds used to pay wages froze. Major banks in the US and the UK were literally hours away from shutting down, and ATMs were on the verge of running out of cash. The world was threatened with a big deflationary collapse. A crisis that big comes around only twice a century. Families and governments were swamped with too much debt and not enough money to pay them off. But cent ral banks and governments saved the day by printing money, providing almost unlimited amounts of liquidity to the financial system. Like a doctor's putting a large jolt of electricity on a dying man's chest, the extreme measures brought the patient back to life. The money printing that central bankers did after the failure of Lehman Brothers was entirely appropriate in order to avoid a Great Depression II. The Fed and central banks were merely creating some money and credit that only partially offset the contraction in bank lending. The initial crisis is long gone, but the unconventional measures have stayed with us. Once the crisis was over, it was clear that the world was saddled with high debt and low growth. In order to fight the monsters of deflation and depression, central bankers have gone wild. Central bankers kept on creating money. Quantitative easing was a shocking development when it was first trotted out, but these days the markets just shrug. Now, the markets are worried about losing their regular injections of monetary drugs. What will withdrawal be like? The amount of money central banks have created is simply staggering. Under quantitative easing, central banks have been buying every government bond in sight and have expanded their balance sheets by over nine trillion dollars. Yes, that's $9,000,000,000,000 – twelve zeros to be exact. (By the time you read this book, the number will probably be a few trillion higher, but who is counting?) Numbers so large are difficult for ordinary humans to understand. As Senator Everett M. Dirksen once probably didn't say, "A billion here, a billion there, and soon you're talking about real money." To put it in everyday terms, if you had a credit limit of nine trillion dollars on your credit card, you could buy a MacBook Air for every single person in the world. You could fly everyone in the world on a round-trip ticket from New York to London and back. You could do that twice without blinking. We could go on, but you get the point: it's a big number . In the four years since the Lehman Brothers bankruptcy, central bankers have torn up the rulebook and are trying things they have never tried before. Usually interest rates move up or down depending on growth and inflation. Higher growth and inflation normally mean higher rates, and lower growth means lower rates. Those were the good old days when things were normal. But now central bankers in the US, Japan, and Europe have pinned interest rates close to zero and promised to leave them there for years. Rates can't go lower, so some central bankers have decided to get creative. Normally central banks pay interest on the cash that banks deposit with them overnight. Not anymore. Some banks like the Swiss National Bank and the Danish National Bank have even created negative deposit rates. We now live in an upside down world. Money is effectively taxed (by central bankers, not representative governments!) to get people to spend instead of save. These unconventional policies are generally good for big banks, governments, and borrowers (who doesn't like to borrow money for free?); but they are very bad for savers. Near-zero interest rates and heavily subsidized government lending programs help the banks to make money the old-fashioned way: borrow cheaply and lend at higher rates. They also help insolvent governments by allowing them to borrow at very low costs. The flip side is that near-zero rates punish savers, providing almost no income to pensioners and the elderly. Everyone who thought their life's savings might carry them through their retirement has to come up with a Plan B when rates are near zero. In the bizarre world we now inhabit, central banks and governments try to induce consumers to spend to help the economy while they take money away from savers who would like to be able to profitably invest. Rather than inducing them to consume more, they are forcing them to spend less in order to make their savings last through their final years! Savers and investors in the developed world are the guinea pigs in an unprecedented monetary experiment. There are clear winners and losers as prudent savers are called upon to bail out reckless borrowers. In the US, UK, Japan, and most of Europe, savers receive close to zero percent interest on their savings while they watch the price of gasoline, groceries, and rents go up. Standards of living are falling for many and economic growth is elusive. Today is a time of financial repression, where central banks keep interest rates below inflation. This means that the interest savers receive on their deposits cannot keep up with the rising cost of living. Big banks are bailed out and continue paying large bonuses while older savers are punished. In the film A Few Good Men Jack Nicholson played Colonel Nathan Jessup. He was guilty of using an unconventional approach to discipline by ordering a Code Red, an extreme discipline method, on his soldiers. Colonel Jessup explained in court towards the end of the film that while his methods are grotesque and abnormal, they are necessary to preserve freedom. While central bank Code Red policies are unorthodox and distasteful, many economists believe they are necessary to kick-start the global economy and counteract the crushing burden of debt. David Zervos, chief market strategist at the investment bank Jeffries &amp; Co., humorously observed that if Ben Bernanke, the Chairman of the United States Federal Reserve, could be honest with the public, he would paraphrase Colonel Jessup's speech: You want the truth? You can't handle the truth! Son, we live in a world that has unfathomably intricate economies, and those economies and the banks that are at their center have to be guarded by men with complex models and printing presses. Who's gonna do it? You? You, Lieutenant Mauldin? Can you even begin to grasp the resources we have to use in order to maintain balance in a system on the brink? I have a greater responsibility than you can possibly fathom! You weep for Savers and creditors, and you curse the central bankers and quantitative easing. You have that luxury. You have the luxury of not knowing what I know: that the destruction of savers with inflation and low rates, while tragic, probably saved lives. And my existence, while grotesque and incomprehensible to you, saves jobs and banks and businesses and whole economies! You don't want the truth, because deep down in places you don't talk about at parties, you want me on that central bank! You need me on that Committee! Without our willingness to silently serve, deflation would come storming over our economic walls and wreak far worse havoc on an entire nation and the world. I will not let the 1930s and that devastating unemployment and loss of lives repeat themselves on my watch. We use words like "full employment," "inflation," "stability." We use these words as the backbone of a life spent defending something. You use them as a punchline! I have neither the time nor the inclination to explain myself to a man who rises and sleeps under the blanket of the very prosperity that I provide, and then questions the manner in which I provide it! I would rather you just say "Thank you," and go on your way. Central bankers must hide the truth in order to do their job. We may dislike what they are doing, but if politicians want to avoid large-scale defaults, the world needs loose money and money printing. Ben Bernanke and his colleagues worldwide have effectively issued and enforced a Code Red monetary policy. Their economic theories and experience told them it was the correct and necessary thing to do – in fact, they were convinced it was the only thing to do! Chairman Ben Bernanke could not be further from Colonel Nathaniel Jessup, but they are both men on a mission. Colonel Jessup is maniacally obsessed with enforcing discipline on his base at Guantanamo. He has seen war and does not take it lightly. He is a tough Marine who would not hesitate to kill his enemies. He is not loved, but he's happy to be feared and respected. Ben Bernanke, by contrast, is a soft-spoken academic. You can't find anyone with anything bad to say about him personally. His story is inspiring. He grew up as one of the few Jews in the Southern town of Dillon, South Carolina; and through his natural genius and hard work, he was admitted to Harvard, where he graduated with distinction, and soon he embarked on a brilliant academic career at MIT and Princeton. Sometimes when Bernanke gives a speech, his voice cracks slightly, and it is certain he would much prefer to be writing academic papers or lecturing to a class of graduate students than de aling with large skeptical audiences of senators. But Bernanke is one of the world's experts on the Great Depression. He has learned from history and knows that too much debt can be lethal. He genuinely believes that, without Code Red-type policies, he would condemn America to a decade of breadlines and bankruptcies. He promised he would not let deflation and another Great Depression grip America. In his own way, he's our Colonel Jessup, standing on the wall fighting for us. And he gets too little respect. Bernanke understands that the world has far too much debt that it can't pay back. Sadly, debt can only go away via: 1) defaults (and there are so many ways to default without having to actually use the word!), 2) paying down debt through economic growth, or 3) eroding the burden of debt through inflation or devaluations. In our grandparents' age, we would have seen defaults. But defaults are painful, and no one wants them. We've grown fat and comfortable. We don't like pain. Growing our way out of our problems would be ideal, but it isn't an option. Economic growth is elusive everywhere we look. Central bankers are left with no other option but to create inflation and devalue their currencies. No one wants to hear that we'll suffer from higher inflation. It is grotesque and not what central bankers are meant to do. But people can't handle the truth, and inflation is exactly what the central bankers are preparing for us. They're sparing some the pain of defaults while others bear the pain of low returns. But a world in which big banks and governments default is almost by definition a world of not just low but (sometimes steeply) negative returns. As we said in Endgame, we are left with no good choices, only choices that range from the merely very difficult to the downright disastrous. The global situation reminds us very much of Woody Allen's quote, "More than any other time in history, mankind faces a crossroads. One path leads to despair and utter hopelessness. The other, to total extinction. Let us pray we have the wisdom to choose correctly." The choice now left to some countries is only between Disaster A and Disaster B. Today's battle with deflation requires a constant vigilance and use of Code Red procedures. Unfortunately, just as in A Few Good Men, Code Reds are not standard operating procedures or conventional policies. Ben Bernanke, Mario Draghi, Haruhiko Kuroda, and other central bankers are manning their battle station using ugly means to get the job done. They are punishing savers, encouraging people to borrow more, providing lots of liquidity, and weakening their currencies. This unprecedented global monetary experiment has only just begun, and every central bank is trying to get in on the act. It is a monetary arms race, and no one wants to be left behind. The Bank of England has devalued the pound to improve exports by allowing creeping inflation and keeping interest rates at zero. The Federal Reserve has tried to weaken the dollar in order to boost manufacturing and exports. The Bank of Japan, not to be outdone, is now trying to depreciate the yen. By weakening their currencies, they hope to boost their exports and get a leg up on their competitors. In the race to debase currencies, no one wins. Emerging market countries like Brazil, Russia, Malaysia, and Indonesia will not sit idly by while developed central banks weaken their currencies. They are fighting to keep their currencies from appreciating. They are imposing taxes on investments and savings in their currencies. Countries are turning protectionist. The battles have only begun in what promises to be an enormous, ugly currency war. If the currency wars of the1930 and 1970s are any guide, we will see knife fights ahead. Governments will fight dirty, they will impose tariffs and restrictions and capital controls. It is already happening and we will see a lot more of it. If only they were just armed with knives. We are reminded of that amusing scene in Raiders of the Lost Ark where Indiana Jones, confronted with a very large man wielding an even larger scimitar, simply pulls out his gun, shoots him, and walks away. Some central banks are better armed than others. Indeed, you might say that the four biggest central banks – the Fed, BOE, ECB, and BOJ – have nuclear arsenals. In a fight for national survival – which is what a crisis this major will feel like – will central bankers resort to the nuclear option; will they double down on Code Red policies? The conflict could get very messy for those in the neighborhood. Providing more debt and more credit after a bust that was caused by too much credit is like suggesting whiskey after a hangover. Paradoxical as the cure may be, many economists and investors think that it is just what the doctor ordered. At the star-studded World Economic Forum retreat in Davos, Switzerland, the billionaire George Soros pointed out the contradiction policy makers now face. The global financial crisis happened because of too much debt and too much money floating around. However, according to many economists and investors, the solution may in fact be more money and more debt. As he said, "When a car is skidding, you first have to turn the wheel in the same direction as the skid to regain control because if you don't, then you have the car rolling over." Only after the global economy has recovered can the car begin to right itself. Before central banks can be responsible and conventional, they must first be irresponsible and unconventional. The arsonists are now running the fire brigade. Central bankers contributed to the economic crisis the world now faces. They kept interest rates too low for too long. They fixated on controlling inflation, even as they stood by and watched investment banks party in an orgy of credit. Central bankers were completely incompetent and failed to see the Great Financial Crisis coming. They couldn't spot housing bubbles, and even when the crisis had started and banks were failing, they insisted that the banks they supervised were well regulated and healthy. They failed at their job and should have been fired. Yet governments now need central banks to erode the mountain of debt by printing money and creating inflation. Investors should ask themselves: if central bankers couldn't manage conventional monetary policy well in the good times, what makes us think that they will be able to manage unconventional monetary policies in the bad times? And if they don't do a perfect job of winding down condition Code Red, what will be the consequences? Economists know that there are no free lunches. Creating tons of new money and credit out of thin air is not without cost. Massively increasing the size of a central bank's balance sheet is risky and stores up extremely difficult problems for the future. Central bank policies may succeed in creating growth, or they may fail. It is too soon to call the outcome, but what is clear (at least to us) is that the experiment is unlikely to end well. The endgame for the current crisis is not difficult to foresee; in fact, it's already underway. Central banks think they can swell the size of their balance sheet, print money to finance government deficits, and keep rates at zero with no consequences. Bernanke and other bankers think they have the foresight to reverse their unconventional policies at the right time. They've been wrong in the past, and they will get the timing wrong in the future. They will keep interest rates too low for too long and cause inflation and bubbles in real estate, stock markets, and bonds. What they are doing will destroy savers who rely on interest payments and fixed coupons from their bonds. They will also harm lenders who have lent money and will never be repaid in devalued dollars, if they are repaid at all. We are already seeing the unintended consequences of this Great Monetary Experiment. Many emerging market stock markets have skyrocketed, only to fall back to earth at the hint of an end to Code Red policies. Junk bonds and risky commercial mortgage-backed securities are offering investors the lowest rates they have ever seen. Investors are reaching for riskier and riskier investments to get some small return. They're picking up dimes in front of a steamroller. It is fun for a while, but the end is always ugly. Older people who are relying on pension funds to pay for their retirement are getting screwed (that is a technical economic term that we will define in detail later). In normal times, retirees could buy bonds and live on the coupons. Not anymore. Government bond yields are now trading below the level of inflation, guaranteeing that any investor who holds the bonds until maturity will lose money in real terms. We live in extraordinary times. When investors convince themselves central bankers have their backs, they feel encouraged to bid up prices for everything, accepting more risk with less return. Excesses and bubbles are not a mere side effect. As crazy as it seems, reckless investor behavior is, in fact, the planned objective. William McChesney Martin, one of the great heads of the Federal Reserve, said the job of a central banker was to take away the punch bowl before the party gets started. Now, central bankers are spiking the punch bowl with triple sec and absinthe and egging on the revelers to jump in the pool. One day the party of low rates and money printing will come to an end, and investors will make their way home from the party in the early hours of sunlight half dressed, with hangovers and thumping headaches. The coming upheaval will affect everyone. No one will be spared the consequences – from savers who are planning for retirement to professional traders looking for opportunities to profit in financial markets. Inflation will eat away at savings; government bonds will be destroyed as a supposedly safe asset class; and assets that benefit from inflation and money printing will do well. This book will provide a roadmap and a playbook for retail savers and professional traders alike. This book will shine a light on the path ahead. Code Red will explain in plain English complicated things like zero interest rate policies (ZIRP), nominal GDP targeting, quantitative easing, money printing, and currency wars. But much more importantly, it will explain how what is in store will affect your savings and offer insights on how to protect your wealth. Code Red will be an invaluable guide for the road ahead. Code Red will be available on Amazon on Monday, Oct. 28.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382931364856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 23:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382931405840-117</Id><Title>Tuesday, October 29th has a history....remember 1929?</Title><Msg>Monday, don't know. But Tuesday, October 29th 1929 ("Black Tuesday") was a 12% down day on the biggest volume day of the ,29 crash. Just saying. maybe this time is different. valuations are already up there with pre-crash 1929.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1382931405840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 23:36:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382931426001-118</Id><Topic><Title>LION BRODCAST VS FRAUD STREET BANKSTER FRAUD ANALYST TERRORIST: OUTRIGHT DUMP AND AVOID RATIUNG ON AMAZON ENFORCED</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382730679201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 15:51:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This unprecedented global monetary experiment has only just begun, and every central bank is trying to get in on the act. It is a monetary arms race, and no one wants to be left behind. The Bank of England has devalued the pound to improve exports by allowing creeping inflation and keeping interest rates at zero. The Federal Reserve has tried to weaken the dollar in order to boost manufacturing and exports. The Bank of Japan, not to be outdone, is now trying to depreciate the yen. By weakening their currencies, they hope to boost their exports and get a leg up on their competitors. In the race to debase currencies, no one wins. Emerging market countries like Brazil, Russia, Malaysia, and Indonesia will not sit idly by while developed central banks weaken their currencies. They are fighting to keep their currencies from appreciating. They are imposing taxes on investments and savings in their currencies. Countries are turning protectionist. The battles have only begun in what promises to be an enormous, ugly currency war. If the currency wars of the1930 and 1970s are any guide, we will see knife fights ahead. Governments will fight dirty, they will impose tariffs and restrictions and capital controls. It is already happening and we will see a lot more of it.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382931426001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 23:37:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382931554903-119</Id><Topic><Title>THE NEW NORMAL IN USA?HELLO USA 99% ZOMBIES: CAN YOU FIX BRAINS TO ABSORB HARSH REALITY FACTS AKA TRUTH OR FRAUD PROPAGANDA $UCKED BRAINS CAN NOT BE REPROGRAMMED?</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382803262890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-26 12:01:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Question: The Fed wizards have been pushing buttons and pulling levers rather furiously since 2008. The discount rate is rock bottom, and the Fed balance sheet has swelled to the tune of trillions. What button is left for them to push? Steve Hochberg: That is a really interesting question the way you phrased it because the fact that they have been pushing buttons and have gotten very little in return tells us … that the Fed is not in control. The Fed does not control the markets, and it doesn’t control the economy. Both are bigger than the Fed. You say they have been doing this furiously. They have been doing this historically! Yet if you look at inflationary measures, such as the Personal Consumption Expenditures, which is the Fed's favorite way of measuring inflation, it's bumping along at 1%. We have had historic fiscal and monetary stimulus and yet no inflation. Why? The forces of deflation are overwhelming the forces of inflation. The Fed dropped interest rates in 2000 to 2002 and that did not stop the Nasdaq from dropping 78%. The Fed dropped rates from 2007 to 2009 and it did not stop the Dow from going down 59%. There is historical evidence that the Fed does not control the markets but that the markets control the Fed. As the next leg of the bear market starts unfolding, they are going to do more unconventional things. Things will accelerate to the downside when the public realizes the central banks aren't in control.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382931554903</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 23:39:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382931770723-120</Id><Title>SINGING LION TAKE A SEDATIVE--SHOUTING IN CAPS IS ANNOYING AND MAKES PEOPLE IGNORE YOU</Title><Msg>SYBIL CALLS YOU A NUT--I DONT KNOW IF YOU ARE BUT SHOUTING DOESNT MAKE YOU LOOK SERIOUS. Be calm, lower case discusssions. Thank you.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1382931770723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 23:42:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382932332958-121</Id><Topic><Title>FELLOW USA 99% GO AND SURROUND "SEC" HEAD QUARTERS WHERE THESE CRIMINALS GET ALL FRAUD WEAPONS TO SCAM/BANG/LOOT US ALL</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382716651223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-25 11:57:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you think Ben Bernanke and his cohorts at the Federal Reserve worry about the average person who doesn’t own stocks, has to fill up their gas tank, feed their kids, make the mortgage, auto, and credit card payments, and figure out Obamacare, while working two part time jobs? Quantitative Easing (MONEY PRINTING) has one purpose and one purpose only – to further enrich the owners of the Federal Reserve – Wall Street banks. The .1% own most of the stocks in this country and their greed and avarice can never be satisfied.This artificial prosperity plan for Wall Street has the added benefit of allowing the captured politicians in Washington D.C. to continue their $1 trillion per year deficit spending with no consequences for their squandering of future generations’ wealth. Bernanke and Yellen will never taper, because they can’t. The Fed balance sheet will continue to grow by at least $1 trillion per year until they crash the financial system again. Except this time, there will be no money printing solution. We are all trapped like rats in this monetary experiment being conducted by evil mad scientists. No one will get out alive. Welcome to the new normal. Now eat your cheese.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1382932332958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 23:52:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382932365249-122</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer pumping the top and chiding bears on realmoney. he refuses to look at the Accounting trick Amazon used</Title><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1382912231646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 18:17:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love how the shorts call the longs morons when the longs made fortunes on this. Does it matter how or why the longs cleaned up on this? Nope. The $ gains all look the same whether they are from a stock that's undervalued, overvalued, or short-squeezed. Thank you for supporting my long gain$! Nosmo</Msg><Username>nosmo_king_01</Username><Timestamp>1382932365249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-10-27 23:52:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>