<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-10-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382156669102-1</Id><Topic><Title>Has Anyone Seen My Stalkers stinky And stinky Jr.????</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1380641298183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-01 11:28:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those boys are hiding under their rocks.............</Msg><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1382156669102</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 00:24:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382167802204-2</Id><Title>The Platform - Patented Local Shopping Technology</Title><Msg>Powered by Krillion®, Krillion delivers the most robust and accurate location-based product search data available. Our solutions provide dynamic, up-to-the minute information about where specific branded products are sold, and which retailers have them in stock the instant shoppers are ready to buy. Our patented Krillion® localization engine provides aggregated and structured local product shopping data to our business customers and channel partners. We pioneered local shopping search and are committed to the continuous growth of our dynamic platform that supports multi-channel retailers and brands looking to engage consumers wherever they research products and where to buy. As a result, our patented data normalization platform offers the most comprehensive cleansing and distribution capabilities in the available today</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1382167802204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 03:30:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382167903445-3</Id><Topic><Title>The Platform - Patented Local Shopping Technology</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1382167802204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 03:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Krillion for Publisher Enhance your site’s content while creating more traffic and better monetization. Our patented location-based product search technology seamlessly integrates hyper-local shopping content into your properties so you can optimize monetization of your sites’ traffic</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1382167903445</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 03:31:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382167934122-4</Id><Topic><Title>The Platform - Patented Local Shopping Technology</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1382167802204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 03:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Krillion for Retailers Increase visibility and reach more local shoppers Now you can promote your products across a vast network of high-quality, location-based publishers and partners by including your national and local store assortment in the Krillion® localization engine.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1382167934122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 03:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382168043714-5</Id><Topic><Title>The Platform - Patented Local Shopping Technology</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1382167802204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 03:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Krillion for Developers Build robust applications with the same local shopping data used by leading brands and publishers Ideal for powering all types of web and mobile apps, our patented local product search technology provides consumers with real-time shopping data tailored just for them</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1382168043714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 03:34:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382168080545-6</Id><Topic><Title>The Platform - Patented Local Shopping Technology</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1382167802204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 03:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Krillion for Brand Manufacturers Help shoppers find your products at stores nearby Provide online shoppers with a seamless web-to-store experience on their desktop or mobile device that makes it easy to buy your products online and offline.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1382168080545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 03:34:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382168158179-7</Id><Topic><Title>The Platform - Patented Local Shopping Technology</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1382167802204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 03:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sell all your Yelp shares at once: Yelp has only the 2.4-fold revenues of Local Corp, but the 110-fold market-cap! Income Statement of Local Corp (Market Cap = 43.47 million): • Sequential revenue growth up 6% to $22.7 million in Q2 from $21.5 million in Q1 • Adjusted EBITDA up 72% to $1.2M in Q2 from $685K in Q1 Income Statement of Yelp (Market Cap = 4,810 million) • Net revenue was $55.0 million in the second quarter • Adjusted EBITDA for the second quarter of 2013 was approximately $7.8 million, compared to $1.6 million for the second quarter of 2012</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1382168158179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 03:35:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382172120364-8</Id><Title>PEG is only 9.5</Title><Msg>very cheap very cheap stock consider PEG=2 is expensive but this is not the point AMZN do not have valid PE...... next year PE is 150...... do you really understand what are you buying???</Msg><Username>emanuel_dabah</Username><Timestamp>1382172120364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 04:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382180498031-9</Id><Title>Waaaaaaaatch out!!!!! If you didnt cover yesterday then your broker will do it for you on wed.</Title><Msg>Shorts - YOU NEED TO COVER .....if you do not cover then sybil will short the stuck az your broker coverz it for you. Go out on your own termz and pull your own trigger - dont make your broker shoot you. Sybil works morgue duty and will short your coverz ....</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382180498031</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 07:01:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382180946804-10</Id><Title>Shorts the action doesnt look good - here's how its gonna play out</Title><Msg>Monday range 322-330 Tue range gap up open 335 -355 353-365 close at 365 / brokerz cover and sybil shorts. Wed pm..... Missed earningz generates a 15% drop - it wont crash though because earningz dont matter until the markets crash. Sybil will swing trade and sling the blood of the dead shorts.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382180946804</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 07:09:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382181643974-11</Id><Title>Tail risk iz right..... Now you idiots get to hear sybil say all weekend that sybs warned of this...</Title><Msg>Believe sybs when sybs says: this iz only the beginning.... The music haz spead up expineyially and will play at LEAST through december stox can see 40% increasez or more with Sseemingly in explicable 15 % increasez happening in a single day ..... You will want to COOOOVERRRRR. COVER MONDAY MORNING. DO NOT BUY PUTS.... Even the long term onez wont pay off - the premiumz are too high .</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382181643974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 07:20:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382182040042-12</Id><Title>Brokerage housez ALWAYZ raise house margin maintenance requirements at your darkest hour</Title><Msg>What the stock run doesnt kill, the margin house call doez az its raised from 35%-70% equity requirements, thereby sparking a calamatous wave of short covering and a blow off top where every bandwaggon short iz murdered once and for all. A 60% rize on 50% margin equity iz a 120% loss, but your broker wont let that happen and eat 20% of insolvancy. They will raise your house requirement and cover for you until youvare wiped out.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382182040042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 07:27:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382182629230-13</Id><Title>Bernankes QE iz a circular up cycle that works against the bandwaggon of shorts</Title><Msg>QE prints the money that sheeple shorts wouldn't have had to short had not qe been in place. They take the money that bernanke haz handed them and use it to short and then cover, short and then cover, short and then cover az the too big to save 'banks' transfer wealth from the many sheeple to the few wolvez. Sybil asks you idiots this: When have you ever seen or heard of sheep rising up and successfully defeating wolvez? Use your headz: COVER. DO NOT RUN DIRECTLY AT A PACK OF WOLVEZ BY STAYING SHORT. DO NOT RUN AT A PACK OF WOLVEZ WITH A GAPING WOUND AND BROKEN LEG- THAT WOULD BE BUYING OPTIONZ.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382182629230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 07:37:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382183749265-14</Id><Title>SHORTS!!!!! Do not fall into tech's value trap</Title><Msg>Fundiez dont matter, they havent in 20 yearz or more. what matter's iz the mechanics of a bitcoin stock market that robots can compute and control in a nanosecond. Its basic supply and demand of bit coin stox that determinez the speed of wealth transfer.... the demand of short covering out strips the supply of available daily float... This causez the stox to rise. The bigger the supply / demand imbalance the faster / steeper the price . This iz exacerbated by qe (banks dont need to sell), by retail house margin maintenance requirements being raised on existing shorts to generate forced buying to cover, and by hedgie'z and or momo banks that lack moral hazard and use other sheeplez money to buy long in the greater fool cycle. Retail shorts have no chance in this environment. This seemingly endless cycle endz, not on fundiez, but on bit coin market mechanics. The cycle endz from NOSE BLEED LEVELZ where volume of buying goez to zero. "When doez buying approach zero , sybil? ", You ask. Simple : WHEN ALL THE BANDWAGGON SHORTS ARE LONG SINCE DEAD( no more buying on covering), WHEN BERNANKE STOPS QE (forcing 'banks' dump their float to generate cash), WHEN HEDGIEZ and PROP TRADING DESKS THAT LACK HAZARD or THE LAST SVCKER FUND MANAGER HAZ STOPPED BUYING. WE ARE A LONG WAYZ FROM BUYING VOLUME OF ALL FORMZ DRYING UP. THIS HAPPENZ FROM A MUCH HIGHER PRICE LEVEL. COVER !!!! COVER IMMEDIATELY!!!! SAVE WHAT YOU HAVE LEFT. DO NOT BUY PUTS.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382183749265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 07:55:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382184366260-15</Id><Topic><Title>Remember this one kidz? Opening position on the new run of the new new</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1375286118625</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-31 11:55:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Sybil is the dead short." wrong, geegee..... Sybil iz a practicle short with mucho gunpowder, calmy waiting on the side linez. Whereaz Geegee iz a broke dioeck optionz trading crackhead that losez hiz 200.00 account weekly. He livez in asylum with internet service after being furloughed from the gaurdz, he iz now AWOL.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382184366260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 08:06:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382185293867-16</Id><Topic><Title>Has Anyone Seen My Stalkers stinky And stinky Jr.????</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1380641298183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-01 11:28:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A large balloon when I look at the graph.</Msg><Username>ruudkrul</Username><Timestamp>1382185293867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 08:21:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382186804064-17</Id><Topic><Title>SHORTS!!!!! Do not fall into tech's value trap</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382183749265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 07:55:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This time is never different, except when it is... Closed system with only 1 path out that puts Amazon into world of hurt. Had another highly questionable and questionably timed upgrade yesterday, which means they'll probably be underwriting as well. Biggest scam since Enron, but this one is fully enabled (if not run by) by transaction fee collecting/underwriter/float jam scam trading institutions. Wonder what material information with respect to AMZN's financial conditions and true leverage (on and off BS) will be omitted? Wonder how they'll sell zero risk for a company that raised $3B less than 12 months ago and has effectively burned through it (and raised its burn rate by locking in higher fixed costs along the way)? Maybe Amazon didn't have a big Kindle HDX promo because it is now managing cash/earnings more closely. That's what folks typically do when BS show signs of stress (extending days payable by 10%, which accounted for about $750MM of its cash balance...). Whoever refuels in flight this time will be subject to gross negligence suits in the future. Amazon's market cap has gone up over 200% since 2009, yet cash from ops (I won't even bother focusing on true FCF...), is up only 20%, with most of that coming from the cash conversion cycle rather than earnings. So, investors are paying 3X as much for lower quality cash flows... For those interested, check out GOOG's multiple of cash from ops (which is what AMZN pumpers like to focus on because of all AMZN's "investment"). What is that multiple, even after the huge increase yesterday and how much come from actual earnings? Sybil, scream from the mountains that fundies don't matter. You're right that they don't matter to traders. But, they do to investors and investors are going to be handsomely rewarded because we just crossed the tipping point.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382186804064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 08:46:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382187974064-18</Id><Title>Amzn finds cure for cancer?</Title><Msg>When do the details arrive?</Msg><Username>fig_plucker</Username><Timestamp>1382187974064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 09:06:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382190753800-19</Id><Title>Tech, fundiez havent mattered for more than 20 yearz or more</Title><Msg>Stock markets have alwayz been about "trading", its just that the patternz and reasonz for them are out in the open and blatantly reek of bitcoin. Common stock Fundiez of companiez that have alwayz, and forever will be , divorced of common stock are simply talking points for the bla bla bla media to "justify" one direction or the other. To make sybils case crystal clear: did accurate fundiez return make whole the money short traderz lost going broke against enron before it collapsed, or any other company? Answer : no. Stop drinking koolaid, dude. You are wrong with your assumption that fundiez matter. Take the red pill that sybil iz offering you so that you mat see the matrix of 1's and 0's for what it really iz. You are stuck in the matrix and being used by the robots az a battery, you will be expelled when you are spent. Sybil offerz you reality, but you must chose for your self. Take the red pill tech and you will wake up, swallow the blue pill and you will stay comfortably in the matrix.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382190753800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 09:52:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382191155077-20</Id><Title>"Sybil iz a practicle short with mucho gunpowder" BWHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!! UTTER NONSENSE!!</Title><Msg>You've been a leveraged up COWBOY the last 14 months , doing the very thing you warn others here now about, leveraged up short on the market that ripped against your trades(fake by the way) in huge way, ripping your nads off. Now you act as if it never happened. You're a complete BS arrtist with NO MONEY! ZERO, ZILCH, and have the dumbest trading strategy knwon to man: leveraged up shorting and adding to losses with no stops, until it smoked like a PIG on a SPIT. lol! No wonder you fear monger toward others now: the very thing you warn about: ALREADY HAPPENED TO YOU. LMFAO!! YOU ARE THE BIGGEST CLOWN TO EVER COME ACROSS THESE MESSAGE BOARDS!! PERIOD END OF STORY!! YOU WIN THAT AWARD HANDS DOWN!! YOU HAVE ZERO CREDIBILITY WHICH IS WELL EARNED FROM ANYONE WHO WANT TO LOOK BACK AT YOUR MESSAGES THE LAST YEAR. ......that was fun...!!! lol!!</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382191155077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 09:59:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382191746499-21</Id><Title>this pig is a short !!!!</Title><Msg>maybe i'm missing something but they have negative EPS</Msg><Username>creditrescueny</Username><Timestamp>1382191746499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 10:09:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382191813647-22</Id><Title>Tech, when will you ever learn</Title><Msg>It haz been well documented Fundiez havent mattered az far backbaz the tulip bubble of the 15th century. What does matter? Human psycholog and Supply and demand mechanics . Fundiez dont recover sheeple'z unsecured lossez when those people are found to be correct long after they are wiped out. They didnt recover wrong way bets in tulipomania, 1890valley (panic sell), 1929 (peak panick buy), 1932 (valley panick sell) 1968 (peak), 1972 (valley), 1974 (peak), 1977 valley, 1987 peak, 1992 valley, 2000 PEAK, 2003 valley, 2007 peak, 2009 VALLEY, 20?? PEAK (sybil iz guessing and its only a guess that we are peaking right now but individual stox and markets could go MUCH MUCH higher).... Get a clue dude. Peaks and valleyz are not about fundiez, they are about wealth transfer. Bif you want fundiez then you need to operate your own successful or unsuccefull business, but even that iz about supply, demand and the ability or resourcez to influence human psychology.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382191813647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 10:10:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382192266769-23</Id><Topic><Title>this pig is a short !!!!</Title><Username>creditrescueny</Username><Timestamp>1382191746499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 10:09:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"this pig is a short !!!! maybe i'm missing something but they have negative EPS" Youre missing something very important: the fact they have negative earingz doez not matter. They have access to an endless supply of bernanke bux with robot backing. Thats what matterz. You will smash your head on the rocks if you short in the parabola, and conversly longz will do the same az it collapsez. Be smart, think before you act. Do not succume to group think. Sybil.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382192266769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 10:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382193524755-24</Id><Title>sick trade alerts right here</Title><Msg>These guys know their stuff. Every pick skyrockets. Best decision I made trading was signing up. Text the word PROFIT to 5,5,5,8,8,8</Msg><Username>gfry679</Username><Timestamp>1382193524755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 10:38:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382194390124-25</Id><Topic><Title>Has Anyone Seen My Stalkers stinky And stinky Jr.????</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1380641298183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-01 11:28:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stinky, are you having another timeout?</Msg><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1382194390124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 10:53:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382194402222-26</Id><Topic><Title>"Sybil iz a practicle short with mucho gunpowder" BWHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!! UTTER NONSENSE!!</Title><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1382191155077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 09:59:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil made a call agez ago: "qe ending in 2013 with market top in july". The circumstancez changed and sybil bets with them on endless qe - nor taper in july, did not bet against bernanke in dec, and calling a BLOW OFF market top in dec. now did sybil every go "long" ? of course not. Iz sybil a margin short now? absolutely not. Iz sybil placing reasonable short bets within sybils meaz on panick buying stox? Yes, but carefully / cautiously. Will sybil cover them on no change on qe at the next fed meeting at a loss? Yes. Will sybil be margin short the collapse ? yes. Haz sybil lost money in ytd 2013 - yes. Will sybs go insolvant? No, sybil knowz better and iz disciplined.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382194402222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 10:53:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382195396208-27</Id><Title>Trust sybil when sybs sayz : COVER</Title><Msg>If you dont then your broker will.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382195396208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 11:09:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382196049518-28</Id><Title>Sybil haz spent an exhibanant amount addressing the bandwaggon of shorts, how about rhe psycho longz now?</Title><Msg>If there are any real retail longz - most are just pumperz that went broke or bailed from their miniscule positionz yearz ago.... Just long robots for the most part now.... But if there are any retail longz - you MUST trade az if your livez depended on it with lightening speed if you are to capture a blowoff short covering rally, but you take GREAT risk in doing so. The muzak iz playing at a nano second pace and when it stops, robots will find a seat before you can blink. You are crazy to go long anything in theze markets, but if you do then you must NOT "buy, and hold", while sipping koolaid, az you "dollar average" the 'dips'. That iz sybs advise to the psycho longz.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382196049518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 11:20:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382196386971-29</Id><Title>Nasdaq_6000 iz very insecure. He'z been imagining sybils death and sporting liez to back up hiz wild imagination</Title><Msg>He iz broke, angry, and not a participant in the run up, so he lets hiz imagination run wild and vents hiz frustrationz on sybil and otherz.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382196386971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 11:26:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382198333990-30</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, when will you ever learn</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382191813647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 10:10:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are many differences this time. Financialization gone parabolic, while trading has gone higher order exponential. Financialization (and particularly trading which creates zero value) IS a cancer. It saps the blood flow to healthy/productive sectors of the economy. The impact was hidden in the 80's and early 90's as global productivity growth (via exporting our manufacturing technology to China and other low wage countries) was able to withstand the burden. But, by the mid 2000's most of the labor rate arbitrage benefit from India and China was gone and we moved into ponzi mode, the US "investing" in consumption (housing, consumer discretionary while China, in particular, overinvested in production/infrastructure. The difference is they hold $1.5T in UST and $3.5T in foreign exchange assets. When, not if, China decides to turn, it will have plenty of $ to buy natural resources from the many countries rich in natural resources with a lower marginal cost of production than us (sybs, understanding the "supply" means understanding the shape and evolution of the supply curve) and the cost to them will be lower... The US consumer is f'd and Amazon could not be more f'd. Have fun.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382198333990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 11:58:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382199646132-31</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, when will you ever learn</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382191813647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 10:10:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While the specifics are different, the outcome iz the same: wealth iz tranfered from the many to the few az efficiently az possible. Thats what markets do on a macro and micro scale... On a macro scale finance tranfered 95% of the entire globe'z wealth to 3% of its population, which mostly residez in the USA. On a micro scale within the USA , 90% of the wealth haz and iz being transfered to 1% of the population. You can grind into the detailz from there if you want to beat your head against the wall at great expense, which you seem to enjoy doing, but it doesnt take a genious to see the bigger picture for what it really iz: Mechanics of supply demand and leverage Human psychology Every time iz 'different' be it tulip bulbz, bucket shops, technology, housing, or unsustainable debt, but the end result iz very much the same : wealth iz tranfered from the many to the few. Wake up, tech. Take the red pill.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382199646132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 12:20:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382201640283-32</Id><Title>Levered bandwaggon Shorts, you need to cover az if the solvancy of your trade accounts count on you doing so</Title><Msg>Because they do.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382201640283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 12:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382201700576-33</Id><Topic><Title>Levered bandwaggon Shorts, you need to cover az if the solvancy of your trade accounts count on you doing so</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382201640283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 12:54:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deep down, you know who you are. There are many of you.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382201700576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 12:55:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382202648832-34</Id><Topic><Title>this pig is a short !!!!</Title><Username>creditrescueny</Username><Timestamp>1382191746499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 10:09:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are not wrong. In addition YELP has a flawed model on reliability.... In the LR reviews will be in the 10's of thousands for a coffee shop, with 20% being fake... Go figure who trusts that service... YELP is a fad and very overbought.. I don't know when this will happen, but the stck will have to dip 20-40%...</Msg><Username>symmetrypvt</Username><Timestamp>1382202648832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 13:10:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382204721843-35</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, when will you ever learn</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382191813647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 10:10:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is more complicated than that Sybs. As I said at $19 and holds true today, INTC at roughly 6-8X EV/EBITDA simply isn't in a bubble, especially when you play out the implications of globally coordinated QE and the currency end game. The fixed assets AMZN is investing in will have limited value in the future as the consumption infrastructure is already overbuilt. In contrast, INTC will see its cost advantage (and it does have a cost advantage as well) grow... The market isn't in a bubble. It is plainly upside down/inverted etc. QE has been used to amplify and extend the imbalance. But, we've crossed the event horizon.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382204721843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 13:45:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382211664238-36</Id><Topic><Title>you got to see this!</Title><Username>dicksonsam191</Username><Timestamp>1382045936014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-17 17:38:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i agree</Msg><Username>jamesjucas</Username><Timestamp>1382211664238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 15:41:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382216444948-37</Id><Title>Latest Barrons (out today) calls Amazon a mysterious "Black Box"</Title><Msg>"Lots of press releases" but few hard numbers according to barrons. basically what Techstrategy says, I guess. Article also says that Amazon sells Kindles at cost, trying to profit on content. Beware of "earnings" next week--a "black swan" dive may emerge from the "black box" that Barrons calls Amazon.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1382216444948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 17:00:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382217178462-38</Id><Title>Sybil thought that sybs would check in ... This comming week will be the biggest jump up for scamazon of all time</Title><Msg>Sybs check in yeildz the following observatioz: 1. Tech iz still in deep denial of what iz in front of him 2. Shorts are obcenely complacent of what lay ahead. Oh well - sybby tried.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382217178462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 17:12:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382221031601-39</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN going to hit 500 now, buy before it is too late</Title><Username>shares245</Username><Timestamp>1382214848459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 16:34:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pls keep the deep analysis coming</Msg><Username>tail_risk</Username><Timestamp>1382221031601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 18:17:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382221860944-40</Id><Topic><Title>Latest Barrons (out today) calls Amazon a mysterious "Black Box"</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1382216444948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 17:00:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and it hit its top trend line finally after all these years.</Msg><Username>imshortemc</Username><Timestamp>1382221860944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 18:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382230079789-41</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, when will you ever learn</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382191813647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 10:10:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is hilarious. Two of our biggest losers are getting engaged in an armchair discussion . . . again. You must have noticed that losers posts long messages. Do you know why? That's because talking is the only thing they still can do after losing so much for so long.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1382230079789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 20:47:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382230776466-42</Id><Title>All this rally are setup for a great fall... watch out below</Title><Msg>after earning....</Msg><Username>andyliew</Username><Timestamp>1382230776466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 20:59:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382231718075-43</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, when will you ever learn</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1382191813647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 10:10:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GG, you are the closest thing a message board has seen to single cell parasitic life form. This might have been one of your most content oriented posts ever. I'm about to make one helluva comeback. I appreciate the casino increasing the ROIC as I'm scaling in more continuously through April...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1382231718075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 21:15:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>