<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-09-21"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379761336025-1</Id><Topic><Title>Any reason for the gap and rally in he morning.</Title><Username>paths_ca</Username><Timestamp>1379718821182</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-20 19:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Smart move rename the share and sell them. Don't worry amzn probably will never make a substantial profit they don't know how</Msg><Username>rocketman2001ab</Username><Timestamp>1379761336025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 07:02:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379763916426-2</Id><Topic><Title>If You Covered Today</Title><Username>geegenbottle</Username><Timestamp>1379718514729</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-20 19:08:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then you will be MUCH better off then having your broker do it for you under forced margin call over the next 3-5 weeks. In all fainess the brave shorts that are attempting to rationize irrational pricez of pig stox are not abject idiots - they simply didnt experience 1st hand the 1998 - 2000 run up into the dotbust . They will soon find out 1st hand and right where they live the power of the parabolic wipe out move that iz about to take place. Just to put it into perspective - pcln, a surviving reminate of the insane cycle of 14 yrz ago that can be readily looked up, went from an ALL READY INSANE 440 to 994 in a 3 week period (plenty of time for a forced margin call). It did this without the 5 trillion dollarz of fed dollarz that have been pumped into the markets under talf, tarp, qe1, qe2, operation twist, qe3, and now qe infinity at 85 bil / month, and 0% Fed interest rates "for an extended period of time".... And it did so under robot technology that waz LIGHT YEARZ behind the real time capabilitiez of todayz algo bots. Theze brave souls will soon find the hard way the age old adage that irrational markets canw far out last a rational traderz solvancy... This holdz true now more than ever.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379763916426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 07:45:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379765449377-3</Id><Topic><Title>If You Covered Today</Title><Username>geegenbottle</Username><Timestamp>1379718514729</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-20 19:08:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe. But, it will be interesting trying to do that while underwriting yet another offering to raise funds within 12 months. See my other post on YOY trends in net working capital. That's the problem with Amazon becoming a loss leading proprietary hardware maker...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1379765449377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 08:10:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379767525810-4</Id><Topic><Title>If You Covered Today</Title><Username>geegenbottle</Username><Timestamp>1379718514729</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-20 19:08:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I should be clear. Go to the capital markets twice in a 12 month period. Except this time, it won't be able to get away with omissions on cash position and trends. And the nonexistent 'Chinese firewall" between the analysts and IBanking ops won't matter. Companies that are truly doing well don't need to access capital twice in 12 months 20 years after their founding. The Enron of this decade, not from company fraud, but abuses/manipulation in the financial sector.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1379767525810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 08:45:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379767889853-5</Id><Title>Sybs revised 3 month prediction</Title><Msg>Revision rest on current qe events and chart technicalz: S&amp;P 1750-1800 A 25-35% rize in Momo Pig stox: Amzn: 380-425 Nflx: 375 - 415 Pcln 1150-1300 Lvs: 75-110 Cmg: 480-550 Tsla: 300-330 Good luck. The jam packed bandwaggon of market shorts iz hopping along a trail that leadz to their destruction. Dont buy optionz az a hedge or a trade because if you are not wiped out on the way up, then your contracts will not be honored in the market crash lockups on the way down. There iz not enough underlying stock to honor crackhead derivative bucket shop bets. Contracts will be canceled in the crash az what little faith that remainz in the markets gets flushed down the toilet in a swirling bowl of worthless 'paper' contracts</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379767889853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 08:51:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379768458118-6</Id><Topic><Title>If You Covered Today</Title><Username>geegenbottle</Username><Timestamp>1379718514729</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-20 19:08:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tech, you are wrong in your assptionz that : "they wont be able to raise capital (get away with it)". If they need capital then they will get it - bernanke just got done telling you that. You are leading people to their deaths on your 'rationalization' of poor fundementalz, quite convincingly sybs might add. You sound convincing but you are studying and pontificating the wrong topics.... You need to look strictly st market mechanics, and the fact that the fed hasnt even BEGUN to back Off and cool thingz down...... You are wrong here. Sybil waz wrong until july, and haz NO PROBLEM sitting out on the maddness thats about to ensue, and warning people about it. You didnt trade 98-2000, did you? Be honest.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379768458118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 09:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379769676283-7</Id><Topic><Title>If You Covered Today</Title><Username>geegenbottle</Username><Timestamp>1379718514729</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-20 19:08:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sadly no. My office mate from McKinsey and I had a bet what would happen to MSFT and CSCO when it broke. I said all would get whacked huge (the market was valuing everyone as a "real option" while not recognizing the interdepency, just as Amazon cannot justify its valuation without WalMart and Costco ceasing to exist today). He thought the outflow from pure .scam bubbles into them ("flight to quality") would hold them. We were going to buy options to express the bet in a levered way, but never got around to it. Would have made a few million...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1379769676283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 09:21:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379770278695-8</Id><Topic><Title>If You Covered Today</Title><Username>geegenbottle</Username><Timestamp>1379718514729</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-20 19:08:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil didnt ask you if you traded the 2000 to 2003 market. Sybil asked you if you traded the 1998-2000 market. You gave sybs the answer that sybs suspected. Sybs traded both, and learned some very valuable lessonz..... You will have to learn hardway what those that had to learn the 2000 runnup and subsequent fall the hardway. There were very few reatailorz that made out well.,. those few on the receiving end of wealth transferz of ipo's and stok cashinz made out well... This will prove even worse for retailorz on the way up and the way down.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379770278695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 09:31:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379772124938-9</Id><Title>Sybil haz never seen pig markets and bubbly stox rise to infinity</Title><Msg>However, on several brutal occasionz, sybil haz seen them rize very quickly into to stubborn short trader insolvancy . Infinity iz theoretical, insolvance due to levereaged margin call upon levered margin call upon levered margin call iz very very real - thereby negating the need for thinking of infinity az real while on the on the bandwaggon short side. Conversly, sybil haz never seen the markets go to 0, but haz seen margin longz get wiped out entirely, az many many bitcoin stox went to zero. This iz how wealth iz transfered from the many to the few at inflection pounts of 'infinity' and 'zero'. Sybil haz yearz and yearz of direct experience with both ..... While many traderz will learn new lessonz of old wayz that repeat themselvez over and over, each lesson more harsh and amplified then the last. All you short fvckerz are about to learn a very harsh lesson in a dramatic fashion that being short in a parabola iz to be approached with EXTREME caution. And buying derivativez of any sort or etfs that use them (all etfs - the more levered the etf the worse) should be avoided like the plague.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379772124938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 10:02:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379773630546-10</Id><Topic><Title>If You Covered Today</Title><Username>geegenbottle</Username><Timestamp>1379718514729</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-20 19:08:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ur an idiot Sybil: I traded during the times of 1998-2000: what you fail to show is that stuff like NFLX has went from 50 to over 300 already the last year when QE went into overdrive last August: it was last that you should have been putting up these warnings. Insteady, you stupidly levered up to the hilt your fake postions, which if real, would have bankrupted most people. Plain and simple. And you warned with zillion of messages in late July saying the same damn thing.....then came back wtih those fakes tickets stating: that while you werre warning people to cover, that you were shorting. So shut up and stop your BS. Why these boards feel they should listen to anyone giving advice is beyond me: exspecially a slime like you. Indeed, anything can happen here, but you are about a year late, and $10 million in the holde to your fake leveraged up shorts the last year, in saying it: idiot.</Msg><Username>buy_bubblestocks</Username><Timestamp>1379773630546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 10:27:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379773762283-11</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil haz never seen pig markets and bubbly stox rise to infinity</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379772124938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 10:02:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the message is clear: don't trade up in leverage of kinky favored stocks where you can go broke: in other words: dont follow the path of Trading for Dummies: like you showed in the last year. idiot.</Msg><Username>buy_bubblestocks</Username><Timestamp>1379773762283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 10:29:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379774853891-12</Id><Title>Buy bubblestox iz quick to hammer sybs call, which iz quite easy to make...</Title><Msg>Pig stox are going SIGNIFICANTLY higher then current levelz in that the markets have only just BEGUN to price in 510-765 BILLION dollarz of fed infusion that it DID NOT anticipate happening in july.... This unexpected infusion haz ONLY JUST BEGUN to move the pigz into another, steeper leg in the parabola.... If he iz short 30 cents or less for every dollar he haz in equity and haz no money in optionz , like sybil currently iz , then he might be just fine unless he panics out with the herd that will be shooting each other az they jump off the bandwaggon of shorts.... But alas, judging from hiz incessant posting and tone of dejection - sybil veiwz this clown az not only lying to the board, but lying to himself .... Sybil suspects that hiz short bets are MUCH larger than sybil would recommend here.....sybil could be wrong, but call it an 'educated' guess steeped in a wealth of experience.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379774853891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 10:47:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379775314865-13</Id><Title>Shorts - if you want to live another day to fight then you must consider the following:</Title><Msg>If you must be short pig stox then you should be NO MORE than 30 cents of every dollar you have to lose in the markets - dollarz that you absolutely do not need antime soon or ever. You should have 0 derivativez - optionz of any kinfd, etfs that use them etc etc.... If you stick with this - you will survive.... If you scoff at it then you will be murdered by robots, and they will steup your money off of tour dead corpse.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379775314865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 10:55:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379775565726-14</Id><Title>Buy bubblestox, are you aware that in order to short trade you must have a margin account?</Title><Msg>Why do you think that iz? Answer in detail please. Why must you account be marginable to trade ahort?</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379775565726</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 10:59:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379775952142-15</Id><Topic><Title>Buy bubblestox, are you aware that in order to short trade you must have a margin account?</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379775565726</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 10:59:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because your losses can be unlimited but there not unlimted b/c you define the "size" of your short trade, so your losses are not unlimted: I know all a about the 1998-March 2000 Nasdaq move to 5132. Stopp screwing with people's minds here spreading fear: you were the idiot who took massive losses: if the trades were real the last year: those losses were much bigger than $380,000...and one the biggest reasons is you didn't define your sell stop, you guessed. You have zero good interntions on thses boards and you messages, on than telling you that you are a slime, Fraud, means pretty much zero on what I'll do ahead. I don't your advice about anything regarding trading. In fact, sounds to me you need a refresher or dealing with risk you didn't understand.</Msg><Username>buy_bubblestocks</Username><Timestamp>1379775952142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 11:05:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379776204315-16</Id><Title>and by the way, Sybil, tell the board you DIDN"T come back to say you shorted AMZN, while warning to cover a zillion times in July</Title><Msg>the messages are there to see along wtth your fake tickets you fraud. Holy moly, you REEK OF FRAUD. Even if you are ever right, no one should listen to you. And the fact that you say it over and over, tells me that there's intentions involved, as if it makes a difference to give advice on a yahoo message board. lol! you're more of a loser than geegenjar.</Msg><Username>buy_bubblestocks</Username><Timestamp>1379776204315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 11:10:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379776324307-17</Id><Topic><Title>and by the way, Sybil, tell the board you DIDN"T come back to say you shorted AMZN, while warning to cover a zillion times in July</Title><Username>buy_bubblestocks</Username><Timestamp>1379776204315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 11:10:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and I can only imagine who the person is, and lifestyle that person lead, behind that SYBIL_LIVES moniker of yours. Not even close to what you try to convey. lol!</Msg><Username>buy_bubblestocks</Username><Timestamp>1379776324307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 11:12:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379783988899-18</Id><Topic><Title>Buy bubblestox, are you aware that in order to short trade you must have a margin account?</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379775565726</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 10:59:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Stopp screwing with people's minds here spreading fear" Sybil haz taken a 15% hit and stinted the hemorraging to a trickle by scaling back all bets to a manageble level , and will take more hits az the pigz SPIKE the fvck up. Those that think sybby's assesment iz 'fear mongering' are in over their headz, those that read and understand sybby's assement and why in a calm cool and collected manner are not and have nothing to fear. Which are you? Hmmmmmmmmmmn..............</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379783988899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 13:19:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379784382169-19</Id><Title>OVER 700 BILLION DOLLARZ OF ADDITIONAL STIMULOUS THAT THE MARKETS WERE NOT ANTICIPATING UNTIL A WEEK AGO</Title><Msg>Do not bet against bernanke, he iz determined to murder you if you do and he will succeed in doing so with ease.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379784382169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 13:26:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379785366451-20</Id><Topic><Title>OVER 700 BILLION DOLLARZ OF ADDITIONAL STIMULOUS THAT THE MARKETS WERE NOT ANTICIPATING UNTIL A WEEK AGO</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379784382169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 13:26:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>buy high, sell low; short low, cover high, classical mistake.</Msg><Username>yakimariver</Username><Timestamp>1379785366451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 13:42:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379787239728-21</Id><Title>Shorts: even the most optimistic projectionz had bernanke curtailing stimulous. IT NOT YOUR FAULT - YOU DID NOTHING WRONG</Title><Msg>Now that we have that cleared up - 700 BILLION DOLLARZ of unanticipated stimulous iz about to be priced into the markets VERY quickly. If you chose not to cover and you go broke then you will have no one but yourselvez to blame.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379787239728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 14:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379789419797-22</Id><Title>This iz where the mack truck tire rubber meets the road and where the shorts are jammed solidly in between the two</Title><Msg>Any bandwaggon short that doesnt recognize this predicament iz already road pizza, they just dont realize it yet. OVER the next 5 weeks, theze markets are going to LAUNCH INTO HYPERDRIVE and smash the shorts that dont truelly understand this with a resounding THUD. Blood, bone, and guts will be strewened across the brand new highway az the trick speedz over the shorts on a road of death that will soon be known to be Bernanke Memorial Highway. Bernanke haz a full scale fleet of over weight haull trucks that are going to squish all in their way az he runz high speed and without brakes</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379789419797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 14:50:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379789836928-23</Id><Title>Let's try to focus on some content...</Title><Msg>What is Amazon's cash depletion rate? What has the typical drop been between EOQ2 AND EOQ3? What is the starting point in 2013 compared to prior years, despite the net $1.5B infusion? Answer: Amazon typically sees its NWC drop by about $300M in Q3 (of course, growth is slowing which will not help).</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1379789836928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 14:57:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379790217249-24</Id><Title>Tech, focus all you want on fundiez.... Your results will be the same az those in 1999</Title><Msg>Its that simple. Your taking people down a road of death with discussion that iz irrelevant for the next 3 months if not longer. You should know and understand that by now. Sybil iz only here to "help", but there iz only so much sybil can do in a limited space of time.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379790217249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 15:03:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379791118436-25</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, focus all you want on fundiez.... Your results will be the same az those in 1999</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379790217249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 15:03:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No Sybs. I want to document the real situation so that the gross negligence of those doing the next financing is clear. I also want anyone that might actually still be invested in this stock to understand how fast it will collapse.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1379791118436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 15:18:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379792277648-26</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, focus all you want on fundiez.... Your results will be the same az those in 1999</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379790217249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 15:03:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So youre eager to document the shorts getting wiped out after being lead out into the highway by the pied piperz , and THEN document the passive longz getting wiped out in every 401k and pension fund known to man. That sybilz short friend iz EXACTLY what iz about to play out. There are no active retail longz of the pigz other than those looking for a quick hit, which they WILL score on - sybs not one of them, but sybs not an INSANE SHORT standing in the road either.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379792277648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 15:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379793194126-27</Id><Topic><Title>Shop By Local: Find national brands, locally, with the worlds most relevant local search engine, Krillion</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1376825608369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 07:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Local Corp’s Message to Brand Manufacturers: Capture more customers and increase retail channel sales with a dynamic local shopping where-to-buy solution Help shoppers find your products at stores nearby Provide online shoppers with a seamless web-to-store experience on their desktop or mobile device that makes it easy to buy your products online and offline. Partner with the pioneer in local shopping: We built the first inventory-aware where-to-buy shopping solution, and partner with numerous major brands to drive both online and local retail channel sales. We help you turn more of your online visitors into in-store customers by providing a seamless, dynamic experience that drives more sales to your authorized dealers. Maximize Engagement While Minimizing Costs: Save money and time by implementing a fully integrated where-to-buy solution. Drive Qualified Shoppers to Your Retailer Partners: Turn online consumers into in-store buyers with real-time StockCheck™ technology. Connect Ready Buyers with Authorized Dealers: Facilitate the buying process by showing consumers a unified view of all their buying options, including which stores have your products in stock.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1379793194126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 15:53:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379795430925-28</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, focus all you want on fundiez.... Your results will be the same az those in 1999</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379790217249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 15:03:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" I also want anyone that might actually still be invested in this stock to understand how fast it will collapse." How is somebody who has been so incredibly wrong in both time and price still acting like they have a better handle on the future than any other random individual?</Msg><Username>aapljack</Username><Timestamp>1379795430925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 16:30:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379797383251-29</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, focus all you want on fundiez.... Your results will be the same az those in 1999</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379790217249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 15:03:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a handle on reality and fundamentals. They haven't mattered for well over a year here, but they will. The fact that the trading games have gone into hyperdrive doesn't make it sustainable. Bernie ran his ponzi for decades. It was a scam the entire time, not just when it formally imploded, aapljackass.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1379797383251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 17:03:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379814847581-30</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, focus all you want on fundiez.... Your results will be the same az those in 1999</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379790217249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 15:03:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How is somebody who has been so incredibly wrong in both time and price still acting like they have a better handle on the future than any other random individual?" Couldn't have said it any better!!! Bullseye!! But let me tryo to answer!! Why? Because the idiot, who's a horrible trader, is a jackass, a mule's butt , i f you will. The biggest piece of pomposity that I've ever seen on almost anywhere! lol!! I've schooled this guy in where AMZn was going from the start last July, and yet he's still filled with bloviating, do good, advice, and has not a clue about Wallstreet's will to make money. You know what would be a better question which will NEVER EVER get an answer? Ask this Techstrategy guy how much he's lost since he came over from a CMG trading strike full of vigor with a bunch of other clowns, in buying puts that expired worthless in AMZN to this point? Will he give you an answer? NOT A CHANCE!! Yet, now he feels he's in postion to do good about telling the board about an imminent collapse in AMZN stock that was supposed to happen long ago. My guess? This guy got absolutley pounded up his bungulator buying puts on AMZN the last year,but because of his utter pomposity, he'll never share with the board how much he lost. Isn't that right TECHSTRATEGY?? I"m calling you out at you are almost as bad as schitzo, SYBIL, who's now found religion , which is hilarious. This board is hilarious with short idiots!! lol!!</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1379814847581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 21:54:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379815252828-31</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, focus all you want on fundiez.... Your results will be the same az those in 1999</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379790217249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 15:03:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you have a handle on your wallet as it's opened to the ground raining out dollar to the sidewalk for the last freaking year!!! You pomposity cost you bigtime!! deal with it!! That's your first step to character correction: you;re not as smart as you think you are!! and your wallet shows it.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1379815252828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 22:00:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379815365796-32</Id><Title>by the way, Sybil you're a MORON!!!</Title><Msg>you got fleeced and greased and you should be bowing and kneeling before me!! Call me ZOD!! #$%$!! lol!</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1379815365796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 22:02:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379815565814-33</Id><Title>Shorties!! REMEMBER as I've said many a time here: BOW AND KNEEL BEFORE ZOD!!!</Title><Msg>And i am zod!! remember that!!! it was all there before you and i warned you!! Even a year ago, for some of you, most 5 years back! Lol!</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1379815565814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 22:06:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379816840990-34</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, focus all you want on fundiez.... Your results will be the same az those in 1999</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379790217249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 15:03:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They haven't mattered for well over a year here, but they will. The fact that the trading games have gone into hyperdrive doesn't make it sustainable." Nothing is sustainable. One day the sun will burn itself out and all human life will cease. That's not insightful, and saying it over and over doesn't make one smarter than anybody else. Predict demise every day and eventually you'll be right. But it won't bring your wheelbarrow of expired long dated puts back to life. And it's certainly not grounds to pontificate.</Msg><Username>aapljack</Username><Timestamp>1379816840990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 22:27:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379816900258-35</Id><Title>What up with you Sybil? lol!! did you go to rehab? lol!! every post warning bears like you were!!! lol!</Title><Msg>coming here and seeing seeing warn shorts of being crushed has got to be one of the funniest things I've ever seen on these boards!! This guy was the biggest RECKLESS DRUNK WITH SHORTS! ever !! lol!! now he went to the monestary line Jim Carry in Ace Ventura!!! lmfao!! BWHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!@!!!!</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1379816900258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 22:28:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379817283473-36</Id><Title>And before you take anything from Techstrategy's repeated, pompous, bloviating, you might want to look back about a year</Title><Msg>when I warned this guy rover and over, that ongoing QE is what mattered most in the stock market, which he dismissed like a pompous blowhard that he is, but was, and continues to be dead wrong!! This guy suffers from "I'm smarter than the market" syndrome!!!!! BWHAHAHAHAHAHAH!!! you can't make up how funny these guys, techstrategy and Sybil ,are. Two idiots with one thing in common, they got absolutely crushed shorting AMZN. period.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1379817283473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 22:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379822280265-37</Id><Topic><Title>Tech, focus all you want on fundiez.... Your results will be the same az those in 1999</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1379790217249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 15:03:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AapljackASS, your inept analogy shows your limited intellect. Comparing geological times scales to the 15 months I've been short post CMG gains (and wrong due to cap'ns'crews Crazy Ivan) is just plain dumb. And, unlike all you pumper tools on this board, I don't simply make statements, I provide facts and analysis as I did earlier today on YOY net working capital changes and position heading into the holiday build. It's not just that Amazon will falter but WHY Amazon will falter... Bernie Madoff's investors thought they were doing great through a multidecade ponzi. Real and apparent value can be and often are very different. This is an unsustainable scam that has will be exposed, not in decades and not in years, but in months. Whether that ends up being 3, 6, 9 pr 12 months more, it will happen. And, it won't be a "stopped clock" because I don't simply say it is overvalued, I explain the funamental economic flaws in the business model (the economic tradeoff embedded in the business model and moved against Amazon and will continue to do so). NASDARQ, it isn't just Benny B. It is absolutely structural issues with HFT quants. If and when reform comes (mandatory 1 second order hold period, ORDER tax or whatever it may be) the MOMO scams will fall from the sky. Call it pompous. Call it whatever you want. I am correct about the underlying economics and this scam will crater.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1379822280265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-09-21 23:58:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>