<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-27"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359266955516-1</Id><Title>AMZN WILL FALL BACK $210 AFTER EARNINGG LIKE AAPLE DID.</Title><Msg>We are looking for huge profit not a slaes or revenue. If not AMZN will get hit and hammer</Msg><Username>shortfund_2000</Username><Timestamp>1359266955516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 01:09:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359270003982-2</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN WILL FALL BACK $210 AFTER EARNINGG LIKE AAPLE DID.</Title><Username>shortfund_2000</Username><Timestamp>1359266955516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 01:09:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, AMZN is a momentum ponzi stock. If you claim to know what Amazon will do after earnings, I'd say you were a liar or delusional.</Msg><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1359270003982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 02:00:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359282093302-3</Id><Title>amzn way overvalued and will drop like a tank</Title><Msg>They are a horrible company to third party sellers trying to force them to store their goods in their empty logistic centers and bill them for storage. That a brilliant idea valuing amzn at PE of 3000. Bezos is to be sent in jail and amzn will sink like you have never seen it before. Fair value $100 a share</Msg><Username>bogdanmiltchev</Username><Timestamp>1359282093302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 05:21:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359283737978-4</Id><Topic><Title>Bezos sold $100 Million of Stock right after Christmas Season Started</Title><Username>davecarneyinc</Username><Timestamp>1359191214599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 04:06:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It was $200MM. And he sold $2B over the past two years. Actually, the Cyber week was very strong and that is about when he sold. The issue isn't revenue. It is the underlying profit potential...." Tech, nice job watching the wealth transfer from the many to the few az rich dude bezos cashez hiz locked up private equity before the amzn ipo and/or hiz free optionz and stock grants so that amzn may "keep and retain its quality leadership".... Like you, Sybs corrected the idiot that originated this post a week ago, but here it still sits, az wrong now az it waz last week.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359283737978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 05:48:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359291877549-5</Id><Topic><Title>How are all the short cretins doing???</Title><Username>skiidady</Username><Timestamp>1359261824158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 23:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll tell you all about it at year end...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1359291877549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 08:04:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359293813034-6</Id><Topic><Title>short interest is only 2%</Title><Username>it_all_goood</Username><Timestamp>1359145647992</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 15:27:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spot on, my thoughts too</Msg><Username>jdelgado7723</Username><Timestamp>1359293813034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 08:36:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359295511864-7</Id><Topic><Title>Why talk to women</Title><Username>amiewiedersqmq7754</Username><Timestamp>1303492696000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2011-04-22 13:18:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job guys</Msg><Username>kevin_mortin</Username><Timestamp>1359295511864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 09:05:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359297310013-8</Id><Title>put options are getting expensive</Title><Msg>the feb 260 put is $410 a contract versus the 310 call at $325 per contract ( both options are out of the money by about $25...if you go way out of th emoney the disparity widens...$70 out of the money, the put premium is 5 times higher than the call premium... the bid on the Feb 355 call is $5 per contract while the bid on the Feb $215 put is $35 per contract.</Msg><Username>bluebloodedtrader</Username><Timestamp>1359297310013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 09:35:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359299265762-9</Id><Topic><Title>Stocks to watch Tuesday: N.Y. Times, Amazon</Title><Username>pearliehazellwmlk7157</Username><Timestamp>1309626898000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2011-07-02 13:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting</Msg><Username>kevin_mortin</Username><Timestamp>1359299265762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:07:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359299755789-10</Id><Title>Sorry guys had to short Friday @ 284 x 1000 shares.</Title><Msg>There always is a sell off whether they meet or not so i'll cover either way lower tomorrow. If they miss I won't. This should see mid 260's even with a beat for a moment where i'll cover. Easy money here</Msg><Username>philthyesthoodlum</Username><Timestamp>1359299755789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:15:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359300392762-11</Id><Topic><Title>Sorry guys had to short Friday @ 284 x 1000 shares.</Title><Username>philthyesthoodlum</Username><Timestamp>1359299755789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:15:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BS handsome!!! :)))) yer just a junior boy with a big mouth in actuality... ALWAYS remember that on the Net anyone can YAP!!! yer either a BRILLIANT chap or an outright #$%$ who belongs in a loony asylum! :)) hahahahahahahahahah</Msg><Username>davdddd</Username><Timestamp>1359300392762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:26:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359300813343-12</Id><Topic><Title>Sorry guys had to short Friday @ 284 x 1000 shares.</Title><Username>philthyesthoodlum</Username><Timestamp>1359299755789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:15:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got big cash to back up my mouth Trollboy. I'll be laughing all the way to the bank idiot.</Msg><Username>philthyesthoodlum</Username><Timestamp>1359300813343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:33:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359301119654-13</Id><Topic><Title>put options are getting expensive</Title><Username>bluebloodedtrader</Username><Timestamp>1359297310013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 09:35:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what does it mean ?</Msg><Username>orliskas</Username><Timestamp>1359301119654</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:38:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359301589887-14</Id><Topic><Title>put options are getting expensive</Title><Username>bluebloodedtrader</Username><Timestamp>1359297310013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 09:35:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i guess it means that option speculators believe that if bad news is released the shares would drop significantly more than they would go up, if good news was reported.</Msg><Username>bluebloodedtrader</Username><Timestamp>1359301589887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:46:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359301960776-15</Id><Topic><Title>put options are getting expensive</Title><Username>bluebloodedtrader</Username><Timestamp>1359297310013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 09:35:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$250 put is $34 away while $310 call is $26 away, so just based on dollar basis the put is $2 closer. However an equal difference form stock price always makes the puts a larger percent differential than the call, therefore puts will carry a bit more premium. As you get closer to earnings you might see the value of the same strike actually rise. Option sellers make money no matter what, except if your options call was correct by the differential and premium and direction. For example if you buy the $300 calls exp this week for $6, you will only make money if the stock goes to $306 plus by the time options expire. If stock goes down, stays unchanged or even goes up but not over $306, you lose money. So as you can see, you can be right that Amazon will rise and if Amazon only rises $15 which is significant by itself, you still lose money. This is why playing options before earnings is very risky, even if you call the direction correct. Almost all premium will be sucked out of options the day after earnings. AMZN seems to be carrying a 7-8% implied volatility which is very high.</Msg><Username>balastona</Username><Timestamp>1359301960776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:52:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359301986303-16</Id><Topic><Title>put options are getting expensive</Title><Username>bluebloodedtrader</Username><Timestamp>1359297310013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 09:35:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe it means they are gonna pull the rug on put buyers like they do most time in buying AMZN puts. Afterall, it's the put sellers who have made huge gobs of money selling put options as the prices rise in them and the demand is high: when do put buyers in AMZN ever make any money? maybe when the demand for them was low and prices low. So there's less for the sellers lever on. Just a thought.</Msg><Username>ayahtolla2003</Username><Timestamp>1359301986303</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:53:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359303005868-17</Id><Topic><Title>I think Amazon is gonna post blow out earnings</Title><Username>imshortemc</Username><Timestamp>1359238354282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 17:12:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Based on the stock price movement the last couple of weeks, I suspect they'll have blow out earnings as well. Insiders know what the earnings will be, why else would the stock move so much just before earnings?</Msg><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1359303005868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 11:10:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359304935612-18</Id><Title>Don't be a ding #$%$</Title><Msg>People often forget that Netflix went from $300 to $52 in ONE YEAR.</Msg><Username>valueftw88</Username><Timestamp>1359304935612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 11:42:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359305079937-19</Id><Topic><Title>DISGUSTING</Title><Username>valueftw88</Username><Timestamp>1359165165914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 20:52:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What will happen if AMZN misses again? I suspect longs will be grabbing their ankles this time.</Msg><Username>valueftw88</Username><Timestamp>1359305079937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 11:44:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359305588818-20</Id><Topic><Title>I think Amazon is gonna post blow out earnings</Title><Username>imshortemc</Username><Timestamp>1359238354282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 17:12:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't get distracted by the trading surrounding the Apple unwind. AWS price cuts, Kindle, sales tax, vigorous pricing competition, etc., etc. equates to a soft quarter with an EPS loss and quite possibly a revenue miss. There is no debate to be had. The sell off will be material and there will be no recovery bounce like past quarters.</Msg><Username>powerchump</Username><Timestamp>1359305588818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 11:53:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359305878257-21</Id><Topic><Title>DISGUSTING</Title><Username>valueftw88</Username><Timestamp>1359165165914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 20:52:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This stock seems very gamed. Just look at the last quarter. The sell-off after hours and then an immediate rebound. AAPL money being rotated to this stock in a big way. I am very interested to see the action the next 2 days going into earnings. Earnings themselves won't matter only top line growth and let me take the first part back, the way it goes with this stock bottom line results will only matter if they are strong and then of course they will give a wide range of guidance and the analysts won't hold their feet to the fire. As someone who favors fundamentals much more so than technicals I never understood why this stock gets such a rich valuation but the fact is those that have bet long here (not me!) have done very well. At some point they won't but when that will be is the million dollar question.</Msg><Username>hapihammer</Username><Timestamp>1359305878257</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 11:57:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359308754264-22</Id><Topic><Title>Don't be a ding #$%$</Title><Username>valueftw88</Username><Timestamp>1359304935612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 11:42:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd like to remind everyone acting as a fiduciary to clients, family, or otherwise: it is immoral to chase bubble stocks. Go pay off some debt while you can. This earnings report is a dangerous situation. Long or short, you should be scared.</Msg><Username>powerchump</Username><Timestamp>1359308754264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 12:45:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359309610060-23</Id><Topic><Title>DISGUSTING</Title><Username>valueftw88</Username><Timestamp>1359165165914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 20:52:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the event of a loss of a couple hundred million and/or a revenue miss, then look out below. I think the mile markers are $240, $225, $205, $185, and $165. If the move is swift and vicious like Apple with forced liquidation, then maybe even lower. It might take a few more quarters for an indictment of the business. There's a problem with all out pursuit of growth: what happens if you make a mistake or the economy/competition forces one on you? There's no savings to pivot and the knife has to come out.</Msg><Username>powerchump</Username><Timestamp>1359309610060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 13:00:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359309976740-24</Id><Topic><Title>I think Amazon is gonna post blow out earnings</Title><Username>imshortemc</Username><Timestamp>1359238354282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 17:12:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>even motley fool says they will post blow out earnings...300 is a short trip away...go amzn</Msg><Username>blastoff1212</Username><Timestamp>1359309976740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 13:06:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359310255885-25</Id><Topic><Title>EPS of 8 pennies. p/e of 3,900. A POS but the thieves luv it!</Title><Username>rb15301</Username><Timestamp>1359146926826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 15:48:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You hit another topic that gets my nerve. The fact of high tech compensating people with options. Then they conveniently exclude stock based compensation from their earnings and call them adjusted earnings. GAAP is GAAP baby. When companies overly rely on this compensation you really need to figure it back and look at earnings with those adjustments back in. Not only that but stockholders get screwed with all the dilution. Even when companies have these grandiose buybacks they don't even buy enough back to offset the stock dilution. I can name only couple companies out of all the companies out there that actually buy back enough to reduce float vs stock option issuance. And then buybacks are normally done when the shares are grossly overpriced. On the free cash flow topic they can continue generating cash off of the a/p balance as long as sales grow and they drag out payments to vendors. It is a one time thing in the sense it makes a contribution the day that program starts. Then it gets to where there is no add back to operating cash flow when sales stagnate. Then it reverses and causes negative effects when the program that created the big a/p ends. When we ended our relationship with our vendor we had a relationship with that caused the big working capital adjustment it reversed big in that qtr that the program ended. With AMZN it won't really reverse unless they were to close their doors. They will always exploit that cashflow from vendors. It eventually gets to looking at current assets vs current liabilities excluding short term maturity of debt. Need to be at 1+. AMZN just has enough cash plus receivables plus inventory to cover a/p. If they were doing well the current ratio should be well above 1. The fact it is where it is at shows how this scheme has helped them. They could have a much lower ap balance but also a much lower cash balance. Conclusion is we both agree this is a scam. Bezos has always schemed to exploit any advantage he can get.</Msg><Username>pricewowens</Username><Timestamp>1359310255885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 13:10:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359312405208-26</Id><Topic><Title>DISGUSTING</Title><Username>valueftw88</Username><Timestamp>1359165165914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 20:52:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...those that have bet long here (not me!) have done very well. At some point they won't but when that will be is the million dollar question..." All you have to do is buy the dips, sell the rips. It's really easy, even a dumb hillbilly can do it. I'm waiting for earnings to sell, if it spikes I'll sell some, if it dives I'll watch it and buy when it looks like its at a bottom. Now is the time to sell, if you haven't already. It's not the time to buy. The time to buy is when it dips 20%, which would be $230. AMZN always hits new all-time highs, so if you buy at $230, you can be assured it will go up to $285 again.</Msg><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1359312405208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 13:46:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359313384925-27</Id><Topic><Title>EPS of 8 pennies. p/e of 3,900. A POS but the thieves luv it!</Title><Username>rb15301</Username><Timestamp>1359146926826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 15:48:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You shorts are the smart ones. Too bad the market is so stupid causing you to lose money. You don't deserve it.</Msg><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1359313384925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 14:03:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359314728537-28</Id><Topic><Title>$350-$400 before it implodes by 50-75%</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1359233848401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 15:57:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They want to kill shorts.</Msg><Username>shares245</Username><Timestamp>1359314728537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 14:25:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359315454109-29</Id><Topic><Title>ONLY SUCKERS WOULD BUY AMZN WITH A PE OF 84</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1306256564000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-05-24 13:02:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suspect AMZN may drop big time, when JB retires. He's a lot younger than me, so I don't worry about that. In the meantime, I hope it does drop. Even if it drops to $100 before I get a chance to sell any. If that happened, I'd buy lots more. AMZN always hits new all-time highs.</Msg><Username>brucetheharmonicaguy</Username><Timestamp>1359315454109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 14:37:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359315513368-30</Id><Topic><Title>EPS of 8 pennies. p/e of 3,900. A POS but the thieves luv it!</Title><Username>rb15301</Username><Timestamp>1359146926826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 15:48:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are smart but you are the "smartest"....I mean who would not want to ride a stock from 240 to 170 and back.....who does not like roller coaster. Don't tell me there are stupids out there who sold at 240 and got back in at 170 again.</Msg><Username>jagdeep_m2000</Username><Timestamp>1359315513368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 14:38:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359315515491-31</Id><Title>Im in a low margin business</Title><Msg>and when I undercut my competition in housing, its nice to sell product, but their is no money left to pay overhead. What I need is stock to finance my whims.</Msg><Username>imshortemc</Username><Timestamp>1359315515491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 14:38:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359315766645-32</Id><Topic><Title>EPS of 8 pennies. p/e of 3,900. A POS but the thieves luv it!</Title><Username>rb15301</Username><Timestamp>1359146926826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 15:48:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>anyone joining is you is playing the side with a real dummy dowto6000. Because that is what you are : a "real dummy" dowto6000. Which is why you have multi-ID's after losing so much.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1359315766645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 14:42:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359322802525-33</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon could surprise to the upside anytime now</Title><Username>eskay89</Username><Timestamp>1359254615141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:43:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Once the massive build out and business expansion is done, Amazon will suddenly surprise to the upside big time and all analysts will adjust their forecasts. But, by then, Amazon would be $500+ stock." The award for the most idiotic post of the week goez to this poster.... Amzn exceeding low balled "estimates" after the bezos "build out" at the top of the levered commercial realestate market will coincide with huge corporate welfare bond debt comming due in 2015 and the stock will be trading sub 80.... By the time amzn scorez any real earningz (if they can even do so), the stock will have tanked and bezos will have cashed out.... Bezos timed the bond issue with the release of massive locked up sharez and iz DUMPING hiz stake in drovez az he cashez in on the debt issue, the baggiez buying here, and 401 k and pension fundz loading this trash onto the general public... Gs and ms bond issuerz now pumperz to cash in their stock feez for underwritting trash bond debt in 2014-2015 will turn into BOND BULLIEZ and obscond the "build out" of corporate offices, warehouses, and commercial realestate for 20-40 cents on the dollar while the sharez drop from 80 to 20 on their way to BK... Share holderz will end up with 0.00 in 2015-2016 with a 3 cent class action lawsuit kicker, or if they are lucky and the financial markets az a whole arent locked up and if a white knight wants to associate themselves with what will be a very damaged brand, the white night will scooooooop up what remainz of scamazon and assume its debt for 3.00 / share or less and the sharez will be folded into a new ticker .... This stock iz a scam, and its buyerz soon to be baggiez along with knife catcherz and unsuspecting ownerz of it in their retirement mutual fundz will be mercilessly shredded.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359322802525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 16:40:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359322952673-34</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN will post lose and revenue less then 22B</Title><Username>magiv_hegyoni</Username><Timestamp>1359187247959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 03:00:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think they miss based on the tax issues for a few of their big states, but also Hurricane Sandy. No one mentions that.</Msg><Username>thewad71</Username><Timestamp>1359322952673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 16:42:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359323798249-35</Id><Topic><Title>amazon 3/8 of Google volume</Title><Username>lawrencemata823</Username><Timestamp>1359026497851</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 06:21:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>nathanshuler742</Username><Timestamp>1359323798249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 16:56:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359324269105-36</Id><Topic><Title>amazing week coming</Title><Username>anthonyferguson10</Username><Timestamp>1358855587033</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 06:53:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>nathanshuler742</Username><Timestamp>1359324269105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 17:04:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359327895522-37</Id><Title>I am predicting 295 by tuesday, 320+ by wednesday</Title><Msg>A big beat is in the card people the big money has been front running this puppy since november. Time to get on board the express train to $500 by next yr!</Msg><Username>goldbuggerin</Username><Timestamp>1359327895522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 18:04:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359329740362-38</Id><Title>Very Important Facts About Amazon and LivingSocial</Title><Msg>I have read several messages about how fast LivingSocial is growing and the potential it has for Amazon. I am amazed at the stupidity of retail longs. First, you need to understand that LivingSocial is not part of Amazon! LivingSocial is its own (non-public) company. Amazon has only a 29% investment in LivingSocial (minority stake). Secondly, LivingSocial has operating losses of $753 million in the first 9 months of 2012! If they continue to lose at the same rate for the final quarter of 2012, LivingSocial will have operating losses of over $1 billion for the entire year! That is an incredible amount of money to lose . I don't understand how anyone could possibly get excited over any company that loses that kind of money, all of which has been funded by venture capitalists and Amazon (be aware that since Amazon has only a minority stake they don't show these losses on their income statement).</Msg><Username>davecarneyinc</Username><Timestamp>1359329740362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 18:35:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359329810005-39</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon could surprise to the upside anytime now</Title><Username>eskay89</Username><Timestamp>1359254615141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:43:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and owns about 87 million shares you idiot. keep trying the scare tactics you idiot. Because "your blood and guts" distribution" blah blah blah has done nothing but see AMZN skyrocket against. What a fool.</Msg><Username>nasdaq_6000_baby</Username><Timestamp>1359329810005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 18:36:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359330284619-40</Id><Topic><Title>Im in a low margin business</Title><Username>imshortemc</Username><Timestamp>1359315515491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 14:38:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good luck got any tips for me</Msg><Username>xdon69</Username><Timestamp>1359330284619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 18:44:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359331012131-41</Id><Topic><Title>EPS of 8 pennies. p/e of 3,900. A POS but the thieves luv it!</Title><Username>rb15301</Username><Timestamp>1359146926826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 15:48:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry Bruce. Its NASDAQ that "claimed" that he rode AMZN from 240 to 170 and back.....NASDAQ600 has been awarded as the dumbest person of the year. NASDAQ600...but the board is not as idiot as you...we know you have no position..so go get in a line for food stamps.</Msg><Username>jagdeep_m2000</Username><Timestamp>1359331012131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 18:56:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359331809441-42</Id><Topic><Title>CONGRATS LONGS...SHORTS', YOU ARE STOOPID!!!</Title><Username>philandjoelle</Username><Timestamp>1359147700584</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 16:01:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're comparing a 15 year old company like AMZN to NFLX and GMCR??? How broke are you?</Msg><Username>philandjoelle</Username><Timestamp>1359331809441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:10:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359332359445-43</Id><Topic><Title>CONGRATS LONGS...SHORTS', YOU ARE STOOPID!!!</Title><Username>philandjoelle</Username><Timestamp>1359147700584</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 16:01:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If sybs got anything wrong with that statement then please enter the specifics of your share count and entry point for you could actually be long and stupid... Besides sybs wants to know how much coin that you'll be stripped of if you are indeed long.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359332359445</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:19:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359332561583-44</Id><Title>Philjoe pumped pcln 'a real 15 year old company' at 640 and up</Title><Msg>sybil was shorting it from 640-773 and bought them back at 520 ... Dont remember seeing philjoe on nflx az sybs was shorting from 220-300, which sybby bought back from 180 down to 120....</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359332561583</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:22:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359332830299-45</Id><Topic><Title>EPS of 8 pennies. p/e of 3,900. A POS but the thieves luv it!</Title><Username>rb15301</Username><Timestamp>1359146926826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 15:48:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil agreez and awardz a thumbs up for nasdaq_6000 winning the dumbest person of the year award, followed in a 3 way tie for close 2nd place by geegee, philjoe, and skiidady.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359332830299</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:27:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359332863138-46</Id><Topic><Title>CONGRATS LONGS...SHORTS', YOU ARE STOOPID!!!</Title><Username>philandjoelle</Username><Timestamp>1359147700584</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 16:01:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're being made fun of on the PCLN board...for old time sake! Better get started on those nice salty crackers ya monkey!</Msg><Username>philandjoelle</Username><Timestamp>1359332863138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:27:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359333340888-47</Id><Topic><Title>CONGRATS LONGS...SHORTS', YOU ARE STOOPID!!!</Title><Username>philandjoelle</Username><Timestamp>1359147700584</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 16:01:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>baaah. sheep.</Msg><Username>kqforever</Username><Timestamp>1359333340888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:35:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359333644319-48</Id><Topic><Title>EPS of 8 pennies. p/e of 3,900. A POS but the thieves luv it!</Title><Username>rb15301</Username><Timestamp>1359146926826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 15:48:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but Sir/Ms: CRUS is merely yet another semiconductor concern... like fleas on doodoo ya know... AMZN is practically the largest retailer in the world! surely it should deserve in the least a couple brownie points for having attained this milestone and its transactions run seamlessly more often than not! in my own experience at least... davdddd</Msg><Username>davdddd</Username><Timestamp>1359333644319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:40:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359333842368-49</Id><Topic><Title>CONGRATS LONGS...SHORTS', YOU ARE STOOPID!!!</Title><Username>philandjoelle</Username><Timestamp>1359147700584</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 16:01:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Philjoe, Sybil doesnt feel the need to skulk the pcln board after sybs hatchet already wacked that pig to the tune of a $300k gain.... Unlike you, who without a position stupidly chase sybil around the internet for continuous abuse. Judging you have not declared a position, sybil iz found to be correct az stated in the subjuct header... Too funny... Did you get your Sandy Relief fundz yet? At least you still have internet access through your phone.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359333842368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:44:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359334078676-50</Id><Topic><Title>EPS of 8 pennies. p/e of 3,900. A POS but the thieves luv it!</Title><Username>rb15301</Username><Timestamp>1359146926826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 15:48:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everything has a price at which it is fully valued (or in AMZN's case over-valued). You would pay 2 grand for a computer, but would you pay 2 Billion dollars? I guess not.</Msg><Username>stock_selector1</Username><Timestamp>1359334078676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:47:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359334083152-51</Id><Topic><Title>Philjoe pumped pcln 'a real 15 year old company' at 640 and up</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359332561583</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:22:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those salty crackers are making you dumber than usual Do you think anyone on these boards thinks that any of your trades are real? What kind of idiot shorts PCLN at $550, right before it explodes to $773, and then claims to have made money?</Msg><Username>philandjoelle</Username><Timestamp>1359334083152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:48:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359334183094-52</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon could surprise to the upside anytime now</Title><Username>eskay89</Username><Timestamp>1359254615141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:43:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they will be like WMT and target ....... operation cost will soar and AMZN will have to pay taxes</Msg><Username>emanuel_dabah</Username><Timestamp>1359334183094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:49:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359334301667-53</Id><Topic><Title>I am predicting 295 by tuesday, 320+ by wednesday</Title><Username>goldbuggerin</Username><Timestamp>1359327895522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 18:04:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think 200 is more likely to happen</Msg><Username>magiv_hegyoni</Username><Timestamp>1359334301667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:51:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359334608446-54</Id><Topic><Title>AMZN will post lose and revenue less then 22B</Title><Username>magiv_hegyoni</Username><Timestamp>1359187247959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 03:00:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point about Hurrican Sandy. The only argument against it would be the notion of catch-up transactions or goods replacement later in the quarter, whatever that may be. I was stuck in Lower Manhattan for Sandy week while there for a work trip, I can say first hand that there was almost no commerce taking place other than repairs and food. This really is a game of inches with AMZN with their tight, unforgiving margins, so this does matter.</Msg><Username>powerchump</Username><Timestamp>1359334608446</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:56:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359336812260-55</Id><Topic><Title>I am predicting 295 by tuesday, 320+ by wednesday</Title><Username>goldbuggerin</Username><Timestamp>1359327895522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 18:04:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What if both of you are wrong and the stock stays essentially flat. It will kill lots of fat option premium and the big holders of the stock won't lose anything on their underlying stock. Entirely possible IMO. I will not play earnings long or short for this reason.</Msg><Username>algaebb</Username><Timestamp>1359336812260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:33:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359338689475-56</Id><Topic><Title>Very Important Facts About Amazon and LivingSocial</Title><Username>davecarneyinc</Username><Timestamp>1359329740362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 18:35:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder if Amazon will take another writedown this quarter. This quarter could be so bad that they might as well kitchen sink it and take all the losses they can.</Msg><Username>powerchump</Username><Timestamp>1359338689475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 21:04:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359338920405-57</Id><Topic><Title>Philjoe pumped pcln 'a real 15 year old company' at 640 and up</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359332561583</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:22:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You got 1/2 right, philjoe. sybil shorted the high - you were there. But sybs opened a postion at 640, and shorted aaaaaaallllll the way up to the high steady eddy.... Avg short 730, avg cover 605 .... Sybs made a mint and iz now worried about 2012 taxez.... Sheit! Thars gonna be a big bill.</Msg><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359338920405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 21:08:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359339142565-58</Id><Title>the zoomed</Title><Msg>The zoom thing loses money on most on line sales. It's best selling product is a loss leader. It is in direct competition with SAP/IBM/ORCL/MSFT and a whole host of smaller players for the cloud. They keep dropping prices due to the competitors are getting better at the game. They spend on some new project announcement daily which never seems to get to the bottom line. Insiders have been selling with wicked speed. States are starting to tax. Profits have been falling for years. The more they sell the more they lose. Shipping costs are going up and we are entering the weak spring period. Spending on warehouses never ends and id they want to be big overseas they haven't even started to figure out how to get the goods there without adding ware houses to the moon. PE is currently 3000 plus. Stock is overly owned by institutions and has a very low short interest. SOUNDS GREAT TO ME</Msg><Username>penystoc</Username><Timestamp>1359339142565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 21:12:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359340734018-59</Id><Topic><Title>Probability and magnitude of Q4 loss</Title><Username>powerchump</Username><Timestamp>1359257553069</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 22:32:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am short but why is the stock going up an why is it so over own if u can do the math why cant everyone else ???????</Msg><Username>xdon69</Username><Timestamp>1359340734018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 21:38:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359341020893-60</Id><Topic><Title>Philjoe pumped pcln 'a real 15 year old company' at 640 and up</Title><Username>sybil_lives</Username><Timestamp>1359332561583</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:22:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blah...blah...blah... You have no coin monkey boy</Msg><Username>philandjoelle</Username><Timestamp>1359341020893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 21:43:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359341620919-61</Id><Topic><Title>Probability and magnitude of Q4 loss</Title><Username>powerchump</Username><Timestamp>1359257553069</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 22:32:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the rise is from two things: the fiscal cliff "resolution" rally and the Apple unwind. There must have been some massive long Apple : short Amazon, Netflix, S&amp;P 500, etc. trades on that had a forced unwind last week. Eventually the math will win, when is the question. Q4 earnings on Tuesday is a very good opportunity. I can't remember a quarter in recent years where Amazon faced as many headwinds as they do right now.</Msg><Username>powerchump</Username><Timestamp>1359341620919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 21:53:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359342242141-62</Id><Title>How high do we go before the selloff?</Title><Msg>Looks like it wants to break out to $325-$350 short-term.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1359342242141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 22:04:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359345550594-63</Id><Title>CRM announces 4:1 stock split, could AMZN be next?</Title><Msg>$100 post split?</Msg><Username>goldbuggerin</Username><Timestamp>1359345550594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 22:59:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359347338181-64</Id><Topic><Title>How high do we go before the selloff?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1359342242141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 22:04:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am going to take the $$$ and run here before earnings are announced. I always get burned trying to get greedy</Msg><Username>lrcourtney56</Username><Timestamp>1359347338181</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 23:28:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>