<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373179266826-1</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone make a case for Amazon trading above $150, or even $100?</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1366481868089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:17:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Analysts are not generating numbers on fundamentals but rather on price. So they take their price figure out a beta and multiply it and magically have a number for the stock. I like it when stocks start getting close to the number and they revise up or down. And then the stock changes direction. So few a times have I seen analysts report the price has been reached now is the time to change your position. It just does not happen often. Why? Because they don't want to be caught wrong. It seems if they are wrong alone they are not qualified, but in a herd then the outcome obviously could not be foreseen.</Msg><Username>rick_dzzz</Username><Timestamp>1373179266826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 02:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373192403585-2</Id><Title>MicroVision Kindle Fire PicoP Projector Prototype</Title><Msg>Search "spam mola" on YouTube to see the videos</Msg><Username>geoffreyporter</Username><Timestamp>1373192403585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 06:20:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373208077233-3</Id><Topic><Title>Great to see that moron from seeking alphalpa krieger short AMZN and LNKD, 2 of my longs for months that continue</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1372978239322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:50:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sybil is a fkin nutcase on a sugar buzz. that needs a good strong spankin by a man with investment insight as to what a stock is all about.</Msg><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1373208077233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 10:41:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373208596057-4</Id><Title>If sybil the 'analyst' set a price target "amzn = $450"</Title><Msg>Sybil would would reverse engineer the 'foward looking' stats to come up with "$450", using revenuez, clicks, unique userz, subs, and eyeballz. Then sybil would take a shieottpile of other peoplez money and with a robot trigger a price spike while selling arsloadz of puts and let weak handed shorts and crackhead put buyerz do the heavy lifting while floating a front end fee loaded corporate bond issue to keep the ponzi scheme alive. But sybs would have the robots programed to unload this worthless stock in a LARGE wave of high volume distribution between 10-15% of the "target range". At 10% of the target range sybs bots would be completely divested and be shorting the same stok through a separate robot entity, and buying cheap after market march 2014 puts from retailorz in september that retailerz bought az high priced LEAPS. How hard would that be? If it turned out that the stok waz 450 in march 2014, and sybils bots lost, then o well - its other peoplez money any way - better luck next time.... But rest assured that sybby's bots would rarely lose.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1373208596057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 10:49:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373211461178-5</Id><Title>Notice, amongst bashez and pumperz alike that the following iz a forgone conclusion known by all to be true:</Title><Msg>1. This stok iz a high priced pig that hasn't matched its fundiez in YEARZ. There are many like it such az NFLX, LNKD, PCLN, TSLA, and many more. 2. Bernanke's endless money printing for TBTF robots that lack moral hazard iz at the root of these INSANE stok valuationz of worthless bit coin stox. Betnanke has forced the globez central banks into the same printing mode turning the globe into an entire bitcoin market fronted by fiat currency. 3. At some point, although nobody knowz exactly when, it will end badly for tgeze stox and global finance markets az a whole. Theze beliefs are held more common by all who agree to disagree, pumperz and basherz alike, far more so than: 'amzn at $285 iz a "growth story" whose current valuation iz under what its market performance truely reflects and therefor it should be agressively bought, held, and accumulated for the long term looking forward 18 to 36 months' Click 'thumbz up' if you agree with what sybs holdz az evedince to be true; Click 'Thumbs down' if you view amzn along with a whole market full of pigz like it are of great intrinsic value far above their current trade pricez. Retail pumperz and basherz, in the wordz of the deceased rodney king, "why cant we all just get along?".</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1373211461178</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 11:37:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373211855958-6</Id><Title>User rbg5r iz under survalence by the NSA for posting while svck ing sloppy cox</Title><Msg>This type of activity iz frowned upon by the NSA, CIA, and IRS more so then the actionz of wikileaks, snowden, hacker group anonymous, tea bagger'z tax rates az non profit status, and state sponsored terrorist. By svcking sloppy cox while he posts a mouth full of spooge it comez out az garbled "blub, blub, blub", which destroyz the fabric of society and iz found az a risk to national security.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1373211855958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 11:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373212513940-7</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Divergence on Nasdaq</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372522608397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Myth: “In-view” ads are consistent across site and ad type. Many advertisers and agencies take for granted that serving a user an ad means the ad will be viewable to that user — but it’s far from a given. The truth is, in-view ads are inconsistent and vary by site and ad type. A recent c..Score report found that among the 5.3 trillion impressions served in the U.S., three out of 10 were never seen by the end user, while another c..Score study of 2 billion impressions from 12 major brands similarly found 31% of those display ads weren’t viewable. The latter study found dramatic inconsistencies in viewability across Web properties — in one case, 100% of ads on one property were in-view, but only 7% were in-view on another, all within the same ad campaign. Other recent studies even show that up to about half of all ads placed directly may stay in view for one second or less. Advertisers should consider partnering with a vendor that can assure consistent visibility on all properties in which the ad appears. Local ad networks can help reach audiences on sites at the right place, the right time and wherever they may be, including on mobile and tablet web properties. But the key takeaway is to look closely at what that network promises and what it can deliver.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1373212513940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 11:55:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373213048733-8</Id><Title>Shorts, Sybil appears stupid now, right?</Title><Msg>She represents all of you. She's going to lose her house. Don't end up like her. Cover while you can still recover at least some of your money with some dignity left in you.</Msg><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1373213048733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 12:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373213523844-9</Id><Title>Then there'z gomer pile weekend warriorz like geegee that do not know any better because they were used az test subjects</Title><Msg>In secrets studiez conducted by the US military to determine efficacy of the US biologiccal and chemical weaponz program. In return, They give him free food (C-RATS) and access to the interenet with a fake trade account. Geegee iz az happy az a clam, but hiz hair fell out, he haz headaches, he cant get it up, and he barfs a lot.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1373213523844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 12:12:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373214516653-10</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Divergence on Nasdaq</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372522608397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And therefore it makes sense to sell about 20% of your Amazon-shares and buy for the amount shares of extreme undervalued Local Corp.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1373214516653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 12:28:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373217436421-11</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts, Sybil appears stupid now, right?</Title><Username>geegenjar</Username><Timestamp>1373213048733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 12:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This idiot must be related to "skiidady" the d'ckless clown....maybe one in the same?</Msg><Username>matzoh_myron</Username><Timestamp>1373217436421</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 13:17:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373218691600-12</Id><Topic><Title>User rbg5r iz under survalence by the NSA for posting while svck ing sloppy cox</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1373211855958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 11:44:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>leave him alone. he made some incredible calls in the past and he knows much more than he posts. btw, alpha writers are doing kukk sukkin job for hedge funds who are always long in case of float jams.</Msg><Username>junkfood_pe</Username><Timestamp>1373218691600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 13:38:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373219598540-13</Id><Title>another Kindle Price cut?</Title><Msg>such a good business that both all lose money in ereaders.</Msg><Username>buy_bubblestocks</Username><Timestamp>1373219598540</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 13:53:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373219749966-14</Id><Topic><Title>User rbg5r iz under survalence by the NSA for posting while svck ing sloppy cox</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1373211855958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 11:44:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you a clown junkfood? with a bag full of rocks for brains?</Msg><Username>buy_bubblestocks</Username><Timestamp>1373219749966</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 13:55:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373220293683-15</Id><Topic><Title>Great to see that moron from seeking alphalpa krieger short AMZN and LNKD, 2 of my longs for months that continue</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1372978239322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:50:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>one sick on line chick.</Msg><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1373220293683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 14:04:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373224006664-16</Id><Title>All you idiots ( buy bubble stox, junkfood pe, matzoh, et al) need to specify who the fvck your ranking on because of yahoo's shieotty setup</Title><Msg>The reader cant tell who the fvck your banging on because yahoo no longer threadz posts, stupidz. And if your comming at 'ol sybs then be prepared to battle, 'cause sybs doesnt take an eye for an eye, sybil takes a skull for an eye and callz it an even trade.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1373224006664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 15:06:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373226416261-17</Id><Title>I"m taliking to you Sybil!! You #$%$, loser, tranny!!! YOu call yourself a trader?????</Title><Msg>yeah you're a trader!! You trade money to those long in AMZN skidaddy tells me!! He also tells me you have been shorting AMZN for over a year now and AMZN is at alltime highs? You must be some trader to be here all the time while you have millions. Instead of sailing etc, you bless us with your horrible trading and predictions! nice job!!</Msg><Username>buy_bubblestocks</Username><Timestamp>1373226416261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 15:46:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373226645164-18</Id><Topic><Title>I"m taliking to you Sybil!! You #$%$, loser, tranny!!! YOu call yourself a trader?????</Title><Username>buy_bubblestocks</Username><Timestamp>1373226416261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 15:46:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>by the way, kindle cut prices again , watch out shorts, that's a reason for more rally tomorrow.</Msg><Username>buy_bubblestocks</Username><Timestamp>1373226645164</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 15:50:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373227911982-19</Id><Topic><Title>I"m taliking to you Sybil!! You #$%$, loser, tranny!!! YOu call yourself a trader?????</Title><Username>buy_bubblestocks</Username><Timestamp>1373226416261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 15:46:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil understandz, bubble ars. Sybs can see your all bent over with that junk lubed up and ready to get robo fvcked az this pig blows off the top and TANKS all in the same day with you sorry ars stuck in a bozo trade and a robot stvck deep in the bubble ars.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1373227911982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 16:11:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373228020952-20</Id><Title>Bubble ars takes it in the dumper from skiidady az he screamz</Title><Msg>"Feed me more, skiidady, feed me more!"</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1373228020952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 16:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373228149236-21</Id><Title>Fast Money</Title><Msg>Says the thing is going higher. NOt until they report very little earnings way off the mark will it go to over 300. Each earnings report for the past year has seen lower earnings and higher prices. if their PE drops bellow 2000 a massive ralley will take it up. Long live the longs or at least until the Hedgies decide to pop the balloon.</Msg><Username>penystoc</Username><Timestamp>1373228149236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 16:15:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373231199038-22</Id><Topic><Title>another Kindle Price cut?</Title><Username>buy_bubblestocks</Username><Timestamp>1373219598540</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 13:53:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil shorted pig flix north pf 290 in 2011 on such ill timed pumper posts and made a fvck in MINT for doung so. Eom.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1373231199038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 17:06:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373240225646-23</Id><Title>Has "skiidady" morphed into another ID???</Title><Msg>rbg? bubbles? Still to be determined.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1373240225646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 19:37:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373240513721-24</Id><Topic><Title>Has "skiidady" morphed into another ID???</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1373240225646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 19:37:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sherlock Buylowv is investigating.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1373240513721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 19:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373244406658-25</Id><Title>Sybil supposez that the 'recovery' iz taking hold. Here's what college grads got to look forward to besidez doubling loan int rates</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (AP) — Hiring is exploding in the one corner of the U.S. economy where few want to be hired: temporary work. From Wal-Mart to General Motors to PepsiCo, companies are increasingly turning to temps and to a much larger universe of freelancers, contract workers and consultants. Combined, these workers number nearly 17 million people who have only tenuous ties to the companies that pay them — about 12% of everyone with a job.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1373244406658</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 20:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373254252174-26</Id><Topic><Title>Sybil supposez that the 'recovery' iz taking hold. Here's what college grads got to look forward to besidez doubling loan int rates</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1373244406658</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 20:46:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for sure "service" employment is about permanents being substituted by temporary and higher pay by lower pay. one step closer to the future social revolution of some kind but hardly a black swan for longs. i wish u could stop attracting retail shorts to this security so longs can start back stabbing process.</Msg><Username>cash_back_7</Username><Timestamp>1373254252174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:30:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>