<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-08-18"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376825608369-1</Id><Title>Shop By Local: Find national brands, locally, with the worlds most relevant local search engine, Krillion</Title><Msg>Shop By Local: Find national brands, locally, with the worlds most relevant local search engine, Krillion. Example: Frigidaire in Orange 1.12 Miles Frigidaire Gallery 22.6 cu. ft. Side-by-Side Refrigerator ENERGY STAR $1399.99 See It 1 Sears Orange 1.12 Miles Danby 3.2 Cu. Ft. Designer Compact Refrigerator - Black with Spotless Steel Door ENERGY STAR $199.99 See It 1 Sears Orange 1.12 Miles KitchenAid 21.8 cu. ft. French-Door Refrigerator w/ Internal Water Dispenser ENERGY STAR $2879.99 $3199.99 10% OFF See It 1 Sears Orange 1.12 Miles Frigidaire 26.0 cu. ft. Side-by-Side Refrigerator ENERGY STAR $1149.99 See It 1 Sears Orange 1.12 Miles Frigidaire Professional Series 22.6 cu. ft. Side-by-Side Refrigerator (FPHS2386) ENERGY STAR $1799.99 See It 1 Sears Orange 1.12 Miles Frigidaire 26.0 cu. ft. Side-by-Side Refrigerator ENERGY STAR $1049.99 See It 1 Sears Orange 1.38 Miles Scotsman Brilliance 50 lb Ice Machine $2155.00 See It 2 Wal-Mart Orange 1.38 Miles Magic Chef 3.6-Cubic Foot Refrigerator, Black $129.00 See It 2 Wal-Mart Orange 1.38 Miles Igloo 3.2 cu. ft. Refrigerator and Freezer with RCA 1.1 cu ft Microwave Value Bundle $209.00 $229.00 9% OFF See It 2 Wal-Mart Orange 1.47 Miles Samsung - 19.7 Cu. Ft. Bottom-Freezer Refrigerator - Black $1299.99 See It 3 Best Buy Orange 1.47 Miles KitchenAid - 23.6 Cu. Ft. Counter-Depth Side-by-Side Refrigerator - White $2599.99 See It 3 Best Buy Orange 1.47 Miles Whirlpool - 21.7 Cu. Ft. French Door Refrigerator - Monochromatic Stainless-Steel $1699.99 See It 3 Best Buy Orange 1.47 Miles Whirlpool - 21.2 Cu. Ft. Top-Freezer Refrigerator - White $849.99 $999.99 15% OFF See It 3 Best Buy Orange 2.84 Miles GE GSHS9NGYSS 29 Cu. Ft. Stainless Steel Refrigerator Side By Side Refrigerator $1399.90 See It 4 Fr</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1376825608369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 07:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376827014550-2</Id><Topic><Title>Black Berry</Title><Username>penystoc</Username><Timestamp>1376771750406</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-17 16:35:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazon doesn't have cash for acquisitions and any share based large buyout like BBRY would completely ruin the float jam scam by increasing float outside of the cartel.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1376827014550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 07:56:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376833101234-3</Id><Title>Google code hacked and cracked - global shut down</Title><Msg>Like the financial servicez industry, the internet too iz bot driven and interconnected in wayz unimaginable. This little newz item az it relates to google iz gonna take puny AWS right the fvck out and murder the world of online shopping and web servicez. In the blink of a robot, we will be cast into the stone age az all thingz digital collapse. Thats why you have to have your GTC "buy to cover" limit orderz set az low az possible AHEAD of the internet crash that will coincide with / escalate / or create the crash of bot driven digital bit coin markets. You will not be able to enter your orderz or reach your broker diring the middle of it. Your limit orderz will be set to trip When system switchez attempt to reclose and come back on line in between shut shut downz. Shorts with low buy limit orderz and daring dip buying longz with low buy orderz will be considered to be heroz az they will be the only bidz and buyerz on the planet when the meyhem insuez .... Once sytemz are back on line , you can reopen your shorts on the 'bounce' before the 'controled' collapse. There'z gonna be lots of wealth to transfer az the black swan swoops down scalping the accounts of the many and deposits the money into the accounts of the few that understand and are prepared.... NOTE TO OPTION BUYING CRACKHEADZ: optionz will be entirely useless in this environment, they will fail to trade and go to 0. DO NOT USE CRACK OPTIONZ TO PREPARE FOR THE IMPENDING DISASTER. That would be like a peice of paper stating that you have access to drinking water vs actually owning a working well during a global water shortage.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1376833101234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 09:38:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376834062362-4</Id><Title>Also - you should have at least 2 months of your house hold or business cash flow stuffed into your matressez next to a sawed off shotg</Title><Msg>When the internet locks up, ATMz, digital gas pumps, etc will fail to operate.... What you need ahead of internet armeggodon Canned Food Plenty of Drinking water Seeds to grow food A stash of cash (hopefully it will still have some value despite bernanke doing hiz all out best to murder the dollar) Some precious metalz - use your jewlrey no need to buy added precious metalz Supplemental heat and electricity separate from the power grid preset LOW buy to cover GTC limit orderz on your shorts Passports / za paperz to travel in the open Weaponz - gunz , knivez, and crossbowz to shoot zombiez and hunt for food. Some karosene, gasoline, and a propane tank Thats about all sybs can think of .....</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1376834062362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 09:54:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376834899574-5</Id><Title>Mitt who? Sybil haz a vague recallection of some rich cracker named "Mitt"</Title><Msg>Didnt he get chopped up into peicez in 2012? Sybil thinks that OB's got hiz head stuffed and hanging above the master fire place mantel at the WH ... Bernanke stops by once in a while to congradulate OB on a fine kill in the world of big game hunting. Bernanke waz the guide on that hunt.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1376834899574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 10:08:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376838939404-6</Id><Topic><Title>Also - you should have at least 2 months of your house hold or business cash flow stuffed into your matressez next to a sawed off shotg</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1376834062362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 09:54:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're clearly an indoor dog Sybil. You buy hQ camping water filration systems (like those of us who camp in the backcountry do... You cannot carry enough water for extended periods and you will soon be nomadic. High quality tent, external frame backpack, fishing pole (much easierto get food fishing), and garden/vegetable seed packs (if you find a safe home base) :-) If it comes to all that, life on earth is hell and all you precautions will means nothing. We are going to witness a big deflationary collapse (so the banks can get control of physical gold from forced liquidations) and then a heathly inflation which rebalances global purchasing power, backed by fractional gold standard. It is the only stable path out of this mess. The intergenerational wealth transfer to the boomers will be reversed, financial asset holders will see worth drop reducing the gap/disparity, nominal incomes will rise (but not until currency markets reflect fundamentals) and balance will be restored. Those that rotate from financial trading scams to productive assets positioned to meet critical global needs will win.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1376838939404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 11:15:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376842606365-7</Id><Title>AMZN peaked on Jul 26th</Title><Msg>Just a matter of time now as more and more states follow CA and TX lead and force Amazon to collect sales taxes. The showroom effect goes away and stores like Best Buy and Wal-Mart see their in-store sales improve</Msg><Username>chrisbtownerr</Username><Timestamp>1376842606365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 12:16:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376843693765-8</Id><Topic><Title>I Followed Sybiljar's Advice (and their cut/paste skills)</Title><Username>mitt_romney_will_win</Username><Timestamp>1376783297850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-17 19:48:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's my short on this guy's bullshvt: Status: FILLED at $.05 Symbol: SYBS Description: sybil_rulez Action: Sell Short Quantity: 1000000 Filled Quantity: 1000000 Execution Price: $0.05 Execution Date: 7/26/2013 Execution Time: 01:27 PM ET</Msg><Username>hapihammer</Username><Timestamp>1376843693765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 12:34:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376848376870-9</Id><Topic><Title>Shop By Local: Find national brands, locally, with the worlds most relevant local search engine, Krillion</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1376825608369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 07:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Krillion is now shopbylocal Test it: Enter with shopbylocal and the most well-know suffix for the internet, which I can't post, because Yahoo would blocking my posting.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1376848376870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 13:52:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376863980631-10</Id><Topic><Title>I Followed Sybiljar's Advice (and their cut/paste skills)</Title><Username>mitt_romney_will_win</Username><Timestamp>1376783297850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-17 19:48:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Status: FILLED at $.05 Symbol: SYBS Description: sybil_rulez Action: Sell Short" Selling sybil short iz a BIG MISTAKE... Many before you have tried, and they have lost EVERYTHING. Many that have have found themselvez homeless or in an insane asylum curled up in a fetal pisition muttering "that sybil... It was sybil. Sybil got me.... Keep that sybil out of my head."</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1376863980631</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 18:13:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376864531816-11</Id><Topic><Title>Also - you should have at least 2 months of your house hold or business cash flow stuffed into your matressez next to a sawed off shotg</Title><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1376834062362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 09:54:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tech, Sybs doesnt mind being called an "indoor dog".... With ghe arsinal sybby's got - this dog haz a bite... Sybil Going nomadic / leaving the homestead shelter with land , back up power, and a working water supply would be a LAST resort... While Sybs not quite a prepper, nor a montanana big game hunter / survivor, sybil iz paaalenty prepared for any apocalyps that sybil would care to survive... If it got beyond what sybs prepped for, and a passport with cash couldnt get you you out , then he'll could have it - sybs wouldnt want to survive it....</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1376864531816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 18:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376864714563-12</Id><Topic><Title>I Followed Sybiljar's Advice (and their cut/paste skills)</Title><Username>mitt_romney_will_win</Username><Timestamp>1376783297850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-17 19:48:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm shorting your BS posts, i.e. you saying one thing and doing another. The tickets, the point is they are easy to fake. I do agree with the general premise of our economy but probably not quite as extreme as you. Are things f'ed up here in the US, dang straight, more municipalities going bankrupts etc. I also agree with tech in terms of the lack of faith in the markets. Fundamentals in any individual company don't matter until they do. That's for those that have very little of them like this one and are way too high and that's also for some suppressed companies. I believe in fundies and you don't. My best investment have been driven by not good but great fundamentals.</Msg><Username>hapihammer</Username><Timestamp>1376864714563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 18:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376865118067-13</Id><Title>Happihammer, one only haz to look back from current day to 1997 to understand that fundiez havent mattered in 17 yearz</Title><Msg>The markets are driven by the supply / demand mechanics of bit coin stox and robots that sniff out leverage in them - period.</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1376865118067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 18:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376868732607-14</Id><Topic><Title>More insider selling on 8/16/2013</Title><Username>rocketman2001ab</Username><Timestamp>1376732234351</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-17 05:37:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder if Jeff B will find another company to buy to justify selling more shares</Msg><Username>rocketman2001ab</Username><Timestamp>1376868732607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 19:32:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376878098319-15</Id><Title>Listen up dooouchbagz if you want to make some cake here</Title><Msg>Sybil iz gonna hunker down, dig deep, and ........ Short a boatload on the open..... Got that?</Msg><Username>sybil_rulez</Username><Timestamp>1376878098319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 22:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>