<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345456867000-1</Id><Title>Obama EPA to force 100 power plants to close</Title><Msg>due to strict new rules on emmissions of coal plants. (One emission gas is what you breath out called carbon dioxide which plants consume) Expect more blackouts and expensive power bills. The Republicans in the Democrat majority Senate, voted to block the EPA rules, but they were outnumbered. http://www.altoonamirror.com/page/content.detail/id/561888/Senate-vote-zaps-coal-plants.html Where is Yahoo "news" on this important news article and issue?</Msg><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345456867000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:01:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345470645000-2</Id><Topic><Title>The duck:</Title><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1345410933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:15:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>QWAK,You talking to ME?? ;) I have been busy stacking and rearanging SILVER in my vault making room for MORE -- it is amasing how heavy the real stuff is! LOL http://www.silverbearcafe.com/private/08.12/billionaire.html TPTB have managed to keep the price of both GOLD and SILVER down for about a year now to help there buddies get out from under huge short positions befor BOTH do a moon shot in 2013.:) I expect a signifigent increase this fall but after the elections and early in 2013 --- KAITY bar the door because TPTB won't be able to hold back the tide of higher taxes and inflation any longer and the price of both will soar as the plunge protection team backs off from the stock market and lets it collaps along with some of the bigist banks in the world! :( The dollar is NOT money it is just curency which is a substitute for actual MONEY which has always been GOLD and SILVER! When the curencies devalue because they can always make more out of thin air --- all that will mater is -- do YOU have the real stuff or NOT! BUMMER if you don't! the DUCK</Msg><Username>uglyduck555</Username><Timestamp>1345470645000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:50:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345475551000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Calling All Longs&gt;</Title><Username>sandralofa26</Username><Timestamp>1345473437000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:37:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice Post</Msg><Username>narriswhit51</Username><Timestamp>1345475551000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345495855000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Owned KO for 20 years.</Title><Username>insurancefla1</Username><Timestamp>1344943543000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 07:25:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I smell a liar-- 20 years would have 4 splits in it... not two.</Msg><Username>vwdiesel10</Username><Timestamp>1345495855000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:50:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>