<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-29"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343594778000-1</Id><Title>KO largest customer has Black CEO</Title><Msg>McDonald's is probably Coke's largest and most important customer. Now McDonald's has a Black CEO - Don Thompson. McDonald's has a great record of diversity because it realizes and respects its customer base. "Diversity fuels innovation, and innovation fuels success," Thompson said. The company doesn’t want to just have a diverse employee base, Thompson said, but also be sure that its suppliers and franchisees are as well. The company is looking to help women and minorities own more franchises and is willing to help some of them financially to make it happen. When it comes to suppliers, McDonald’s currently “buys 55 percent of its food and paper products from women and minority-owned businesses,” according to Thompson. And that adds up to be a nice chunk of change. McDonald's US alone spends $9 billion annually on groceries. When will Coke catch up? Does Coke want to catch up? Can Coke continue to march its army of non-minority managers in front of its biggest customer? Is Coke as serious as McDonald's about the diversity in its employee base, its suppliers and its franchisees? Judging from history, Coke does'nt care about diversity, but this will soon catch up with them, very soon!</Msg><Username>kofrankwhite</Username><Timestamp>1343594778000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:46:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343594959000-2</Id><Title>KO and African Americans</Title><Msg>"African-American teens not only spend $96 more per month than the average teen, but exert far-reaching influence on mainstream cultural trends, points out Seth Freeman, senior brand manager, sparkling beverages, African-American marketing for Coca-Cola North America. Furthermore, the Coca-Cola Company estimates that roughly 86% of its growth going forward will come from Hispanics, African-Americans and Asian Americans, he says." If Coke admits that African American teens are huge buyers of thier products and admits 86% of thier growth will come from Hispanic, African-Americans and Asian Americans, can someone tell me why these groups are NOT represented in Coke's upper management and in Coke bottling distributors? Talk about biting the hands that feed you. Its time for those hands to start slapping Coke instead of feeding them!</Msg><Username>kofrankwhite</Username><Timestamp>1343594959000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:49:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343595508000-3</Id><Title>Coca-Cola is downright delicious!!!!!</Title><Msg>I think that we know that's what it all comes down to. Final taste tests prove this.</Msg><Username>ghostridr772</Username><Timestamp>1343595508000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:58:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343606821000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Does dividend split too?</Title><Username>hey_rob69</Username><Timestamp>1341948069000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-10 15:21:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know what exactly will happen however I looked at the historical prices, dividends only for KO on this Yahoo Finance site for as far back as it goes and this shows what the dividend was the three dividends before the split and the three dividends after the split. Will it happen this way again? I hope so but I have no crystal ball: Date Dividends 9/9/1965 0.00885 11/26/1965 0.00885 3/14/1966 0.0099 5/13/1966 May 13, 1966 2 for 1 stock split 6/9/1966 0.0099 9/9/1966 0.0099 11/28/1966 0.0099 9/10/1976 0.01379 11/24/1976 0.01379 3/10/1977 0.01604 6/1/1977 June 1, 1977 2 for 1 stock split 6/10/1977 0.01604 9/12/1977 0.01604 11/25/1977 0.01604 11/24/1987 0.035 3/9/1988 0.0375 6/9/1988 0.0375 7/1/1988 July 1, 1988 3 for 1 stock split 9/9/1988 0.0375 11/25/1988 0.0375 3/9/1989 0.0425 9/11/1989 0.0425 11/27/1989 0.0425 3/9/1990 0.05 5/14/1990 May 14, 1990 2 for 1 stock split 6/11/1990 0.05 9/10/1990 0.05 9/9/1991 0.06 11/22/1991 0.06 3/9/1992 0.07 5/12/1992 May 12, 1992 2 for 1 stock split 6/9/1992 0.07 9/9/1992 0.07 11/24/1992 0.07</Msg><Username>winslowm22</Username><Timestamp>1343606821000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 20:07:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>