<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343392194000-1</Id><Topic><Title>split info straight from the horses mouth.</Title><Username>mycomputersux</Username><Timestamp>1343175085000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 20:11:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, may be short-sighted or the other hand may be an opportunity to obtain more KO shares cheaper. Thanks for the split info.</Msg><Username>merritt12</Username><Timestamp>1343392194000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 08:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343400672000-2</Id><Topic><Title>July 27, 2012</Title><Username>lisa_in_shoreview</Username><Timestamp>1342459750000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-16 13:29:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just got off the phone with Coca Cola Investor Relations. Here is what they told me: Today (7/27) is the date of record; if you own shares at close of business today, you will receive the 2-for-1 split. August 10 is the date of distribution. The stock is currently being traded under two symptols: KO and KOWI. KO is the pre-split price, which is the current market price and includes the split. KOWI is the post-split price; it is an approx. price, without the split. I am pretty sure what Fidelity and Coca Cola Investor Relations told me is accurate. Finally, I own 3,500 shares (and that is before the split.) I feel pretty confident with my info:)</Msg><Username>lisa_in_shoreview</Username><Timestamp>1343400672000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 10:51:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343402520000-3</Id><Topic><Title>July 27, 2012</Title><Username>lisa_in_shoreview</Username><Timestamp>1342459750000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-16 13:29:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Today (7/27) is the date of record; if you own shares at close of business today, you will receive the 2-for-1 split." Yes, but if you sell them before August 13th you'll have to forfeit the split shares to whoever you sold them to via the due bill that are attached to all shares sold from July 25th through August 10th. Not only does the company outright tell you that in the passages I quoted in a previous post, but those are the rules of the stock exchange for every similar situation. It also applies to cash dividends that are 25% or more of a company's stock price. This explains it much better than KO does on their website: http://groupssa.com/understandingdividenddates.html#the_following_section "KO is the pre-split price, which is the current market price and includes the split." Yes. Those are the ones we're talking about. "I feel pretty confident with my info:)" I'm sure your confidence makes you feel good, but when you say things like "this means if you buy the stock AFTER July 27, you will NOT receive the 2-for-1 split" you are simply wrong.</Msg><Username>cwn600</Username><Timestamp>1343402520000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 11:22:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343406062000-4</Id><Topic><Title>July 27, 2012</Title><Username>lisa_in_shoreview</Username><Timestamp>1342459750000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-16 13:29:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why people have such a hard time understanding a simple event such as a stock split? Incredible, almost amusing...</Msg><Username>domenexx</Username><Timestamp>1343406062000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 12:21:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343409278000-5</Id><Topic><Title>July 27, 2012</Title><Username>lisa_in_shoreview</Username><Timestamp>1342459750000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-16 13:29:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is all too funny. If you buy the shares 1 minute before close the day before the split takes effect, your will still get the split...twice the shares at half the price. It isn't rocket science. As opposed to a cash dividend, the ex date serves no real purpose.</Msg><Username>jpm8282</Username><Timestamp>1343409278000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 13:14:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343412713000-6</Id><Topic><Title>July 27, 2012</Title><Username>lisa_in_shoreview</Username><Timestamp>1342459750000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-16 13:29:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If you buy the shares 1 minute before close the day before the split takes effect, your will still get the split" Yes. And if you buy the shares 1 minute before the close ON the day the split takes effect, you will also get the split. The split becomes effective after the close on August 10th, when the split shares will be delivered to the accounts of those who are shareholders as of the record date. (Those who bought between the record date and the ex-date will have to wait until the due bill redemption date.) "As opposed to a cash dividend, the ex date serves no real purpose." No true. With splits the ex-date serves the exact SAME purpose as it does with a cash dividend: buy before the ex-date (and hold), get the split (or dividend), by on or after the ex-date, don't get the split (or dividend). Buy KO on or before August 10th (the payment date), you get the split. Buy on or after August 13th, which is the ex-date for the split, you don't get the split -- but the shares will already be trading on a split adjusted basis on the ex-date. "It isn't rocket science." No, it isn't. Yet you still got it partially wrong.</Msg><Username>cwn600</Username><Timestamp>1343412713000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 14:11:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343413311000-7</Id><Topic><Title>July 27, 2012</Title><Username>lisa_in_shoreview</Username><Timestamp>1342459750000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-16 13:29:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you and excuse my wording in my previous message. People seem to be treating today's date, the stock of record date, like an ex dividend date. You can buy KO anytime from now till the closing day before the split, and still receive it.</Msg><Username>jpm8282</Username><Timestamp>1343413311000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 14:21:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343413679000-8</Id><Topic><Title>July 27, 2012</Title><Username>lisa_in_shoreview</Username><Timestamp>1342459750000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-16 13:29:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"People seem to be treating today's date, the stock of record date, like an ex dividend date." I've noticed that with a lot of stocks that use a deferred ex-date. It doesn't make sense on two counts 1. It's not the real ex-date, and 2. Even if the stock were using a normal ex-date, it would've been two trading days before the record date, not the record date itself. I guess it's just a matter of complete confusion. Goes hand in hand with the bogus idea that it's worth jumping into a stock and running up the price just to get a dividend.</Msg><Username>cwn600</Username><Timestamp>1343413679000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 14:27:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343415906000-9</Id><Title>pulls breaks on 80</Title><Msg>how is it possible to have the stock stop at 80 on the nose and not 80.01?</Msg><Username>hey_rob69</Username><Timestamp>1343415906000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 15:05:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343416156000-10</Id><Topic><Title>pulls breaks on 80</Title><Username>hey_rob69</Username><Timestamp>1343415906000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 15:05:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>80.08 now. much better</Msg><Username>hey_rob69</Username><Timestamp>1343416156000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 15:09:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343421360000-11</Id><Topic><Title>New Analysis on The Coca-Cola Company Suggests Drop</Title><Username>lakitacatino</Username><Timestamp>1343416195000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 15:09:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAM!</Msg><Username>investor_wizard</Username><Timestamp>1343421360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 16:36:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>