<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-17"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350449277095-1</Id><Title>Ideas</Title><Msg>Democratic ideas are so good for America that Mitt Romney has decided to steal all those ideas and ride on them.</Msg><Username>sanseh2003</Username><Timestamp>1350449277095</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:47:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350495905169-2</Id><Topic><Title>Ideas</Title><Username>sanseh2003</Username><Timestamp>1350449277095</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:47:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The latest Democratic idea that showed up last night on Twitter is to shoot Romney if he wins. Shows just how far the libs are taken in by Obama's smoke screen. I suppose the idea of putting a max limit for tax deductions is a Democratic idea.</Msg><Username>unclelarry66</Username><Timestamp>1350495905169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350498784798-3</Id><Title>Chinese currency manipulation hurts companies like KO</Title><Msg>Romney was right on target in that analysis. The proof is in the pudding (earnings I mean!)</Msg><Username>whoozyurdaddi</Username><Timestamp>1350498784798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:33:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350503706065-4</Id><Title>ATTD distribution agreement announcement, 2200% GAINS POSSIBLE, UNDERVALUED, CHEAP BUY,READ</Title><Msg>ATTD distribution agreement announcement, 2200% GAINS POSSIBLE, UNDERVALUED, CHEAP BUY,READ WALMART DISTRIBUTION AGREEMENT ANTICIPATED BY SHAREHOLDERS.TRADERS SUGGEST ANNOUNCEMENT COMING ANY DAY NOW. Attitude Drinks, has recently announced record orders and expanded distribution of their recently launched Phase III Energy Recovery drink and brand, and has made tremendous progress as of late, by increasing that distribution to the likes of Walgreen's in Florida and Sam's Mart Stores in the Carolinas and Georgia. ATTD is expected to pull in tens of Millions. Analyst suggests ATTD is ready for a MASSIVE BREAKOUT. This Stock price has the potential to 5cents to 20cents. And buying the stock for nothing at 0.0009 will bring unbelievable profit. Buying 1 million shares@ 0.0009, cost= $900. Sell 1 million shares@ 1 cent = $10,000 or 5 cents= $50,000 With 2200% gains, ATTD can turn around your losses and bring your trading account back positive.</Msg><Username>agreenview</Username><Timestamp>1350503706065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350504985933-5</Id><Topic><Title>Ideas</Title><Username>sanseh2003</Username><Timestamp>1350449277095</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:47:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH PLEASE!!! open your eyes and ears</Msg><Username>poorhah</Username><Timestamp>1350504985933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:16:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>