<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344421854000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Quit Asking these Stupid Questions about the Split</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1344376745000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:59:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or we are just tired of the 10,000 questions about a simple 2:1 stock split....</Msg><Username>DrunknDangerous</Username><Timestamp>1344421854000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 06:30:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344430044000-2</Id><Title>McDonalds tanking negative COMPS !</Title><Msg>McDonalds KO largest customer I believe.. The little people 99% are running out of cash..</Msg><Username>obamaloveswallst1</Username><Timestamp>1344430044000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 08:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344438743000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Quit Asking these Stupid Questions about the Split</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1344376745000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:59:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The concept of getting two shares for each one you own is indeed simple. The delivery of those split shares involving deferred ex-dates and due bill settlements are not.</Msg><Username>cwn600</Username><Timestamp>1344438743000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 11:12:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344439136000-4</Id><Title>Losing Hard?</Title><Msg>Excellent analysis and commentary! They regularly provide the best rundown on the US market. These guys are awesome!! With this great analysis, and there is no way I could have made money this year without this site! I signed up for there FREE daily videos. See for yourself, you will be glad you did! http://STOCKMARKET-RESEARCH.INFO</Msg><Username>lorialex961</Username><Timestamp>1344439136000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 11:18:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344445089000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Losing Hard?</Title><Username>lorialex961</Username><Timestamp>1344439136000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 11:18:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't Believe This WOW</Msg><Username>joshep_nicol</Username><Timestamp>1344445089000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 12:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344465621000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Quit Asking these Stupid Questions about the Split</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1344376745000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:59:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>actually, it is all fairly simple. Seriously. If you don't think so, then don't invest in stocks directly.</Msg><Username>DrunknDangerous</Username><Timestamp>1344465621000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 18:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344467378000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Quit Asking these Stupid Questions about the Split</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1344376745000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:59:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I get it that the questions are simple....TO US. Everybody started out small and everybody asked stupid questions at one point. I get it that it's irritating and shows a lack of research. You're NOT wrong. BUT Remember when you first started or try to imagine what it would be like if your grandmother was asking about stocks.</Msg><Username>dividaddy</Username><Timestamp>1344467378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 19:09:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344471259000-8</Id><Topic><Title>McDonalds tanking negative COMPS !</Title><Username>obamaloveswallst1</Username><Timestamp>1344430044000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 08:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still, in spite of that, we have seen that before at times, and the company sometimes performs well with time. My hunch is that these news items don't count for that much and it is just about the overall popularity of the company and the good management.</Msg><Username>foxeelicious</Username><Timestamp>1344471259000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 20:14:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344473459000-9</Id><Title>August 10, 2012</Title><Msg>It is Aug. 8, and I just finished discussing the 2-for-1 stock split with Fidelity. The date of record was 7/27. You needed to own the stock at close of business on 7/27 to qualify for the stock split. If you bought AFTER 7/27 you will NOT get the 2-for-1 split. You CANNOT buy this stock at the last minute and get the 2-for-1 stock split; it does not work that way. I'm confident that Fidelity knows what they are talking about because this isn't their first rodeo.</Msg><Username>lisa_in_shoreview</Username><Timestamp>1344473459000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 20:50:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344473920000-10</Id><Title>Info. from the Coke's website</Title><Msg>What does a two-for-one stock split mean to shareowners of The Coca-Cola Company? Shareowners will be issued one additional share of common stock for every share of common stock held at the close of business on the record date, and will have twice as many shares after the payment date. The split will double the number of shares outstanding but the corresponding market value per share will be decreased by half. The overall market value of the shareowner's investment remains the same. For example, assuming that as of July 27, 2012, the record date, a shareowner owned 100 shares of common stock at a market price of $75 per share. The shareowner's investment value would be $7,500. On August 10, 2012, the distribution date, shareowners of record will be sent notification of the shares received as a result of the split. After the split, the shareowner will own 200 shares at an initial market price of $37.50 per share (assuming a $75 stock price on August 10, 2012). The shareowner's total investment value would remain the same at $7,500 until the stock price moves up or down.</Msg><Username>lisa_in_shoreview</Username><Timestamp>1344473920000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 20:58:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344477571000-11</Id><Topic><Title>August 10, 2012</Title><Username>lisa_in_shoreview</Username><Timestamp>1344473459000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 20:50:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lisa, you keep repeating the same mistake: "If you bought AFTER 7/27 you will NOT get the 2-for-1 split" KO's FAQ on their website tells you this isn't so, yet you continue to believe it. So one more time, the question on KO's Two For One Stock Split FAQ asks: "What happens if I sell my shares of stock after the record date and before the payment date (distribution date)?" And the answer is: "We've been advised by the New York Stock Exchange that beginning as early as two days before the record date (July 25 th ) through the payment date (August 10 th ), two separate markets for common stock of The Coca-Cola Company will trade on the NYSE. The "regular way" market, traded under the ticker symbol "KO", will continue to trade at the higher, pre-split price. Shares sold in the market at the "regular way" price will receive full value for the shares sold and the seller is not entitled to the split shares they will receive by virtue of their being holders on the record date." ******************** Now, the New York Stock Exchange has advised KO that you do NOT have to be a shareholder on the record date to get the split shares. So who do you think is correct, the NYSE or a customer service rep at Fidelity? You go on to make another wrong claim: "You CANNOT buy this stock at the last minute and get the 2-for-1 stock split; it does not work that way." Yet KO and the New York Stock Exchange both say you can because it DOES work that way. KO explains that too in their Two For One Stock Split FAQ: "Therefore, the split shares are transferred to the buyers by means of "due bills"." http://www.thecoca-colacompany.com/contactus/faq/stock-split-faq.html#9 "I'm confident that Fidelity knows what they are talking about because this isn't their first rodeo." Your misplaced confidence isn't letting you see the truth. It's not the NYSE's first rodeo either. Why don't you do yourself a favor and ask your rep at Fidelity why the NYSE says Fidelity is wrong and see what they say. Or, more accurately, see how fast they do an about-face.</Msg><Username>cwn600</Username><Timestamp>1344477571000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 21:59:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344477705000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Info. from the Coke's website</Title><Username>lisa_in_shoreview</Username><Timestamp>1344473920000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 20:58:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We've been advised by the New York Stock Exchange that beginning as early as two days before the record date (July 25 th ) through the payment date (August 10 th ), two separate markets for common stock of The Coca-Cola Company will trade on the NYSE. The "regular way" market, traded under the ticker symbol "KO", will continue to trade at the higher, pre-split price. Shares sold in the market at the "regular way" price will receive full value for the shares sold and the seller is not entitled to the split shares they will receive by virtue of their being holders on the record date. Therefore, the split shares are transferred to the buyers by means of "due bills"." http://www.thecoca-colacompany.com/contactus/faq/stock-split-faq.html#9</Msg><Username>cwn600</Username><Timestamp>1344477705000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 22:01:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>