<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357664175855-1</Id><Topic><Title>KO has a problem being a new Competitor</Title><Username>tejdem1</Username><Timestamp>1356715498151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:24:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>KO, is the leader in soft industry. It know how to handle the competition and grow at the same time. Strong management, is always looking into new area to increase.</Msg><Username>dirtpoordog</Username><Timestamp>1357664175855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:56:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357692280130-2</Id><Topic><Title>KO has a problem being a new Competitor</Title><Username>tejdem1</Username><Timestamp>1356715498151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:24:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"10x much salt"? One 8oz serving of plain soy milk has 150mg of sodium. One 12oz serving of Coke has 45mg of sodium. Based on your comment, Coke would be better for you. I'm sorry but you're an embarrassingly poor salesperson. With promotors like you, Sodastream has no chance. You didn't even need to mention the #1 complaint about it, which is the outrageous cost and hassle of replacing the carbonation cartridges. Analysts who have studied the cost savings concluded that the machine doesn't break even on cane sugar syrup until you reach your 360th serving, and that's without the added costs of replacement bottles and cylinders. I don't know what it is that you're addicted to but I suggest you try to sell it somewhere else.</Msg><Username>nothingsmissing</Username><Timestamp>1357692280130</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:44:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357695508480-3</Id><Topic><Title>KO has a problem being a new Competitor</Title><Username>tejdem1</Username><Timestamp>1356715498151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:24:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok swifty see below. I think the hassle is having to lug around seltzer, soda and energy drinks... Also Sodastream it is cheaper. A 12 pack of coke not on sale is 5.50. If you get a sale lets say 3 12 packs for 10 bucks. The sodastream syrup which is 5 bucks and creates 33 cans of soda. The savings is about 20% or so or much more if the Coke,Pepsi is not on sale. I used to drink a ton of diet coke and made the switch 2 years ago and never again purchased Coke /Diet coke for my house. The Sodastream product taste better, cheaper, and no more lugging bottles and cans. The C02 canister can be swapped at WMT, TGT, M,SPLS and now many grocery stores. Think to yourself why KO,PEP and MNST is under performing over the last 6 months.Watch my friend and you will see... We have 110M households in the USA last xmas season the sellout of Sodastream machines was 300,000 machines in the USA. This year my estimate is 600,000. Also keep and eye put for the next 24 hour HSN sodastream special. Last time they sold 33,000 machines in 24 hours about 3 months ago. I expect this number to rise to about 55,000. KO has never experienced competition like this.... Calories Carbs Sugar Sodium Caffeine Pepsi速 100 27g 27g 25mg 25mg Coca-Cola速 100 27g 27g 35mg 23mg SodaStream Cola 34 9g 9g 2mg 15mg 7-UP速 100 26g 26g 50mg 0mg Sprite速 100 26g 26g 45mg 0mg SodaStream Lemon Lime 36 9g 9g 25mg 0mg</Msg><Username>tejdem1</Username><Timestamp>1357695508480</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:38:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>