<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345438417000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So? What business is of yours what his life style is? Did you start your own business and make it possible to make that much money? NO? Then shut the he&amp;&amp; up!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345438417000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345439095000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"that someone who makes that much money in one year, on a regular basis should be paying more money in taxes." No unless the tax laws say they must. The tax laws and the existing loopholes are the product of Congress and their sugar daddies. The loopholes exist because of those people. The tax laws were written and passed by Congress, mostly Democratic controlled Congress' of the past few decades. Do you ask if the Kennedy's, the Reid's, Nut Job Nancy, or Kerry have outside investments? No? Neither does the media. It makes little difference what the President wants to do about taxes unless Congress goes along, unless of course you are Obama and you change laws by fiat when you get a wild hair up your butt. Look at recent history and see how many years the Democrats controlled Congress and had more than ample opportunity to change tax laws and DIDN’T! You seem very worried about Romney's taxes. Do you ever worry about all the things the current President is hiding about his past? Do you look at his administration appointments and wonder why? Do you wonder about his past relationships with known criminals and terrorists or a radical preacher? If not, you should not be voting.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345439095000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 01:04:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345439266000-3</Id><Topic><Title>romney will never win</Title><Username>ser3324</Username><Timestamp>1345048976000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And it is spelled yokel. You yokel.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345439266000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 01:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345439535000-4</Id><Topic><Title>romney will never win</Title><Username>ser3324</Username><Timestamp>1345048976000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't answer the question? I didn't think so. So much for the intelligence of the liberal masses. With all the questions about Obama's past, Romney religious mission is your main concern? You're simply a talking points and media sound bite voter aren't you? You’re reading too many of Ricky/Echo’s postings, or are you just another handle for the same evil twins?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345439535000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 01:12:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345439716000-5</Id><Topic><Title>romney will never win</Title><Username>ser3324</Username><Timestamp>1345048976000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again, dumb butt, learn to spell the word if you're going to blast it all over the Internet. You're shameless; or as Ricky would tell you, you have no sense of self-awareness. Geez’s are all you talking point, media sound bite, MSNBC stupid liberals all alike?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345439716000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 01:15:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345451463000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Then shut the he&amp;&amp; up!" I thought all you GOPers were good christians? Probably a fraud like Huckabee and Ayn Ryan.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1345451463000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 04:31:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345460883000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>winholder, the fact is that I did have doubts about Obama at the time of the last Presidential election and so I did not vote for him. However, in general, he has seemed to be very practical in most of his decisions. He has continued to try to protect us against the terrorists. He went after and got Bin Laden. He has been putting extreme pressure on Iran to try to prevent them from having nuclear weapons. He didn't remove our troops from Iraq and Afghanistan immediately but has tried to do it gradually.</Msg><Username>eseyfried</Username><Timestamp>1345460883000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 07:08:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345461088000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>winholder, it seems that in the past every candidate for President has always allowed the public to see his or her tax returns etc. Also if the Kennedys, Kerry etc. were putting their money outside of the country to avoid paying U.S. taxes, I am pretty sure we would have heard about it. The Republicans would have made sure that we did.</Msg><Username>eseyfried</Username><Timestamp>1345461088000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 07:11:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345461836000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>winholder, I am sorry but I thought we still had freedom of speech in this country. I guess we don't if we are criticizing a Republican. Oh and the reason why I think it is my business is that if a person makes so many millions of dollars and could pay some more in taxes without it changing their lifestyle one bit, they should not be selfish. Since a lot of the money spent by the government is necessary (such as the wars, homeland security etc.) and we have deficits, they should be willing to pay a little more if they love their country. In the past they did not cut taxes for the rich when we were at war. Also economists had said that some spending was necessary to prevent us from going into another Depression because we had been in the worse recession that we have had since the last Great Depression.</Msg><Username>eseyfried</Username><Timestamp>1345461836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 07:23:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345465420000-10</Id><Title>T may be up 28 % in 1 year BUT</Title><Msg>If it corrected back to 30-32, you would need to collect 3-4 years of dividends just to recover lost principle and break even with valuation. After the election, many expect the irrational exuberance of the market to vanish making a major market pullback more probable than ever.</Msg><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1345465420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345466092000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It could be that Romney got caught in the Swiss banking scandal and took IRS amnesty. This guy wants you to believe he's a great business man, but where is the independent proof of this. I have not seen one non partisan article on this subject. Obama is going to eviscerate this clown in the debates. Flip, where are the tax returns?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1345466092000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:34:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345466474000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Esey, check the expiration date on your meds! Romney gives more to charity then any other candidate in history. He is humble, charitable, and fairly smart with good lifetime experience and history. What about the economy and the unemployment rate that you do not get! What Mitt chooses to do with his money is his business. Don't you think that the IRS would have issues with his tax returns. If you don't like the tax laws, vote for a Congress that will change them. BTW, look out for the mortgage deduction, that will probably be in the first batch of tax loop holes that Congress will close.</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1345466474000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:41:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345466745000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"BTW, look out for the mortgage deduction, that will probably be in the first batch of tax loop holes that Congress will close." Right, for more tax cuts for the Romney/Ryan types.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1345466745000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:45:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345467664000-14</Id><Topic><Title>T may be up 28 % in 1 year BUT</Title><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1345465420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, it is pretty darn clear DC is going to do nothing about the mess we are in until after the election dust settles. It seems most of us can't handle the truth! So, we probably have a couple of months until the next potential shock has a chance to hit markets. Enjoy while you can.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1345467664000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:01:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345469138000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, let’s all talk about the tax returns, his wife never having a job, his business success, 'is it real or did someone one else cause that'. Let's not talk about the economy, they still failing jobs programs, the failure of many of the bailout programs, the failure of Obama's regime to do most of what he promised to do when elected. Let’s talk about Ryan’s budget proposal when Obama hasn’t even presented one and when he did the members of his own Party won’t bring it up for a vote. Let's talk about trivial crap and not about the issues that impact the largest parts of the population. "Patriotism means to stand by your country. It does not mean to stand by your President." -Theodore Roosevelt.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345469138000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:25:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345469305000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This conservative is not a Bible Thumper as you liberals put it. I gave up my Bible, but not my guns or my commonsense. This conservative is also registered as an Independent, not a Republican. I like to think for myself, not be told what to think, and if I can’t spell it, I look it up. You should try it. Now, please shut the he&amp;&amp; up. Thank you.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345469305000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:28:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345469794000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are of course free to say almost anything you want, regardless of silly, stupid and misguided it might be. Economists? Which ones? You ask 100 of them for the opinion; you will get 100 differing opinions. Working hard to obtain wealth and the things that go along with it is selfish? The government coming along and taking away more of what you worked for simply because some others can't give them the money they want to spend is not selfish? I might agree with some of your points if the government cared enough to control themselves, to be good stewards of the people's money they confiscate. They aren't and you know it. There is so much silly, wasteful and outright corrupt spending in this country it is unbelievable and even when pointed out to the government they do little if anything to solve the problem. Their answer is to get more from the people. They can't satisfy their campaign contributors and the people they buy votes from...the folks forever on the government dole...if they can't rob from the rich. Explain to me where the fairness that liberals rant about in that philosophy!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345469794000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:36:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345470092000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, according to the like of you and Esey, the rich don't have mortgages. Folks like me and others that had/have mortgage that we could afford for homes we could afford will lose so the government can give away yet more of the money we didn't earn. Someone else did that for us, so the government is going to take it from us. More liberal ‘fairness’. "Socialism is a philosophy of failure, the creed of ignorance, and the gospel of envy, its inherent virtue is the equal sharing of misery" -- Winston Churchill</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345470092000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345470680000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>winholder, I have read that it is the Republicans who want to do away with the deduction for mortgages including the interest that people have to pay for their mortgage loans.The Republicans consider this to be a "loophole". This could cause the tax for many of the people in the middle class to go up. The Republicans also want to cut the taxes for the millionaires at the same time.</Msg><Username>eseyfried</Username><Timestamp>1345470680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:51:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345470979000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>winholder, the fact is that many of those people who make millions of dollars a year don't even work as hard as many people who make modest incomes. In addition, if their tax is raised a little, it would not effect their life style one bit. It seems that it is patriotic for them to pay more when money is needed for wars etc. since it wouldn't affect their lifestyle at all.</Msg><Username>eseyfried</Username><Timestamp>1345470979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:56:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345471179000-21</Id><Topic><Title>T may be up 28 % in 1 year BUT</Title><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1345465420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No way that BO will let the mkt drop before the election. That would diminish his popularity even further. Like a puppet on a string, he keeps a tight rein on Bernanke. Gold and SLV being manipulated along with most everything else. Gas creeping UP again.</Msg><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1345471179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345471406000-22</Id><Topic><Title>T may be up 28 % in 1 year BUT</Title><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1345465420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Gas creeping UP again." ...and it seems there is a better than fair chance he will manipulate it by tapping into our reserves.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1345471406000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345471711000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cisco, yes he gives money to charities of his choice such as his Mormon Church, however when his country needs money because we are involved in wars, have to spend money on homeland security etc.,he doesn't have the same feeling. He avoids paying taxes on his large income anyway he can, even though the tax rate for the wealthy is at its lowest. Oh and it is the Republicans who want to get rid of the so-called loophole of being able to deduct the interest a person has to pay on their mortgage loan. They want to do that while cutting the tax rate for the rich even more. That could hurt those in the middle class that have mortgages and are living paycheck to paycheck. It can even hurt the economy because it might be more difficult for some people to buy houses and those that do have mortgages will have less money to spend at the store. I repeat if the tax rate went up a little for those who make millions of dollars a year, it would not affect their ability to spend at all. They will still be able to buy whatever they want.</Msg><Username>eseyfried</Username><Timestamp>1345471711000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:08:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345472652000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fine Easy, tax the rich some more. I wish the Republicans would agree simply to shut up people like you and the rest of the far left. If you really think raising their taxes will even begin to solve the spending mess we are in you are living in a cave and don't begin to understand the numbers.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1345472652000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:24:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345472757000-25</Id><Topic><Title>WE NEED HELP</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345326413000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 17:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WE NEED HELP 18-Aug-12 05:46 pm PLEASE COME BACK JIMMY CARTER. TURNS OUT YOU WEREN'T THE WORST PRESIDENT AFTER ALL... Jimmy, call him, we need you, don't let him put this great country into bankruptcy....We can't afford any more debt....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345472757000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:25:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345475968000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's good to see a non-bible-thumping conservative retain his God-given right to be a huge blowhard.</Msg><Username>brainstemonly</Username><Timestamp>1345475968000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:19:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345475970000-27</Id><Topic><Title>WE NEED HELP</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345326413000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 17:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least Carter was not purposely trying to destroy America; it just happened.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1345475970000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:19:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345476348000-28</Id><Topic><Title>T may be up 28 % in 1 year BUT</Title><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1345465420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reserves are for a national emergency and what could be more of an emergency to Obama than his re-election?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1345476348000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:25:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345476874000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>t.bfine, I am not on the far left. I am one of those people who are in the middle. I try to consider the details of each issue. Everything should not be to the far left or the far right. I know that just raising the tax on those who make millions of dollars every year will not get rid of the deficit, but it will help. I know that in the past when we were at war, we did not cut the taxes that the wealthy had to pay. I know that when Clinton was President, he raised the top tax rate in his first year as President and the Republicans could not lower it during his entire administration. In addition Clinton tried to cut wasteful spending. The plan was to get the deficit to be cut a little every year until it was gone and it worked. Oh and I want to add that if the Republicans can they would shut up everyone who disagrees with them whether they are on the far left or not. I hope that we remain a country where we have freedom of speech so that they cannot do so, but they might just do that.</Msg><Username>eseyfried</Username><Timestamp>1345476874000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:34:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345477055000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Where is JOE ??</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1345476266000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:24:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did every household in Virginia get a DVD "Dreams From My REAL Father" in the mail? Ohio, Florida, and Virginia were to be the first three states covered. It will be a waste sending them here to California. It seems that the best way to get elected in California is to brag that you are a Communist; and a Communist sex pervert is a shew in.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1345477055000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:37:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345477527000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is a loophole pure and simple. If we want to fix the tax code then all loopholes should be removed and and a flat tax instituted.</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1345477527000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:45:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345480168000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, a huge blowhard got elected to President last time out. If you haven't tried it, don't knock it. Now leave me alone or I'll hit you with my Bible.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345480168000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:29:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345480563000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not gonna happen; too many political careers at risk to even suggest such a thing. I was reading an analysis of how to fix SS this morning. Several fixes point out that such a fix would take care of 25% of the problem or 45% of a certain problem...the interesting thing was that in those suggested fixes, had they been implemented three years ago, the percentage fix would have been 47% and 73% respectively. Congress dilly-dallies around and the situation only gets 'progressively' worse. I guess that is what they mean when they say they are 'progressives'. You see the President is a real pain in the XXX but Congress is the key to resurrecting this country and our economy. The problem with the current Congress is that when the current President says jump they ask how high…sometimes; the rest of the time they do NOTHING, which is often the lesser of two evils.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345480563000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:36:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345481116000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did Kennedy give more because we were at war? Does Kerry give more because we are at war and the economy is failing? No, he moved his yatch to avoid taxes in his home state. Does Nancy's husband quit doing business overseas and bring his investment money home because we have 45% more people on food stamps since 2009? Does George Soro’s give money to the government to help pay down the deficit? No, he gives it to President Obama, one of the many reasons we are all worse off now than four years ago. The right does not have a monopoly on wealth; the liberals only try to paint it that way. Most of the voters on the right are wealthier than the left because they don’t pander to a voting bloc that doesn’t pay taxes, gets most of the food stamps, most of the welfare or are here illegally in the first place. The Democrats would never do anything publicly to upset the largest economically challenged voting bloc in the country. NO! A resounding NO! The Democrats helped get these folks in their economic positions and they aren’t smart enough to realize that the Democrats are trying to keep them there so they will continue to vote for them. If they got better off financially, they might get educated enough to think with an open mind instead of their government check and that would doom the Democratic Party.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345481116000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:45:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345482098000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a time in our history, when cuts are necessary, tax laws need revamping, and also a time when we need to know our President's values regarding these issues. He would I believe give himself, and his money donors more of the the cake. He is a want to be, I've heard he dressed up as a Michigan Trooper in his youth. Even stoped people, a prankster you know. His daddy tried to get elected, he will try to out do him, just as I feel GWB did. Look what a mess we are in now. What will happen if we find a serious crime uncovered in his taxes after he is elected?</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1345482098000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:01:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345482216000-36</Id><Title>$36 ST Target?</Title><Msg>50 DMA, also would bottom out the RSI and the Fast Stochastics again. Nearly bottom bollinger band and the MACD would be more in line. Any thoughts?</Msg><Username>vwdiesel10</Username><Timestamp>1345482216000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:03:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345482265000-37</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just curious, rather than blast criticism toward Romney and name calling, why don't liberals tout the vast many accomplishments of your president? Just say'in. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1345482265000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:04:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345483436000-38</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What if we really find about Obama's trip to Pakistan? What if we find out the real deal with his house in Chicago and the crook that helped him buy it? What will happen if we find about how he got those scholarships to such nice universities while spending the last two years of his HS career smoking drugs and drinking beer? What if we find out he did apply as a foreign exchange student? What will happen if we find out he never renounced his Indonesian citizenship? Seems like a lot bigger risks in these than what you wonder about.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345483436000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:23:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345483571000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Question...Obama has been calling pastors of black churches to support his stand on gay marriage. Why doesn’t the MSM want to know if this violates the separation of church and state?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345483571000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:26:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345483664000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Having the Obama Presidency End</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345483664000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:27:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345483803000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama started his term with the Democrats in charge of both houses of Congress. He had all the power. As a professional 'organizer' one would think they could have organized this group to do most anything he wanted, when he wanted. It appears he wasted on his political capital on his health care wishes and after that couldn't organize a dog race. He has failed even at his chosen profession.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345483803000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:30:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345484002000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And I have read that Obama was not born in Hawaii. I have read that he is of a Middle Eastern religion. I have read that he went to Pakistan on a foreign passport. I have read that he and Pastor Wright are still close friends. Of course Tricky Ricky and Echo tell us all that these are just lies. Did you read your information in the same public media? What is your point?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345484002000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:33:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345484323000-43</Id><Topic><Title>$36 ST Target?</Title><Username>vwdiesel10</Username><Timestamp>1345482216000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think I will stay with my prediction of two weeks ago of $36.67 bottom. It hit $36.63 last Thursday but bounced back. I expect a double bottom near there before the rise continues.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1345484323000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:38:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345484664000-44</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, their attacks on Romney's taxes are a smoke screen for Obama's past? Nah. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1345484664000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:44:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345484825000-45</Id><Topic><Title>$36 ST Target?</Title><Username>vwdiesel10</Username><Timestamp>1345482216000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Okay, then long term what's your guess (into 2013 I mean), considering the possibility of div tax rates increasing? How much impact from that on this high-yielder?</Msg><Username>vwdiesel10</Username><Timestamp>1345484825000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:47:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345484953000-46</Id><Topic><Title>T may be up 28 % in 1 year BUT</Title><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1345465420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or you could buy November 35 puts for 60 cents and get rich if it drops to $30.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1345484953000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:49:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345485344000-47</Id><Topic><Title>$36 ST Target?</Title><Username>vwdiesel10</Username><Timestamp>1345482216000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My former prediction was for a top was $44 but, if Mitt doesn't reinstate the Bush tax cuts as soon as he takes office, I doubt that we will even see $40.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1345485344000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:55:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345488540000-48</Id><Topic><Title>$36 ST Target?</Title><Username>vwdiesel10</Username><Timestamp>1345482216000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can agree to that. Not sure why the gov't doesn't just pull a massive land sale/auction for mineral rights to make up some of the deficits for the tax breaks. Auction off 5-10 yr land rights, get the companies in there producing and hiring, building out infrastructure. It's "trickle down" but with actual employment.</Msg><Username>vwdiesel10</Username><Timestamp>1345488540000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345488633000-49</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You better hope we get the "Romney/Ryan types" or we are in serious trouble. See www.2016themovie.com to see what will happen if Obama is elected.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1345488633000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:50:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345489050000-50</Id><Topic><Title>$36 ST Target?</Title><Username>vwdiesel10</Username><Timestamp>1345482216000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you mind if I write your name in on my ballot for President? That is the best idea I have heard in a long time. Almost as good as my idea to pay all corporation employees half in stock and half in cash.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1345489050000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:57:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345490068000-51</Id><Title>re: - ask the twit about his taxes...</Title><Msg>... “Most of the voters on the right are wealthier than the left because they don’t pander to a voting bloc that doesn’t pay taxes, gets most of the food stamps, most of the welfare or are here illegally in the first place.” - jonwindandale You know, I can’t even begin to fathom WTF that asinine statement means. Okay, boys and girls, a lesson in Economics 101. If you don’t, I repeat, DO NOT “pander” to poor people, you WILL become rich. That’s how it works…simple as that. Read my lips…no new pandering. What exactly is “pandering” to someone, anyhow? And if we don’t know what pandering is, how do we NOT do it anymore? On the other hand, might we then assume that, rather than NOT pandering to poor people to become wealthy, if we pander to rich people, will we become poor? Is that how it works? Who do we have to “pander” to continue to be middle class? Ling-Ling or Hsing-Hsing? I had a friend who pandered poor people out of all their food stamps, cashed them in and opened an oriental restaurant, The Pander Buffet. It was very successful, and he became extremely wealthy, because he permitted no choices from column A and none from column B. For $12.95, you didn’t get any food except for a fortune cookie that said, “You’ve just been pandered by a demagogue.” “If they got better off financially, they might get educated enough to think with an open mind…” Oh, puleeeeese! The Republican party – the party of education? Sure. Uh, don’t you fools want to do away with the Department of Education and privatize the schools so you can assure only the wealthy get educated? Don’t you home school your kids in superstitious, anti-science mumbo-jumbo nonsense like creationism, while denying evolution, global warming, racial equality and anything based on empirical evidence? That’s really some “open mind.”</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1345490068000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:14:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345490528000-52</Id><Topic><Title>re: - ask the twit about his taxes...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1345490068000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:14:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, list all the major accomplishments of your messiah!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1345490528000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345492555000-53</Id><Topic><Title>re: - ask the twit about his taxes...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1345490068000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:14:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You know, I can’t even begin to fathom WTF that asinine statement means." I think you have stumbled onto something very basic among Democrats. They just don't have time to THINK!!! Forget Economics 101 and just think about the statement: "Most Republicans are wealthier than most Democrats because The Republican Party doesn't pander to a voting bloc that doesn’t pay taxes, gets most of the food stamps, most of the welfare or are here illegally in the first place.” Why is that so hard for you to understand??? You must know that is is Democratic policy to take from the rich and give to the poor in order to buy the votes of the poor.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1345492555000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:55:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345493898000-54</Id><Topic><Title>re: - ask the twit about his taxes...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1345490068000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:14:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My solution is to buy - (oil&amp; gas marketing) stocks and take from the rich, the poor and the middle class, that just about covers it.Look at- (vlo, tso, wnr, and alj).good luck!!!</Msg><Username>johncccxvi</Username><Timestamp>1345493898000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:18:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345494152000-55</Id><Title>bleed, bleed, bleed,...drift, drift, drift....</Title><Msg>I'm long but I've seen this before with other stocks- esp. after a big run like T has had. A stock drifting down everyday and nobody thinks it's a big deal. 10 cents here, 25 cents there, 65 cents on a bad day... before you know it you go from $38 to $32 a little teeny bit at a time. All of a sudden your down over 15% ($38 to $32). This has that ugly feeling to me. $37 has now been broken for the first time in quite a while. T never has good days anymore. Long term (5-10 years) I'm not too concerned, but short term I see some real pain.</Msg><Username>joejames40</Username><Timestamp>1345494152000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:22:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345494679000-56</Id><Topic><Title>Where is JOE ??</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1345476266000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:24:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.usmessageboard.com/politics/211220-feeding-animals-causes-dependency-46-million-americans-on-food-stamps-5.html</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1345494679000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:31:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345496029000-57</Id><Topic><Title>ceo pay</Title><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1344181027000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>26 Companies Paid CEOs &gt; They Paid in Taxes By Barry Ritholtz - August 18th, 2012, 12:00PM Astonishing assembly of data, from AP via the Daily Mail: “Twenty-six big US companies paid their CEOs more last year than they paid the federal government in tax, according to a study released Thursday by a liberal-leaning think tank. The study, by the Institute for Policy Studies, said the companies, including AT&amp;T, Boeing and Citigroup, paid their CEOs an average of $20.4 million last year while paying little or no federal tax on ample profits, according to regulatory filings. Astonishingly, nearly all of the the companies received a net tax refunds of up to $1billion. Others had a tax bill of $0. On average, the 26 companies generated net income of more than $1 billion in the US, the study said.” Taxes, why would we pay any stinking taxes . . . ? The Institute for Policy Studies lists these 26 companies that paid their CEOs more than they paid the federal government in taxes: Company CEO CEO pay Taxes Profits Abbott Laboratories Miles D White $19million $586million refund $4.73billion AMD Rory P Read $15.6million $3million refund $491million Altera John P Daane $29.6million $22million $771million AIG Robert Benmosche $14million $208million refund $17.8billion Anadarko Petroleum James T Hackett $19.5million $381million refund $2.65billion AT&amp;T Randall Stephenson $18.7million $420million refund $3.94billion Boeing James McNerney Jr $18.4million $605 refund $4.02billion Broadcom Scott A McGregor $16.1million $0 $927million Chesapeake Energy Aubrey McClendon $17.9million $13million $1.74billion Citigroup Vikram S Pandit $14.9million $144million refund $11.02billion Cooper Industries Kirk S Hachigian $21.1million $29million refund $828million Danaher H Lawrence Culp Jr $21.7million $6million refund $2.17billion Devon Energy John Richels $13.9million $143million refund $4.7billion FirstEnergy Anthony J Alexander $14.4million $243million refund $885million Ford Motors Alan Mulally $29.5million $4million refund $20.21billion Halliburton David J Lesar $15.8million $1.03billion refund $2.84billion International Paper John V Faraci $13.9million $78million refund $1.34billion Leucadia National Ian Cumming $28.2million $0 $68million Marathon Oil Clarence P Cazalot $29.9million $210million refund $2.95billion Marsh &amp; McLennan Brian Duperreault $14.3million $7million $993million Motorola Mobility Sanjay K Jha $47.2million $0 $249million loss Motorola Solutions Gregory Q Brown $29.3million $2million $1.16billion Newell Rubbermaid Michael B Polk $18.9million $37million refund $125million Salesforce.com Marc R Benioff $17.7million $9million $11million loss Travelers Companies Jay S Fishman $15.8million $176million refund $1.43billion Tyco International Edward D Breen $16.5million $4million refund $17.36billion Source: Revealed: The 26 ‘kingpin’ corporations that paid their CEOs more than they paid in taxes… and for most the public paid THEM a refund Associated Press, 10:05 EST, 16 August 2012 http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2189264/Institute-Policy-Studies-26-companies-paid-CEO-paid-taxes.html</Msg><Username>rdcn100</Username><Timestamp>1345496029000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:53:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345496526000-58</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is not the state. Obama is President. The Constitution states "Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion or prohibiting the free exercise thereof. . ." It does not in anyway prohibit the President from trying to convince people support his policies. I do not know why you would think it does. Presidents often use faith to motivate support. Oh well, another so-called patriot who does not understand his country. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1345496526000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:02:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345496710000-59</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You quoted the definition in the Constitution correctly. Good for you. Now if only the government practiced the law as written...</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345496710000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:05:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345497006000-60</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So-called patriot? I fought for this country. I have voted in every election presented to me for voting. I have volunteered with the Wounded Warriors organization. My brother fought and was wounded fighting for this country. A cousin that I grew up with died for this country. Stick your definition of patriotism where the son doesn't shine. I lost all respect for you and your opinions eon's ago. You are a blind, radical liberal and I am not sure even you understand why.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345497006000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:10:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345497192000-61</Id><Title>Apple up AT&amp;T down?</Title><Msg>Apple up AT&amp;T down? Yeah, that makes sense. Thats like Cars sales up and tires sales down</Msg><Username>hey_rob69</Username><Timestamp>1345497192000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:13:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345497807000-62</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My, my, what a surprise. I get your typical look in the rearview mirror response. Same old, same old backward looking, whose fault is it song and dance. You best be looking forward Easy. You're about to hit a bridge abutment. Yep, taxing the rich will help ever so slightly assuming even then the clowns don't spend it on a new wet dream. You have no assurance of that, do you? Furthermore, we need far, far more than a little financial help. Again, if you don't see that, you don't begin to understand the gravity of our financial mess. Right, go ahead and tax the rich, but you won't see but the slightest ding in the deficit. The good thing is it would shut up the far left for at least a day or two. Then, of course, they will have something else to carp about that won't solve a thing.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1345497807000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:23:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345498970000-63</Id><Title>re: where is joe...</Title><Msg>... jonwindandale lecturing on education... …”to pulled (sic) their kids out of the public schools and enroll them in private sch.” Sch????? What’s up with that? Did your pen run out of ink, mid-word? You can’t just make up abbreviations at your whim… Let’s see…sch? Private schizophrenia?...private schemes?...private schlock?…private schnappes?…private schadenfreude?… schlongs? Shomoes? Schmucks? Scholastics? Oh, schools. Now I’m with ya’! …”they'd have a better chances (sic)…” Your next sentence (about unions) isn’t even a sentence, but a fragment, having a noun, multiple adjective clauses, but no verb connected to the subject. “…becomming (sic) (we hope) great leaders “The practical ability to ‘reason’ is a result good parents (sic) and a good education ...for someones (sic) elses (sic) hard work !! I see. The irony of your perverted views on education is a testament to your cause. Tee Partyers Untie!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1345498970000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:42:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345500563000-64</Id><Topic><Title>re: where is joe...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1345498970000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:42:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UNBELIEVABLE THIEVERY Obama Daughters are Michelle's 'Senior Staffers' Michelle was caught cheating on her expense report. What a show of arrogance! This information was obtained by Judicial Watch March, 2012. The administration had to be sued to get this through the FREEDOM OF INFORMATION ACT. Michelle Obama listed daughters as 'Senior Staffers' to justify her expensive African vacation and safari. October 5, 2011, Judicial Watch said the U.S. Air Force provided a C-32 ( a Boeing 757 ), modified by the military for the purpose of flying big-wigs around the world, to fly the First Lady and her entourage to and from Africa , at a cost of $424,142. Another $928.44 was listed as ' bulk food' costs per meal for the 192 on board meals for the 21 people who made the trip. Lobster ain't cheap when you fly it around the world. The Obama daughters were listed on the manifest as senior staff. 'This trip was as much an opportunity for the Obama family to go on a safari as it was a trip to conduct government business,' said Judicial Watch President Tom Fitton. 'This junket wasted tax dollars and the resources of our over extended military. No wonder we had to sue to pry loose this information .' The nation is suffering with the economy sputtering, the national debt soaring and Obama's economic rescue policies not only failing, but actively making things worse. Meanwhile, the First Lady justifies an expensive trip to Africa to take a vacation and safari with her daughters by saying it's 'official business' and even going so far as to list her children as staffers. The level of arrogance and dishonesty on display here is nothing short of shocking. But, er, 'hope for change' and yes we can. It's a true story. Check out this link and read it yourself: http://www.judicialwatch.org/press-room/press-releases/judicial-watch-obtains-documents-detailing-the-cost-to-taxpayers-for-michelle-obama-s-family-trip-to-africa/</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1345500563000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345500785000-65</Id><Topic><Title>ceo pay</Title><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1344181027000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're getting paid to do a job, why do you think all excessive profit must go to you? It is the stockholder's money! Don't like it, start your own company!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1345500785000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:13:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345502422000-66</Id><Topic><Title>WE NEED HELP</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345326413000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 17:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jimmy, every person including yourself has a share of this new debt which equals $61,000 per person. Can't you do something before the US turns into the Roman Empire? Maybe it's too late but we have one more shot to prevent this from happening in Nov....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345502422000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:40:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345503750000-67</Id><Topic><Title>ceo pay</Title><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1344181027000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Don't like it, start your own company!" Exactly, and according to Obama all he needs to make it happen is Obama.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1345503750000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:02:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345509177000-68</Id><Title>Apple, Now There's A Joke! Can You Say 'Manipulation?'</Title><Msg>That's why I don't invest in the racket they've got going. What a joke. Are we expected to believe "the numbers" when even the SEC didn't detect Lehman's $50 BILLION money shift to the U.K. right under their noses just before the collapse that almost brought the world's economy down? Apple? C'mon, a joke. I think one day it will be discovered that Apple was losing money all this time. By who and when remains to be seen, imo.</Msg><Username>ifpigscouldfly269</Username><Timestamp>1345509177000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:32:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345509187000-69</Id><Title>re: separation of church and hate...</Title><Msg>... Once again, jon, you make absolutely no sense, whatsoever. WTF are you even talking about? Did you somehow smoke your dinner salad? “Separation of Church and State…this should settle any debate…” Who’s debating about separation of church and state? Jerry Falwell? Billy Graham? Pat Robertson? Bob Jones? Joel Osteen? Oral “Hygiene” Roberts? You’re suddenly suggesting that your Tea Party mentality is for separation of church and state. Sure they are…On the contrary – you think Secular Humanists are Disciples of the Devil. “Tea Party supporters are typically: white and unfriendly toward immigrants and blacks, as well as self reportingly ‘deeply religious.’ Tea Party supporters typically want religion in government. They approve of religious leaders engaging in politics and political leaders engaging in religion. Despite using the Constitution in their talk they have little or no sympathy for the Constitutional Principle of Separation of Church &amp; State.” (Putnam &amp; Campbell, American Grace) “…of anyone of this statute (sic) soliciting any Clergy…? Yes, Statute # 1704, Revised Code of Lunacy, states specifically, “Tea Party bloggers and sign painters must at all times demonstrate complete incompetence in spelling, sentence structure, grammar and any other outward signs of intellectual curiosity. Dressing funny and looking goofy is also recommended, but optional. Tee Partyers Untie</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1345509187000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345509571000-70</Id><Topic><Title>re: separation of church and hate...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1345509187000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:33:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... Oh, yeah, I forgot this. More real class: "We know that the 'Big MFIC" would exempt himself from any such decision due to his lacking !! - jon Have you sleezeballs really stooped so low as to refer to The President of the United States, as a Mother Focker? Have another shooter and continue to embarass yourself and your party.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1345509571000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:39:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345511054000-71</Id><Topic><Title>ceo pay</Title><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1344181027000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump..</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1345511054000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:04:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345520688000-72</Id><Topic><Title>re: separation of church and hate...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1345509187000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:33:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look echo get away or get a life or stop with your false trying to be a soldier that you are NOT !!! Your posts concerning our fallen reek of a want to be that could never be ....for you are a coward that has never been remotely involved with true combat...it is displayed with your sorry message describing the mortal wounds of a hero ....you dare pass yourself as a veteran...your messages suggest that you are the one that spat upon us in airports...bus stops ..etc. you are the coward that everyone feels so sorry for...yet rebukes for you are truly a sick sad sorry looser...laughable...that is you.</Msg><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1345520688000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 23:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>