<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354519616504-1</Id><Topic><Title>Say it ain't so. A dem wouldn't do this.</Title><Username>coulddobetter</Username><Timestamp>1354294434866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 11:53:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>deemed to be without merit in the 2012/2013 debt cycle</Msg><Username>coppershrt88</Username><Timestamp>1354519616504</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 02:26:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354545145324-2</Id><Topic><Title>your dividend will be gone next year!</Title><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1354205331328</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 11:08:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please! We have not even scratched the surface of mobil technology. T, VZ, &amp; VOD will be profitable for years to come. Keep buying during lows and re-investing divis in T and you will be fine!</Msg><Username>johnh834</Username><Timestamp>1354545145324</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 09:32:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354545795055-3</Id><Topic><Title>Say it ain't so. A dem wouldn't do this.</Title><Username>coulddobetter</Username><Timestamp>1354294434866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 11:53:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is two faced or forked-tongue about judging people on their merits rather than their wealth or class? Democrats don't think wealthy people are awful. We like, for instance, President Obama, Warren Buffet &amp; George Soros. Susan Rice's wealth has little interest to me. It is Republicans who label all wealthy people as job creators, and 47% of Americans as worthless freeloaders--based entirely on their income taxes in one particular year. "However it is NOT about "RACISM or GENDER BIAS" - GET A CLUE" Then why on earth is this poster talking about what Susan Rice "looks like"? Does she have some ink I'm not aware of?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354545795055</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 09:43:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354546024304-4</Id><Topic><Title>Norquist Popular With Lib. Democrats</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1354046450537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:00:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How does that equate to 'working' with people to find a common ground?" When the president makes concrete proposals, and then bends on them, and the only response he ever gets is it's a non-starter. That's how. Republicans need to realize they are in the minority, and have been for four election cycles. They don't get to set the agenda anymore.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354546024304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 09:47:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354547744676-5</Id><Topic><Title>T is one of top picks like crimson on apex</Title><Username>ethelvillarreal43</Username><Timestamp>1353943269318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:21:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice one!</Msg><Username>jacobvang488</Username><Timestamp>1354547744676</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 10:15:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354548979031-6</Id><Topic><Title>Will our Enemies Launch a Sneak Attack?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354332244349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Wish I had a bunker to hide in." On that, many agree with you</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1354548979031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 10:36:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354549563441-7</Id><Topic><Title>Will our Enemies Launch a Sneak Attack?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354332244349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Daughter of a bus driver I believe" You have a lot of brass to lie about a good man: You have the nerve to sit on a chair posting nonsense messages all day while Americans are out working. Quote: "Fraser was born on August 1, 1935 in Chicago, Illinois. He grew up there and married Marianne Shields who was also born in Chicago. They had two children, Craig and Michelle LaVaughn, who they raised on the southside of Chicago. Fraser was a pump worker for the City of Chicago. He tended the boilers at a water-filtration plant. On the 2008 campaign trail, we learned from both Barack and Michelle, that Mr. Robinson developed multiple sclerosis as a young man. In spite of having this disease, he continued working and according to Michelle, he hardly ever missed a day of work. Michelle told how she would see her father walk to work using two canes. Even though he had to sometimes struggle to get ready for work, he knew this was what he needed to do. Certain things just took a little longer for him. He was also active on the political front. Fraser Robinson was a Democratic Precinct Captain. Michelle and her brother, Craig looked up to their dad as their hero. They worked hard not to disappoint him. Both Fraser and Marianne valued hard work, independence, and honesty. They worked together to instill these values in their children. Craig tells the story of how he and Michelle ended up attending Princeton after they finished high school. Coming out of high school, Robinson was heavily recruited by both the University of Washington and Princeton. The former was offering a full ride, Princeton a financial-aid package that would leave his parents with a bill of $3,500 per year. "It might as well have been a million dollars," Robinson says. He told his father, Fraser Robinson, that he wanted to go to Washington. His father asked why, and Craig said he didn't want his parents to have to pay anything. The response prompted his father to drop his head, and shake it. "If you pick a school based on what I have to pay, I'll be very disappointed," Fraser Robinson told his son. Fraser Robinson suffered from multiple sclerosis, an affliction that did not stop him from going to work every day in Chicago's water department. He was a man that you desperately did not want to disappoint. Fraser Robinson's son wound up at Princeton, his parents funding it with cash from an insurance policy and a credit card.Says Craig now, "My father's decision changed my whole life. It changed all of our lives. If I hadn't gone to Princeton, my sister probably wouldn't have gone to Princeton and she never would've met Barack and none of this would've happened. All because of my father." ~ New York Daily News ~ 11-08-2008"</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1354549563441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 10:46:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354549846400-8</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet: cap gain 30%, 50% tax on the rich</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353097971771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I am aware of the philosophies of liberals like you that want the government to control everything, including your personal lives." I am aware you're nuts.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1354549846400</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 10:50:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354551327190-9</Id><Topic><Title>Will our Enemies Launch a Sneak Attack?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354332244349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So all this mess is all Craig's fault. I wonder if he feels guilty?</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1354551327190</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 11:15:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354551516754-10</Id><Topic><Title>Will our Enemies Launch a Sneak Attack?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354332244349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep and after watching several political shows Sunday and all the Democrats talking about how much the economy is improving and growing and then today we find out that the mfg. sector is in the tank and about equal to Nov. 2009. Yes sir, we are speeding right along, right along to the cliff regardless of what Congress does, but if they do the wrongs things, we just stomp on the accelerator.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1354551516754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 11:18:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354552070037-11</Id><Title>Cliff Jumping Companions</Title><Msg>Folks I would go over the cliff with: 1. A Kardashian girl 2. Scarlet Johanssen 3. Ashley Judd 4. Eva Longoria Well., you get the idea. If I have to go, it would be OK with jumping buddies like that</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354552070037</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 11:27:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354552335438-12</Id><Topic><Title>Say it ain't so. A dem wouldn't do this.</Title><Username>coulddobetter</Username><Timestamp>1354294434866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 11:53:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I heard more defense of Rice this weekend, that she only said what the intelligence community wrote for her to say and why is no one asking why the now disgraced ex-CIA Director allowed it to be passed on.. One point is that the intelligence community has consistently insisted that yes, they did write some talking points that would not give out confidential information, but that the changes that Rice used were not done by anyone in the intelligence community. So who did make the changes? They keep insisting that Rice had no personal knowledge of the situation so she couldn't have lied. If she had no knowledge, why was she the one sharing the information when the President and the SOS were both in town on that date? As McCain said, he has no problems with Rice being nominated for SOS because of her gender or color, but because he thinks she is not qualified for the job! There is no racism or gender bias in that comment, but he has been called a racist because he doesn't think she is qualified. Rice was purposely made sent out as the sacrificial lamb in case this went south and Obama is trying to reward her for accepting the job. She claims she was only saying what was thought to be the case, but if you listen to her presentation she clearly says, 'it is a fact' that this was a response to the video. She does not say, 'we believe' or 'current information indicates' or 'we think', she says 'it is a fact'. Someone lied. If she was just reading the sheet, we need to know who set her up and why. Alas, like with Fast and Furious, we may never know the truth because the administration wants this to go away and the MSM will help all they can.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1354552335438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 11:32:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354552605484-13</Id><Topic><Title>Say it ain't so. A dem wouldn't do this.</Title><Username>coulddobetter</Username><Timestamp>1354294434866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 11:53:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MoJust more deflection, it is not about her; let’s look at others from the past. What happened to moving forward, openness, and honesty in this administration? If she is nominated, it should be on her merits, her experience, and her back ground, not that of someone NOT nominated. Why is Obama fighting this so hard when she HASN'T been nominated for anything?</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1354552605484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 11:36:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354552972810-14</Id><Topic><Title>Norquist Popular With Lib. Democrats</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1354046450537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:00:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'This has been the Republican problem all along--they talk the talk but when it's time to get down to the business of making cuts, they don't walk the walk.' Then why don't the Democrats walk the walk, show some leadership, and propose the cuts? Are they too afraid to do anything when the economy is still tanking with an election just two years away? If the Democrats have the knowledge to solve the financial problems of the century, why aren't they taking the lead? Propose the fearful cuts and begin a negotiation over a final list, just claiming that they want stuff but it has to be our stuff is not showing leadership or negotiation, but an extreme dictatorial attitude. Harry Reid couldn't lead a parade of ants to a picnic let along the Senate. Even Little Timmy was waffling and saying they could get this done if the Republicans would just roll over and do what we want.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1354552972810</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 11:42:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354553004794-15</Id><Topic><Title>Say it ain't so. A dem wouldn't do this.</Title><Username>coulddobetter</Username><Timestamp>1354294434866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 11:53:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She does look like colin Powell</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1354553004794</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 11:43:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354553242475-16</Id><Topic><Title>Norquist Popular With Lib. Democrats</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1354046450537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:00:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And that pledge does not pass legislation. That is just an excuse the Democrats use to help the MSM make them the hero’s. The members of Congress pass the legislation. The members of Congress write (well their staff and lobbyist write) the bills proposed and passed. There has to be discussion and give and take to find a solution in order for there to be a negotiation. The Democrats are not negotiating. They are waiting for the axe to fall so they can point and scream 'see what the Republicans did' thinking then they can simply do as they please. Kind of like the smart, but biggest bully in the playground.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1354553242475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 11:47:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354553595579-17</Id><Topic><Title>Norquist Popular With Lib. Democrats</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1354046450537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:00:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When has Obama or Reid bent? You stated that neither side wants to make the cuts, so why won’t the President or his staff show the leadership they claim and propose the cuts required? The Democrats want more money in Washington to spend more. They are concerned with the debt or the deficit. They want more spending money in order to make the American people more and more dependent on the government for their daily lives. Most American's don't want that. They aren't smart enough to vote against that premise, but I don't believe that most Americans want to be dependent on Washington.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1354553595579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 11:53:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354553661731-18</Id><Topic><Title>Will our Enemies Launch a Sneak Attack?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354332244349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"with a bill of $3,500 per year" Who do you think you are fooling. It cost that much to go to a community college much less Pinceton. Moochelle lived in a upper middle class neighborhood, Have you seen pictures of the giganitic house she grew up in. She attended private schools only the wealthy could afford. She got accepted to Pinceton because of her brother she was too stupid to get in on her own.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1354553661731</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 11:54:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354554450835-19</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Senate Pounded by John Boehner</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1354240116860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:48:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Such rank arrogance without rationalization! What a pity!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1354554450835</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 12:07:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354554826997-20</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1354316145918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 17:55:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Before I go on with this short history, let me make a general observation – the test of a first-rate intelligence is the ability to hold two opposed ideas in the mind at the same time, and still retain the ability to function. One should, for example, be able to see that things are hopeless and yet be determined to make them otherwise. This philosophy fitted on to my early adult life, when I saw the improbable, the implausible, often the ‘impossible,’ come true…In a real dark night of the soul it is always three o'clock in the morning, day after day.” – F. Scott Fitzgerald I guess this disqualifies the members of Congress as possessing 'first-rate intelligence? “I’ve said consistently that no employer ever really accepts a union. They tolerate the unions. The very minute they can get a pool of unemployment they'll challenge the unions and try to get back what they call managements prerogatives, meaning hire, fire, pay what you want.” – Jimmy Hoffa Or as many free market economists might say, ‘pay what the market will demands’.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1354554826997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 12:13:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354556478414-21</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1354316145918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 17:55:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonder what 'ol Jimmy's up to these days?</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1354556478414</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 12:41:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354558546650-22</Id><Topic><Title>T is one of top picks like crimson on apex</Title><Username>ethelvillarreal43</Username><Timestamp>1353943269318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:21:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report</Msg><Username>millerrichard290</Username><Timestamp>1354558546650</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 13:15:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354564811569-23</Id><Topic><Title>AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD</Title><Username>powerball754</Username><Timestamp>1354286612981</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 09:43:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this really the AT&amp;T board? Could have fooled me! It's been hijacked by newsletter trolls and political spammers.</Msg><Username>catfisherman201</Username><Timestamp>1354564811569</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 15:00:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354574626303-24</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Senate Pounded by John Boehner</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1354240116860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:48:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bonmer is one goofy drunk kinda like a former prez called w.</Msg><Username>orri1934</Username><Timestamp>1354574626303</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 17:43:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354584290875-25</Id><Topic><Title>Will The MEDIA Grow "Kahuna's" ??</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1354567946217</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 15:52:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why Romney Lost: Romney said, "When I'm elected, I will put Americans back to work," and 51% said, "Screw That!!"</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1354584290875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 20:24:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354588387983-26</Id><Topic><Title>Will The MEDIA Grow "Kahuna's" ??</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1354567946217</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 15:52:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's a vast Left-Wing Conspiracy goin on and the Liberal Media is a Willing Participant in it!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1354588387983</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 21:33:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>