<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348468057109-1</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt has Super Energized his Base</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348016247399</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who wants a Mormon Bishop running this country? Google White Horse Prophecy, and you sure will vote against Romney.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1348468057109</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 02:27:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348469114940-2</Id><Topic><Title>Does Barry Believe in God?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347739167038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 15:59:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What, his neighbors at the zoo? From what I hear, robfisk and jon2retarted love to suck on a "Big Cuban".</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1348469114940</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 02:45:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348469447087-3</Id><Topic><Title>The Quote of the Decade:</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348404784971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 08:53:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How's the Prius, robfisk? Are you still the only black man in America driving one?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1348469447087</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 02:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348469572155-4</Id><Topic><Title>Dem Polls aren't what they Seem</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348445228622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:07:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The polls say your party is SCREWED! Thanks Mitt.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1348469572155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 02:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348486254769-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama appologizes to Mooslums but not Christians</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348333358469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“…you really ARE waisting (sic) your time scrutinizing my spelling &amp; grammar ... after all, I'm anomyous (sic) .. AND RETIRED…” – jonthehapless… …I may be wasting my time scrutinizing your spelling…but somebody’s got to do it… Obviously, you’re not! …You really are anomyous, whatever that is…and dumber than a Zamboni machine parked in the desert. As I said, you’re a mormon, minus the 2nd “m” (chuckles, giggles, drool, slobber, gag, aghhh…) BTW, what did you retire from? I’m guessing you weren’t an orthographist. “THX. for making my day ‘Echo’ “ That was the highlight of your day? On a gorgeous Fall afternoon? Wow, nice life. Why don’t you take winholder out for dinner at Chuck E. Cheese next Friday night? You guys are missing a lot.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348486254769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 07:30:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348487288053-6</Id><Topic><Title>The Quote of the Decade:</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348404784971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 08:53:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Little Red Hen’ (Modern Version) "Who will help me plant my wheat?" asked the little red hen. "Not I," said the cow. "Not I," said the duck. "Not I," said the pig. "Not I," said the goose. "Then I will do it by myself." She planted her crop and the wheat grew and ripened. "Who will help me reap my wheat?" asked the little red hen. "Not I," said the duck. "Out of my classification," said the pig. "I'd lose my seniority," said the cow. "I'd lose my unemployment compensation," said the goose. "Then I will do it by myself," said the little red hen, and so she did. "Who will help me bake the bread?" asked the little red hen. "That would be overtime for me," said the cow. "I'd lose my welfare benefits," said the duck. "I'm a dropout and never learned how," said the pig. "If I'm to be the only helper, that's discrimination," said the goose. "Then I will do it by myself," said the little red hen. She baked five loaves and held them up for all of her neighbors to see. They wanted some and, in fact, demanded a share but the little red hen said, "No, I shall eat all five loaves." "Excess profits!" cried the cow.. (Nancy Pelosi) "Capitalist leech!" screamed the duck. (Barbara Boxer) "I demand equal rights!" yelled the goose. (Jesse Jackson) The pig just grunted in disdain.. (Harry Reid) And they all painted 'Unfair!' picket signs and marched around and around the little red hen, shouting obscenities. When the farmer (Obama) came he said to the little red hen, "You must not be so greedy." "But I earned the bread," said the little red hen. "Exactly," said Barack the farmer. "That is what makes our free enterprise system so wonderful. Anyone in the barnyard can earn as much as he wants. But under our modern government regulations, the productive workers must divide the fruits of their labor with those who are lazy and idle." And they all lived happily ever after, including the little red hen, who smiled and clucked, "I am grateful, for now I truly understand." But her neighbors became quite disappointed in her. She never again baked bread because she joined the 'party' and got her bread free. And all the Democrats smiled. 'Fairness' had been established. Individual initiative had died but nobody noticed; perhaps no one cared so long as there was free bread that 'the rich' were paying for. And perhaps....this is the end................... And the next week, there was no bread, or anything else to eat. So, they all starved equally. EPILOGUE Bill Clinton is getting $12 million for his memoirs. Hillary got $8 million for hers. That's $20 million for the memories from two people, who for eight years repeatedly testified, under oath, that they couldn't remember anything. DO WE LIVE IN A GREAT BARNYARD OR WHAT?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348487288053</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 07:48:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348494786836-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obama appologizes to Mooslums but not Christians</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348333358469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's too cheap to take him to Chuck E. Cheese.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1348494786836</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:53:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348494954436-8</Id><Topic><Title>Dem Polls aren't what they Seem</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348445228622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:07:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now the Dems have started a rumor that Obama has a private pole that indicates he will lose in a landslide. The rumor continues that he is about to make an offer on a $35 million home in Hawaii. They even show pictures of the interior of the home. What will those Democrats think of next?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1348494954436</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348496660749-9</Id><Title>T at 3 Year high ........</Title><Msg>and the buying continues? The markets are all propped up right now this will play out in nov</Msg><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1348496660749</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:24:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348497215792-10</Id><Topic><Title>The Quote of the Decade:</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348404784971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 08:53:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"WMD's, WMD's, WMD's"</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1348497215792</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:33:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348497537357-11</Id><Title>NTWK $6.85...Up 3%......Breakout Alert!!......Hottest NASDAQ stock….Up every day since record earnings......Fundamentals can support $16 per analysts with $21 max target......In 2010 it went from $8 to $24 in 4 weeks with 50% lower revenues…..Cloud Division is growing exponentially.....Only 6 PE and 1 times sales is 30% of sector average......Strong 2013 guidance calls for over 30% revenue growth and $1/share net income due to strong global demand for its Legacy and Cloud software solutions</Title><Msg>Short-term Target: $16 per Upgrade………Take a look at incredible NTWK chart. In 2010 NTWK went from $8 to $24 in a few weeks. Today NTWK is a much stronger company with far more revenue sources including new Cloud Divisions. Unlike 2010, NTWK today has the flexibility to deliver reliable software products and services not only from Pakistan but also from excellence centers located in Bangkok, Beijing, the US, and the UK. The float today is 1/10 of what it was then and 2013 revenues are expected to breakaway into the mid $40 million for the first time in company history. During 2010 (and 2007) NTWK's market cap reached over $100 million on 50% lower revenues of what is projected for 2013. During the September 4Q CC NTWK officials stated that revenues are expected to reach $100 Million in 2015 up significantly from the $38 Million reported in 2012. They also expect margins to continue to go up as the high-margin Cloud divisions keep continuing exponentially to revenues. MUST READ ……This Week’s Analysts Comments on Upgrade: We project 13% annual growth to FY14 from FY10 reflecting 80 significant NFS legacy customers in FY14, up from 52, 37, and 28 in FY12, FY11, and FY10, respectively. The new Vroozi Cloud Division contributed $1.3 million in FY12. We expect at least $4 million in FY13 and $6 million to FY14 Our price target is based on the average forward 2013 P/E multiple of 13.2X (up from 12.8X in August 2012). NTWK is trading at 6.4X our FY13 projections. We are forecasting EPS of $0.85 per share. We applied an 11X multiple to our FY13 EPS forecast. We anticipate a richer multiple as earnings momentum builds in FY13. The company guidance calls for $1/share net income in 2013. NTWK is entering FY13 with a $25 million backlog and approximately $100 million in qualified leads. One quarter of the backlog is from four new NFS platform customer implementations that began in 4Q12. In August 2011, NetSol launched its Cloud Vroozi Division, an e-procurement search tool for SAP supplier relationship management (SRM) users. SAP AG is a global vendor of enterprise management systems that has the largest market share (24%) based on a worldwide Gartner survey. Vroozi should provide sales diversification and a higher margin recurring revenue stream. The Vroozi division contributed $1.3 million in FY12 sales and is expected to grow to $4 million in revenues in 2013 NTWK announced its 2nd Cloud Division last week offering an array of products and services to capture a greater % of the cloud applications in North America. The company is implementing this division using their significant software development capabilities and infrastructure. === MORE NTWWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Company projects Doubling/Tripling revenues and net income by 2015 - Significant Institutional investor ownership and growing - Insiders bought over 5% of the Outstanding shares the last 2 years and never sold a single share - Total share count is only 7.5 million shares. The float is only 3 million shares - Trading at forward PE of 5 - Strong balance sheet with $1.5/share cash - Has global agreement with Mercedes Benz - Already 7 countries with NTWK software for leasing and financing Mercedes Benz/Daimler including China, India, Japan, and others…and a few more coming in quarters/years ahead. - No.1 in China and APAC in leasing/financing software products and services. NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Volvo, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc. About NTWK: NetSol Technologies, Inc. ((NASDAQ: NTWK) is a worldwide provider of global IT and enterprise application solutions that include credit and finance portfolio management systems, SAP consulting and services, custom development, systems integration, and technical services for the global Financial, Leasing, Insurance, Energy, and Technology markets. Headquartered in Calabasas, Calif., NetSol's product and services offerings have achieved ISO 9001, ISO 20000, ISO 27001, and SEI (Software Engineering Institute) CMMI (Capability Maturity Model) Maturity Level 5 assessments, a distinction shared by only 178 companies worldwide. The company's clients include Fortune 500 manufacturers, global automakers, financial institutions, utilities, technology providers, and government agencies. NetSol has delivery and support locations in San Francisco, London, Beijing, Bangkok, Lahore, Adelaide, Rio de Janeiro, and Riyadh</Msg><Username>d.malkkey</Username><Timestamp>1348497537357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:38:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348498226274-12</Id><Topic><Title>The Quote of the Decade:</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348404784971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 08:53:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ask the Kurdish people.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1348498226274</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348498549204-13</Id><Topic><Title>The Quote of the Decade:</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348404784971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 08:53:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ask the families of the KIA (Iraq) .</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1348498549204</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:55:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348500933502-14</Id><Topic><Title>The Quote of the Decade:</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348404784971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 08:53:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 2006 during a booming economy, the massive increase in deficit spending by Republicans was ludicrous. Most of that deficit financed wars and tax cuts for the wealthy--the economic equivalent of sugar. Well, now we've had our crash. Obama has ended one war and is winding down the other. Obama is trying to end the tax breaks for the wealthy. He is trying to rebuild an economy and a country that was collapsed by Republicans by investing in our future. Romney wants to give the wealthy even more tax breaks, and possibly more wars, while cutting investments in our future. Is this a recipe for rebuilding our economy and country? Is this a recipe for cutting deficits? More sugar doesn't fix a crash. We need to slowly and intelligent rebuild our economic foundation. That is what Obama offers.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348500933502</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348501347401-15</Id><Topic><Title>Dem Polls aren't what they Seem</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348445228622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:07:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the best poll analysis, read the 538 blog from the NYT. Just search "538".</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348501347401</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:42:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348501810681-16</Id><Topic><Title>Obama appologizes to Mooslums but not Christians</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348333358469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is not an excuse for the violent response, but it is understandable that a minority of people in some countries which have little exposure to democracy or free media would need to have the concept explained to them. They may benefit from being advised that every time some #$%$ posts something on YouTube, it is not a reflection of America or its values. The president is wise to provide this education. Your ignorance, however, is not understandable. No further education on the matter will benefit you. Or winholder. Or jon.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348501810681</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:50:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348501958914-17</Id><Title>same old story...</Title><Msg>giving everything back yet AGAIN (so predictable).</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1348501958914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:52:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348502960074-18</Id><Topic><Title>The Quote of the Decade:</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348404784971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 08:53:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of mindless, robfisk you fit the definition to a T.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1348502960074</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:09:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348506577570-19</Id><Title>UALL BACK IN</Title><Msg>Chains no but obama will put you in the poor house. With the increse in taxes plus high gas and high food cost,</Msg><Username>scotthuc</Username><Timestamp>1348506577570</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348507154641-20</Id><Title>Campaigns and Dow</Title><Msg>Is there a correlation between campaigns and the Dow? Jan 1, 2007 Dow = 12,398 (Rep Pres, Dem House and Senate) Dec 24, 2007 Dow = 13,365 (Start of Rep caused recession per MSM and Dems) Jul 28, 2008 Dow = 11,326 (Rep and Dem identified) Sep 8, 2008 Dow = 11,421 (Rep and Dem poll numbers equal) Nov 17, 2008 Dow = 8046 (Dems win House, Senate and POTUS) Jan 26,2009 Dow = 8000 (Dems in charge House, Senate and POTUS) Mar 2, 2009 Dow = 6626 (Dems in charge House, Senate and POTUS) Dec 28, 2009 Dow = 10,428 (End of first year with Dems in charge) Nov 15, 2010 Dow = 11,203 (Rep reclaim House) Dec 26,2011 Dow = 112,217 (End of first year with Rep House) Aug 13, 2012 Dow = 13,275 (Rep and Dem about same in polls) Sep 20, 2012 Dow = 13,596 (Rep and Dem about same in polls) Sep 24, 2012 Dow = 13,554 (Edge to Dem per polls) Based upon the above should a prudent investor make investment choices using campaign polls and outcomes as a factor.</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1348507154641</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:19:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348507574719-21</Id><Topic><Title>T at 3 Year high ........</Title><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1348496660749</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:24:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>loving this stock!!</Msg><Username>bhaley36</Username><Timestamp>1348507574719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348507581809-22</Id><Topic><Title>T at 3 Year high ........</Title><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1348496660749</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:24:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>loving this stock!!</Msg><Username>bhaley36</Username><Timestamp>1348507581809</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348509020605-23</Id><Topic><Title>The Quote of the Decade:</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348404784971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 08:53:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just pay for your stuff, that's what Fake tRicky always says!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348509020605</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:50:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348509069501-24</Id><Topic><Title>The Quote of the Decade:</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348404784971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 08:53:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW! That's the first time you mentioned T on this board!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348509069501</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348509155882-25</Id><Topic><Title>T at 3 Year high ........</Title><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1348496660749</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:24:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So am I !!!</Msg><Username>popndrop</Username><Timestamp>1348509155882</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:52:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348509195395-26</Id><Title>Cheapest oil stock on NYSE, TXS is ....</Title><Msg>CHEAPEST OIL STOCK, highest risk reward is LPR..... currently 1.63, NAV of more then $9 risk reward of 500% Evi Resource Opportunity Overlooked: We feel the focus on Q1 operational issues and near term guidance changes has masked progress on drilling density at Evi. Operated activity was focused on the northern block of Evi during Q1, where LPR drilled eight wells in a single section. All eight wells are now on stream and initial rates indicate no signs of interference between wells. LPR has regulatory approval for up to 16 wells per section in certain sections at Evi and has plans to initiate a pilot of up to 12 wells per section in H2. Notwithstanding certain step-out wells that did not perform as expected, we believe LPR ultimately has the opportunity to double its current 500 well location inventory and surface up to ~$9/share. As well managements guidance For second half of 2012 was for 90$ wit with a differential of 12 meaning they only expected to receive 78$ a barrel for oil vs. The 100$ we are getting today. Wti at 92 Edmonton par wit premium of 7.50$ That is a big deal especially when oil accounts for 70% of rev. At current cap ex and prices we will be fc positive in q3 with 1 rig in evi, I suspect we will add back the second one and ramp up into 2013.....and if we sell off some ng acreage, then add more evi......look out ....this stock came public at the wrong time and forest shouldn't have dividended out the ownership....there is no short interest, no interest, completely unknown which is great for us in at these vast discounts. Time will reprice. The oil is flowing. Liquidity secure with over a 100 million available and that to will expand as banks use higher price decks. No worries on a possible winfall tax from US govt should and when oils spikes. Land in NWT more productive then Barnett Shale, once Ng recoveries LPR is a ATM, spitting out cash. See my research on board. :o)</Msg><Username>jimjones62</Username><Timestamp>1348509195395</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:53:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348511441029-27</Id><Topic><Title>The Quote of the Decade:</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348404784971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 08:53:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. Pay for your stuff. Even the tea partiers are backing away from the cuts they demanded--but still want lower taxes for the wealthiest 1% of Americans. Good economic policy isn't difficult. Invest early &amp; wisely and pay for your stuff.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348511441029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348511581023-28</Id><Topic><Title>Obama appologizes to Mooslums but not Christians</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348333358469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently five letters is his limit.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348511581023</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:33:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348513283520-29</Id><Title>52-week high</Title><Msg>Looks ready to break 52-week high of $38.58. (see stoxline website)</Msg><Username>opfment</Username><Timestamp>1348513283520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:01:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348513478568-30</Id><Topic><Title>The Quote of the Decade:</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348404784971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 08:53:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, fake Ricky, how much lower should Oprah's tax rate be to get rid of the deficit?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348513478568</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348513991554-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obama appologizes to Mooslums but not Christians</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348333358469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are laughing. Not with you. At you. Man you're an idiot.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348513991554</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:13:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348521801670-32</Id><Title>cwa accepts mobility deal without locals input</Title><Msg>unbelievable....the cwa national has agreed on a new contract for its at+t mobility people with att without even allowing the union locals to have any say at all.....thats right they took it upon themselves to work out a deal with at+t without any input from its locals nationwide.....our local is telling its mobility members to vote NO.......the cwa has to be the worst union to be a member in....</Msg><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1348521801670</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:23:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348522169034-33</Id><Topic><Title>cwa accepts mobility deal without locals input</Title><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1348521801670</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:23:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like you really had a say!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348522169034</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:29:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348523541501-34</Id><Topic><Title>cwa accepts mobility deal without locals input</Title><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1348521801670</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:23:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya think? And CWA has no problem taking yer money and supporting the DNC.</Msg><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1348523541501</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:52:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348523822920-35</Id><Topic><Title>cwa accepts mobility deal without locals input</Title><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1348521801670</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:23:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It seems you never win!</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1348523822920</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348530190063-36</Id><Topic><Title>cwa accepts mobility deal without locals input</Title><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1348521801670</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:23:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like I said awhile back, C.W.A. Company Wins Again.</Msg><Username>tip_ring_sleve</Username><Timestamp>1348530190063</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348532458082-37</Id><Topic><Title>cwa accepts mobility deal without locals input</Title><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1348521801670</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:23:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I could recite many double dealings CWA did with it's members going back to the 60's and Beirne's rule. I would suggest that instead of voting that a fund be raised and sue the daylights out of them. If local leadership won't go along with it then kick them out.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348532458082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 20:20:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348534534336-38</Id><Topic><Title>Detained for paying by cash at FL toll booth</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1348509904633</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:05:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've been to Florida many times. I'm always amazed that I almost never see patrol cars. The first time in Miami, I saw a guy get shot. I've witnessed drivers with their tinted windows drive at well over a 100 mph. But, my last time there I saw a take down team, six patrol cars driving very fast on the expressway, with no lights, or sirens. It was quite apparent, they were going to visit someone, around 2:30 in the morning, and wanted a show of force. Maybe the majority are in plain clothes. Someone once said, they don't rely on Police. Everyone is armed, and take care of things on their own. Quite an interesting state.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348534534336</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 20:55:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348534849555-39</Id><Topic><Title>Dem Polls aren't what they Seem</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348445228622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:07:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They say cause of early voting, almost 35% of voters have weighed by Election Day. They should provide a total to date. But, that might surpress turnout</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348534849555</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:00:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348536427588-40</Id><Title>UN Small Arms Treaty hangs in Election Balance.</Title><Msg>Barrack's plan to essentially change America, should be taken very seriously. Look around you, we have open borders, in a welfare state. The Police in many areas of the country don't even show up, if they do it's just to take a report.. Criminal gangs operate with immunity. In many cases the criminals, many being illegal are given breaks, that manys Brothers could only dream of. Their Bosses tell them leave illegals alone, the Dems need their votes. So please, get involved. As Mark Levin said tonight, if everyone just contacted 5 people, in there circle of contacts, we'd win in an landslide. So please, it's overused, but this really is true. This is the most important election, you'll ever vote in. Don't forget what the Founders did for you. They are watching, and hoping that the US, does,'t fall victim the Barrack's #$%$ It's not like this man took over, without telling you what his plans are. Regime change is just weeks away!</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348536427588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:27:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348538818282-41</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what do you say now that BO was caught lying and was forced to admit this attack was not about any movie? He failed the embassy people and it cost them their lives</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348538818282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:06:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348539260045-42</Id><Topic><Title>UN Small Arms Treaty hangs in Election Balance.</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348536427588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:27:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Regime change is just weeks away!" Try again in 2016, jon2retard.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1348539260045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:14:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348539661821-43</Id><Topic><Title>Christians fight HHS mandate</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347728733761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 13:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Saturday, September 29, 2012 •3:30 P.M. Pre-event rally, worship and prayer vigil. This rally will include national leaders and speakers and will be a preparation for the event which will begin at 5:00 p.m.. •5:00 P.M. ActsFive29 officially begins! What a powerful and prophetic way to begin the event: People will walk over to the White House and risk arrest, speaking a prophetic word to President Obama and our elected officials that we will “obey God rather than man” and “we will not comply” with any mandate or law which forces us to violate our conscience and our core faith beliefs and values. This will begin a 72 hour vigil of prayer, public witness and arrests at the White House. From this point on, there will be a continual presence at the White House. Sunday, September 30, 2012 •10:00 A.M. Sunday Morning Worship and Prayer service at Lafayette Park across from the White House. •12:00 P.M. Praying the Rosary with Fr. Frank Pavone, the National Director of Priests for Life. •1:30-3:30 P.M. Stand Up for Religious Freedom Rally with nationally known speakers. *Important: If you can only make one event, the afternoon rally and prayer service in front of the White House is the one!* •4:00 P.M. Corporate prayer, public witness and group arrest in front of the White House. Monday, October 1, 2012 •12:00 P.M. Corporate prayer, public witness and group arrest in front of the White House. •6:00 P.M. Praying the Rosary. •7:00 P.M. Evening rally and prayer with national leaders and speakers. Tuesday, October 2, 2012 •12:00 P.M. Corporate prayer, public witness and group arrest in front of the White House. •5:00 P.M. Final evening rally and prayer with national leaders and speakers.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348539661821</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:21:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>