<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346569954000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Feinstein Complains Gas Too High?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346201792000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey rob, the only black man with a Prius, how's your fuel mileage?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1346569954000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 03:12:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346570165000-2</Id><Topic><Title>European Social Programs &amp; Ours</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346535423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:37:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More right wing BS. You guys use the same old lying talking points, like Bishop Robme and Lyin Ryan.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1346570165000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 03:16:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346570310000-3</Id><Topic><Title>California's Brown to Ok Illegals &amp; Cars</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346534860000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:27:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey rob, any of those blacks your ancestors?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1346570310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 03:18:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346578990000-4</Id><Title>The Socialist Party endorses President Obama</Title><Msg>The announcement of their endorsement of Obama was in Aug 2011 so it wouldn't be front page news and an embarrassment to Obama if announced near the 2012 election. So I figured I would pitch in a little help to report the link to the article. http://www.examiner.com/article/socialist-party-endorses-president-obama</Msg><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1346578990000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 05:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346589683000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan`s Black college sweetheart</Title><Username>lavenderisin2</Username><Timestamp>1346561056000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:44:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lavander, I think you are about the dumbest person I have ever read. Get help or at least be quiet.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1346589683000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:41:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346589688000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... "Romney did not need the money so the (sic) donated it." Right, some to a church, and some to his children. Hey, it's wonderful hearing facts from some do#chebag faking someone else's alias on an inheritance stock message board. I'm sure everyone here believes you. I have a better idea, however. How about we look at the Obamas' tax returns, which are available, and we look at the Romney's, which are not. How you people can defend that is completely beyond me. How you fools can even consider voting for a guy who is obviously hiding how he's lived his life and who he will be looking out for if elected is mind boggling. You are being duped by very wealthy people who want to maintain the status quo and blame it on the middle class and the poor. Claiming birther nonsense, while running a candidate who wants to perpetuate a system rigged in favor of the one percenters is pathetic. I debate this stuff on a regular basis, with friends who benefit from this. They, at least, acknowledge that they are out for themselves. Little creeps like you spending all day doing their work for them through lies and deceit is reprehensible and pitiful.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346589688000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:41:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346590425000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... "He is completetly leftist in his thinking and politics!Why would anybody believe he would he would accept any moderate view?s" "Expand the Earned Income Tax Credit — a wage supplement for lower-income people" Looking out for the less fortunate is "leftist"???? "higher marginal income tax on the top five percent" That's leftist? "invest in education for lower income communities" Wanting to improve the lives of all citizens in a country is leftist?" "Reich is pro-union, saying 'Unionization is not just good for workers in unions, unionization is very, very important for the economy overall, and would create broad benefits for the United States'." Being pro-union is also "leftist"? I'm pretty sure that you are about to find out that the majority of Americans don't agree with you and, conversely, would consider you (although they aren't out throwing around buzz words like this) to be a "rightist". (wrongish, but nonetheless, rightist.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346590425000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:53:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346594074000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SUNDAY NIGHT - VERY IMPORTANT. This Coming Sunday -- Set Your DVR for the Fox News channel at 9:00 PM . Maybe this is why the White House has been discounting FOX. Sounds like this could be history in the making someone may go down - either Obama or Fox News. It may be that Fox has been holding this information back due to the sensitivity of it and out of courtesy. But, Obama has taken on Fox and it appears they are ready to spill the ugly beans of truth about the background of this individual who has had an extremely radical past. This Sunday, Fox News is going to air a very important documentary about Barack Obama, Sunday night at 9 P.M. Eastern. The report will go back to Obama's earlier days, showing even then his close ties to radical Marxist professors, friends, spiritual advisers, etc. It will also reveal details about his ties to Rev. Wright for 20+ years, i.e., how he was participating with this man, and not for the reasons he stated. The report has uncovered more of Obama's radical past and we will see things that no one in the media is willing to put out there. It will be a segment to remember. Mark your calendar and pass this on to everyone you know: Sunday night, 8 PM CT; 9 PM ET. Democrat or Republican, this report will open your eyes to how YOUR country is being sold down the road to Totalitarian Socialism. If you care about the direction of our country, pass this notice on to everyone you know.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346594074000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 09:54:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346595107000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What will you do if Obama is defeated? There is a good chance that he may be. And, pro union is leftist in my opinion. It doesn't make me a 'hater' or a 'neanderthal'. I am just a person who does not value 'unions'. I helped defeat them when they tried to organize my industry (computer technology) and did not see how it hurt us. There must be a reason that there are so very few private industry unions left.</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1346595107000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:11:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346597355000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Simply put; Obama's version of Hillary's 'it takes a village'. Yes, we all understand that we are a nation, not simply a group of individuals. We are also not a group of mindless drones that believe we can’t do anything without the able assistance of the government. Things like roads, fire departments, police services, armed forces to protect the nation are things the government is chartered to provide. Jobs, food, using your brain for more that separating your ears, raising our children, etc. are not things the government provides. We need government for certain things. Those things used to be clearly understood and segregated in our lives. Obama wants the government to control too many facets of our lives. He wants to control what we do, how we should thinks, our individual resources. He is pushing government to overstep its charger and boundaries. Yes, if I built the next greatest mouse trap, I wouldn’t be able to sell them if there weren’t roads to get to my shop, but I also paid to have the government build those same roads. They didn’t do it on their own. There weren’t built with ‘government’ money, they were built with OUR money. Money the government took for all those that had shops to sell products, factories to build those products and jobs for people to have the resources to buy those products. While he is correct that we didn’t do everything alone, we also didn’t do just because of the government. He insulted a great many business people and now he is trying to walk it back. He is an insulting person.</Msg><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1346597355000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346597438000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder if Andrea Mitchell and Chuck Todd will be as condescending and biased next week as they were this past week?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1346597438000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:50:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346597727000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congress is a failure that neither candidate can fix. http://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/EW5IdwltaAc?rel=0</Msg><Username>texlec</Username><Timestamp>1346597727000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:55:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346598118000-13</Id><Topic><Title>European Social Programs &amp; Ours</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346535423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:37:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The insurance companies love Obamacare. Now there will be no uninsured, everyone will be a customer of health insurance. This should cut their marketing expenses and drive profits even higher. Why do you think they kicked in $150M to help him advertise it?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1346598118000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:01:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346598237000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Feinstein Complains Gas Too High?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346201792000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe she should just shut up. Period, end of sentence. That is all she really needs to do. This lady is dumber than Nut Job Nancy and if possible even more corrupt.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1346598237000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:03:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346598348000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Feinstein Complains Gas Too High?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346201792000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He now understands that his political career is over (he is a bit of a slow learner) and he has all the money he needs. There is no more need for him to hold himself out to ridicule.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1346598348000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:05:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346598412000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Feinstein Complains Gas Too High?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346201792000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They pay roughly the same price for the basic fuel that we do. What planet are you living on?</Msg><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1346598412000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346598876000-17</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346210905000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 23:28:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To Obama his father, the drunk, child deserting, bigamist, socialist is a God and he views himself in the same terms.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1346598876000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:14:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346599504000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But you no longer hear the MSM telling of the Governor and the Mayor refusing to do things in a timely manner or not allowing Bush to federalize the local National Guard to help out. You no longer read about the buses that the Mayor refused to use or allow to be used or the corrupt police department that all but deserted the folks in their hometown. You no longer read much about the government funds sent to enhance the flood protection facilities over twenty or thirty years that were diverted by the state and local governments either. Ever wonder why?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1346599504000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346599917000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The day the Democrats decided to make a no nothing, unproven a$$-clown their candidate. The day the majority of the black people in this country got stupid and voted for a Presidential candidate based on his color, not his character. The day Obama was sworn in was the day of their crowning glory of their collective stupidity.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1346599917000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346600596000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was very, very slow to react. I know he had an excuse. He did not want to upset the children. Poor excuse, all he had to say was Excuse me children. Something very important, has happened, I must go to help.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346600596000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:43:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346601129000-21</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346210905000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 23:28:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why, does the have to affect the offspring of a person. Any person. You are putting in a arstocratic ideal for success, just what my decendant left Germany to escape. They were part of a feudal system. Even Mitt Romney said he wanted to get away from the car business, for then people could say his father was CEO of American Motors. He say he wanted to be his own man. So he went to Harvard got a law degree, and MBA, I believe.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346601129000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:52:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346601609000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Feinstein Complains Gas Too High?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346201792000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get smart, and I am not talking about the show.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346601609000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:00:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346601949000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Feinstein Complains Gas Too High?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346201792000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.vtpi.org/tdm/tdm17.htm Here is a link that will inform you. It is the vertical graph blue shows fuel costs. I have a brother in law like you. He told me America buys in volume, and that is why our fuel prices are lower.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346601949000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:05:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346602309000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Reagan_administration_scandals In case you think that Republicans never do anything wrong- Here is one example.</Msg><Username>eseyfried</Username><Timestamp>1346602309000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:11:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346602602000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Be Leery!</Title><Username>florida_gabriela1</Username><Timestamp>1346588214000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:16:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are increasing fixed expenses.</Msg><Username>vergie_jayne14</Username><Timestamp>1346602602000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:16:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346603132000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you serious? I can recall that Clinton authorized the bombing of an area in which he was told that Bin Laden was situated and he was bashed by the Republicans who said that he was just trying to deflect people away from the "important" issue of Monica etc. Also Clinton put together a bi-partisan commission who finished their work at the start of the year that G.W. Bush became President and they presented him with their suggestion on how to protect our country from a terrorist. G.W. Bush completely ignored their suggestions. In addition G.W. Bush had gotten word that the terrorists were planning an attack against us but he never alerted us. Clinton had always alerted us when he got word of a potential terrorist attack against us and they couldn't pull it off. I read that there were two possible attacks that we know were prevented. G.W. Bush said that he didn't alert us because "who would have thought that they would attack us on our soil".</Msg><Username>eseyfried</Username><Timestamp>1346603132000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:25:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346604004000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry, Esey...the DNC is rolling out ole Bill to try and help Obama win again! You can swoon for him all over again!</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1346604004000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:40:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346604579000-28</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346210905000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 23:28:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;If it would cost the remainder of society money, I would vote for abortion This says it all, pretty sick, you value money over human life. You share the same point view about abortion as the athiests who post on this MB. &gt;&gt;&gt;I am a pragmatic Christian This sounds like a fancy term for an atheist &gt;&gt;&gt;I am not afraid of death Two types of people don't fear death, atheists and those with a strong Christian faith. You may be able to quote bible verses but we know who you are</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346604579000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:49:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346608319000-29</Id><Topic><Title>California's Brown to Ok Illegals &amp; Cars</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346534860000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:27:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not,much factual in your statement.</Msg><Username>floridabeachie</Username><Timestamp>1346608319000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 13:51:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346608470000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan`s Black college sweetheart</Title><Username>lavenderisin2</Username><Timestamp>1346561056000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:44:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not m.uch factual here either, reported , I heard. Well I here a mouse scream, I believe he said do not vote GOP. Or, maybe it was the sound when I stepped on him.</Msg><Username>floridabeachie</Username><Timestamp>1346608470000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 13:54:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346608562000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Feinstein Complains Gas Too High?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346201792000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My sister-in-law lives in Chicago. She has buyers remorse. Being a single women with a child, she bought into Barry's spiel. Now she curses, everytime I mention gas, and THE ONE'S name. Barry Husein Obama. She has to use hi-test in her very expensive BMW.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346608562000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 13:56:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346608594000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry cisco that it bothers you, but Clinton was a very good President.</Msg><Username>eseyfried</Username><Timestamp>1346608594000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 13:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346609236000-33</Id><Topic><Title>European Social Programs &amp; Ours</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346535423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:37:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, don't forget AARP. They have a mint invested in the re-election of Obama. They will make a ton off of seniors, once they really find out what Barry has done to medicare, in order to get illegal aliens health care. Barry's math just doesn't add up. How can you cut $800 BILLION from seniors, and not harm their healthcare. Heavy medication, pain pills will be their main treatment in Barry's 2nd term. I hope old folks don't fall for Barry's fuzzy math.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346609236000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:07:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346609493000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It doesn't bother me at all. You were always a one trick pony and at your age, you will never change!</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1346609493000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346609932000-35</Id><Topic><Title>The Socialist Party endorses President Obama</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1346578990000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 05:43:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent. The Republicans, Tea Party, or some other Conservative group should run a commercial, about those who are in favor of an Obama 2nd term. Why anyone with a half a brain would ever vote for this guy again is a mystery to me, somehow they say this race is close. It would read like a who's who of people, or groups who would like to see America fall by the way side. This is just a short list off of the top of my head. The American Socialist, and Communist Parties. Care, the !slamic organization, Move on.org, La Raza (the Hispanic Takeover Group),and may other bad groups, intent on doing harm to us as a Nation. Regime change is just weeks away.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346609932000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:18:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346611215000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Plus they are exempt from ObamaCare! A sweetheart deal that stiffs the middle class! http://www.nypost.com/p/news/national/unions_get_pecial_treatment_in_health_AB053CwqPIJlIxXAm37DOM</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346611215000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:40:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346611723000-37</Id><Topic><Title>The Socialist Party endorses President Obama</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1346578990000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 05:43:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, my God that really scares me! OF COURSE THAT WAS THE WHOLE POINT RIGHT!</Msg><Username>floridabeachie</Username><Timestamp>1346611723000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:48:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346612211000-38</Id><Title>Rising Oceans in the World</Title><Msg>I live in paradise, Florida. Most of Florida's prime beachfronts, and costal cities will be the first affected by this. Florida Light and Power has been very progressive on solar power. In fact next monthe they will be having a promotion, I plan on checking this out. Romney made's light of this just like the Bush carbon, oil money story tellers did. It seems to me we have unlimited access to the Sun, water pow- er, wave, or tidal power, lets make use of them. Also AT&amp;T even if they sandbag their buildings, and towers will have few people left here as the Ocean continues to rise. Let's get involved, call your local representatives, and vote Obama.</Msg><Username>floridabeachie</Username><Timestamp>1346612211000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:56:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346617773000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You just had to mention Slick Willy, didn't you? Now we will hear for a week about what a great President Easy thinks this disbarred, lying, sex abuser was.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1346617773000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 16:29:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346618086000-40</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346210905000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 23:28:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No you incoherent twit, it means he has stated he loved his fathers ideology; he loved his father even though he only saw him once he can recall. These, per his own words are dreams FROM his father, not of his father and he embraces them. Genetics have little to do with it; it is acceptance and embracement of his father’s ideals that are frightening.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1346618086000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 16:34:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346622659000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fake Ricky, I didn't drag Bush into anything. Someone wondered why Bush was viewed badly for his handling of Katrina, and why Obama wasn't following Isaac. I explained it and it is pretty simple. Bush was viewed badly because he handled Katrina badly. Obama was not viewed badly because he handled Isaac well--as he does most things. William J. Jefferson has nothing to do with either president's response to a hurricane and his criminal acts are his own. Like I said, you have nothing else to say on the matter so you just go on random Democrat attack. Well, I can pull out random Republicans. But Bush' poor handling of Katrina is the only relevant one here.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346622659000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 17:50:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346622796000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blame Clinton?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346622796000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 17:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346622904000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;Ever wonder why? Because most people don't believe email forwards or Paul Ryan.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346622904000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 17:55:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346623199000-44</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All you have to do is look at the fiscal situation when Clinton left to know he was a good president. Then compare it to the situation when Bush left.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346623199000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 17:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346623370000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;2012 White House Revision: The White House revision is "give a man a fishing pole". . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346623370000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:02:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346623604000-46</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? You're going to try to argue that Romney had a rough upbringing, and the Obama's were born with silver spoons? Did Paul Ryan tell you that? But hey, why not. Like Clint, you create an imaginary Obama. May as well make up an imaginary Romney.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346623604000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:06:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346623701000-47</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your man is going down. Will you lose your shill job when that occurs?</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1346623701000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:08:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346624156000-48</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;Why would anybody believe he would he would accept any moderate view? That is a moderate view. What is immoderate about supporting a limited safety net and wanting to pay for it? What is immoderate about expanding the EITC (Something Bush did, btw)? What is immoderate about supporting education? What is immoderate about supporting unions (about 12% of American workers are IN unions, a higher number support them)? What is immoderate about wanting extremely wealthy people to pay a tax rate similar to working people. According to you, 99% of Americans are extremist. I'm sure you think you're a moderate, but you are incorrect. You are the extremist. And the fact that you list these moderate views as "extreme", and think people will buy it, indicates you are blinded by that extremism.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346624156000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346624471000-49</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah. Set the DVR. Watch The Family Guy. I'm beginning to think you *are* Paul Ryan, fake ricky. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346624471000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346624583000-50</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;It doesn't make me a 'hater' or a 'neanderthal'. No it doesn't. But supporting unions does not make Reich an extremist. It makes him the left-leaning moderate he is.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346624583000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:23:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346625154000-51</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;Your man is going down. &gt;&gt;&gt;Will you lose your shill job when that occurs? Obama is not "my man". He is the President of the United States of America. Your president, and my president. A Romney win in November is a long-shot at best. That's simply how it is. I am a professional analyst. I do not do political work. I have multiple clients in both the public and private sector. Why on earth would you think my livelihood depends on who is President?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346625154000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:32:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346625416000-52</Id><Topic><Title>The Socialist Party endorses President Obama</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1346578990000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 05:43:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you a socialist? Then why do you care who the Socialist party endorses. If the Nazi party endorsed Romney, would that tell us anything about Romney? Does' Lavendar's endorsement of Paul tell us anything about him?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346625416000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:36:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346626121000-53</Id><Topic><Title>The Socialist Party endorses President Obama</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1346578990000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 05:43:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The kenyan is a socialist, why wouldn't they support him?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346626121000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:48:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346626193000-54</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many believe that the GOP, party want nothing of winning in 2008. Just let the Democratic Party win, and plan their comback. This is why they were reportedly plotting to the decide on a plan to make Obama, a one term President. Why, so they as they have done pin the blame on Obama, for the crash. It was bigger then they, or anyone thought so I would not be supprised that they would not mind, viewing the extent of the problem not mind losing again. Thus the divided Party, and weak team of candidates.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346626193000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:49:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346626213000-55</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tRicky, you're a poster child for liberals!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346626213000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:50:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346626915000-56</Id><Topic><Title>European Social Programs &amp; Ours</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346535423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:37:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Best, get educated on this also. Eighty percent of the premium, under the Affordable Healthcare Act has to go toward care for the insured. Leaving only twenty percent for advertizing, operating, and gigantic bonuses for the CEO's. This will cause them to operate more efficently, this helps them, and us. This is why already to date billions parts of premiums have been returned to the insured. Trouble is that the companies are not required to mention it is a result of Obamacare. Thus once again the ignorant may decide, to vote for the GOP, fearing not getting another rebate.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346626915000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:01:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346627071000-57</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazing, I did not say extremist...you did in your reply. The vast majority in unions today are in public employee unions. America spoke along time ago about unions and they are not popular.</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1346627071000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:04:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346627391000-58</Id><Topic><Title>European Social Programs &amp; Ours</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346535423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:37:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This also is not true. I know many Canadians, German, and some Norweigian, still in contact with them when they were exchange students to our country. A form of triage is used, which means they are seen in the order of need. Actually with Obamacare this may be a problem in the beginning. That is why it is best to be phased in. It requires ten years to produce a doctor. At the end of that time most have a debt of nearly 200k dollars. Far too few becomes GP doctors, thus the PD program, and other solutions will be required as the numbers of American patients increase. Sad, but they too all want be like Romney, and make the most money, and it is not made being in general prcactice.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346627391000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:09:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346630846000-59</Id><Topic><Title>Be Leery!</Title><Username>florida_gabriela1</Username><Timestamp>1346588214000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:16:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Getting good benefit.</Msg><Username>nannette_sondra74</Username><Timestamp>1346630846000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:07:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346631511000-60</Id><Title>Apple Sucks! - I Suspect Foul Play and Manipulation</Title><Msg>Just a hjunh, but I think Apple is manipulating eps numbers and is full of crapple. Jobs would have the stock price at least double by now. Cook is no chef!I think he's awful and should be fired.</Msg><Username>proofsintheprofits</Username><Timestamp>1346631511000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:18:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346632608000-61</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Monica sure thought he was great! Definitely left an impression on her!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346632608000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:36:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346634410000-62</Id><Topic><Title>Be Leery!</Title><Username>florida_gabriela1</Username><Timestamp>1346588214000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:16:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice site.</Msg><Username>inge_tonia25</Username><Timestamp>1346634410000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:06:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346635188000-63</Id><Title>Socialized medicine causing Europe &amp; Canada doctor loss</Title><Msg>Supporters of Obamacare should take note: Since 2008 alone, more than 8,000 doctors have left Britain to practice elsewhere, and the chief reason cited is the country’s long-established system of socialized medicine. “When a government declares that it will provide ‘free’ healthcare, there is no escaping the fact that such a system will one day be overwhelmed by demand and the providers — the doctors and other professionals who are extensively and intensely trained — won’t be able to keep up,” an editorial in Investor’s Business Daily (IBD) observes. “They will be overworked, underpaid, and frustrated with the difficulties in performing the task they feel called to, namely healing the sick.” Britain’s National Health Service is “rotted,” according to IBD, which states that waiting times to see a doctor are “often fatal,” denial of care is “sometimes deadly,” facilities are “often miserable,” and the pay is “base.” That, along with more appealing tax rates, is encouraging many doctors to relocate to Australia and New Zealand, the editorial reports. One anesthesiologist who fled Britain and came to the United States years ago told IBD: “Now we are getting the same thing. Obamacare stinks, and the people will regret it. What happened to docs there will happen here.” IBD opines: “If America doesn’t want physician flight in its future, voters will have to turn President Obama out of office this fall so that repeal of Obamacare can be possible.” Otherwise, “today’s U.S. physicians will simply retire early or change careers, and tomorrow’s will choose another profession, one less regulated and more remunerative.” And the problem isn’t confined to Britain — 10 percent of doctors trained in Canada, which also has universal healthcare, end up in the United States.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346635188000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:19:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346636786000-64</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good, New Orleans is a sewer anyway.</Msg><Username>jbspowa</Username><Timestamp>1346636786000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:46:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346637121000-65</Id><Topic><Title>The Socialist Party endorses President Obama</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1346578990000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 05:43:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Birds of a feather flock together. Barry, certainly has flocked up the Country, with his anti-American policies. It's no wonder he is trying to stop our soldiers over seas from voting. In Ohio, early voting is alright, but he doesn't want to count the overseas ballots from our Military. This is typical Obummer, say one thing, and do another.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346637121000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:52:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346637581000-66</Id><Topic><Title>Clint should have heeded his own advice::</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1346446714000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:58:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jimmy Carter is scheduled to speak at the DNC Convention. An honest man, but boy was he in over his head. Similar to Obama, also great family man, but a gigantic ego, in love with himself. But as Clint reminds us, when somebody fails as miserably as Barry, we gotta let him go. I can't wait to see Mouchelle's face when she learns her extravagant, free, Air Force One vacations are over, for her and her extended family.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346637581000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:59:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346638050000-67</Id><Title>Why Isn't the Media Covering Arson?</Title><Msg>Several weeks ago, out west, several men were lighting newspapers off the back of a pickup truck. They were throwing them into the dry grass. The media buried the story. These were Hispanics, likely illegals starting fire to get work. If you lost your home to these wild fires, we hope you can get aid from this Administration. But this unlimited, open border stuff is costing us Billions. Romney will deport these criminals once, and for all.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346638050000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:07:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346638386000-68</Id><Topic><Title>Obama standards will double car prices</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346175055000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:30:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If were just converted our vehicles to natural gas, we would be way ahead of the game. As Mitt has said, we are the Saudi Arabia of natural gas. Barry would never recommend this approach cause it uses our resources. His redistribution program dictates that we gave money to dictators. Chavez in Venezuela.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346638386000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:13:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346638429000-69</Id><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN</Title><Msg>you choose.....</Msg><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346638429000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:13:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346638842000-70</Id><Topic><Title>Socialized medicine causing Europe &amp; Canada doctor loss</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346635188000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:19:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://my.brainshark.com/The-President-s-8-Billion-Coincidence-356086344</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346638842000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:20:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346638905000-71</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346638429000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:13:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right, the mus.lim is out!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346638905000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346639127000-72</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I liked Larry the Cable Guy's explanation: "Build a city 12 feet below sea level, fill it with democrats, what the hell could go wrong?"</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346639127000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346639580000-73</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346210905000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 23:28:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thats a lie... he said his father was not a good person... a drunk...and absent from his life.... he did not know him... after he was killed in a car wreck, he found out more of how awful his father was to his kids... so stop lying... you Mormon Follower........</Msg><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346639580000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:33:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346639929000-74</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;Definitely left an impression on her! Better her than the soldiers who were killed in Iraq &amp; Afghanistan. Get your priorities straight, man. People's lives are on the line. You think anyone cares if Clinton got a little on the side? Obama is a loyal family man. He's taken the fight to the terrorists, but in a smart way. The RNC spent half the time talking about the need to do more in Syria and Iran. Romney didn't mention Afghanistan once. You want to be there another ten years? Elect Romney and see who he decides to invade instead of finishing the job in Afghanistan.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346639929000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:38:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346640297000-75</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Larry the Cable Guy never said that. He has some class.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346640297000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:44:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346640625000-76</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More jobs created in less than one term than GWB did in two terms. Bin Laden and many of his follower are dead, and GM is alive, and hiring. Also if you child is born with a disease, it is not pre-existing. You also may get a rebate check from your health insurance provider. Only 20% profit is allowed. Bet you have a signed photo of all show GWB on the Carrier with MISSION Acomplished</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346640625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:50:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346640734000-77</Id><Topic><Title>Socialized medicine causing Europe &amp; Canada doctor loss</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346635188000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:19:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And where does the article say all those British &amp; Canadian doctors are going? America. I wouldn't worry about losing doctors. Physicians make more money here than anywhere in the world. Medical schools do not lack for qualified applicants in any country. We make the slots, they'll get filled.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346640734000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:52:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346640877000-78</Id><Topic><Title>Socialized medicine causing Europe &amp; Canada doctor loss</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346635188000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:19:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also, it goes without saying, we do not have a system anything like the NHS or Canada's system, and Obamacare does not resemble Socialism.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346640877000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:54:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346641492000-79</Id><Title>Legalized drugs to help our Economy</Title><Msg>I have been watching Prohibition on PBS, a production of Ken Burns. They ended Prohibition in 1933, Why because it did not work, and to help the economic come back. Could we benefit also from legalizing some drugs?</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346641492000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:04:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346642130000-80</Id><Topic><Title>Socialized medicine causing Europe &amp; Canada doctor loss</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346635188000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:19:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;And where does the article say all those British &amp; Canadian doctors are going? America. Exactly, European and Canadian doctors came here to escape a system that will be imitated by Obamacare. Once Obamacare is fully implimented America can expect the same result.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346642130000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346642212000-81</Id><Topic><Title>Socialized medicine causing Europe &amp; Canada doctor loss</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346635188000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:19:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People go where the money is. Today, most of our doctors are not GP type doctors, they all want to be specialists. That is where the money is 300+k, as apposed to 180-200k for a GP. This is also why the Canadian doctor comes here. Fact is we need more GP, or PD types to keep our people healthy, and not overload our emergency rooms. If they go the ER today the person with health care is usally the one to pay for these peoples care, in the form of an increased bill. This is also the same reason Romney types crush a company, and send the work to Vietnam, or China. Follow the money or the lack of it.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346642212000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:16:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346643355000-82</Id><Topic><Title>Legalized drugs to help our Economy</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346641492000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:04:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>let's see, you value money over human life you are an atheist want drugs leagized endorse gay marriage you align yourself with democrats because most of them are drawn to you you are a bitter, angry and will stand behind anything evil and try to convince others to follow. We were warned about you, we know who you are.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346643355000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:35:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>