<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-23"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348373180704-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he believes in redistribution</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348073752677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:55:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I did not ask about how she may or may not use the tax breaks Romney wants to give her. I asked how much lower do you think her rate should be. 10%? 5%? 1%? What?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348373180704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 00:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348373760354-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. The account of what happened has become clearer as we gained more information. I know you don't use that stuff (information), so it must be confusing to you.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348373760354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 00:16:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348374252827-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"they haven't figured out how to handle it without lying to the American public." Yeah, we know. You've managed to figure out the truth from Breitbart &amp; email forwards. Everyone else is lying. You're a broken record. Senile.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348374252827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 00:24:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348399205101-4</Id><Topic><Title>Univision does the job liberal media won't</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348350543988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 17:49:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One might first ask why anyone should pay any attention to some clown who needs to use copycat aliases on a message board? How valid is anything that you have to say if you must resort to trying to fool people into thinking you’re someone else? Do you honestly believe that anyone takes such juvenile behavior seriously? “Their left-wing bias has become all too apparent. Indeed, a new Gallup Poll shows Americans now distrust the mainstream media.” – fake Ricky with the “L” not 1. No, the poll doesn’t say any such thing. The poll discusses media – not “Main Stream Media” – There is no such thing, other than in the cluttered minds of folks unconcerned with factual information. “Republicans continue to express the least trust in the media, while Democrats express the most. Percent who express a great deal or fair amount of trust in the media: Democrats = 58% Republicans = 26% Well, no sh#t Sherlock! I wouldn’t trust them too much either if all I watched was Fox, Limbaugh, or Glen Beck.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348399205101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 07:20:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348399590651-5</Id><Topic><Title>losing customers</Title><Username>leemadison321</Username><Timestamp>1348360623077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 20:37:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If lost market share represents high cost causing customers, that is not such a bad thing.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1348399590651</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 07:26:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348404784971-6</Id><Title>The Quote of the Decade:</Title><Msg>The Quote of the Decade: "The fact that we are here today to debate raising America 's debt limit is a sign of leadership failure. It is a sign that the US Government cannot pay its own bills. It is a sign that we now depend on ongoing financial assistance from foreign countries to finance our Government's reckless fiscal policies. Increasing America 's debt weakens us domestically and internationally. Leadership means that, "the buck stops here.' Instead, Washington is shifting the burden of bad choices today onto the backs of our children and grandchildren. America has a debt problem and a failure of leadership. Americans deserve better." ~ Senator Barack H. Obama, March 2006 Pass it on 'til eternity...or at least until he is defeated.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348404784971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 08:53:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348405332688-7</Id><Topic><Title>Univision does the job liberal media won't</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348350543988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 17:49:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Republicans continue to express the least trust in the media, while Democrats express the most." And you have to wonder why? It is not Fox News that won't print anything real about Obama. It is not Fox News that will not ask pointed questions of Obama, Harry, or Nancy, it is only the network media that refuses to do. Why are the media asking for 'detailed' economic recovery plans from Romney when they don't ask the same question of Obama? We are the American media not asking hard questions about who knew what and when about Fast and Furious or Arab Spring or Libya? Why do they always just assume that the Democrats are telling the truth, the full truth, not just selected portions but just the opposite with anyone else? Why do they not care more about the truth, the full truth than ratings? Of course you will not answer these questions, first because you can’t, second because it wouldn’t fit with your political philosophy and political naivety. Nice to hear another side, although you’re side is always the same old list of Democratic talking points. You must watch a ton of TV to have such a wide understanding of what Fox and the rest of the media really do. You’re a sound bite baby.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348405332688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:02:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348405438092-8</Id><Topic><Title>After learning of Benghazi attack Obama goes to bed as events surrouding the attack continue</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348371039113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:30:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He had to rest up for his next fund raiser and his next meeting with some rappers. Give the guy a break, campaigning if hard work and he has only been at it this time for the last three years. It is hard to change old habits.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348405438092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348405696857-9</Id><Topic><Title>Does Barry Believe in God?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347739167038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 15:59:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why should anyone else help his brother if he won't? Why doesn't he want to give his brother the 'opportunity' that he wants to give all the 'Dreamers'? Could it be because his brother can't vote for him? Could it be that any mention of his brother and his plight would be an immediate political embarrassment for Obama? Nah, none of that could matter to such a compassionate, understanding and caring person, could it? Heck, this guy even threw Grandma under the bus after she raised him.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348405696857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:08:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348406060824-10</Id><Topic><Title>Obama appologizes to Mooslums but not Christians</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348333358469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mostly because he doesn't have to afraid that Christians in the US will rise up and burn someone's embassy or kill protestors. The big difference is that religion in most countries is a personal belief system, not a quasi government that wants to be the entire government. We do not believe in or accept killing people because we are offended. Contrary to what many believe and our courts are beginning share, there is no Constitutional right to NOT BE OFFENDED. Be offended if you must, but the government does not have the power and should not act as if they have the power to protect you from never being offended. Our President believes that Is lam should be protected.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348406060824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:14:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348410126399-11</Id><Topic><Title>The Quote of the Decade:</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348404784971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 08:53:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"or at least until he is defeated" Defeating him will be difficult because he and his team have seen to the following: To plagiarize President John F. Kennedy, America has too many people who want to know what government can do for them, instead of asking what they can do for their country. -Drew A. Roy</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1348410126399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:22:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348412930957-12</Id><Topic><Title>After learning of Benghazi attack Obama goes to bed as events surrouding the attack continue</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348371039113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:30:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope he enjoyed his hot bedtime coco delivered by his houseboy while Ambassador Stevens was being tortured and murdered.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348412930957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 11:08:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348413730609-13</Id><Topic><Title>Univision does the job liberal media won't</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348350543988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 17:49:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I make far better use of this alias than the other jerk.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348413730609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 11:22:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348416673442-14</Id><Topic><Title>losing customers</Title><Username>leemadison321</Username><Timestamp>1348360623077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 20:37:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just cover SHORTY' going to new 52 week high this week. Institutions and funds know better than you.</Msg><Username>catspaw33129</Username><Timestamp>1348416673442</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:11:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348416827984-15</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T is showing historic technical movement</Title><Username>shanellecannington</Username><Timestamp>1348342206967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:30:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok SHORTY! Cover now because you will pay more later. Going to new 52 week high this week. The technical move is to high price. Listen to Institutions and Funds. DD.</Msg><Username>catspaw33129</Username><Timestamp>1348416827984</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:13:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348416963714-16</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T is showing historic technical movement</Title><Username>aricablacketer</Username><Timestamp>1348321649625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 09:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IMHO points to a new 52 week high. Long term new I phone will add millions to T value. DD.</Msg><Username>catspaw33129</Username><Timestamp>1348416963714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:16:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348417456950-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obama appologizes to Mooslums but not Christians</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348333358469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obama's insistance that the film was the cause the riots and killing coupled with his continuing apologies and promises to stop the hate towards 'lims is boxing him into a corner that has the United States establishing the' lim religion as the prefered one having more protection than all others.</Msg><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1348417456950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:24:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348431246210-18</Id><Topic><Title>Does Barry Believe in God?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347739167038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 15:59:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course you're not. Because you're an idiot. An impotent, illiterate, boring idiot.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1348431246210</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 16:14:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348433643083-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama appologizes to Mooslums but not Christians</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348333358469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Profit's (sic) Idiology (sic) being the Surpreme (sic) Law of the Land” – jonthehapless Well, that about sums it up! In a run of five words, with one of them being “the”, you misspelled three out of the other four. You are truly a #$%$ Now, tell us again why we should do away with the Department of Education? Is it so imbeciles like you can pretend to be Supreme Prophets spreading your Ideology of Profits?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348433643083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 16:54:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348433830630-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obama appologizes to Mooslums but not Christians</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348333358469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are kidding me, Yahoo. You censored the word #$%$?????????????/ Give me a focking break!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348433830630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 16:57:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348434062998-21</Id><Topic><Title>Obama appologizes to Mooslums but not Christians</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348333358469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*#$%$ Are you serious? How is that word censorable?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348434062998</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 17:01:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348434684225-22</Id><Topic><Title>Obama appologizes to Mooslums but not Christians</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348333358469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The word begins with an “M” and it ends with an “n” and it has a couple of “o’s” in it. Vanna wants to know if you’d like to buy an “r”? So, that word is not permitted on Yahoo’s message board, even though when you search for it, there are countless references going back 10 years. Who’s running the yahoo cops – Ernest Angley? Let’s see how many of these synonyms get by these crack guardians of virtue: Synonyms airhead, birdbrain, blockhead, bonehead, bubblehead, chowderhead, chucklehead, clodpoll (or clodpole), clot [British], cluck, clunk, cretin, cuddy (or cuddie) [British dialect], deadhead, dim bulb [slang], dimwit, dip, dodo, dolt, donkey, doofus [slang], dope, dork [slang], dullard, dumbbell, dumbhead, dum-dum, dummkopf, dummy, dunce, dunderhead, fathead, gander, golem, goof, goon, half-wit, hammerhead, hardhead, ignoramus, imbecile, jackass, know-nothing, knucklehead, lamebrain, loggerhead [chiefly dialect], loon, lump, lunkhead, meathead, mome [archaic], #$%$ mug [chiefly British], mutt, natural, nimrod [slang], nincompoop, ninny, ninnyhammer, nit [chiefly British], nitwit, noddy, noodle, numskull (or numbskull), oaf, pinhead, prat [British], ratbag [chiefly Australian], saphead, schlub (also shlub) [slang], schnook [slang], simpleton, stock, stupe, stupid, thickhead, turkey, woodenhead, yahoo, yo-yo</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348434684225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 17:11:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348445228622-23</Id><Title>Dem Polls aren't what they Seem</Title><Msg>Just ask Carter, Dukakis, and Kerry. If you haven't embraced the Presidente by now, you probably won't. Being in a Union automatically puts you in the Dem column. Always remember tell them what they want to hear, so they'll quit calling. I tell them I'll vote early, and often. That way they know, I know the system here in the People's Republic of Maryland. You go girl, Barbara Mikuski may be a carpet cleaner, but at least she can't reproduce.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348445228622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:07:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348448000927-24</Id><Topic><Title>Does Barry Believe in God?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347739167038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 15:59:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, 2retarded, you repetitive lickspittle, your posts are worthless crap the first time they appear. If you want to continue to regurgitate your cud, go for it, but do it someplace private.</Msg><Username>argonthecat</Username><Timestamp>1348448000927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:53:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348448019791-25</Id><Topic><Title>The Quote of the Decade:</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348404784971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 08:53:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"deficits don't matter"-- D. Cheney</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1348448019791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:53:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348449431103-26</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt has Super Energized his Base</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348016247399</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Congress has decided to go on vacation, till after the election. They will be going home to their districts. Tell them, you are voting for someone else. Someone willing, to stop following this bigoted Predident off of the fiscal cliff.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348449431103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:17:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348449872684-27</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt has Super Energized his Base</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348016247399</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I listen to Mitt on 60 Minutes tonight. It looks like the Republicans have brought back W. Let's send all the problems to the states ( medicare and medicare ) and let them deal with it; let's start another war ( Iran ); let's pledge to not raise taxes to finance the war; let's cut taxes for everyone and that will balance the budget. Mitt is an embarassment.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1348449872684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348456700694-28</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt has Super Energized his Base</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348016247399</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama same old stuff, after 4 years still blame everyone else, no ideas, no leadership, filled with excuses, condescending- the picture said everything, Obama visually and verbally talking down to Steve Kroft like some peon that appeared to be kneeling before Obama.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348456700694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 23:18:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348456821710-29</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt has Super Energized his Base</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348016247399</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rommey is a loon, the puks will drop his losing #$%$, never hear from him again.</Msg><Username>orri1934</Username><Timestamp>1348456821710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 23:20:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>