<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344255308000-1</Id><Topic><Title>OWS and SEIU protesters turn on Obama</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344091223000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:40:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Abbott sounds much like our Ricky.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344255308000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 08:15:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344255912000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama denies military right to vote in Ohio</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344183077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That doesn't mean you should join the dark side. I'm just sayin'.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344255912000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 08:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344256034000-3</Id><Topic><Title>ceo pay</Title><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1344181027000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then strike. The problem is the majority of your peers won't go out.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344256034000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 08:27:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344258853000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama denies military right to vote in Ohio</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344183077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right. The problem continues to be Republican attempts to make it easier for some groups of people to vote and harder for others. Don't mess with our elections. Of course, this attempt is likely to backfire on Republicans, as members of the military favor Obama: http://www.reuters.com/article/2012/05/13/us-usa-poll-military-idUSBRE84C02120120513</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1344258853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 09:14:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344258990000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama denies military right to vote in Ohio</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344183077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"harder for others." Yep, the illegal ones.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344258990000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 09:16:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344260274000-6</Id><Title>re Nice weekend, jon...</Title><Msg>... “...but there is a lot to do...lots &amp; lots of room for ‘big boy’ toys, like spud launchers” Wow, jon, you mean in between all your postings over the weekend you and the rest of your Mensa group had time for playing with potato cannons? How cerebral! Hope you didn’t blow up the trailer. “It’s really nice here in the country…” So, I see, jon. And, as you call them, “the wives” also seemed to be enjoying themselves. I’m so sorry I missed it. Maybe next time. http://www.keithwhite.us/rncupholder.jpg</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1344260274000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 09:37:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344260466000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obama denies military right to vote in Ohio</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344183077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;Yep, the illegal ones. No. In this case, it would be harder for the entire civilian population of Ohio to vote compared to members of the military. It would be easier for all members of the military to vote--including the undocumented immigrants serving in the military. Of course, undocumented immigrants in the military cannot register to vote so I don't think it will help them. They all do, however, have Federal IDs.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1344260466000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 09:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344261042000-8</Id><Topic><Title>OWS and SEIU protesters turn on Obama</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344091223000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:40:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL Too funny and the truth</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344261042000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 09:50:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344262031000-9</Id><Title>Unsustainable</Title><Msg>Sure I like the company T but they pay more in dividend then they earn infact now it trades 50 times earnings Who's with me to short T at 38</Msg><Username>macnaughtonr</Username><Timestamp>1344262031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:07:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344262121000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Obama denies military right to vote in Ohio</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344183077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a crock. First you tell me the military will vote for Obama, then you tell me the Republicans are trying to make it easier for them to vote &amp; the Dems are opposing the initiative because it would make it harder for all other voters. Jeez! This post gets the Acadamy Award for spinning. You would think this issue would be one both sides could agree on, especially if the military folks are primarily in Obama's camp as you suggest. Sounds like the hard core left has gone goofy on this one. Of course, you always suggest that only happens on the right. Perhaps those pesky maga hard to get along with Tea Party folks have infiltrated the left. WOW!</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344262121000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:08:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344262254000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Unsustainable</Title><Username>macnaughtonr</Username><Timestamp>1344262031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:07:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"50 times earnings Who's with me to short T at 38" If this is driving your investment decision, I suggest you do a bit more homework.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344262254000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:10:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344262533000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Unsustainable</Title><Username>macnaughtonr</Username><Timestamp>1344262031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:07:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's basing his investment decisions off the numbers put up on Yahoo! initial page for the company and nothing more.... I'll buy his shares if he's willing to sell outright, and get one more weak hand out of the way.</Msg><Username>vwdiesel10</Username><Timestamp>1344262533000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:15:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344264179000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama denies military right to vote in Ohio</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344183077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;This post gets the Acadamy Award for spinning. What spinning? Is that not what is happening? &gt;&gt;&gt;You would think this issue would be one both sides could agree on, especially if the military folks are primarily in Obama's camp as you suggest. The military makes a great effort to ensure those serving overseas can exercise their right to vote-something it should do--but there is no reason to make the rules different for military personnel exclusively. Giving preferential treatment to one group over another is merely the flip side of giving inferior treatment to other groups. There is a history in this country of using supposedly innocuous rules to deny certain groups the right to vote. We are seeing a concerted effort to do this again this election cycle. This is one more effort--designed to for maximum PR effect to be sure--but one designed to skew the vote unfairly. Voting may be something you don't care much about. Americans, however, consider it a right. If you continue to mess around with this right, there will be consequences. Your attempts to make our electoral process unfair are anti-American. I will not tolerate them. Any of them. And I expect the people I vote for to not tolerate them either.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1344264179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344264391000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama denies military right to vote in Ohio</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344183077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ricky, there has always been trouble counting the military vote dating back as long as I can remember. In Ohio where every vote counts it has become an important issue.</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1344264391000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:46:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344264451000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Unsustainable</Title><Username>macnaughtonr</Username><Timestamp>1344262031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:07:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have already sold my shares at $35.70 Waiting to pick em back up at $31 So don't bash me because I havent made as much as you. Now i see that all analysts are recommending Buy but the resistance at $38 is very obvious and yes the P/E ratio is confirmed by TDAmeritrade as %50.02x So you 2 expect it to break through resistance at $38 and rise to $40 like the analysts But I say with P/E so high this is unsustainable and I want to chat with others who see this as well</Msg><Username>macnaughtonr</Username><Timestamp>1344264451000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:47:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344264716000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Obama denies military right to vote in Ohio</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344183077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Your attempts to make our electoral process unfair are anti-American." My attempts?! What a ridiculous charge.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344264716000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:51:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344264846000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Unsustainable</Title><Username>macnaughtonr</Username><Timestamp>1344262031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:07:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But I say with P/E so high this is unsustainable" One more time: Do your homework.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344264846000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:54:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344265179000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Unsustainable</Title><Username>macnaughtonr</Username><Timestamp>1344262031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:07:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AT&amp;T earned 63 cents a share last quarter and paid 44 cents in dividend. That was typical of every quarter. The dividend will only go higher. Last years EPS was effected by a 3 billion dollar one time charge off and by 2.5 billion income tax charge. There were areas of concern in that profit margin went down and G&amp;A expense went up. However the projected P/E ratio is 15 and that is what the current market price is based on. In the short term I doubt the wisdom of shorting T. Wait until it hits $44.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1344265179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344265248000-19</Id><Topic><Title>OWS and SEIU protesters turn on Obama</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344091223000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:40:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sheesh people. Learn to square a measure or an indicator with reality. The unemployment rate measures what it measures--the number of people who are not working and who looked for work in the past four weeks. This is what the unemployment rate has always measured. The unemployment rate is a very good indicator of the health of the labor market. When the labor market is good, it goes down. When it is bad, it goes up. That is what an indicator is supposed to do. Correlate with what it indicates. It is not the only indicator. Here are some more: http://www.bls.gov/news.release/empsit.t15.htm/ These alternative indicators report ALL of the things you people constantly whine about not being reported in the unemployment rate. In fact, if the BLS did not report these figures, neither you nor Rush Limbaugh would know to whine about them not being included in the unemployment rate. You complain that someone is trying to trick you by citing figures from the people who you accuse of tricking you. So please, simply do what economists do, and note that the unemployment rate is an indicator of the health of the labor market, but not the only indicator, and that the unemployment rate is exceptionally high right now and has been for some time. Think about yourselves for a moment. You are people who swallow every outlandish email forward without a whiff of skepticism but who have decided every consistent scientific poll or measure is some sort of a lie or a trick. You need your heads examined.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1344265248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:00:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344265368000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Unsustainable</Title><Username>macnaughtonr</Username><Timestamp>1344262031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:07:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Troublemaker. "Strong Sell" he/she sez?. Easy choice. Off to ignore land.</Msg><Username>dm74575</Username><Timestamp>1344265368000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344265650000-21</Id><Topic><Title>OWS and SEIU protesters turn on Obama</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344091223000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:40:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You are people who swallow every outlandish email forward without a whiff of skepticism but who have decided every consistent scientific poll or measure is some sort of a lie or a trick. You need your heads examined." We didn't swallow anything Ricky. It was a joke, so get off your high horse. ...and we would only need our heads examined if we bought half or more of your garbage.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344265650000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:07:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344265772000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Unsustainable</Title><Username>macnaughtonr</Username><Timestamp>1344262031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:07:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, you did his homework for him. Maybe he will send you a Christmas card.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344265772000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:09:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344265900000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama denies military right to vote in Ohio</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344183077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;Ricky, there has always been trouble counting the military vote dating back as long as I can remember. In Ohio where every vote counts it has become an important issue. Then improve the absentee ballot process for those overseas. I fully support that, as does everyone else. There is no reason these days we can't get absentee ballots out to our troops in time. This has nothing to do with that, however. In this case, ALL Ohioans used to be able to vote early up until the Monday before the election. Last year, Republicans passed a law limiting early voting but they carved out an exception for a constituency they consider friendly. It backfired but it is still an illegal attempt to skew the vote. The Obama campaign is not trying to prevent military personnel from voting. They are trying to allow all Ohioans to vote early under the old laws. If the suit is successful, military personnel will still be able to vote under the same rules as they would if the suit is unsuccessful. It is simply that all other Ohioans will be able to join them.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1344265900000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:11:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344266018000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Obama denies military right to vote in Ohio</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344183077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;My attempts?! What a ridiculous charge. Oh yes, how could I forget. You're not responsible for what the people you vote for do.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1344266018000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:13:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344266960000-25</Id><Topic><Title>OWS and SEIU protesters turn on Obama</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344091223000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:40:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;We didn't swallow anything Ricky. It was a joke, Yeah. One minute it's a joke, the next minute Winholder &amp; the Reaganite Republican shows up.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1344266960000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344267066000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Unsustainable</Title><Username>macnaughtonr</Username><Timestamp>1344262031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:07:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you should be looking at forward P/E, not historical P/E, to better understand the future direction of this stock. You're basically looking in the rear view mirror. FPE is around 13 last time I checked.</Msg><Username>sblowmeh</Username><Timestamp>1344267066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:31:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344270522000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Unsustainable</Title><Username>macnaughtonr</Username><Timestamp>1344262031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:07:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks good post but they earned 67 cents last quarter 63 was consensus estimate I see your forward P/E 2012 annual as 15.8 But what's to stop another stupid t-Mobile like decision to waste more money and bring down the actual earnings. Do they typically subtract income tax after reporting earnings? Here's what dividend valuation is on tdameritrade: "T's dividend is not sustainable. Over the past 12 months the company paid more in dividends than it earned. Over time this cannot continue. "</Msg><Username>macnaughtonr</Username><Timestamp>1344270522000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 12:28:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344271837000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Unsustainable</Title><Username>macnaughtonr</Username><Timestamp>1344262031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:07:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"T's dividend is not sustainable. Over the past 12 months the company paid more in dividends than it earned. Over time this cannot continue. " Well then, it pretty much boils down to who you believe: August 2, 2012, 2:40 P.M. ET Verizon, AT&amp;T, Altria Among Top CDS-Adjusted Dividend Stocks By Michael Aneiro Citi equity strategists are out with their latest CDS-adjusted dividend stock screen, which hunts for stocks of companies with high dividend yields that are also on top-tier financial footing as judged by the market for credit-default swaps. Citi filters for global stocks with a market cap greater than $10 billion, a dividend yield 1.5% higher than median-yielding stocks and CDS under 100 basis points (the lower the CDS, the lower the perceived credit risk). Citi’s resulting list consists of 41 companies with a 4.8% average yield, and Citi forecasts these dividends to grow by 7% in 2012 and 5% in 2013. The constituents have an average five-year CDS of 70 bps, equivalent to the sovereign CDS of Germany, indicating a similar perceived likelihood of default over the next half-decade. Sector-wise, the list skews toward an overweight in Europe and defensive stocks and an underweight in financials. largely due to their high perceived CDS risk. Here are the nine U.S.-based companies on Citi’s list: Altria Group Inc. (MO) CDS 73 basis points, dividend yield 4.6% American Electric Power (AEP) 63 bps, 4.5% AT&amp;T Inc. (T) 81 bps, 4.6% ConocoPhillips (COP) 61 bps, 4.8% Duke Energy Corp. (DUK) 38 bps, 4.5% Eli Lilly (LLY) 53 bps, 4.5% Lockheed Martin Corp. (LMT) 71 bps, 4.5% Southern Co. (SO) 77 bps, 4.1% Verizon Communications Inc. (VZ) 58 bps, 4.4%</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344271837000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 12:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344272716000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Obama denies military right to vote in Ohio</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344183077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “The Obama campaign is not trying to prevent military personnel from voting. They are trying to allow all Ohioans to vote early under the old laws.” Thank you for accurately depicting the issue at hand – As I live in Ohio, I was going to explain it, but you are 100% factually correct. No one in Ohio has any problem whatsoever with additional time for the military to vote. The problem is that the Republicans in charge in Ohio took away that same privilege from everyone else simply because they thought it would benefit them – just as their insane gerrymandering has done in this state. These are all manipulative political ploys based on their insecurities about their shrinking base of like-minded cronies. DOING it is bad enough – doing it surreptitiously, and then, waving their flags of jingoism while trying to present it as the Democrats taking away something from our servicemen and women, is pathetic and beneath contempt. This is factual information and it would be nice to see people concerned with the truth, reacting accordingly to this repugnant behavior. Better yet, why don’t those who back these actions, explain in detail what the purpose of taking away these rights from everyone else are supposed to be (other than to benefit the republicans who changed the rules.) Here’s how their legislation explained it: “Republicans faulted the extra time for civilians as too costly for local governments and prone to fraud and abuse.” Gee, that sounds familiar! And of course, Romney’s jumped on the bandwagon, as well. "I think it's shameful that Governor Romney would hide behind our servicemen and women to try and win a lawsuit to deprive other Ohioans of the right to vote.” – David Axelrod So, all you clowns who accuse others of spinning. One last time – No one in Ohio wants to take away any voting rights for the Military – they simply want to get back those exact same rights for everyone else from whom they were stolen.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1344272716000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 13:05:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344280206000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Obama denies military right to vote in Ohio</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344183077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You're not responsible for what the people you vote for do." This just in from the land that gives us Nancy!</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344280206000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 15:10:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344280993000-31</Id><Title>re Obama denies military...</Title><Msg>... jon - I said this previously: “This is factual information and it would be nice to see people concerned with the truth, reacting accordingly to this repugnant behavior.” Your response to that, like most of your posts, demonstrates that you have no concern for the truth, and that you are an advocate of repugnant behavior. Your tired refrain ignores any semblance of truth, and falls back on the lame “blame the MSM.” Facts are facts, man, and here’s why we Ohioans are upset with the repeated Republican efforts to make it more difficult for citizens to vote: “More than 1.7 million Ohioans voted before Election Day in the 2008 presidential election — about 30 percent of all ballots cast. And nearly 100,000 of them voted in-person in the final three days before the November election.” Now, if you want to make an argument that “procrastinators” will be excluded from the polls, so be it…but where do you draw the line? I’m sure they would much rather have said, only white males over 60 who drink tea can vote, but knew they couldn’t. And here’s the Republican Sec. of State’s most recent reasoning behind their decision: “Husted said the reasons for the legislature’s decision to eliminate in-person early voting for the days immediately preceding the election were to give elections boards time to prepare for Election Day and to help with uniformity among the boards.” Time to prepare for the Election????????? Right! Interestingly, his name is Jon, too. “Let me take another ‘whack’ at my prev. short response !!” – jon3retired Perhaps you should stick to whacking that which you know.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1344280993000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 15:23:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344287411000-32</Id><Topic><Title>re Obama denies military...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1344280993000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 15:23:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Texas offers early voting. It makes voting so much more convenient. We vote at our grocery store! You must show some form of ID and there are some 8 or 9 acceptable forms.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344287411000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 17:10:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344290102000-33</Id><Topic><Title>re Obama denies military...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1344280993000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 15:23:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Any significant voter fraud issues there ??" I haven't seen much reported. The ID requirements may be a fairly decent deterrent. If you don't have early voting you might press for it. Makes the process so much easier. Interestingly, only about 20% of voters take advantage of the option. What I don't have a feel for is if it adds signifcantly to the cost of voting.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344290102000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 17:55:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344292770000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Be Leery!</Title><Username>lavernehhm800</Username><Timestamp>1344256338000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 08:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow!!!</Msg><Username>larinaocm876</Username><Timestamp>1344292770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 18:39:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344295885000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Technical Chart</Title><Username>noraxkx613</Username><Timestamp>1344272848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 13:07:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the site</Msg><Username>iseabalvkq722</Username><Timestamp>1344295885000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 19:31:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344298108000-36</Id><Title>Strike in DIST 9?</Title><Msg>?????</Msg><Username>josieinib</Username><Timestamp>1344298108000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 20:08:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344301340000-37</Id><Topic><Title>Strike in DIST 9?</Title><Username>josieinib</Username><Timestamp>1344298108000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 20:08:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm posting this in a strictly personal capacity. Speaking from personal opinion, if such a thing were to happen, it might be due to employee outrage over the twenty-plus unfair labor practice charges filed against AT+T- or the fact that the bargaining process is dead in the water at present. Sadly for AT+T, the company appears to expect everyone to follow the precedents set in a tentative contract arrived at in District Four- a region largely comprised of "Right to Work" states. The majority of the states in the remaining districts have not yet tacitly agreed to any of the provisions of this contract. Also, an unfair labor practice action is not a strike per se- and can happen several times over the course of bargaining and remain a protected joint action. This tactic might serve to get AT+T's attention- or it might not. If not, remember that the members of district four- many already annoyed by their district's second capitulation in a row- need not ratify the agreement. It therefore remains a possibility that the entire company could walk out at the same time. Once again- the ideas expressed above are solely my opinions. I do not claim to represent AT+T, District 9, or CWA in any capacity.</Msg><Username>n1tr0x3n</Username><Timestamp>1344301340000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 21:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344304328000-38</Id><Topic><Title>Strike in DIST 9?</Title><Username>josieinib</Username><Timestamp>1344298108000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 20:08:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have to report to San Ramon tomorrow so I guess there is a strike. Hopefully it won't last long and as a former union tech I'm surprised that a strike would be called in an economy like this. I think there are some in my group that may have to report to the east coast for duty.</Msg><Username>sflens412</Username><Timestamp>1344304328000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 21:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344304369000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Strike in DIST 9?</Title><Username>josieinib</Username><Timestamp>1344298108000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 20:08:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Walk out? No way. They are all going to settle - they don't want a year to go by like Verizon. The CWA is dead meat!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1344304369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 21:52:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344304607000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Strike in DIST 9?</Title><Username>josieinib</Username><Timestamp>1344298108000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 20:08:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for a post that made sense. Locals websites are finally catching up</Msg><Username>josieinib</Username><Timestamp>1344304607000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 21:56:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344306296000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Strike in DIST 9?</Title><Username>josieinib</Username><Timestamp>1344298108000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 20:08:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I made no definitive predictions. You could be absolutely right about that entire string of speculations and innuendo. Unlike you, I have no infallible crystal ball. But I'm confused...if you're impeccable at predicting the future, and not just another hired mouth...why aren't you too rich to bother with the picayune concerns of the ants so far beneath you?</Msg><Username>n1tr0x3n</Username><Timestamp>1344306296000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 22:24:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344306419000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Strike in DIST 9?</Title><Username>josieinib</Username><Timestamp>1344298108000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 20:08:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The pleasure was entirely mine.</Msg><Username>n1tr0x3n</Username><Timestamp>1344306419000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 22:26:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344306773000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Unsustainable</Title><Username>macnaughtonr</Username><Timestamp>1344262031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:07:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for your succinct and well supported post- if more were like it, this site would be a pleasure to visit- not a pigsty to winnow for the rare pearl of genuine wisdom...</Msg><Username>n1tr0x3n</Username><Timestamp>1344306773000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 22:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344308756000-44</Id><Topic><Title>Strike in DIST 9?</Title><Username>josieinib</Username><Timestamp>1344298108000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 20:08:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rick, I'm not sure why they would have me report to the company headquarters in California if there wasn't a walkout. Like I said, I hope it doesn't last long.</Msg><Username>sflens412</Username><Timestamp>1344308756000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 23:05:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344311961000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Strike in DIST 9?</Title><Username>josieinib</Username><Timestamp>1344298108000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 20:08:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>n1tr0x3n ,, I've been reading your posts, along with several others on this board, for several years. I would like to say, you have earned my respect with your understanding of employee mistreatment. Employees are taken advantage of on a daily basis. If the CWA members do not take a stand, they will be working for minimum wage soon. As an employee, I gave the CWA an ultimatum to either "grow a pair" or I would drop out of the union and teach 10% each year how to do the same (as you may know the employees can't just walk away from the union, there are rules). The CWA has not stood up for us in many years. As of now, I have not been a member for 2 years. I support my brothers/sisters all of the way, however, I don't believe the CWA deserves my dues. I am more mad at the CWA for allowing AT&amp;T to do what they do, than I am at AT&amp;T for doing it. I know I may have alienated some union members, but the CWA is no different than AT&amp;T,, they are both in it for the money. The CWA represents more than just Communications Workers,, they represent, city employees and electrical workers and much more. Heck, wave a dollar in front of them and they will negotiate a lousy contract for you and tell you it's the best they could do. I could go on and on,, and even give you instances,, but it would only satisfy my need to vent,, the UNION MEMBERS and Employees need to strike and stop the abuse. I see comments putting down union employees because they say we are over paid for what we do. And all I can say to those people is walk a mile in my shoes before you say another word. Thanks n1tr0x3n for opening the can of worms that will make this one of the most read posts on the board.</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1344311961000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 23:59:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>