<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346506085000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Original Chinese Proverb: Give a man a fish and he will eat for a day. Teach a man to fish and he will eat for a lifetime. 2012 White House Revision: Give a man a welfare check, a free cell phone with unlimited free minutes, cash for his clunker, food stamps, section 8 housing, free contraceptives, Medicaid, ninety-nine weeks of unemployment, free meds, and he will vote Democratic the rest of his life; even after he's deceased.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346506085000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346510700000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Have a look at AT&amp;T,Inc. (T)</Title><Username>winifredcol704547</Username><Timestamp>1346332625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 09:17:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got it for free. Thank you</Msg><Username>peggyhyw487916</Username><Timestamp>1346510700000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 10:45:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346513900000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Have a look at AT&amp;T,Inc. (T)</Title><Username>winifredcol704547</Username><Timestamp>1346332625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 09:17:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just subscribed. I am hoping for the best.</Msg><Username>rosettefpz99868</Username><Timestamp>1346513900000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:38:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346514706000-4</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT</Title><Username>nova_janine34</Username><Timestamp>1346502510000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 08:28:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good luck to everyone!</Msg><Username>santos_lesley07</Username><Timestamp>1346514706000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346514877000-5</Id><Topic><Title>In all circumstances of dealings AT&amp;T Inc. is a Crack in One Stock</Title><Username>molinaware916</Username><Timestamp>1346513731000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:35:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you can keep "duct tape" on his mouth and a full cast on his "left hand" for the next couple of months, the market may do ok !!</Msg><Username>skinneroconnor344</Username><Timestamp>1346514877000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:54:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346515821000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The orignal plan of herding people into the dome did not work out the last time, maybe rommie is looking into plan #2. Sorry repuks!!</Msg><Username>orri1934</Username><Timestamp>1346515821000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:10:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346516198000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The biggest liar in our history, has to be jerking GWB, invaded a country and caused the death of 400,000 people. Give it up puks he cost us big time.</Msg><Username>orri1934</Username><Timestamp>1346516198000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:16:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346516826000-8</Id><Topic><Title>In all circumstances of dealings AT&amp;T Inc. is a Crack in One Stock</Title><Username>molinaware916</Username><Timestamp>1346513731000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:35:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be waiting for more great news to come.</Msg><Username>burgesssantos913</Username><Timestamp>1346516826000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:27:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346517854000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True leaders would have stayed and taken action. GWB, using his powers could have forced to take action, or else get less in Federal Money. 11 Just like on 9/11 when he sat, and read the book to he children. This time he posed a photo out AF1 looking down on New Orleans His next major photo opt was in the rubble of the Twin Towers with the mayor Then best of all on the flight deck with flight jacket, and Mission Accomplished. I would take Clints preformance over all of these.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346517854000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:44:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346518359000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unlike the Obama's the Romney's did not have it easy when they started out living in a basement apartment. BO lived a privledged life attending private school in Hawaii few people could afford. BO never had a regular job or ran a business. Michelle Obama revealed that she got into Princeton not on the strength of her grades, which she admits were unexceptional, but thanks to her brother Craig, a star athlete and gifted student who preceded her to the school. As a ‘legacy’ candidate and a beneficiary of affirmative action, Michelle Obama was granted an opportunity that others more accomplished were denied. The thesis written by Michelle LaVaughn Robinson (now Obama) in 1985, contains three unmitigated impediments that would have rendered the paper an automatic F in the Introduction to the Research Paper yet it was accepted at her Ivy League Princeton University alma mater. Moochelle came from a upper middle class family. The Obama's are out of touch with America having never faced the struggles that most Americans face. Aided by affirmative action, big money connections and insulating themselves from a multi cultural America they don't understand life outside the black community and are of the opinion they were screwed by white America and carry a chip on thier shoulder when the opposite is true.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346518359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:52:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346519042000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Clinton had the opportunity to stop bin laden and prevented 911 and 2 wars. Instead he decided to do nothing. Bush had to deal with the aftermath of Clinton's non action and did so with the approval of democrats that included Hillary Clinton at the time. Where have you been living, in a cave with the Taliban</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346519042000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:04:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346519485000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ignores New Orleans</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346432456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;Just like on 9/11 when he sat, and read the book to he children. What is your point. Yeah W was at a school reading a book to children when he got the awful news.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346519485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346520169000-13</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346210905000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 23:28:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As a good Christian, what do you think about abortion and gay marriage that your democrat party and leader support?</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346520169000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:22:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346531935000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Feinstein Complains Gas Too High?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346201792000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These are the highest Labor Day Gas prices ever. Barry's energy policies (there really isn't one), is to close down all the coal fired plants, never again build another refinery, and funnel money to his cronies. Those at Soylindra, and those other similar companies are stealing our hard earned money. Regime Change is just weeks away. Giving billions to Venezeula, of our stimulus money should be an impeachable offense. He gave them boatloads of money, saying build it. Employ your people, and we will be your biggest customers. Now Chavez is getting cozy with the Chinese. So now we are getting it at both ends. The overburdened, American Taxpayer is being forced to bankroll these dictators. But, via the American Voter, we can end the economic slavery we are forced to endure under this Presidental Fool. Slavery will end once, and for all,here in November. This Black man can't wait. Help me retire Obummer to the golf course. VOTE FOR ROMNEY RYAN. Then watch the gas prices fall.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346531935000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346532255000-15</Id><Topic><Title>In all circumstances of dealings AT&amp;T Inc. is a Crack in One Stock</Title><Username>molinaware916</Username><Timestamp>1346513731000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:35:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see enormous potential and great expansion of the hispanic market in the U.S.I am glad I was able to get into this at the beginning stage.</Msg><Username>lynda.guy74</Username><Timestamp>1346532255000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346534621000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Feinstein Complains Gas Too High?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346201792000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama never said that about gas prices. He never said that regarding European Gas Prices. Europe funds many of their social programs, health, education, road repairs etc. from the price of fuel. They pay roughly the same price for the basic fuel that we do. The higher price funds social programs.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346534621000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:23:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346534860000-17</Id><Title>California's Brown to Ok Illegals &amp; Cars</Title><Msg>Gov. Jerry Brown in a pre-election payoff, is expected to sign into law a bill shortly, that gives young illegals driver's licenses, in heavily Dem controlled California. Is it really fair to give them El Presidente Obummer's 2 year freeze on deportations, and then expect them to walk, or take public transportation? Blacks were brought here in chains over 450 years ago. Will we ever get something from this Presidente? Like, maybe a job or something. If illegals don't like it here, they can always head south of the border, down Mexico way.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346534860000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:27:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346535423000-18</Id><Title>European Social Programs &amp; Ours</Title><Msg>Comparing health care in the United States to Obamacare, the European System and our Socialized Program. A person is in need of health care, and does not have any doctors, or may even be in another city. What do they do, go the the nearest emergency room of course. They get in to the streams of care, slowing that of others. They are given the care they need to stabilize, or remedy there needs. Well, without insurance,or money, we the people who have health insurance each get charged more so the hospital gets their money. In a non-socialized responsible system everyone would be have to carry insurance, just like driving a car. This would be the fair responsible solution. Instead we have an unfair Socialized one where the responsible are paying more, due to these free loaders. In Europe they pay higher taxes, higher cost of Petro, and get free healthcare, and education based on their abilities. All the people are better off, except for the Insurance Companies that used to screw you out of services you thought you were covered for.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346535423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:37:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346535631000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Feinstein Complains Gas Too High?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346201792000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sorry Minnie, but you should look it up. Barry has said very clearly, several times. He believes, even his Energy Secretary has said so also, that they prefer higher gas prices here, much closer to those of Europe. The only problem, which he isn't saying much about, is oil/gas peaking right before his re-election. Clearly, he has said that we should stop subsidizing oil, many times. He wants to subsidize algae, and other hair brain schemes. I believe as Romney, we should have an all out approach. We should do everything we can to make America energy independent.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346535631000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:40:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346537249000-20</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346210905000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 23:28:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I personally do not chose abortion. I would recomend adoption. If it is definitly known a newborn will be a mass burdon on society, I would recommend the parents decide. If it would cost the remainder of society money, I would vote for abortion, the Eskimos, Indians, Viking, and most societies have done the same. If one has the money, or chooses to care for the individual let them. As a Christian, abortion policy, birthcontrol, for birthcontrols sake, should follow church guidelines. Our churches have failed us, and helped make it a political issue. More sinner makes for more business. In fact that is why the Vatican has decided we are not alone, maybe for the same reason. If our Government is involved it would only be to regulate, and license providers capable of providing safe, women's health services. This would be on a personal health card to prevent abuse. Regarding the GOP they use it as a hot button issue. Why, because their tent is becoming smaller. Look at them mostly rich, or think their rich white people as voters. They need the relgious right, for their support and vote. I personally feel they never really plan on stopping abortion, for they will lose support. It is like a cure for cancer, let's treat it instead of preventing it. A Christian is a sinner that knows he is, and believe most the the people also have a dark side. He tries to do unto other as they do unto him. Life is sacred, all life, rich, poor, or powerful. I am a pragmatic Christian, who is disappointed with the reason's I feel many are Christian. They, are purely in it for their own benefits. I have been near death, three times, I am not afraid of death. Once, the first time I truly did not want to come back. A true Christan, or ______religion should not have a fear of death.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346537249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346537495000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “Unlike the Obama's the Romney's did not have it easy when they started out. The Obama's are out of touch with America having never faced the struggles that most Americans face.” – fake ricky with the L Dude, just putting nonsense together doesn’t mean it’s remotely true, or that you’re influencing anyone at all. You are beyond delusional and look hideously foolish. Right, Mitt had it really tough, growing up in the ghettos of Bloomfield Hills, Michigan, and having to fight it out in the ‘hood at Cranbook Preparatory School. His dad became Governor when Mitt was only 15. I’m sure a 3 time Governor and CEO of American Motors didn’t leave much inheritance to pass on - probably just an old Nash Rambler and a savings bond. He also said earlier this year, that he didn’t inherit any money from his father. But then he qualified that: “What I got from my parents when they passed away I gave away to charity and TO MY KIDS.” “Passing your inheritance on to your children is not the same as not inheriting money at all. And it actually makes me a bit curious: a common estate-tax reduction strategy known as a dynasty trust relies on skipping generations. Did Romney pass on his inheritance to his kids for tax reasons? It's hard to know without seeing his tax returns—and that's another reason why he should release them.” – Nick Baumann, Mother Jones So, in your eyes, he’s a self-made man. Let’s see how he did that, and what you, some dipstick in a cubicle at minimum wage, is defending: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rodifJlis2c</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346537495000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346537841000-22</Id><Topic><Title>European Social Programs &amp; Ours</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346535423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:37:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With european socialized care, you will need to wait months to get the service you require and depending on the budget you may need to wait until the following year when the budget is renewed to receive care , the care is rationed depending on your age and productivity, you may not be eligible for care according to government tables depending on your age and other factors, like Obama likes to say take the pill to deal with pain because you are not getting life saving care your time is up. Ask your doctors what they think of Obamacare.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1346537841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346539316000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Romney's were married on March 21, 1969, Mitt received an inheritance from is father 26 years later in 1995 long after he became successful. Romney did not need the money so the donated it. So what are you saying where was the benefit from the inheritance when it took 26 years to get it? The Obama's did not grow up poor. Since you brought up donations lets talk a little about the Obama's donations to charity which amouted to less than 1% during a time when they were multi millionares.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346539316000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:41:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346539553000-24</Id><Topic><Title>European Social Programs &amp; Ours</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346535423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:37:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Christian what are you views on abortion and gay marriage the Obama supports?</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1346539553000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:45:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346540816000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Feinstein Complains Gas Too High?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346201792000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just heard Lester Holt report tonight. So you know this is gospel. Gas in California, and in Chicago is around $4.74 a gallon. It makes me feel better to know that these 2 Dem infested areas should be the highest in the Nation. It's hopeless change, moving forward. Or some other Communist inspired manta. I just hope a few of my fellow Americans wise up before the election. If Barry's words solved anything, then I'd gladly support him. It's like the Seinfeld skit, about reservations. He makes a reservation, then goes there, and they don't honor it. He says you know how to make a reservation, but you don't know how to keep it. Just like Barry's promises, reservations never kept. Now many of his former supporters are having reservations about voting for him again. Four more years of this would be pure insanity. What plan does he have? Spend and tax, and more illegal immigration. That's going to make the average American's life better.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346540816000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:06:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346543714000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is Robert Reich's beliefs: "Political and philosophical stances Official Department of Labor portrait of Robert Reich In an interview with The New York Times, he explained that "I don't believe in redistribution of wealth for the sake of redistributing wealth. But I am concerned about how we can afford to pay for what we as a nation need to do."[22] In response to a question as to what to recommend to the incoming president regarding a fair and sustainable income and wealth distribution, Reich said, "Expand the Earned Income Tax Credit — a wage supplement for lower-income people, and finance it with a higher marginal income tax on the top five percent. For the longer term, invest in education for lower income communities, starting with early-childhood education and extending all the way up to better access to post-secondary education."[22] Reich is pro-union, saying "Unionization is not just good for workers in unions, unionization is very, very important for the economy overall, and would create broad benefits for the United States."[23][24]" He is completetly leftist in his thinking and politics! Why would anybody believe he would he would accept any moderate view?s</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1346543714000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:55:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346544041000-27</Id><Topic><Title>California's Brown to Ok Illegals &amp; Cars</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346534860000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:27:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The number they frequently throw around for the unemployed is 23 Million people. So wouldn't it just stand to reason that some of these unemployed Americans, have lost their jobs to illegals. The estimate of illegals here is anywhere from 11 Million to 40 Million. We've been Barracked.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346544041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:00:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346544473000-28</Id><Topic><Title>California's Brown to Ok Illegals &amp; Cars</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346534860000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:27:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Betcha this don't come out at the DNC!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346544473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:07:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346544620000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Clint's speech...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346421841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney's donation was 15% of his income.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346544620000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:10:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346549376000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Feinstein Complains Gas Too High?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346201792000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea, and the stock market too. No, pres can control gas prices until we stop the give aways to them.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346549376000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346549999000-31</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT</Title><Username>nova_janine34</Username><Timestamp>1346502510000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 08:28:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess I agree with that.</Msg><Username>giselle_daphne47</Username><Timestamp>1346549999000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346551113000-32</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT</Title><Username>nova_janine34</Username><Timestamp>1346502510000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 08:28:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are best.</Msg><Username>ardith_ester23</Username><Timestamp>1346551113000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:58:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>