<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350733430753-1</Id><Topic><Title>BO Libya coverup</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350676056846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea, he got Osma bin Laden alright. 8 years and nothing. It took Obama to do the job. W could talk. W could swagger. All hat but no cows---just like the rest of the Republicans.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1350733430753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 07:43:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350734326463-2</Id><Topic><Title>BO Libya coverup</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350676056846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Real cover up who is Willard Mitt Romney. He grew up so rich, I do not think he knows himself, nor can he relate to people without a script. Maybe he can relate to a company he wants to take over, but me or any common man forget it. He is like an android from another place.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1350734326463</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 07:58:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350734565860-3</Id><Topic><Title>BO Libya coverup</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350676056846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well after the big screw-up 9/11 he did not want another. also compared to 9/11 what does this libya thing amount to other than political hay. sure we lost 4 americans. yet, in the same time how many were killed in afganistan?</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1350734565860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:02:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350734987527-4</Id><Topic><Title>Weapons Ban in the US .. By U.N. (thru Obama's back door deal)</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1350699340119</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 22:15:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “This weapons ban for the U.S. is due to be voted on by the U.N. in the very near future…it's another one of his backdoor deals to be voted on by a U.N. Charter to "disarm" all of it's (sic) current member countries…blah, blah, bluster and bull snot…then Obama has now allowed ‘firearms’ ownership to become ‘illegal’ !! – lying jon You are truly a disgusting, lying piece of trash. This coming election is going to demonstrate that evil special interests cannot buy and lie their way into owning this country. As if trying to politicize the loss of public servants isn’t bad enough, you add this Tea Party email garbage, knowing full well that it’s a bunch of lies designed to scare people. From Fact Check (jon, ask someone in the next cubicle to explain to you what a “fact” is.) Q: Has Obama found a "legal way around the Second Amendment"? A: The administration’s agreement to talk about writing a United Nations treaty to regulate arms exports and imports is a far cry from banning possession of firearms, which Obama says he doesn’t want to do and the Supreme Court has said can’t be done anyway. We’ve received many queries about this chain e-mail, which refers to a proposed United Nations treaty to regulate the global trade of conventional weapons. Much of what this e-mail claims is simply false. A "complete ban on all weapons for US citizens" isn’t possible under our Constitution, according to the Supreme Court, which held just last year that: Furthermore, if an arms trade treaty ever materializes, the administration won’t be able to "bypass" Congress, as the e-mail maintains. All international treaties require the approval of two-thirds of the Senate before they are considered ratified and in effect. In addition, the idea that a treaty necessarily would make U.S. citizens ‘subject to those gun laws created by foreign governments,’ as the e-mail claims, is wrong. Treaties don’t subject one nations’s citizens to the laws of other nations. (here a long explanation criticizing con artists from the gun lobby, like jon and John Bolton, about creating fear, followed by) That’s Bolton’s opinion. The fact is that a provision in the resolution’s preamble – included at the request of the U.S. – explicitly recognizes the right of nations to regulate gun sales and ownership within their borders, including through their constitutions.” – Fact Check Once again, jon is spreading intentional lies, assuming that the average American will believe anything. The sad part is that many on his side, do. And who, exactly, would benefit from people believing this nonsense? Oh, maybe the planet’s largest arms exporter, who sells close to 10 Billion in arms around the world. And that would be us – the U.S. Of course, in jon’s world, they’re just more job creators, I’m sure. Won’t any of you moderates stand up for a change and tell your base that if you have to lie about issues, you’re probably wrong about them – or you’re simply representing some very select special interests.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1350734987527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:09:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350736052360-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama will ban guns in his second term!!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1350575258049</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 11:47:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “Back in the day, my assigned weapon was the M 14 .. with a rock &amp; roll switch. On full-auto .. after the 5th round you were just about shootin at da buzzards in flight .. yee-haw !!” – G.I. jon “Yee-haw, we’re drinkin’ more moonshine and shootin buzzards” What are you…Jed Clampett out exploring for oil in the swamps? Hey, jon, if you ever had an M-14 you’d full well know that anyone can take out the trigger mechanism and file down the sear, and…..voilà…you’re on fully-automatic. Of course, you can no longer fire on semi. Plus it’s against the law, mind you and I wouldn’t recommend it, but it really makes most of the argument about fully-automatic and semi-automatic a moot point, because you can do it with most semi’s. But, you’d have known that if you ever had one.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1350736052360</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350736749111-6</Id><Topic><Title>BO Libya coverup</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350676056846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't wait for the kenyan action figure to be released this Christmas! G.I. Obama!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1350736749111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:39:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350742833684-7</Id><Topic><Title>BO Libya coverup</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350676056846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Clinton chased him for years and couldn't get him when people told him where he was, the media was interviewing him and he was still using cell phones. He was easy to find; several foreign units tried to get Clinton to take him out and he wouldn't...missing him might have screwed up his legacy more than missing him. Had Clinton done his job early on, we might not have even had 9/11.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1350742833684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 10:20:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350743970709-8</Id><Topic><Title>BO Libya coverup</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350676056846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yur making up stories to cover up Miff's big failure at the debate. Miff didn't hear the President's statements on Libya, but got info from faux news, Miff didn't know what Lilly Ledbeder law was, nor Blount amendment, just doesn't know everyday facts. His memory is shot, really shot. They call it Romnesia now, but it's true. One day for one thing, next day the opposite thing. Outsouring American jobs to China, right now with his own company, doesn't seem to know about it. It's all over the news. Some of those if not all those people may go on unemployment and even have to get food stamps. Belongs to the mormon cult, preaches non violence yet his kid wants to punch the President for saying "not true", not saying "liar" but just "not true." I really really wished he had run up and tried it, the punk needs a litle time in a cell with some friends.. Obama on the other hand, saved the tire plant in the same town Romney is closing one, and put a tariff on Chinese tires. That's doing something.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1350743970709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 10:39:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350744514434-9</Id><Topic><Title>BO Libya coverup</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350676056846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The President has never said there is no Al-quaeda, never, you made that up. He sure as shootin' has put a big hole in them though.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1350744514434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 10:48:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350744776962-10</Id><Title>stock market indicators</Title><Msg>Excellent analysis and commentary! copy and paste the below to your browser goo.gl/naCJn</Msg><Username>josephjohn977</Username><Timestamp>1350744776962</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 10:52:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350749329880-11</Id><Topic><Title>BO Libya coverup</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350676056846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Al Queda was and still is a front for the CIA. WE are arming Al Queda in Syria. The Muslim Brotherhood is also a front for both British and American intelligence agencies and has been since the 1920's. Americans are fools for believing anything that comes out of government or the privately run propaganda operations of the so called "Free" press.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1350749329880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 12:08:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350749537516-12</Id><Topic><Title>T Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>douglasinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1350733116134</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 07:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well this is not a mind blowing app, but it is useful and I like it - thanks for the tip.</Msg><Username>frozencustardking</Username><Timestamp>1350749537516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 12:12:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350751478585-13</Id><Title>Any info yet *</Title><Msg>On who put that $4 billion dollar payout from T in the merger talks with T Mobile . ....... we would all like to know how they come up with that number ?</Msg><Username>onebellplaza</Username><Timestamp>1350751478585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 12:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350752803530-14</Id><Topic><Title>BO Libya coverup</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350676056846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The President has never said there is no Al-quaeda" I agree with you on that one. However, I did hear him in his stump speeches suggest we had them on the run. Al Qaeda obviously begs to differ given the Libyan Embassy disaster. His position reminds me of Bush's premature victory banner. It sure pains you guys when the shoe is on the other foot.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1350752803530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350752855623-15</Id><Topic><Title>Any info yet *</Title><Username>onebellplaza</Username><Timestamp>1350751478585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 12:44:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>quack, quack, quack...</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1350752855623</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:07:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350753729182-16</Id><Topic><Title>BO Libya coverup</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350676056846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Al qaeda, I hate to even advertise their name by writing it, is on the run, and it takes only fairly small bands or even one nut, to wreak havoc on decent people. 99% of Libyans are going to be found to be nice folks just like everywhere, most folks are nice and just trying to live quietly. When he says they are on the run I don't hear any victory speech like GWB's. I don't criticize GWB for saying that either, not so sensitive on words and monday morning quarter backing. It's all on a best effort basis and to parse every word a person says is sort of a waste of time.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1350753729182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350758104588-17</Id><Title>chart looks like a double top..look out below</Title><Msg>34.60 ish</Msg><Username>rmbdata</Username><Timestamp>1350758104588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 14:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350768690454-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama will ban guns in his second term!!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1350575258049</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 11:47:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What? You'll finally shoot yourself in the head?</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1350768690454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 17:31:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350768740720-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama will ban guns in his second term!!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1350575258049</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 11:47:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're an idiot.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1350768740720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 17:32:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350772041556-20</Id><Topic><Title>BO Libya coverup</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350676056846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorta like putting man on the moon. Neither Kennedy nor Johnson could do it. It took a Republican in 1969 named Nixon.</Msg><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1350772041556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 18:27:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350775708085-21</Id><Title>IF YOU'VE CAUGHT ROMNESIA, GO TO YOUTUBE AND HEAR ROMNEY'S PAST VIEWS?</Title><Msg>He's got none. Romnesia!. Pres. Obama has a cure for you.</Msg><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1350775708085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350776521107-22</Id><Topic><Title>ATT retiree benefits</Title><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1343908864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is an old message board but we just got our costs from AT&amp;T for our healthcare 2013. It tripled! $220+ for one dependent (wife). No prior warning. Anyone else freaking out???? Husband retired in 2008. We're worried. We're on a fixed income.</Msg><Username>byroncaroline</Username><Timestamp>1350776521107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:42:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350777963193-23</Id><Topic><Title>BO Libya coverup</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350676056846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Al qaeda, I hate to even advertise their name by writing it, is on the run" If so, I wonder why he took the term "on the run" out of his stump speech over the last several days. Couldn't be because of the Embassy mess, could it? It's not like him to miss a trick.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1350777963193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 20:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350782015198-24</Id><Topic><Title>BO Libya coverup</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350676056846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all these theories about what Obama thinks and what must be because of how he is etc, what he must have taken out of a speech and why did he, on and on, give it a break already. He is a good decent man who doesn't look for tricks as far as I have seen. you just saw romney looking to trick Obama at the debate trying to catch him on his words, but it failed. Then faux news lies all the next day about what the president said and makes a big artificial story out of it. give it a break, it isn't gaining votes only driving those not entrenched in the tea party away. Romney screwed up, say it like it is and people respect that more.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1350782015198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 21:13:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350783964176-25</Id><Topic><Title>Weapons Ban in the US .. By U.N. (thru Obama's back door deal)</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1350699340119</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 22:15:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why do you republican conversatives always bring up the gun issues near election time? You said similiar things with Clinton.</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1350783964176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 21:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>