<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354001605439-1</Id><Topic><Title>Pensions</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1353718010663</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:46:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" pensions were converted to cash-balance accounts. " That was why I left AT&amp;T after more than 20 years service. BECAUSE THEY SCREWED LONG TERM EMPLOYEES WITH THAT CASH BALANCE GARBAGE. At the time, I read that the ceo was given a 2ndary pension to make up the difference ...but the emps got shafted. I decided to roll my pension into an IRA but have to 'retire' out to do it...which i did.</Msg><Username>zbgb952</Username><Timestamp>1354001605439</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 02:33:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354023686943-2</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet: cap gain 30%, 50% tax on the rich</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353097971771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “I read today where the Obama team is E-mailing donors and other supporters…in support of the administration…blah, blah, blah…Sound like an administration that hasn't developed a good strategy…” - winholder OH, Heavens to Murgatroyd!!!! What kind of unseemly band of unscrupulous, dilettante politicians would stoop to such dastardly shenanigans? Imagine the remorseless group of opportunistic low-lifes who would resort to Machiavellian techniques like using current, highly effective, information technology such as social networks and (gasp) emails!!! How dare them! Oh, wait a minute…isn’t that some of the 21st Century current state of affairs of a well organized political movement in today’s real world, that connects with a broad based coalition of diverse demographic populations?...the same one that just led to the embarrassing blow-out of the party of old, angry, white guys who can’t turn on a computer and rely on yard signs, voter suppression and gerrymandering as their only political strategy.Yeah, thought so. But keep vilifying their efforts with direct mail and windshield hand bills next time. I’m thinkin’ maybe throw in more billboards, some Ham Radio advertising and perhaps some sky-writing in ’16.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1354023686943</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 08:41:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354026566367-3</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet: cap gain 30%, 50% tax on the rich</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353097971771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"needs the mindless, which have no responsibility for spending or tax laws to sell their story for them." Complete lack of self awareness!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354026566367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 09:29:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354030887458-4</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet: cap gain 30%, 50% tax on the rich</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353097971771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Where have they actually acted like sound stewards of OUR money and have spent it wisely" The past is over and we are moving forward. Maybe we can learn and change. If you want to change things go do it. Talking doesn't do it. Don't start unending wars on a credit card. The previous President announced the iraq war was over in 2003. Govt waste is nothing new. Monday morning quarterbacking is so easy, isn't it. The President has the correct approach. There really is no argument any more to keep taxes cut 5% for those making over 250K net income. Grover is being exposed and failing, the jig is up on buying America through a hired lobbyist.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1354030887458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 10:41:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354031797045-5</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet: cap gain 30%, 50% tax on the rich</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353097971771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Grover is being exposed and failing, the jig is up on buying America through a hired lobbyist." It is telling watching him on TV telling elected officials what they can and cannot do. Who's the boss? The American people or Grover Norquist, the lobbyist? With the Citizen's United decision, they thought they could just buy an election. They couldn't.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354031797045</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 10:56:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354034991806-6</Id><Title>ARENA WIGHT LOSS DRUG FRIST IN 13 YEAR FDA APPROVAL DEA ANY DAY ITS A GREAT DRUG BELVIQ FOR OBESTY AND DIBETIC</Title><Msg>$9 a share look for $ 15 or more read up on it you wont be sorry ;over 150 milliion people need this drug ;</Msg><Username>frankiepro1964</Username><Timestamp>1354034991806</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 11:49:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354037921041-7</Id><Topic><Title>why is T so dam popular?</Title><Username>sera.rusch</Username><Timestamp>1354023100159</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 08:31:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Focus on the NEWS only</Msg><Username>berry.attal</Username><Timestamp>1354037921041</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 12:38:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354039710047-8</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet: cap gain 30%, 50% tax on the rich</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353097971771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The past is over and we are moving forward. But you keep referring to the past and to things Bush did or didn't do, how is that moving forward? Does that statement mean no more Bush slamming posts? I don't really care, because you're right on the money, the past is the past and the future with this President and the proven idiots in the Democratic Congress scare the BeJesus out of me.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1354039710047</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:08:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354039849883-9</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet: cap gain 30%, 50% tax on the rich</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353097971771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"OH, Heavens to Murgatroyd!!!! What kind of unseemly band of unscrupulous, dilettante politicians would stoop to such dastardly shenanigans? Imagine the remorseless group of opportunistic low-lifes who would resort to Machiavellian techniques like using current, highly effective, information technology such as social networks and (gasp) emails!!! How dare them!" You nailed it bozo. Good job.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1354039849883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:10:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354039915289-10</Id><Title>ATT.....HORRIBLE DSL SERVICE...</Title><Msg>I've had them for about 4 years. Two years ago I was still happy with their service. Has now deteriorated to a PITIFUL level. Often I can't "connect" and when I can it performs slowly, if at all, unless of course I go on in the middle of the night. That's when I sleep. They have to do something about the bandwidth hogs.</Msg><Username>keltus1952</Username><Timestamp>1354039915289</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:11:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354040215620-11</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet: cap gain 30%, 50% tax on the rich</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353097971771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's the Bully Pulpit. Teddy Roosevelt named it, FDR refined it in the fireside chats, but Reagan is considered the master at using public pressure to bend Congress. Obama's pretty good too.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354040215620</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:16:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354040620323-12</Id><Topic><Title>T is one of top picks like crimson on apex</Title><Username>ethelvillarreal43</Username><Timestamp>1353943269318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:21:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't see that coming</Msg><Username>cynthiagibson333</Username><Timestamp>1354040620323</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:23:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354040841435-13</Id><Topic><Title>Twinkie Defense</Title><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1353156558534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 07:49:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cisco, apparently you haven't heard about the Hostess Bakery bailout: The Feds have come to the rescue again: The State Department hired all the Twinkies, the Secret Service hired all the HoHos, the generals are sleeping with the Cupcakes and voters sent all the Ding Dongs to Congress.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1354040841435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:27:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354042506719-14</Id><Topic><Title>T is one of top picks like crimson on apex</Title><Username>ethelvillarreal43</Username><Timestamp>1353943269318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:21:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very well written!</Msg><Username>herrington.vincent</Username><Timestamp>1354042506719</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:55:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354049413408-15</Id><Title>Run Leemons Run.</Title><Msg>Where are all the cool headed fearless courage and fortitude in the richest brightest largest economy in the world. I know the very very very smartest is out about the world eliminating threats to our nation. fear not stand firm and strong. do not be afraid the news media is useless airtime filled with garbage. They have to selll uselesss unecessary crap to the moonbeams.</Msg><Username>capp013</Username><Timestamp>1354049413408</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:50:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354054406479-16</Id><Topic><Title>Pensions</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1353718010663</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:46:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Retired BELLSOUTH now AT&amp;T, my medical plan going up by $248.19 a month starting Jan.2013.</Msg><Username>frb53</Username><Timestamp>1354054406479</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 17:13:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354057741261-17</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet: cap gain 30%, 50% tax on the rich</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353097971771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But you keep referring to the past and to things Bush did or didn't do, how is that moving forward?" I have blamed GWB, because you kept blaming Obama since jan 2009. Never heard Obama blame him. Just the situation he inherited, he says, no specific name. Put the listening ears on. It's 100% true, so why not say it? GWB needs to be blamed though, should be jailed, even, haw haw haw. Go ahead, anti Obama all you want, all day all night, don't vote for him too.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1354057741261</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 18:09:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354058255442-18</Id><Title>RENO &amp;CALI</Title><Msg>Ready for ESRO offer on Monday?</Msg><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1354058255442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 18:17:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354058674501-19</Id><Topic><Title>Pensions</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1353718010663</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:46:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>glad to hear some likes att. i as a stock holder think u are full of it . how much did u invest or r u just living off the gravy</Msg><Username>marioncohen92</Username><Timestamp>1354058674501</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 18:24:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354061160479-20</Id><Topic><Title>Pensions</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1353718010663</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:46:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure who you are addressing. My investment in AT&amp;T is about 6,200 shares. At current pricing that's over 200 grand. Buying the stock option whetted my interest in investing. My first purchase in the mid 50's was just 4 shares.. I've bought into many other stocks since. Even put money into 3 start up companies. One paid off really well. I sold last year for a better than 8% compounded gain since 1963. It is a well established company that makes a well known brand of sporting goods. The other two went down the drain but the one more than made up for them. I used AT&amp;T shares to stay debt free when I bought my first house in 1963. Many of my co-workers preferred to blow their money on booze, tobacco, ATV's, etc., etc.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1354061160479</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 19:06:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354069225787-21</Id><Topic><Title>Has aggressive 'Fix The Debt' campaign started yet?</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1353427660081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 11:07:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll never forget that special night when Barrack was first placed in charge of this Great Country. The hope, the vision. Barry was a clean slate. He promised to be for the people, the most transparent administration ever. Well, that lasted no time. We got that health care bill. Full of pork. Back to that special night, seeing Jesse Jackson crying, with those big alligator tears. Wondering, what does Barrack have that I don't? It's teleprompter reading, and never taking a stand on anything. Just voting present. I wish Barry would really do what is needed. Now, that he is safely re-elected, I mean. Please Barrack, if you are listening. Please appoint Jesse to a czarship, or something. He was there at the side of Martin when he fell. A real leader. Martin was a Republican. It's is a right thing to give Jesse his due.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354069225787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 21:20:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>