<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347508804664-1</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SHOW US YOUR GRADES ! WHY ARE THEY SEALED FROM THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ! NO OTHER PRESIDENT HAS EVER SEALED THEM BEFORE</Title><Username>americasaveit</Username><Timestamp>1347449773918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's grades make Biden look like a genius</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347508804664</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:00:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347511936016-2</Id><Title>Blood on Obama's Hands</Title><Msg>Obama knew on Sept 5 another attack was coming on 9/11, yet he did nothing. Four people are dead. He has taken out every ruler in the middle east and lead the way for the Muslim Brotherhood. Sharia law is their law. Anyone who can't see this is blind. Obama doesn't bother to take care of business at the White House and refuses to meet with Israel's leader, and yes, Israel asked, Obama said no, when the Muslim Brotherhood has had multiple meetings with White House staff. With the middle east in crisis, Obama continues to campaign in Nevada. Then to cover up his incompetence, he blames Romney for making a statement in support of the United States. Obama has blood on his hands.It is time for this president to be voted out, kicked out, just OUT! Only an anti-American would see this another way. Of course, we already know there are plenty of those stirring up trouble in this country. How much more can this country take? The unemployment numbers are being rigged, inflation is at the grocery store, Obama's team has loaded this country to fail. The stock market is being held up to try and get Obama re-elected because there is no economic reason it should be sky high as it is and is just waiting for the thread it's hanging on....to break. There is no other explanation. That doesn't even cover the 16 Trillion in debt on this country that is about to devalue our currency to equal Mexico City.He is even worse than Jimmy Carter. It is time to get this bad actor out of our country's business.He has failed on everything. Could he do worse, I hope not, but I keep thinking he can't do any worse....but he does.There is no defense of this president that makes sense...except that they're democrat......that's not a sufficient defense.</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1347511936016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:52:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347513367182-3</Id><Topic><Title>Barry's Real Employment Plan</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347156540219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:09:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are correct about the Spanish. Obama has lost the Latino vote. They left a country of corruption......they recognize it when they see it and they do not like Obama. However, latinos stay very quiet. Those who can vote, will vote, but no one will know how they feel. Their way is to be quiet.</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1347513367182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 01:16:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347513797531-4</Id><Topic><Title>DNC insults American veterans with Russian Warship tribute</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347465952007</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:05:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The most revealing part of the DNC was when the democrats took "God" out of their platform, also took "Jerusalem as the capital of Israel", out of their platform.....when it was pointed out by republicans, Obama said it was a mistake and the chairman took a voice vote to have these two items put back in........the chairman had to lie and say the "YEAS" have it, when clearly the "NOS" had it, and wide protests broke out at the convention..........that was embarrassing for all the democrats who are moderates and not socialists democrats. It was a wake up moment for many democrats and Americans in general as to what the democratic party has evolved into. BAD BAD BAD.</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1347513797531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 01:23:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347514272520-5</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SHOW US YOUR GRADES ! WHY ARE THEY SEALED FROM THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ! NO OTHER PRESIDENT HAS EVER SEALED THEM BEFORE</Title><Username>americasaveit</Username><Timestamp>1347449773918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was an EEOC promoted student and could not pass the bar. He had very bad grades, among other things to be revealed after he has left office, If I had his record, I would hide my records also. It doesn't matter at this point because we have learned how unqualified, and unintellectual he actually is. He's just a two-bit con man who can smile at you while he's picking your pocket. No real mystery here at this point.</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1347514272520</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 01:31:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347538779022-6</Id><Topic><Title>Embassy attack - Romney does Obama's job</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347475758963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 14:49:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya, he has GWB's old staffers. That is the problem, Another now is the Mormon religion, similar the Jewish religion consider themselves a lineage through history. Romney going to Israel and setting a deal if he should win is wrong. Wrong because it is what Reagan did with Iran when it had our hostages.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1347538779022</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:19:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347541404985-7</Id><Title>New Analysis on AT&amp;T Suggests Drop</Title><Msg>Wow! AT&amp;T is not looking good right now. MUST READ! goo.gl/Rb94L</Msg><Username>benniecatone</Username><Timestamp>1347541404985</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:03:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347542338831-8</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SHOW US YOUR GRADES ! WHY ARE THEY SEALED FROM THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ! NO OTHER PRESIDENT HAS EVER SEALED THEM BEFORE</Title><Username>americasaveit</Username><Timestamp>1347449773918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's records are sealed not because of grades its because his school records are under his real name Barry Soetoro</Msg><Username>ls3487</Username><Timestamp>1347542338831</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347543361279-9</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SHOW US YOUR GRADES ! WHY ARE THEY SEALED FROM THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ! NO OTHER PRESIDENT HAS EVER SEALED THEM BEFORE</Title><Username>americasaveit</Username><Timestamp>1347449773918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your right. With a history of lying and forgery like he has, we can't believe anything. One thing we are sure of, he is a total failure as President. What more do we need to know???</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1347543361279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347546132122-10</Id><Topic><Title>Barry's Real Employment Plan</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347156540219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:09:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think its time for impeachment.</Msg><Username>ls3487</Username><Timestamp>1347546132122</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:22:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347546435275-11</Id><Title>What's fueling the GOP decline?...</Title><Msg>Why are the Republicans losing ground in this election? Let us count the ways…or, simply read the many lies posted just yesterday here out of a last gasp sense of desperation. Americans are not as stupid as you far-right wackos need them to be to believe your nonsense. I’ll repeat this again – the lunatics you are pandering to are ALREADY on your side! The middle-ground undecideds are being forced into the other camp because rather than discuss issues, you continue the birther nonsense. Read what you wrote here. It’s unbelievable that you think you can influence anyone saying insane things: “Obama was a terrible student and graduated at the bottom of his class from Occidental College to Columbia and then Harvard” – the Geoff holt imposter, who then asks, with no evidence other than him saying so, that if that isn’t true , WE need to show some evidence to disprove it. Dude, were you drunk ALL day long yesterday? Read my post you were replying to. I cited sources, you didn’t! “Obama has sealed his records…because his school records are under his real name Barry Soetoro…What is he hiding? – is3487, spewing more Birther foolishness to cover for Romney’s HUGE mistake of not showing his tax returns. That only forces voters to understand that the only possible reason to hide them is that they would hurt him even more than NOT showing them is already doing. There is NO other possible sane political reason – and claims of privacy are laughable – check out every other Presidential candidate. I’ll give you the link of the Tax History Project – oh, guess not, courtesy of the wonderful Yahoo board improvements. I guess these multiple-aliased clowns who pass along these fictional accounts are delighted with not being able to post URL’s. “(Obama) is purposely trying to torpedo this Great Country.” - robfisk “Hispanics are turning against Obummer” - robfisk (Right, rob, a poll of Hispanics Sept. 10th shows Obama at 66%, Romney at 29, with 5% undecided.) Romney has about as much chance of winning amongst Hispanics as you do of convincing anyone that you’re actually a person of color. And here are three doozies from windyfrostt: “Blood on Obama’s hands. Obama knew on Sept 5 another attack was coming on 9/11, yet he did nothing” “…the Muslim Brotherhood has had multiple meetings with White House staff” And, get THIS one!!!!!!: “The stock market is being held up to try and get Obama re-elected#$%$ The socialist/m#slim/commies are running Wall Street now?????? I had no idea. What stocks are they pumpin’? Collectivism commodities? Again, you folks writing this crap can’t be as stupid as those for whom you intend it. Then again, you can’t be too bright if you don’t understand those extremists are already your most ardent supporters. But everyone else is saying, “Who are these crazy people and why do we want them to run America?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347546435275</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:27:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347548574931-12</Id><Topic><Title>What's fueling the GOP decline?...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347546435275</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:27:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Read my post you were replying to. I cited sources Your sources are a joke and have no creidiblity, where is the evidence to support their fabricated story you liberals will believe anything. Your sources are paid to say whatever Obama tells them to.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347548574931</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:02:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347549046337-13</Id><Title>Romney's response to Libya and Egypt...</Title><Msg>Asked whether Romney's attacks were irresponsible, President Obama said, "I'll let the American people judge that.” And they are: “The conventional wisdom emerged in Washington almost immediately on Wednesday: Mitt Romney's handling of the violence in Egypt and Libya was a disaster.” - CBS “The comments were a big mistake, and the decision to double down on them was an even bigger mistake," Steve Schmidt, senior campaign strategist to Sen. John McCain. "If you think the eye-rolling at Romney is just coming from the MSM, call up some Republican foreign policy hands,” – Ben Smith “How could this happen?” asked Christopher Ruddy, editor of Newsmax Media Inc., a conservative web operation. “If I could put my finger on it, I would say the Romney campaign has been poorly managed. They haven’t staged their candidate well, and their messaging has been incoherent, to put it nicely.” Senate Republican leader Mitch McConnell of Kentucky said Obama "correctly tightened the security overseas." Asked about Romney's remarks, he declined to answer and walked toward his office in the Capitol. "I don't feel that Mr. Romney has been doing himself any favors in the past few hours," she said. – conservative columnist Peggy Noonan, on Fox, no less. "I saw the statement he put out last night and I thought it was maybe a low-level press person who put this out and today they would correct the damage. Instead they're digging the hole deeper. I mean you can't really play partisan politics in U.S. foreign policy." - Darrell West, vice president of Governance Studies at the Brookings Institution. "Mr. Romney’s rhetoric on embassy attacks discredits his campaign.” – Washington Post Romney's account didn't mesh completely with events in Cairo."No, I was not aware that it (the embassy's statement) was issued before there were any attacks." Ohio Republican Rob Portman “Romney appears to have launched a political attack even before facts of embassy violence were known…then uses day to issue vague foreign policy vision.” – David Gregory “Republican are hoping that the North Africa story will quickly fade away — but they fear the worst. “This could be a game-changer,” Alex Castellanos, a 2008 Romney campaign adviser who is not employed by the campaign this year. “Romney's assault on Obama was rare among Republicans. Sarah Palin and Republican National Committee Chairman Reince Priebus joined him in condemning the president, but no other significant GOP leader thought it prudent to immediately single out the president for criticism. House Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio), House Majority Leader Eric Cantor (R-Va.) and Sen. Marco Rubio (R-Fla.) all put out statements on the crisis, none attacking Obama.” – Huff. Post And the slide to oblivion continues. Wait until the debates!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347549046337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347549619720-14</Id><Topic><Title>What's fueling the GOP decline?...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347546435275</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:27:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Your sources are a joke and have no creidiblity (sic)… Well, at least I HAVE a source to quote, unlike you. Then I guess Mitt Romney didn’t graduate Cum Laude from Harvard, either, as I also stated, right? Or is only half of my story credible to idiots like you who can’t even spell credibility, much less have any.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347549619720</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:20:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347551088955-15</Id><Topic><Title>What's fueling the GOP decline?...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347546435275</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:27:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Then I guess Mitt Romney didn’t graduate Cum Laude from Harvard" He absolutely did and there is evidence to prove it unlike Obama who had awful grades and fabricated a story about his grades knowing you liberal #$%$ would believe it. Obama has established himself a liar this is another lie to add to the list.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347551088955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347553216321-16</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SHOW US YOUR GRADES ! WHY ARE THEY SEALED FROM THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ! NO OTHER PRESIDENT HAS EVER SEALED THEM BEFORE</Title><Username>americasaveit</Username><Timestamp>1347449773918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm always stunned when the "Birthers" blither. Wouldn't it make more sense to recognize the Republicans would have used all the investigatory resources to trash President ? Guess there wasn't any truth, or it would have come out long before.</Msg><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1347553216321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:20:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347553339329-17</Id><Topic><Title>What's fueling the GOP decline?...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347546435275</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:27:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the "decline" is fabricated but will stop after the first debate.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1347553339329</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:22:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347553603083-18</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SHOW US YOUR GRADES ! WHY ARE THEY SEALED FROM THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ! NO OTHER PRESIDENT HAS EVER SEALED THEM BEFORE</Title><Username>americasaveit</Username><Timestamp>1347449773918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree that the vast majority of Repubs are not birthers! But you never will get Ricky to agree, right Ricky?</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1347553603083</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347554698292-19</Id><Topic><Title>Embassy attack - Romney does Obama's job</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347475758963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 14:49:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stupid Hillary actually believes this attack was because of a movie because Obama told her it was</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347554698292</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:44:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347555846961-20</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SHOW US YOUR GRADES ! WHY ARE THEY SEALED FROM THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ! NO OTHER PRESIDENT HAS EVER SEALED THEM BEFORE</Title><Username>americasaveit</Username><Timestamp>1347449773918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Problem is; the Democrats refuse to believe the truth. The DVD "Dreams from My REAL Father" reveals that Obama's book was a total fake to conceal his Communist background. As totally logical as the DVD is, Democrats won't believe it.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1347555846961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:04:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347556303836-21</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SHOW US YOUR GRADES ! WHY ARE THEY SEALED FROM THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ! NO OTHER PRESIDENT HAS EVER SEALED THEM BEFORE</Title><Username>americasaveit</Username><Timestamp>1347449773918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You clearly didn't reflect on what I stated ! It's not about Dem's rejecting the truth. There is/was no TRUTH to the allegations from the beginning !! Get your head on straight, if possible.</Msg><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1347556303836</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347556460516-22</Id><Title>Once again..</Title><Msg>..this pig can't hold it's gains even on a great day for markets.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1347556460516</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:14:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347556793245-23</Id><Topic><Title>Fantastic Update for T **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>borisfisher370</Username><Timestamp>1347545729006</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:15:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He are on a volcano hot streak currently. I don't contemplate that they will quit or stall just yet.</Msg><Username>johnniewhaley707</Username><Timestamp>1347556793245</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:19:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347558388538-24</Id><Topic><Title>Embassy attack - Romney does Obama's job</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347475758963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 14:49:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a very sensitive child and I am sorry I rattled your crib. I don't know how you expanded my remarks to those in your post; must be a guilty conscience. I implied none of the things that you indicate. However I do know that Teddy Roosevelt used the phrase that exemplified his foreign and domestic policy on a number of occasions; sometimes using the word "speak" and other times the word "walk".</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1347558388538</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:46:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347559022784-25</Id><Topic><Title>Embassy attack - Romney does Obama's job</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347475758963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 14:49:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you guys were merely as stupid as you sound, some people might at least feel sorry for you. Sadly, you know full well what you are saying is a lie, and you proceed anyhow, because the only interest you know isn’t for America, but self-interest. And you have the audacity to criticize the President as being a foreigner, among other things. The most Un-American people in the nation today are you guys. “Stupid Hillary actually believes this attack was because of a movie…” – the fake Geoff Holt – Now if people are telling the truth, why do they need to use copycat aliases? Please tell us, fake Geoff. The comments released from Cairo (not from the White House) were to let the (at that point) still peaceful protestors know that nobody (myself included) thinks making intentionally incendiary anti-religious statements helps anything. They had not attacked the Embassy in Cairo at that point, and what happened in Libya had NOT happened. What don’t you (and Mitt Romney) understand about that? As I said, you DO know that, but choose to lie about it anyhow. From John McCain about Libya and the Presidents reaction (I believe he was your nominee last time, wasn’t he?) Senator McCain: "It was a terrorist attack. It wasn't the result of a mob being excited. It was a group of jihadists who were well-armed and well-trained and well-equipped, and they decided to attack the consulate in Benghazi and try and kill people. That's far different from what happened in Cairo where a mob was whipped into a frenzy by these people who were talking about this so-called movie that insults Mohammed." As for the Obama administration's handling of the crisis, McCain was almost entirely positive. "I think it was fine. By the way, Secretary of State Hilary Clinton gave a marvelous statement today," said McCain. He did not offer such praise for the Romney campaign’s statements on the events. It’s time to grow up, children. This one’s over and you’re embarrassing yourselves.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347559022784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347559754827-26</Id><Title>New Analysis on AT&amp;T Suggests Drop</Title><Msg>Wow! AT&amp;T is not looking good right now. MUST READ! goo.gl/Rb94L</Msg><Username>ceceliakanduth</Username><Timestamp>1347559754827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:09:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347559769123-27</Id><Title>Dividend</Title><Msg>Does anyone know what time of year AT&amp;T announces the dividend?</Msg><Username>jimboandy57</Username><Timestamp>1347559769123</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347561453164-28</Id><Topic><Title>Fantastic Update for T **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>borisfisher370</Username><Timestamp>1347545729006</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:15:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am grateful. I hadn't opted yet. Doing so at once.</Msg><Username>stanleyanthony36</Username><Timestamp>1347561453164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:37:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347562594511-29</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's response to Libya and Egypt...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347549046337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:10:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Presidential campaigns in this Country are similar to what is done in Military Basic Training, in my opionion. The individual comes in an is stripped of their personal things. Hair gone, the Sargent say give me 20, no you did it wrong. Twenty more. Set up your foot locker this way, and later Sarg comes in and says, no they changed the layout, the soap now goes here. This is done to stress the new recruit, they wil need to be able to react under stress, and basic is a good place to test them . This weeds out those who if allowed to continue, may put themselves, in a situatation, where they, or someone else could be harmed. Similar to this a person who, is acting as his advisors say, or other than themselves sooner or later can flake out. Say things that are not true, trying to act Presidential. React before thinking thoughts through. I beiieve these last moves Romney has made show him under stress. He is not reacting well by the way, better now than later. Later would be too late.</Msg><Username>floridabeachie</Username><Timestamp>1347562594511</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347568420181-30</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend</Title><Username>jimboandy57</Username><Timestamp>1347559769123</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Traditionally, they announce it every 4 years on February 29th.</Msg><Username>dave_martin_2244</Username><Timestamp>1347568420181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:33:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347569719030-31</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's response to Libya and Egypt...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347549046337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:10:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney objected to the message released by the embassy in Cairo. So did Obama, albeit a little later. There is nothing wrong with what he said, the White House later agreed that the released statement was wrong and took it back. Perhaps if Obama hadn't skipped his face-to-face intelligence briefing in favor of a campaign fundraiser, he might have some inkling to what was going to happen. We will never know because they won't release, and shouldn’t, what was contained in the written copy he supposedly read on his way to raising money or meeting with yet another rapper. Grow up, this guy hasn't a clue and is leading us to ruin. The Republican's idea's MAY NOT be any better, we don't know. What we do know is that what Obama is doing isn't working.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1347569719030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347569940199-32</Id><Topic><Title>What's fueling the GOP decline?...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347546435275</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:27:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who says the GOP is in decline? The MSM? Wow, that is a good one. They are about as trustworthy as Obama.......NOT!</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1347569940199</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:59:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347570351834-33</Id><Topic><Title>What's fueling the GOP decline?...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347546435275</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:27:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To your point, there is much we don't know about our fearless 'leader' and he is doing his best to keep those facts from becoming public. Why would he do that while insisting that his opponent release more information? What is he hiding? How does he explain the fact that he won't allow those records to be released? He doesn't, he just shuts up and walks off or has one of his flunkies respond so he can maintain deniability. I don’t expect a coherent reply, you never answer questions put to you; you post Democratic talking points or post what they are paying you to post and obfuscate the issues beyond all recognition. They must pay you well. Has anyone ever hinted that you might make a good politician because you never answer the questions; you just talk and talk and talk, or in this case write. The result is the same.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1347570351834</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:05:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347573183767-34</Id><Topic><Title>What's fueling the GOP decline?...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347546435275</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:27:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better say as many Mormon Prayers as you know.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1347573183767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:53:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347576462195-35</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SHOW US YOUR GRADES ! WHY ARE THEY SEALED FROM THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ! NO OTHER PRESIDENT HAS EVER SEALED THEM BEFORE</Title><Username>americasaveit</Username><Timestamp>1347449773918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His grades are probably doctored just like his birth certificate.</Msg><Username>deebuck53</Username><Timestamp>1347576462195</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347578576120-36</Id><Title>New Analysis on AT&amp;T Suggests Drop</Title><Msg>Wow! AT&amp;T is not looking good right now. MUST READ! goo.gl/5r3Yq</Msg><Username>cleliacorseri</Username><Timestamp>1347578576120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:22:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347580715631-37</Id><Topic><Title>Barry's Real Employment Plan</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347156540219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:09:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The thought that all this fiat money going through the system, is going to help the poor is laughable. Inflation is alive and well in the supermarket, not to mention at the gas pump. (Printing Billions of dollars each month, reminds me of pre-war Germany, where a loaf of bread set you back a basket of cash). Oil of course, causes transportation cost to skyrocket. The working poor is loosing ground every day. Then you toss in MILLIONS of ILLEGALS, wages have fallen due to the over supply of labor. We have to pray for the poor, especially if they vote for Obama, who believes in making us all dependent on his food stamps. Still hard to believe, Obummer is running commercials where one African American lady remarks to another, that their friend looks so full of life lately. Yes, the other one says she has help. Food Stamps! Latest poll, before Obama came to power in 2008, 25% of the American population called themselves poor folks. Now, after just one term, a full third now classify themselves as poor. JUST BELIEVE, one more term of Obummer, and we can definitely get at least 1/2 of the Country say, they aren't very well off.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347580715631</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:58:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347581407144-38</Id><Topic><Title>Embassy attack - Romney does Obama's job</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347475758963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 14:49:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are way to hard on Barry. First of all, he loves to campaign. He had to catch a flight to Vegas. To get some more campaign cash. A very dead Ambassador (who was brutally r@ped, before being beaten to death), and a couple dead ex-Navy Seals, doesn't faze Barry in the least. Then there was the much repeated manta at the DNC Convention, GM is alive, and O$ama is dead, did not set well with in the Arab world. Whatever happened, to not spiking the football?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347581407144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:10:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347582043551-39</Id><Topic><Title>President, or Community Organizer</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347496823010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:40:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Letterman update. Just heard today that Obummer will be giving Dumb Dave a Medal for his achievements. I know of nothing this guy ever did, worthy of medal. Does he give tons to charity? I know he's had affairs with married women on his staff, (bad choice of words). But, if that's the reason for the honor, wouldn't Slick Willy be more deserving?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347582043551</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:20:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347582278057-40</Id><Topic><Title>DNC insults American veterans with Russian Warship tribute</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347465952007</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:05:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So true, why the Conservatives haven't made an ad out of it, I'll never know. It would be very effective. Are the Republicans really trying to win?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347582278057</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:24:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347583673580-41</Id><Title>Where Are Our Leaders??</Title><Msg>We are the only Country in the World, that doesn't have a budget plan. Barry, isn't that your job? We have no immigration plan. We have open borders, the Border Patrol has pics of Arabs with rocket launchers, coming across our southern border. Barry, isn't that your job? We have no national energy plan (despite having 35,000 employees at the Department of Energy). Barry, isn't that your job? I think Clint is right, when someone isn't doing their job, you got to let them go! Regime Change is just weeks away.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347583673580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:47:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347586906891-42</Id><Topic><Title>Where Are Our Leaders??</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347583673580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:47:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt had to fill the void, after Barrack and Hill, left the stage. Mitt, is clearly head and shoulders, above Obummer. Barry went off to Vegas, (a place he warned others to avoid), to raise a little campaign cash.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347586906891</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:41:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347587203746-43</Id><Topic><Title>Embassy attack - Romney does Obama's job</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347475758963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 14:49:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone has to answer these hard questions. Barry is used to getting, who's your favorite basketball team? Or, which do you like better, Letterman, or Leno?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347587203746</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:46:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347587447741-44</Id><Title>Why isn't Barry attending the Daily Whitehouse Briefings?</Title><Msg>Is it really too much, to ask our Presidente to do his job? Clint is right, if you can't do the job, you got to let him go.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347587447741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347588279864-45</Id><Topic><Title>First Time Ever, An Illegal Alien Addresses DNC</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347500758778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:45:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Were there any Vets who spoke at the DNC? How does Barry expect to get any Military Man's vote after telling that big lie. The murderous crowd was trying to get the Ambassador to the hospital. That poor man, and the 2 ex-Navy Seals/Contractors were killed, cause the embassy Marines weren't allowed to use live ammo. It was widely reported the Ambassador was violently R@PED, before being beaten to death. HOW CAN ANYONE REMOTELY CONNECTED TO THE MILITARY, EVER PULL THE LEVER FOR OBAMA AGAIN.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347588279864</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:04:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347589579885-46</Id><Topic><Title>First Time Ever, An Illegal Alien Addresses DNC</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347500758778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:45:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt very much that our Dear Leader will get much support from our Military. We are about to be in some serious trouble in the Middle East and we have a Muslim making our decisions. Kind of scary, huh.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1347589579885</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:26:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347590472174-47</Id><Topic><Title>First Time Ever, An Illegal Alien Addresses DNC</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347500758778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:45:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, their was a female Veteran who spoke. You best watch what your enemy does. I also am a disabled Veteran, and love what Obama has ds one to improve the VA. I will give credit to some of it starting when W was in. It was the big insections that found so many VA facilitys unsatifactory. He will get the Veteran Vote more than an other DNC candidate. Good old McCain skipped out on several votes that would have benefited the VET. This was prior to his attempt. He has his now he is all for sending more lives to die.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1347590472174</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:41:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347590562185-48</Id><Topic><Title>First Time Ever, An Illegal Alien Addresses DNC</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347500758778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:45:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you were planning on getting a give away Ambassador job, I would say forget it.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1347590562185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:42:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347592375855-49</Id><Topic><Title>Why isn't Barry attending the Daily Whitehouse Briefings?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347587447741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He has other ways of getting the information, as well as make his points without being their in person. One might say it very feckless doing it the old way when he is hot on the tail of the terrorists again. By the way how is Willard's feckless campaign going?</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1347592375855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:12:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347593353709-50</Id><Title>Pennsylvania Voter Rights Look Brighter</Title><Msg>It will lead to a march, in November if the Judges do not make the sensible decision. Pennsylvania will not be in the GOP's reach."</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1347593353709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:29:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>