<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355481650444-1</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo censors truth?</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1355247592411</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 12:39:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lavendersin...Did your mother have any children that lived? Didn't think so.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1355481650444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 05:40:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355481826455-2</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo censors truth?</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1355247592411</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 12:39:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice to know it picks up bowel movements aka lewcor.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1355481826455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 05:43:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355482395655-3</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Lie of the Year</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355348157703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:35:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too many uninformed and low intelligence republican voters out there and they know they can get away with the lies and distortions. This Robme puke claims to be a elder in the Mormon religion, but he was one of the biggest liars ever to run for President. So much for "The White Horse Prophecy"</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1355482395655</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 05:53:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355486445090-4</Id><Topic><Title>T is too beneficial to miss right now. Discover why!</Title><Username>kelseyharper45</Username><Timestamp>1355322492052</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 09:28:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>REPORTED AS SCAM VIRUS !</Msg><Username>alphonite</Username><Timestamp>1355486445090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 07:00:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355494492026-5</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Lie of the Year</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355348157703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:35:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the last day weeks of the campaign, you're trying to get the last undecideds, collectively known as "low-information voters", while most people who are decided are locked in or have even already voted. It's a good time to pull out your worst tactic. Still, it's an interesting tactic to tell such a blatant lie in the internet age. Disgust can spread as fast as the lies that cause it. And we also know that just about all of the people who locked into Romney immediately after the primary are also low-information voters. That's why we call them Tea Brains.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355494492026</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:14:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355496990564-6</Id><Topic><Title>War? What for?</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1355496096787</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:41:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please take your political rants elsewhere !</Msg><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1355496990564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:56:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355500077872-7</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Lie of the Year</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355348157703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:35:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are those here who would believe that "lie of the year." Nothing you could say or show them would change their mind what the bishop said was all true. Look at the bishop now, thank you Lord God he wasn't elected. Little Bishop didn't get his way, waaaaaa, is what he looks like.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1355500077872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:47:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355500400141-8</Id><Topic><Title>War? What for?</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1355496096787</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:41:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pissant.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355500400141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:53:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355500467485-9</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo censors truth?</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1355247592411</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 12:39:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Keep your eyes wide open." Oh, your eyes don't have to be open to see what you see, Lavylew. Closing your eyes has probably helps your delusions. But it sure is easy to see your hate. Talk to your fellow Captain D's patrons one day Lavylew. Then you might have your eyes openned. Your problem is that white people run this country and white people hate racists like you.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355500467485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:54:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355503224790-10</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Lie of the Year</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355348157703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:35:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There are those here who would believe that "lie of the year."" The line between gullibility and complicity seems to be fuzzy at best.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355503224790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:40:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355504312562-11</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Lie of the Year</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355348157703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:35:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, they were not uninformed - Hannity and Beck and Limbaugh told them everything they needed/wanted to hear as they sat in their little podunk suburbs looking forward to a night out at Captain D's fussing about "entitlements" after cashing their Federal/State/Municipal pension or SSI check. But it's not an entitlement because they "earned" it.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355504312562</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:58:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355509741279-12</Id><Title>A Monkey, a Homosexual and a Coke Head All Walk into a Bar...</Title><Msg>And the bartender says, "What can I get you Mr. President?"</Msg><Username>xtgeminiman</Username><Timestamp>1355509741279</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:29:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355511845817-13</Id><Topic><Title>Kissinger and the NEW WORD ORDER</Title><Username>todlondon</Username><Timestamp>1355017207404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 20:40:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I tawt I taw a putty tat!" Looney Toons!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355511845817</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:04:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355513330074-14</Id><Topic><Title>Kissinger and the NEW WORD ORDER</Title><Username>todlondon</Username><Timestamp>1355017207404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 20:40:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"that guy is creepy, scary'. Call it intuition I guess" You mistake intuition for bad upbringing by your parents.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1355513330074</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:28:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355520195518-15</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Lie of the Year</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355348157703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:35:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That doesn't even begin to compete with "my daddy was from Kenya". That one proved Stalin's theory about telling a big enough lie and everyone will believe it.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1355520195518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:23:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355523391705-16</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo censors truth?</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1355247592411</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 12:39:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, like it or not if they don't like what you say, they have the right and the power to delete what you posted. I have known it all along, it seems like you and the other censorship complainers are the one's just a bit slow on the uptake.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1355523391705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:16:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355534034074-17</Id><Title>Connecticut</Title><Msg>May the Lord hold the children in his arms to soothe their frightened hearts....also... may He be with the families to soothe their broken hearts .</Msg><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1355534034074</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:13:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355535840200-18</Id><Topic><Title>Connecticut</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1355534034074</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:13:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know what Christ said should be done with those that hurt little kids? I would do the same with those that want to spare them. The world has gone mad. Many that commit this sort of act have had their brains fried on various types of dope.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1355535840200</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:44:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355537311319-19</Id><Title>After Hours Quotes...</Title><Msg>...“Sound is God.” – Ravi Shankar “People do not die for us immediately, but remain bathed in a sort of aura of life which bears no relation to true immortality but through which they continue to occupy our thoughts in the same way as when they were alive. It is as though they were traveling abroad.” - Marcel Proust “We are asleep with compasses in our hands.” - W.S. Merwin “Even in a time of elephantine vanity and greed, one never has to look far to see the campfires of gentle people.” – Garrison Keillor “House Speaker John Boehner says that his efforts to work with President Obama on the fiscal cliff have resulted in a lot of talk but 'no action.' Yeah, a lot of talk but no action – or as I called that in college, ‘a date’.” - Jimmy Fallon “I do not give you to posterity as a pattern to imitate, but as an example to deter.” - Junius “None preaches better than the ant, and she says nothing.” – Benjamin Franklin "Mitt Romney got a job at a Marriott hotel. President Obama’s trying to stop us from going over the fiscal cliff. Mitt Romney is trying to stop people from stealing towels." - David Letterman “The opposite of the religious fanatic is not the fanatical atheist but the gentle cynic who cares not whether there is a god or not.” – Eric Hoffer “I'm not upset that you lied to me, I'm upset that from now on I can't believe you” – Friedrich Neitzsche “There was no respect for youth when I was young, and now that I am old, there is no respect for age--I missed it coming and going.” – J.B. Priestly “Texas Governor Rick Perry says he's taking steps to run for president in 2016. In fact, this week he's meeting with donors. He better hope they're brain donors." - Jay Leno “The United States will have the honour of proving experimentally, that true policy goes hand in hand with moderation and humanity.” – Jean-Baptiste Say, 1832</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355537311319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:08:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355537330656-20</Id><Title>AHQ (3)...</Title><Msg>...“It is a capital mistake to theorize before one has data. Insensibly one begins to twist facts to suit theories, instead of theories to suit facts.” – Sir Arthur Conan Doyle “When you wage war on the public schools, you're attacking the mortar that holds the community together. You're not a conservative, you're a vandal.” – Garrison Keillor “They spotted Mitt Romney at Costco. One day you're running for president f the United States. The next day you're shopping at Costco for giant jugs of mayonnaise. While you're at Costco, go ahead and return that Oval rug you ordered" – David Letterman “The world is not to be put in order, the world is order incarnate. It is for us to put ourselves in unison with this order.” – Henry Miller “I do not define time, space, place, and motion, as being well known to all.” – Isaac Newton “Relativity applies to physics, not ethics” – Albert Einstein "A new book coming out reveals that Florida Sen. Marco Rubio was born a Catholic, became a Mormon, then returned to the Catholic church, then became a Baptist, then again returned to the Catholic church. And I think he's at it again because he's now asking people to call him Marco Rubinstein." – Conan O’brien “A myth is a religion in which no one any longer believes.” – James Feibleman “Neurosis is the inability to tolerate ambiguity.” – Sigmund Freud "McDonald's just announced that it's bringing back the McRib later this month. Or, as the Mayans put it, 'Hey, we tried to warn you’!” – Jimmy Fallon "I'm not worried at all about death; like most people, I'm mildly apprehensive about what happens JUST BEFORE death." – Terry Pratchett</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355537330656</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:08:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355537341551-21</Id><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Msg>...“It was a blonde. A blonde to make a bishop kick a hole in a stained-glass window.” - Raymond Chandler “Some luck lies in not getting what you thought you wanted but getting what you have, which once you have it you may be smart enough to see is what you would have wanted had you known. ” – Garrison Keillor "The governor of Arizona punched a reporter who asked her about global warming. Afterwards she apologized. She said, 'Sorry, I'm a little touchy because it's almost Christmas and it's 135 degrees outside." - Conan O'Brien “I have learned silence from the talkative, tolerance from the intolerant, and kindness from the unkind; yet strangely, I am ungrateful to these teachers” – Kahlil Gibran “I'm an incorrigible punster. Do not incorrige me!” – unknown "A new survey found that 'Sophia' and 'Aiden' were the most popular baby names this year. The least popular baby name was Kim Jong Sandusky." - Jimmy Fallon “All right. Have it your own way. Road to hell paved with unbought stuffed dogs.Not my fault.” – Ernest Hemmingway “Our theories of the eternal are as valuable as are those which a chick which has not broken its way through its shell might form of the outside world.” – Buddha "The Obamas have decorated the White House with 54 Christmas trees. It's all part of their 'For the last time, we're not Mu#slim' campaign." – Conan O’Brien “A wonderful fact to reflect upon, that every human creature is constituted to be that profound secret and mystery to every other.” – Charles Dickens “Consciousness: That annoying time between naps” – Steven Wright “I've seen the truth, and it makes no sense.” – Garrison Keillor “Have a good weekend, all.” – echo2165 “Good wine is a good familiar creature if it be well used. “ – Shakespeare, Othello “You will never find that life for which you are looking. When the gods created man they allotted to him death, but life they retained in their own keeping.” - The Epic of Gilgamesh “Begin at the beginning and go on till you come to the end; then stop.” - Lewis Carrol, Alice in Wonderland</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355537341551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:09:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355539536674-22</Id><Topic><Title>Connecticut</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1355534034074</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:13:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh shut the hell up you stupid piece of #$%$!</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355539536674</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:45:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355539559961-23</Id><Topic><Title>Connecticut</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1355534034074</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:13:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355539559961</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:45:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355540178537-24</Id><Topic><Title>Connecticut</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1355534034074</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:13:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may consider me to be a stupid piece of whatever....yet i stand with my message...i mourn the loss ..my only hope is that those angels are now in peace and comfort !!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1355540178537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:56:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355541241468-25</Id><Topic><Title>Connecticut</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1355534034074</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:13:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not you, agree with you wholeheartedly.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355541241468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 22:14:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355541507864-26</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Lie of the Year</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355348157703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:35:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool, so we know that at least five frequent posters to this board are sucking on the tit of their Federal/State/Municipal pension or SSI check while whining about the "entitlements" of others. Do any of you deluded sh+tbags want to put your names to your thumbs down and verify that you are not currently sucking on the public tit?</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355541507864</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 22:18:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355542105209-27</Id><Topic><Title>Connecticut</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1355534034074</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:13:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiot.</Msg><Username>argonthecat</Username><Timestamp>1355542105209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 22:28:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355543458919-28</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Lie of the Year</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355348157703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:35:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where was your daddy from?</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355543458919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 22:50:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>