<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354789498252-1</Id><Topic><Title>Driving Business Customers Away</Title><Username>courage_and_truth</Username><Timestamp>1354755080748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 19:51:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surely U make a good punto but how is this any differencia than compania XYZ?</Msg><Username>madam_hillary07</Username><Timestamp>1354789498252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 05:24:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354806897688-2</Id><Topic><Title>Say it ain't so. A dem wouldn't do this.</Title><Username>coulddobetter</Username><Timestamp>1354294434866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 11:53:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The top marginal tax rate was 38.5% at the end of Reagan's presidency. Before Reagan, it was 50%. In the 1950s, it was up in the 90%. In exchange, wealthy people get a low rate on capital gains. The idea that "no one in the U.S. should have to pay a 36% Fed. Income TAX" as a marginal rate on earned income just does not match American history or economic reality. I have no idea what Obama tax decrease for the middle class you are talking about. In fact, most of your post is unintelligible.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354806897688</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 10:14:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354807774493-3</Id><Topic><Title>Say it ain't so. A dem wouldn't do this.</Title><Username>coulddobetter</Username><Timestamp>1354294434866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 11:53:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also, Jon, I am a fairly wealthy individual. I was not suffering economically in 2010. I was finishing my fellowship and starting my practice. Most of the income on my early contracts materialized in 2011. I was able to claim certain deductions and credits related to that and other things. My only point in telling this story is to point out just how ludicrous it is to call someone a freeloader because he or she did not pay income tax in a certain year, particularly during the height of a recession. I'm sure alot of very enterprising people took big hits. The types of plush, union jobs that provide stable income throughout life are disappearing. You will see more people who have tight years at some point in their lives. They may need some assistance during those times. There is no reason to treat these people with the contempt they have been treated with. And if Republicans continue to do so they will continue to lose elections. They did not lose the election because 47% of Americans are dependent on government. They lost the election because they do not understand the modern economy and how people live, work and succeed in it.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354807774493</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 10:29:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354810787835-4</Id><Title>Dumping of T continues and continues and...</Title><Msg>...$38 looks like a very distant memory - will be quite some time before we see that again.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354810787835</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:19:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354812629292-5</Id><Topic><Title>T is one of top picks like crimson on apex</Title><Username>ethelvillarreal43</Username><Timestamp>1353943269318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:21:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job mate</Msg><Username>ryanlee700</Username><Timestamp>1354812629292</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:50:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354816174840-6</Id><Topic><Title>Dumping of T continues and continues and...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354810787835</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:19:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The chart http://finance.yahoo.com/echarts?s=T#symbol=t;range=1y;compare=;indicator=dividend+bollinger+sma%2820%29+volume+stochasticslow+rsi;charttype=candlestick;crosshair=on;ohlcvalues=1;logscale=off;source=undefined; does not support your claim of dumping. Average volume is 26 million shares and note that there are only a few days when the volume has varied from that more than a 10%. Also note that the current price is a little above the 20 DMA. The Bollinger Bands are moving together and December seems to be shaping up as a pretty flat month. Don't count out $38. Notice what happens when the Bollinger Bands are close together for a while. A rapid breakout occurs. The last one was downward. The next is most likely to be upward. Don't lose sight of the fact that the dollar is losing its' value and it will take more dollars in the future to buy shares of AT&amp;T.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1354816174840</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:49:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354817414003-7</Id><Topic><Title>Wow - nasty close...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354741942247</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 16:12:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Something is rotten in Denmark - T is being eviscerated.</Msg><Username>catfisherman201</Username><Timestamp>1354817414003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:10:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354817625552-8</Id><Topic><Title>Dumping of T continues and continues and...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354810787835</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:19:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does all that mean? All I know is that T is getting repeatedly bushwhacked.</Msg><Username>catfisherman201</Username><Timestamp>1354817625552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:13:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354817841685-9</Id><Title>T 2013 Price Target $33.50 According To Guggenheim</Title><Msg>I see T falling to $31 in the coming months...</Msg><Username>mooseonaplane</Username><Timestamp>1354817841685</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:17:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354818240045-10</Id><Topic><Title>Dumping of T continues and continues and...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354810787835</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:19:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would be very interested to know why I got a thumbs down on my post. It is a very long URL but, if cut and pasted, it does bring up the chart that supports everything I posted. http://finance.yahoo.com/echarts?s=T#symbol=t;range=1y;compare=;indicator=dividend+bollinger+sma%2820%29+volume+stochasticslow+rsi;charttype=candlestick;crosshair=on;ohlcvalues=1;logscale=off;source=undefined</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1354818240045</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:24:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354818985900-11</Id><Topic><Title>Wow - nasty close...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354741942247</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 16:12:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every day. Scary part is VZ isn't - so it's not a sector or fear of dividend tax increase situation.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354818985900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:36:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354819566755-12</Id><Topic><Title>Norquist Popular With Lib. Democrats</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1354046450537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:00:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I don't consider most of the legislation passed since Obama became President good for this country" Well, this country disagrees with you, and has asked for more, including Obama's take on dealing with fiscal issues. To pretend Obama and Congress have not accomplished anything simply because YOU don't like what it accomplished is nonsensical. And they've done this all in spite of a recalcitrant minority party dead set against America accomplishing anything--at least while Obama is president.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354819566755</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:46:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354820306721-13</Id><Topic><Title>T 2013 Price Target $33.50 According To Guggenheim</Title><Username>mooseonaplane</Username><Timestamp>1354817841685</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:17:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AT&amp;T was $31 just last April but it was $38 by August. The 200 SMA (now $34.46) is still in an uptrend even though trading has been below that line for the past month. In fact it looks as if the 50 EMA will cross below the 200 SMA in about two weeks. That might trigger a short term sell off but I doubt it will take us to $31. If it does, buy all you can because inflation is on the way at it will make stock prices increase.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1354820306721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:58:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354821850157-14</Id><Topic><Title>Norquist Popular With Lib. Democrats</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1354046450537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:00:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"To pretend Obama and Congress have not accomplished anything simply because YOU don't like what it accomplished is nonsensical." Other than health care, what have they accomplished? They can't even get a budget passed for the past three years. That by the way is not the fault of the Republicans when Harry won't even submit it for a vote. Harry is blocking things up as much as anyone. Harry Reid is nonsensical, and useless!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1354821850157</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 14:24:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354822604700-15</Id><Topic><Title>Both Sides are in cahoots</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354658194712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 16:56:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It is not a good reason for rehashing the same old anti-Semitic conspiracy theories loons like you buy into, which in turn make you tools of those making the contributions." Sorry but I failed to read any anti-Semitic comments in lewcors message. If by chance that many of the top levels of Goldman happen to be of that faith, so what? Did he denounce anyone for being of that faith or race? No, you assumed it all on your own and used your supposition to make deprecating comments about someone's post because you disagree with it. Is that a reflection of your character perhaps?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1354822604700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 14:36:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354823040379-16</Id><Topic><Title>Both Sides are in cahoots</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354658194712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 16:56:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Winholder, he didn't say there happen to be many Jewish people at the top levels of Goldman Sachs. He said Goldman Sachs "is the front in this country for the Rothschilds." Now I repeat, that is the same old anti-semitic conspiracy theories loons like you buy into.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354823040379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 14:44:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354825940433-17</Id><Topic><Title>Both Sides are in cahoots</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354658194712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 16:56:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is only one side and both the Republicans and the Democrats are on that side. Both want one World government and are destroying America to accomplish that end. If we don't get a large segment of both parties to switch to the Constitution Party by the 2014 elections, we are doomed.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1354825940433</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:32:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354828334185-18</Id><Title>Horrible day for T while...</Title><Msg>..the markets had a good day and VZ had a very good day. This is not a good sign. The rest of this month/year is going to punish beat down stock a lot further IMO.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354828334185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 16:12:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354828738967-19</Id><Topic><Title>Norquist Popular With Lib. Democrats</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1354046450537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:00:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Other than health care, what have they accomplished?" I just listed several far reaching and historic pieces of legislation. Again, you can try to shift the blame for Tea Party stonewalling all you want, Americans know who is responsible. We had two years of sweeping legislative accomplishment, then nothing. What changed between those two Congresses, winholder? Having trouble remembering?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354828738967</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 16:18:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354838456191-20</Id><Topic><Title>Both Sides are in cahoots</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354658194712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 16:56:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anti-Semitic? You mean Sammy Davis Jr. was a "Semite?" Few if any of the other's are either as their own writings say 85% are of a Turko-Mongol tribe called Khazars converted to Phariseeism 1,200 years ago in So, Russia, Google the word and learn something about "The Big Lie".</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1354838456191</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:00:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354839469436-21</Id><Topic><Title>Will our Enemies Launch a Sneak Attack?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354332244349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, I'm glad some info is available on her college days. Barrack has spent many millions, sealing his records. What info will ever make it to the Obama Presidential Library? If they don't include a teleprompter, I for one will be greatly dissapointed.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354839469436</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:17:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354840865173-22</Id><Topic><Title>No one sure how Dividend Stocks will fare</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354331405310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:10:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Mexicans are so willing to pay taxes why is California going under? You should check out the Numbers USA website. Juan, why do you say such things? Por favour, why don't you go back if things are better in your homeland</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354840865173</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:41:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354843415212-23</Id><Topic><Title>Dumping of T continues and continues and...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354810787835</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:19:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It means that all those socialist types that are in favor of dividend stocks falling, may get their wish. It's a world economy. T is not the only stock one can invest it. Barrack is emboldened by that cry baby, Bayner. Why is he negotiating with someone who is constantly moving the goal posts? Giving Obama more revenue is like giving a crack addict some spending money. He's just going to waste it.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354843415212</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 20:23:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354844143546-24</Id><Title>Is it time we Punish Single Women?</Title><Msg>They gave Obummer the election, cause of all that war on women spin. They were already losing jobs, more than any other segment. Married women voted for Romney in much higher numbers. So, from now on. I refuse to buy any property, or anything else from a women till she proves to me, she didn't support Obummer. There is a war on Women in Egypt. They have roaming bands of rape squads, plundering women who disagree with the dictator. Now that's a war on women. When will Barry weigh in on that one?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354844143546</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 20:35:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354844918368-25</Id><Topic><Title>Election explained</Title><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1352655544210</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 12:39:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's becoming clear. The Middle Class, those renters Obami sat down with in Virginia, are the ones having to pay for Barry's wasteful spending. Barry is willing to throw you under the bus to be able to say he got the rich to pay their fair share. They are already paying their fair share. We need illegals to pay taxes on all the wages they are stealing from our lower skilled citizenry.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354844918368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 20:48:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354845237035-26</Id><Topic><Title>Horrible day for T while...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354828334185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 16:12:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AT&amp;T CEO Randall Stephenson agreed to pay $2 billion if the T-Mobile bid failed, which it did. That was a huge cash dump for T. Yesterday's news said he was raising $4 billion in bonds. Why is he still at AT&amp;T? Has the Board gone to sleep? No wonder the stock is crashing. Stephenson must go!</Msg><Username>timetraveler2u</Username><Timestamp>1354845237035</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 20:53:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354846510280-27</Id><Title>Quit your whining and let T fall lower then buy the krapski out of this dividend winner</Title><Msg>T is not a stock for making big moves just paying a lot better divi than your bank account.</Msg><Username>born_in_a_cage</Username><Timestamp>1354846510280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 21:15:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354846527359-28</Id><Topic><Title>Horrible day for T while...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354828334185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 16:12:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, obviously this guy isn't supported by Obummer. Vz is one of the biggest black employers, and perhaps Barry favors them. I would buy more T, but only after all dividend stocks fall in the New Year.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354846527359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 21:15:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354846686391-29</Id><Topic><Title>Horrible day for T while...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354828334185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 16:12:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is a proven fact that the majority of black workers are lazy so obooba's feelings do not matter. T is a buy buy buy on any dips below $33.</Msg><Username>obama_is_no_hero</Username><Timestamp>1354846686391</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 21:18:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354847518662-30</Id><Topic><Title>Horrible day for T while...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354828334185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 16:12:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A friend told me that their health care costs are way up. Their contract now gives 10 sick days. A first. Upwards of 40% of some units have ongoing health/fmla issues. But, having Barry in your corner, can overcome this handicap.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354847518662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 21:31:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354848872826-31</Id><Topic><Title>No one sure how Dividend Stocks will fare</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354331405310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:10:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A couple years ago, some very dumb illegals got arrested here in Bmore, by ICE. They actually went up to the well dressed, guys in their brand new, large SUV(s), asking if they needed day laborers. The agents got in trouble, as we are an illegal alien welcoming center. The agents said, if they hadn't approached us, we would have never bothered them. We were at 7-11 for coffee. At the very least, we should tax all money going back to Mexico by 25%, to get something for all the welfare costs these people demand. We have 40 million con men here, taking poor American's jobs.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354848872826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 21:54:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354853549939-32</Id><Title>Everything about T SUKS,,,,LAND LINE,CELL PHONE,CUSTOMER SERVICE</Title><Msg>They suk the worst mistake a person can make is getting envolved with the pos service</Msg><Username>kennethshamrock</Username><Timestamp>1354853549939</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 23:12:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354854609775-33</Id><Topic><Title>Quit your whining and let T fall lower then buy the krapski out of this dividend winner</Title><Username>born_in_a_cage</Username><Timestamp>1354846510280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 21:15:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree with the strategy, however, the move to 38 was pretty significant - made some money there, but was not smart enough or quick enough to see the golden short opportunity that opened up right afterwards.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1354854609775</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 23:30:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>