<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351070748294-1</Id><Topic><Title>ATT retiree benefits</Title><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1343908864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's Obamacare not the company. I'm 71 years old and just found out that I have to pay a premium beginning next year. Can't jump very far with $780.-- pension. I guess by the time I'm 80 (hopefully I don't live that long) my few bucks on pension will be consumed by health care premiums.</Msg><Username>lauterner</Username><Timestamp>1351070748294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 05:25:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351079321855-2</Id><Title>AT&amp;T Third-Quarter Results: Solid EPS Growth, Strong Wireless Revenue Gains and Record Free Cash Flow With Increase of $2 Billion in Full-Year Free Cash Flow Guidance</Title><Msg>AT&amp;T Third-Quarter Results: Solid EPS Growth, Strong Wireless Revenue Gains and Record Free Cash Flow With Increase of $2 Billion in Full-Year Free Cash Flow Guidance Dallas, Texas, October 24, 2012 ShareThis $0.63 diluted EPS compared to $0.61 diluted EPS in the third quarter of 2011; $0.62 compared to $0.59 when adjusted for sale of Advertising Solutions, up more than 5 percent year over year EPS up 6 percent year to date; up more than 8 percent year to date when adjusted for Advertising Solutions Record cash from operations of $11.5 billion and record free cash flow of $6.5 billion in third quarter; full-year free cash flow guidance increases $2 billion to $18 billion or higher $3.8 billion in stock buybacks in the third quarter; 101 million shares repurchased Revenue Growth Driven by Wireless, AT&amp;T U-verse® and Strategic Business Services Reported consolidated revenues of $31.5 billion, flat versus the year-earlier period Strong 2.6 percent consolidated revenue growth when adjusted for Advertising Solutions AT&amp;T’s growth engines — wireless, wireline data and managed IT services — continue to transform the company’s revenue mix; represented 81 percent of total revenues and grew 6.4 percent versus the same quarter a year ago, led by: 18.3 percent growth in wireless data revenues, up more than $1 billion versus the year-earlier quarter 38.3 percent growth in U-verse revenues 11.4 percent growth in strategic business services revenues Strong Wireless Performance; Smartphones 81 percent of Postpaid Sales Wireless revenues up 6.6 percent; wireless service revenues up 4.5 percent Strongest postpaid wireless subscriber ARPU (average monthly revenues per subscriber) growth in six quarters, up 2.4 percent to $65.20; phone-only ARPU up almost 3 percent Strong smartphone sales of 6.1 million; postpaid smartphone customer base now 44.5 million, up 1.4 million from second quarter 2012 4.7 million iPhones activated; record sales quarter for Android and Windows smartphones Best-ever third-quarter postpaid churn 678,000 net increase in total wireless subscribers, including gains in every customer category Wireless operating income margin of 26.2 percent; EBITDA service margin of 40.8 percent with strong smartphone sales Wireline Consumer Revenue Growth Accelerates Wireline consumer revenue growth accelerates, up 2.0 percent versus the year-earlier period, strongest growth in more than four years 7.4 million total AT&amp;T U-verse subscribers (TV and high speed Internet) in service; almost 200,000 net gain in U-verse TV subscribers and 613,000 net gain in high speed Internet subscribers Total wireline broadband data ARPU up almost 10 percent year over year Note: AT&amp;T's third-quarter earnings conference call will be broadcast live via the Internet at 9 a.m. ET on Wednesday, October 24, 2012 att</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351079321855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:48:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351079462178-3</Id><Title>Earnings:</Title><Msg>Impressive results. Expect the dividend increase to $1.8o py, to be announced on or about Decembero 17th.</Msg><Username>madam_hillary07</Username><Timestamp>1351079462178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351080041342-4</Id><Title>The case of Warren Buffet:</Title><Msg>The man will go on for hours to tell you how and why Coke has been around for more than 1oo years but not sure what AT&amp;T will look like 5 to 1o years from now. The investor would be wise to take Warren's pontificasyon with a grain of salt since, IMO, he does not tell it like it is. When he tells you he is buying, he is actually selling.</Msg><Username>madam_hillary07</Username><Timestamp>1351080041342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:00:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351081688556-5</Id><Topic><Title>morman women can not get to heaven if divorced</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351039607477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like a democrat to me, say they are for women, put them down every chance they get.</Msg><Username>free2491</Username><Timestamp>1351081688556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351083419334-6</Id><Title>Gotta love AT&amp;T....keeps pumping out good numbers on</Title><Msg>it's overly conservative views........love that div, too</Msg><Username>thebigpitcher17</Username><Timestamp>1351083419334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:56:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351083564476-7</Id><Title>broker says sell my apple and load up T with its</Title><Msg>super dividend (anyone can make a cell phone)</Msg><Username>thebigpitcher17</Username><Timestamp>1351083564476</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:59:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351083798024-8</Id><Topic><Title>WOW Awesome Romeny would not tax dividends</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1350492924834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:55:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama doesn't care about you, look at the artificially low interest rates already. This report is good enough for a .44 to .45 move soon :)</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351083798024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351083856710-9</Id><Topic><Title>Friday is ex-div day..</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1349375130559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:25:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>9% :) sold 38.05 back in 35.50, with a penny I get 5% div.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351083856710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:04:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351084210462-10</Id><Topic><Title>Did Romney Endorse Obama During Debate?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1351017452560</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:37:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “Then the bayonnet, and horse statement didn't play well with women voters.” – rob, chief pollster and political strategist for CPPC (Caucasions Pretending to be People of Color) Is that a fact, rob? And you polled whom, exactly for this bit of wisdom? The Ann Coulter Mounted Lancer Cavalry? The Sara Palin People’s Pugil Stick Platoon? Well, if we’ve lost the entire electorate of women concerned with horses and bayonets, so be it. Chalk up two more for your side. I’m sure they’re both as bright as you are. Hey, when they aren’t riding a horse, do they drive a Prius? “Talking down to the next President of the US, is not very nice.” ???????? Oh, you mean from the existing, sitting, President of the US????? You are seriously twisted.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351084210462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351084408167-11</Id><Topic><Title>A debate strategy that would have made Joel Chandler Harris proud</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351017673993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “I wonts a rel job, an u tel me stuf dat aint tru abuots Obama.” – jon, juiced again and doing his Stepin Fetchit routine. Jon, you’re very mature. Nothing racist here, for sure. You guys should think about dropping all your facades of decency and charades of morality, and just come right out with a massive buy of TV spots with Rush Limbaugh doing a blackface parody of our President as a socialist, cannibal from Kenya, boiling unborn fetuses in a kettle, while burning bibles, espousing an overthrow of the Government, Mom and apple pie and using a witch doctor to create global warming. Add a bunch of mis-spelled signs castigating the Departments of Education and Energy and have Michelle Bachman dressed as Aunt Jemima passing out watermelons to cure gayness. Maybe throw in a Minstrel version of Glen Beck as Clarence Thomas lecturing women on how rich, old white guys know best what’s for women and their bodies. Last, invite Sean Hannity and Laura Ingraham to portray Amos ‘n Andy lecturing on the evils of the 47 % of Americans who sit idly by, on the dole, awaiting hand-outs from God’s chosen, hard-working and patriotic, gun-toting, bible thumping zealots of the lunatic fringe.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351084408167</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:13:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351085049686-12</Id><Title>T: Only 150 K New Wireless. GOIN DOWN!</Title><Msg>Lol forget their SPIN. Only 150 k new contracts added! This P O S is CURTAINS!</Msg><Username>maxxybb</Username><Timestamp>1351085049686</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:24:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351085587902-13</Id><Title>So Much for the Value of a Dividend</Title><Msg>news feeding the stock's demise</Msg><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1351085587902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351085976651-14</Id><Topic><Title>So Much for the Value of a Dividend</Title><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1351085587902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:33:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you serious? buy and hold T to live off a decent div. 1 day means little and you need to listen to CC.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351085976651</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:39:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086121704-15</Id><Topic><Title>A debate strategy that would have made Joel Chandler Harris proud</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351017673993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no, let super lib Ted Danson do that...AGAIN! truth hurts?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351086121704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:42:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086984127-16</Id><Topic><Title>A debate strategy that would have made Joel Chandler Harris proud</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351017673993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cute dog whistle story.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351086984127</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:56:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351088893355-17</Id><Topic><Title>A debate strategy that would have made Joel Chandler Harris proud</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351017673993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nearly six in ten watchers say that Obama did a better job in the debate than they had expected" It's all about the expectations isn't it. That he did better than expected is cetainly not a ringing endorsement and certainly not a strong indication of a 'win'. I think the St. Louis Cardinals didn't better than expected this season, but they didn't win!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1351088893355</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:28:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351089057376-18</Id><Topic><Title>A debate strategy that would have made Joel Chandler Harris proud</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351017673993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're obviously not paying enough attention to the President. He still insists that the economy is recovering, they job market is getting stronger; he has created millions of new jobs. You can't expect facts and continued layoff's, market collapses and rising food stamp participation to allow you to be distracted from the message.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1351089057376</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:30:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351089388060-19</Id><Topic><Title>Did Romney Endorse Obama During Debate?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1351017452560</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:37:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I certainly hope that the 1% that you think he has achieved is the end of his achievements. We can't afford any more success by this man.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1351089388060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351089932678-20</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA'S INVESTMENT TAX</Title><Username>xquestor</Username><Timestamp>1350880260739</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 00:31:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Officials at the White House and State Department were advised two hours after attackers assaulted the U.S. diplomatic mission in Benghazi, Libya, on September 11 that an Islamic militant group had claimed credit for the attack, official emails show. The emails, obtained by Reuters from government sources not connected with U.S. spy agencies or the State Department and who requested anonymity, specifically mention that the Libyan group called Ansar al-Sharia had asserted responsibility for the attacks. The brief emails also show how U.S. diplomats described the attack, even as it was still under way, to Washington. It would have been so simple to state that we have conflicting intelligence about the who, what and why of this attack on our diplomatic mission and we will continue to monitor the situation to determine more information. No, instead they invented a story that they thought would protect the administration, the State Department and the President from criticism and lied for several days. Not only dishonest, but also stupid and accurately reflects the attitudes of this administration.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1351089932678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351090043114-21</Id><Topic><Title>Why did they Take away the Plane?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351047019924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:50:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whats Nov7 gonna do to T? Depends on who wins. If Obama wins, sell everything you have, quickly.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1351090043114</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:47:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351090262950-22</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is a jiving fool*</Title><Username>onebellplaza</Username><Timestamp>1351008638295</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 12:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You might want to pay more attention to the Presidents voice inflections, tone, and diction when he gets in front of a black audience. It is how you say it that he thinks apparently matters to that audience.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1351090262950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351090696919-23</Id><Topic><Title>Just announced</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351005606484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 11:20:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought the new Democratic Party message was 'forward'? Why all the past and a bit slanted history? What happened to 'forward'? What happened to listening to what the current President and candidate are saying instead of a distorted history lesson? Get with the message echo, the move is FORWARD. You do understand what forward means don't you? I guess you must have misplaced your DNC talking points literature and had to wing it. Apparently when you rush, you’re more like Obama without his teleprompter.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1351090696919</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:58:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351090824657-24</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA'S INVESTMENT TAX</Title><Username>xquestor</Username><Timestamp>1350880260739</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 00:31:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “Not only dishonest, but also stupid and accurately reflects the attitudes of this administration. The emails, specifically mention that the Libyan group called Ansar al-Sharia had asserted responsibility for the attacks…” – winjondale Oh, but, in win’s normal editing mode, he conveniently leaves off: ”Embassy Tripoli reports the group claimed responsibility on Facebook and Twitter. So, your administration would react and release information from an anonymous poster on a social network??? No wonder you guys spend so much time here. I guess the State Department should immediately release news that the President is a Muslim, according to your recent post…which, btw, has no more validity than this one. Thanks for your earlier apology, however.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351090824657</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:00:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351090890191-25</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's carbon tax plan*</Title><Username>onebellplaza</Username><Timestamp>1350930797006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:33:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VZ FIOS is amazing. We have had it for about 5 years now and it is fast and reliable.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1351090890191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:01:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351091415397-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's carbon tax plan*</Title><Username>onebellplaza</Username><Timestamp>1350930797006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:33:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Master of the art of deflection and deception says it all. LIES, LIES, AND MORE LIES. The pure plain NUT Biden runs around being his coffee and smokes BOY and makes a dam fool of himself sucking up to the SEAL OBAMA WHO GOT UBL SINGLE HANDED. GIVE HIM THE MEDAL OF DISHONOR - HE WORKED HARD FOR IT.</Msg><Username>hgtacvs11</Username><Timestamp>1351091415397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351091598943-27</Id><Topic><Title>morman women can not get to heaven if divorced</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351039607477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the Mormon Church website: Are Mormon marriages different? Is divorce allowed? Mormon marriages are different from most marriages because they are considered eternal. If a husband and wife are sealed together in the temple, they can be together on into the celestial kingdom. However, the church does have a process for annulment and sees divorce as an unfortunately necessary evil. In Mormon President Gordon Hinckley's words: "There is now and again a legitimate cause for divorce. I am not one to say that it is never justified. But I say without hesitation that this plague among us, which seems to be growing everywhere, is not of God, but rather is the work of the adversary of righteousness and peace and truth." Just as a civil marriage does not automatically translate into a temple sealing for a Mormon couple, a civil divorce does not unseal them. If a divorcing couple wishes to become unsealed, they must receive a cancellation of sealing, which requires approval from high-ranking church officials. A Mormon woman must receive a cancellation of sealing prior to remarrying if she wishes her next marriage to be sealed in the temple. However, because men are permitted to be sealed to more than one woman, they do not have to cancel a previous sealing in order to remarry in the temple.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1351091598943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:13:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351091681282-28</Id><Topic><Title>Why did they Take away the Plane?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351047019924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:50:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “Depends on who wins. If Obama wins, sell everything you have, quickly.” – More sage advice from winholder, who says really stupid stuff just to hear himself talk. Why should anyone pay any attention to your ongoing inaccurate verbosity – you’ve proven time and again, you’re nothing more than a paid shill. Might I also add, you’re not real smart! The Dow opened at 8279 on January 20th, 2009. Gee, I think that is where W passed the torch to the current President, is it not? Today it’s over 13150 around 11:00 a.m. Spin that somehow. Yeah, let’s bring back the Bush years. Maybe even start a couple more wars.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351091681282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:14:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351091730441-29</Id><Topic><Title>l@@k New AT&amp;T, Inc. (T) Analyst Report L@@K</Title><Username>ralphmiller119</Username><Timestamp>1351087801474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:10:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming</Msg><Username>jackspringss</Username><Timestamp>1351091730441</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351092050246-30</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA'S INVESTMENT TAX</Title><Username>xquestor</Username><Timestamp>1350880260739</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 00:31:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... "you couldn't detect his sarcasim ... you poor twitt - (smiles) ' girlyjon . ..The real irony is that you couldn't detect mine. And you still can't spell twit. Incidentally, how do you know that winholder was being sarcastic? Oh, I bet you're having a cubicle party waiting for The Donald's October Surprise. Jolt Cola's all around - on me. Oh, wait, I guess you'll only need one - share it with rob, as well.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351092050246</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:20:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351092070453-31</Id><Topic><Title>morman women can not get to heaven if divorced</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351039607477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The book of mormon says Native Americans are Israelites who believed in Jeezus hundreds of years before his birth. And we have people willing to vote for a mormon cultist devotee who believes in that.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351092070453</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351092105548-32</Id><Title>UBRG gets $120 million loan, UBRG has 1800% Profit potential.$120 million annual line of credit will cause UBRG business to explode.Undervalued and CHEAP. Please see most recent press releases</Title><Msg>UBRG gets $120 million loan, UBRG has 1800% Profit potential.$120 million annual line of credit will cause UBRG business to explode.Undervalued and CHEAP. Please see most recent press releases The stock price has the potential to go up 10 cents to 50 cents. And buying 10 million shares for nothing @ 0.015 will bring unbelievable profit. Sell 10 million shares@ 20 cents = $2,000,000 . 1800% GAINS can turn your trading losses to gains and bring your trading account back to positive. Sector: Energy Sub-Industry: Oil, Gas and Coal Marketing and Distribution Products: Petroleum, Natural Gas, Thermal Coal, Propane, Refined Petroleum Products and Electricity Growth Profile: High Growth of 50% to 75% annually Geography: National and International Customers: 30 major electric utility customers for natural gas distribution, and power generation Suppliers: EDF Trading, Chevron Texaco, Conoco Phillips, Chesapeake Energy OTC Markets Group Exchange: Trading Symbol – "UBRG" Authorized Shares: 1 Billion Outstanding Shares: 503,063,086 Subsidiaries: NDR Energy Group, - Texas Gulf Oil &amp; Gas, - Whitesburg Friday Branch Mine Reporting Status: Registered and fully reporting with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission Highlights and Facts About Universal • Universal is a high growth Company experiencing double digit growth of 50% to 75% annually • Universal reported revenues of $71.74 million for year ended 2011 (audited) • Diversified energy portfolio of natural gas, petroleum, thermal coal and propane • Successful completion and integration of recent mergers and acquisitions • Company is planning to be up-listed to NASDAQ or NYSE/Amex/Equities in 6 to 9 months • Plans to build billion dollar company in the next 2 to 3 years through mergers and acquisitions • February 20, 2012, completed acquisition of Whitesburg Friday Branch Mine, with projected coal sales of $264 million over 5 years • In March 2012, NDR Energy signed gas contract with west coast utility valued at $11.47 million • In April 2012 NDR signed a contract with major utility company for gas storage services • In April 2012, NDR Energy was awarded a gas supply contract with northern California utility • On May 1, 2012, NDR Energy opened new sales offices in Houston, Texas • On May 23, 2012, we signed a gas supply agreement a subsidiary of a $6.44 billion Japanese firm • On June 18, 2012, we signed a gas supply contract with one of the nation's largest municipal utilities • On June 19, 2012 NDR Energy Group, established a new division to market and distribute refined petroleum energy products including diesel fuel, kerosene, jet fuel/aviation fuel and lubricants • On June 20, 2012, the Company paid a special 20% common stock dividend to its shareholders • On June 22, 2012, NDR Energy Group, signed a contract with Houston based Space City Energy Marketing LLC, to market and distribute natural gas, propane and refined petroleum products • On July 2, 2012 NDR announces launch of new wholesale electric power division • On July 3, 2012 we announced we were awarded a gas supply contract with a major west coast utility • On July 6, 2012, we announced NDR applied for registration on several interstate gas pipelines • On July 10, 2012, we completed a strategic conference call with our shareholders • On July 9, 2012, we announced NDR Energy sold over 1.86 billion cubic of natural gas in July • On July 11, 2012, we announced NDR was awarded a propane supply contract for a utility firm • On July 17, 2012, we announced NDR Energy applied for its FERC Power Marketers License to sell wholesale electric power • On August 13, 2012 we announced NDR was awarded a gas supply contract with a Mid-west utility • Plans to acquire interests in intrastate and interstate natural gas transportation pipelines • On August 23, 2012 we announced our second quarter revenues of $21,628,124 • On August 30, 2012, we announced we were in negotiations for a $180 million annually credit facility with a major commercial bank • On September 14, 2012, we announced our plans to hire a new Chief Financial Officer • On September 25, 2012, we announced NDR sold over 2.07 billion cubic of natural gas in August • On September 25, 2012 we announced we received a $10 million credit line with a major gas supplier • Universal has plans for 5 to 7 acquisitions in the $10 to $15+ million range, each with an EBITA of $1 to $1.5 million each for a total of $5 to $10.5 million annually</Msg><Username>hugemargins</Username><Timestamp>1351092105548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351094045864-33</Id><Title>No good news today</Title><Msg>This should be dead money for awhile. Won't see new 52 week high this calendar year for sure.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1351094045864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:54:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351096494833-34</Id><Topic><Title>morman women can not get to heaven if divorced</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351039607477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have read too that a Mormon woman cannoit get into heaven without her husbands permission. I read a most interesting book written by a descendent of Joseph Smith. This lady had inherited most of his papers. Mormons are forbidden to read it or the original Book Of Mormon. (it has 8,000 grammatical errors) Interesting too is his association and problems with the Masons. The church has incorporated much of Masonic ouija board rituals.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351096494833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:34:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351097047792-35</Id><Topic><Title>l@@k New AT&amp;T, Inc. (T) Analyst Report L@@K</Title><Username>ralphmiller119</Username><Timestamp>1351087801474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:10:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great report</Msg><Username>billytomkins</Username><Timestamp>1351097047792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:44:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351097651745-36</Id><Topic><Title>morman women can not get to heaven if divorced</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351039607477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must have had toilet training problems with your obsession with excrement.</Msg><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1351097651745</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:54:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351097776516-37</Id><Topic><Title>Why did they Take away the Plane?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351047019924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:50:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a welcome relief to see someone intelligent/literate on this MB !</Msg><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1351097776516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:56:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351100784527-38</Id><Topic><Title>morman women can not get to heaven if divorced</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351039607477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The alternative, a Muslim Communist, is too horrible to consider.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1351100784527</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:46:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351101186384-39</Id><Topic><Title>morman women can not get to heaven if divorced</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351039607477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"OH pleeez "PeePoop" "Mormonism, originated in the 1820s in western New York during a period of religious excitement known as the Second Great Awakening.[4] Founded by Joseph Smith, Jr., the faith drew its first converts while Smith was dictating the text of the Book of Mormon. This book described itself as a chronicle of early indigenous peoples of the Americas, portraying them as believing Israelites, who had a belief in Christ many hundred years before his birth. Smith dictated the book of 584 pages over a period of about three months[5] saying that he translated it from an ancient language "by the gift and power of God".[6] During production of this work in mid-1829, Smith, his close associate Oliver Cowdery, and other early followers began baptizing new converts into a Christian primitivist church, formally organized in 1830 as the Church of Christ.[7] Smith was seen by his followers as a modern-day prophet.[8]" There ya go typical rwnj who talks a lot of nonsense but never looks up anything. You just are immature as H. Mormonism is a cult.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351101186384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:53:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351101350914-40</Id><Topic><Title>Did Romney Endorse Obama During Debate?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1351017452560</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:37:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We still need to see Romney's Tax Return for the past 5 years...</Msg><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1351101350914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:55:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351102117689-41</Id><Title>broker said dump apple and buy T for safety till election over</Title><Msg>and get big div, too apple has lost its growth</Msg><Username>thebigpitcher17</Username><Timestamp>1351102117689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:08:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351104409030-42</Id><Title>GEEK SUICIDE WATCH STARTING</Title><Msg>They can't fit anymore apple crap in their garages or sheds</Msg><Username>thebigpitcher17</Username><Timestamp>1351104409030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:46:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351104889782-43</Id><Topic><Title>ATT retiree benefits</Title><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1343908864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is #$%$. Our premium notice went up 10-11 fold to $220 per month for myself plus 1 the wife.</Msg><Username>topekabill</Username><Timestamp>1351104889782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:54:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351105049614-44</Id><Topic><Title>ATT retiree benefits</Title><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1343908864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was bargained compensation for retirees in conjunction with the working pay scales when I was working. This is desertion on the part of previous policy by the company.</Msg><Username>topekabill</Username><Timestamp>1351105049614</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:57:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351105620178-45</Id><Topic><Title>morman women can not get to heaven if divorced</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351039607477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wasn't bashing mormonism, just telling about it and that it is an extreme cult. All religions could be called cults to some degree, but to believe in Smith the prophet who, if you read more, was probably insane, is extreme. A President can't impose his/her religious beliefs on everyone, and a mormon would more than likely do that. Ryan also would do that, he's doing it right now. Biden wouldn't, Obama wouldn't. The guy we have as President now is about as perfect a President as we could ever get.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351105620178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351105872056-46</Id><Title>Wonder where all the new customers went? OH! Sprint /Softbank..UNLIMITED DATA for less!hahaha ..thanks!</Title><Msg>see u at 30 pps..GL</Msg><Username>rmbdata</Username><Timestamp>1351105872056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351105990907-47</Id><Topic><Title>ATT retiree benefits</Title><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1343908864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well I certainly hope you are incorrect with your information. Unfortunately, NON of us really know the details including the congress whom I agree probably voted on it without reading it either. Unfortunately either side on this one issue are being straight with us or at least I can't find the facts. It does sound like you may be watching the FOX news channel or listening to Rush for your information. If the Democrats had not caved to the way the Republicans wanted to do this premiums could have been low for all. I have to admit that I am afraid that a guarantee I can get medical coverage does me no good if I cannot afford it in my non working years. One thing is for sure, our Congress can't shoot straight. The whole idea was suppose to be to get the costs under control so people could afford it. I believe it should be improved upon with the focus on affordability for citizens foremost and not for whomever is paying off the Republicans and Democrats in Congress to vote with the healthcare industry that has inflated what it should cost for care or treatment that causes the premiums to be so ridiculous.</Msg><Username>topekabill</Username><Timestamp>1351105990907</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:13:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106114039-48</Id><Topic><Title>ATT retiree benefits</Title><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1343908864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are probably correct.</Msg><Username>topekabill</Username><Timestamp>1351106114039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351107768265-49</Id><Title>You wont want to hide behind a %5 div per year when VZ and T start bleeding customers and 20% pps to</Title><Msg>Sprint/SB UNLIMITED HIGH SPEED LTE DATA NETWORK..gonna chop your T's arrogant management down to size!!! have fun!</Msg><Username>rmbdata</Username><Timestamp>1351107768265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:42:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351107894064-50</Id><Title>The bigger they are the harder they fall! T=General Motors vs S= TOYOTA take a look at history</Title><Msg>GET OUT WHILE YOU CAN.GL</Msg><Username>rmbdata</Username><Timestamp>1351107894064</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:44:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351108021670-51</Id><Title>you think T and VZ will go down KNOWING OBAMA is going to TAX your dividends??? RUN</Title><Msg>to the hills! Run for your life!</Msg><Username>rmbdata</Username><Timestamp>1351108021670</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351110387992-52</Id><Title>T is behind with tower installation</Title><Msg>T is losing customers because their coastal and lake coverage sucks. I am a T user and have condos on Lake Martin and the Gulf of Mexico. Their system sucks in both areas to the point that I am thinking of switching to Verizon as they have great signal on Lake Martin. T is going to have to accelerate capital spending or continue to suffer from churn and the beating they are getting from VZ</Msg><Username>datanurd1</Username><Timestamp>1351110387992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351111419574-53</Id><Title>Most of their Iphone sales went to existing customers</Title><Msg>I had said this when the phone was launched. If the 40% line holds Tomorrow will be a blow out Qtr for sprint. Anyone here think Soft bank didnt already know this? 3.2 billion says they did. Weeks ago before the deal I said a big one was coming. I bet on it and now we will see. I am going to drink some tonight for sure but not too much I got to hear the cc in the morning. Seriously, I hope I was right. I would have held till 20 before the deal. But now, I will take the money for half my position if we get a mjor pump. Appl reports after bell as well. I dont think they will report 2 bad qtrs in a row. Good luck longs!!!!!!! And the hell with you bashers!</Msg><Username>dolphinswin02</Username><Timestamp>1351111419574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351111602172-54</Id><Topic><Title>ATT retiree benefits</Title><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1343908864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Topekabill - Got my notice from ATT and my monthly charge is not going to change for 2013. It will still be about $220 a month. I retired in 2010 after about 32 years as a manager. What is changing in 2013 (for those in the ATT plan administered by UHC) is an increase in the co-pay between the deductible and annual maximum. That is going from 10% to 15% in 2013, and then up to 20% in 2014. Maybe you are getting "promoted" to the management plan?</Msg><Username>silence_implies_consent</Username><Timestamp>1351111602172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:46:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351111810854-55</Id><Topic><Title>Most of their Iphone sales went to existing customers</Title><Username>dolphinswin02</Username><Timestamp>1351111419574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:43:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Umm... Sorry this was supposed to be on the sprint board.</Msg><Username>dolphinswin02</Username><Timestamp>1351111810854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:50:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351112943088-56</Id><Title>More from The GOP War on Women...</Title><Msg>... “Pregnancies resulting from rape are ‘something that God intended to happen.’- GOP Indiana Senate candidate Richard Mourdock. Therefore, so goes the fractured logic of the GOP, according to their privileged insight into Providence and God’s will, abortions should be legislated out of existence for rape victims. “Thus,” said some future Johnnie Cochran, “my client cannot under any circumstance be held accountable for this rape under legal precedent. And while, through the miracles of scientific DNA evidence, it’s been proven that he was, in fact, the perpetrator, he is legally innocent, because it was out if his hands, having been preordained by God.” And I call my first witness, Geraldine Jones, testifying on behalf of the suspect, Killer. Your statement, Ms. Jones. “Your honor, the devil made him do it.” You people just get wackier and wackier. Good luck with the women’s vote.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351112943088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351115607017-57</Id><Topic><Title>l@@k New AT&amp;T, Inc. (T) Analyst Report L@@K</Title><Username>ralphmiller119</Username><Timestamp>1351087801474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:10:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for the interesting report</Msg><Username>jhonylogo</Username><Timestamp>1351115607017</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:53:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351115841786-58</Id><Title>Questions for anyone on the next floor up from us *</Title><Msg>We would like to know if anyone got a notice from the company telling you your retirement perks on the use of the company jet, car lease, tax help, consultant fees, country club membership , healthcare, telephone ,internet , home security ,and lifetime gift card to I HOP have been cut back because it was thought to be rather excessive when combined with your pension too ?</Msg><Username>onebellplaza</Username><Timestamp>1351115841786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:57:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351116918307-59</Id><Title>Since I have nothng to hide</Title><Msg>I would gladly offer my college records &amp; birth certificate to Donald Trump for $5M. That would help a lot of jobless, homeless, needy people. But, if I would lose my job as president, I would laugh it off &amp; have all my supporters discredit the idea. Obama says he wants to help the disadvantaged, here is his opportunity to get private money from people he hates the most. What do you have to hide obama? I believe Mr. Trump has called your hand!!! Aren’t celebrities frequently doing things for charity. Here is a simple, yet lucrative way to help the poor. Don’t you want to help your favorite poor people Mr. Obama or are your words just vote talk? Just think of all those sympathy stories that people have told you during your campaign that you have shared. Surely you know someone who could use $5M.</Msg><Username>cwbyruff</Username><Timestamp>1351116918307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:15:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351117217103-60</Id><Topic><Title>Jobless claims hit an unexpected 4 month high</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1350572391490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 10:59:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surge in Women Voting for Mitt Romney for President of USA and Their Reasons By ladies_4_romney . Oct 24, 2012 2:37 PM Women Democrat Voters and Others are Switching to Mitt Romney in Ohio Michigan Florida Virginia Pennsylvania Wisconsin New York- New Jersey ( East Coast to West Coast ) The Democrat Ladies for Romney in all 50 States Ladies are Switching from Obama very Fast. Read this and you too will Change and become a "Romney Democrat" for a Stronger USA Economy and honest leadership. Women, Jewish Democrats and others are Switching to Mitt Romney for President. Women Review Debate 3 : First, Governor Mitt Romney Pasted the President Test, Ready to Lead USA. By USA_Jewish_Women 10 22 2012 Great Impression: Mitt Romney's Stunning Turnaround in Past 3 Debates after Huge Negative Ads. The Reasons for Change is Obama has Lost the Support and Respect with Women Voters and Others. People Notice: Most Men and Women are Turned Off Against Barack Obama most everywhere and Across All 50 States, Here is the the Review of Debate 3 on October 22, 2012 By a Jewish Women Focus Group of 7,890 Women Connecticut Across America Our Strong Plea for Change in the White House, Why? The following reasons listed bellow. Note: This review is a agreement amongst a Group of almost 8000 Women watching debates. During the Debate 3, President Barack Obama was Arrogant, Disrespectfully, Angry, Rude and Condescending to Governor Mitt Romney. Obama did not Act or Look Presidential. We Feel Governor Mitt Romney Pasted the Presidential Test and is Ready to Lead USA We Support Mitt Romney, found him to be a Smart, Respectable and Decent Gentleman. Governor Mitt Romney Looked Much More Presidential, Ready to be Commander-in-Chief. Mitt Romney said America Needs a Strong Economy in order to have a Strong Military for our National Security right now and the Future. ...... We All Agree. Women came away from this Debate with a Very Good Impression of Governor Mitt Romney, in that he would be a “ A Safe Pair of Hands.” in Foreign Policy and a Strong Economy. We Trust Him More. Obama lied about Libya on 9 11 ( a 8 hour fire fight, Obama watched did nothing) In Foreign Policy We feel Mitt Romney is Tough Enough to do what’s necessary, but laid-back enough not to do too much and get us into another war. Miit Romney Did Not attack President Obama's Policies, he Simply Pointed Out a Few Needed Improvements in a Very Respectable Way. During the debate Governor Mitt Romney Seemed More Like a Leader, Smart, Respectable, Thoughtful and Considerate. He looked and Acted more Like the New American President that our Nation and the rest of the World Needs so Disparately in These Troubling Economic Times. Governor Mitt Romney was Calm, Thoughtful, Relaxed, Steady, Looked Like A Smart Gentleman and More Presidential. Romney Looked and Acted as if he was Ready to Take the Job as Commander-in-Chief ASAP. President Barack Obama Looked more like a Very Disparate Candidate and Challenger, very Negative, Acted like a Disrespectful Attack Dog Instead of the President of the United States. Mitt Romney Expressed his Concern about Iran's Nuclear Threat that is 4 Years Closer and the USA Support of Israel, our Good Friend and Middle East Ally. The strained relationship with the Obama Administration. Tonight Romney Impressed the Ladies Very much, in that a Vote for Him is a Vote for American Security, Peace and Safety, a Strong Economy, a Strong Military, Millions of Higher Paying Jobs, Prosperity for the Middle Class and Others. and a Quiet Peaceful Life for USA and all People. The World is Much to Scary these days, Americans Aren’t Looking For a Scary Arrogant, Angry. Rude, Disrespectfully and Weak President. Barack Obama is Not the One to Lead us Any Longer Tonight we Came Away with the Feeling that President Barack Obama is extremely a more Scary Candidate then the President of USA. We are Concerned about America's Weaken Relationship with Israel, a Nuclear Iran, our Weaken Economy and the Huge 16 Trillion Dollars Debt, that in itself Threatens our National Security. Americans, Black, White, Latinos, Wake Up, USA Debt is Bigger than our Gross National Product. We Can Not Afford Four More Years of President Obama's Spending, Borrowing and lies. We Can Not Afford Another 5 or 6 Trillion Dollars in More Debt From China or Other Countries. Our Jewish Women's Focus Group of almost 8000 Democrats Therefore Proudly Endorse Governor Mitt Romney as the Next President of the United States of America. Vote for Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan Before It's to Late. Do it Now ....ASAP Public Notice: We Feel Strongly that President Barack Obama is No Longer Fit to Lead USA.</Msg><Username>political_gangsters</Username><Timestamp>1351117217103</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:20:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351120832095-61</Id><Topic><Title>More from The GOP War on Women...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351112943088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ignore for you. You don't have a brain in your head, and have other MB's to spam. You must be a mean guy, who would never consider watching PBS. Try a dating service for a distraction !</Msg><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1351120832095</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:20:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351124070576-62</Id><Topic><Title>Since I have nothng to hide</Title><Username>cwbyruff</Username><Timestamp>1351116918307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:15:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hook, line, and sinker it only means something to those already not voting Obama and have nothing else to do My vote for Obama/Biden and every democrat I could pick, is in. dt wouldn't pay a dime, he would get them, and say they aren't the real ones, not paying. there is an end to the game and dt doesn't know it's over.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351124070576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:14:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351125411829-63</Id><Topic><Title>More from The GOP War on Women...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351112943088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>White House knew 2 hours after Libya attack that Ansar al-Sharia claimed responsibility, emails show WASHINGTON -- Two hours after the U.S. Consulate came under attack in Benghazi, Libya, the White House was told that a militant group was claiming responsibility for the violence that killed the U.S. ambassador and three other Americans. A State Department email sent to intelligence officials and the White House situation room said the Islamist group Ansar al-Sharia claimed responsibility on Facebook and Twitter, and also called for an attack on the U.S. Embassy in Tripoli. The document may fuel Republican efforts to show that the White House knew it was a terrorist attack, even as the U.S. ambassador to the United Nations was saying -- five days afterward -- that it appeared to be a protest gone awry. The Obama administration's account of the Benghazi events has become a campaign issue, with Republican challenger Mitt Romney and GOP lawmakers accusing the White House of misleading Americans about the nature of the attack.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351125411829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:36:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351125574602-64</Id><Title>The Donald</Title><Msg>Did anyone see the face of the Republican Party today? The Donald with his $5 million bribe if Obama releases his school transcripts and passport application ( he calls that big news ) and The Donald's Management Company getting fired as managers of Trump Plaza. The Republican Party---"You're fired". Greasers and losers.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1351125574602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:39:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351125575862-65</Id><Title>The Donald</Title><Msg>Did anyone see the face of the Republican Party today? The Donald with his $5 million bribe if Obama releases his school transcripts and passport application ( he calls that big news ) and The Donald's Management Company getting fired as managers of Trump Plaza. The Republican Party---"You're fired". Greasers and losers.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1351125575862</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:39:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351125661643-66</Id><Topic><Title>More from The GOP War on Women...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351112943088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that was 1 nut who said that not the GOP, 1 NUT ! Bible thunpers aer scary but so are wackos like Sean Penn &amp; Michael Moore, did you know Obama knew the ambassador was murdered with 2 hours of it happening and he knew it wasn't due to an youtube video? Now we have a liar in chief but you go ahead and focus on 1 nut in Indiana. That makes you a squirrel I'd say.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351125661643</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351125809265-67</Id><Topic><Title>morman women can not get to heaven if divorced</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351039607477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. The guy we have now is clueless when it comes to business, layoffs are on the rise and you think he is perfect? He had no facts and he said "the police acted foolishly", yes, he is wonderful.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351125809265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:43:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351125858524-68</Id><Topic><Title>Did Romney Endorse Obama During Debate?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1351017452560</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:37:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why? #$%$</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351125858524</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:44:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351125948885-69</Id><Topic><Title>morman women can not get to heaven if divorced</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351039607477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and Catholicism pays to cover up rape and molestation of boys. #$%$</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351125948885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351125965471-70</Id><Topic><Title>Since I have nothng to hide</Title><Username>cwbyruff</Username><Timestamp>1351116918307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:15:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know the difference between Obama voters and Romney voters, don't you? Obama voters sign the back of the check, and Romney voters sign the front.</Msg><Username>ringe53</Username><Timestamp>1351125965471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:46:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351126002205-71</Id><Topic><Title>Profit by examinging these guys right now.</Title><Username>bpatrick115</Username><Timestamp>1350580974806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 13:22:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so does martha stewart</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351126002205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:46:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351127391937-72</Id><Topic><Title>l@@k New AT&amp;T, Inc. (T) Analyst Report L@@K</Title><Username>ralphmiller119</Username><Timestamp>1351087801474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:10:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just got the report via email. about to start reading it. thanks!</Msg><Username>donaldtrump594</Username><Timestamp>1351127391937</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:09:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351127641884-73</Id><Topic><Title>Why did they Take away the Plane?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351047019924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:50:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They said there are over 300 emails on this attack. It will be hard for Hill to take all the blame. She is now saying she's only partly responsible. Some emails went directly to the Whitehouse situation room, oops. OBami was fundraising in Vegas, he could care less how many Ambassadors they rape, and murder. He really believes being El Presidente is just reading off of his teleprompter. The right words, and diversions will make it all right. Where's Big Bird when you need him?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351127641884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:14:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351128155624-74</Id><Topic><Title>Jobless claims hit an unexpected 4 month high</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1350572391490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 10:59:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seniors, run, don't walk to the polls. If you are working a job that doesn't have healthcare, it's now on you. How many under employed, semi-retired people know that as of January fines on those without a health plan begin. I saw it buried in an AARP bulletin. 1%, or $95 per month, if you try to run without health insurance. Who can afford these fines. I guess they have to have something for those 15,000 IRS agents to do. Go after the working poor!!</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351128155624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:22:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351128615470-75</Id><Title>Adelphi Workers got Bamboozled</Title><Msg>Axelrod had to admit it. Some emails have surfaced. Barry insisted that these non union workers loose their pensions under the auto bailout. Axelrod said the Boss saved the larger group, that just made sense. Political speak, hey these Union members have been funneling us money for decades. We had to throw someone under the bus. It might as well been the scabs/non union, and those old, mostly white bondholders. The Chicago Way strikes again.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351128615470</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:30:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351128643272-76</Id><Title>Premarket news on CGUD!</Title><Msg>I've done some DD and CGUD is a guaranteed doubler tomorrow.</Msg><Username>erynncf7413</Username><Timestamp>1351128643272</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:30:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351129741786-77</Id><Title>If Mcdonald's can't make it, who can?</Title><Msg>Barry was forced to exempt Mickey D's from obamacare. They said there was no way they could provide healthcare, and keep prices affordable. Darden Restaurants got no break from Barry. Their solution part time everyone. 40 hours, now down to 30 hours. Thank you Obama. Please pay attention, if you're barely hanging on, vote for Mitt. At least he'll seal the border, so you won't have to compete with 40 MILLION, poor desperate illegals.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351129741786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:49:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351129980926-78</Id><Topic><Title>Why did they Take away the Plane?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351047019924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:50:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are we subsidizing Big Bird? I heard he made $135,000 last year to just put on his feathers. Sounds like Big Bird should buy his own seed.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351129980926</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:53:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>