<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354342578458-1</Id><Topic><Title>Will our Enemies Launch a Sneak Attack?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354332244349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why would china want to attack us when they hold all of our bonds and we buy everything they make</Msg><Username>reroe13</Username><Timestamp>1354342578458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:16:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354371698525-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Get his Money</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354232624025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 18:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “My relatives own a plumbing/heating concern. They just let their secretary go. They found out somehow, that she was a closet Obummer supporter” - robfisk Rob – I’m so happy to see that you don’t hide the fact that your kind would fire employees for their political beliefs. And you dipsticks think you should be running America? Did they, like some of the other “job creators,” send out emails telling their employees that they might not have a job if the wrong person got elected? “These (sic) election was rigged.” Were they really? How many did you vote in? Were they all rigged, or just the one’s you lost?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1354371698525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 09:21:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354374909938-3</Id><Topic><Title>T is one of top picks like crimson on apex</Title><Username>ethelvillarreal43</Username><Timestamp>1353943269318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:21:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well done!</Msg><Username>josephcarroll548</Username><Timestamp>1354374909938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:15:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354377932628-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Get his Money</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354232624025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 18:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's my point robfisk. He has a backup plan which will tax us one way or another. He will not cut the spending to his people.</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354377932628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:05:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354379333204-5</Id><Topic><Title>Will our Enemies Launch a Sneak Attack?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354332244349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America's real enemies aren't in China. They are in DC and Wall Street. People like Ca. Sen. Diane Feinstein do business in China and ship their junk to us putting American workers out of business and helping fund the Red Army. Many firms listed on Wall Street do the same thing. "Why do none dare call it treason? When treason prospers none dare call it treason."</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1354379333204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:28:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354381454442-6</Id><Topic><Title>Will our Enemies Launch a Sneak Attack?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354332244349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gosh. Where is Pearl Harbor? The Sandwich Islands? Was that the Japanese or Chinese? What year is this?</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1354381454442</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 12:04:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354393243429-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Get his Money</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354232624025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 18:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “My relatives own a plumbing/heating concern…” – robfisk Hi. We’re Rob’s Aunt and Uncle. We don’t own squat, but we DO have concerns about both our plumbing and our heating. We also have a serious concern about our nephew, a 42 year old, jobless, junior-high school drop-out, who is as white as Edgar Winter, but thinks he looks like Harriet Tubman</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1354393243429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:20:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354394648559-8</Id><Topic><Title>Will our Enemies Launch a Sneak Attack?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354332244349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe you can hide in your Prius, jon2retard.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1354394648559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:44:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354409356184-9</Id><Topic><Title>Will our Enemies Launch a Sneak Attack?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354332244349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a theory. China has talked of refusing to lend us any more money. Their economic head, asked the question, "why should we lend you money, to pay your unemployed, more than we pay our employed?" You see, the Chinese are afraid they may never get their money back. So it only stands to reason, they may decide to come here and take back, what they feel is rightfully theirs. You see the takers refused to vote a businessman as President, Mitt Romney. Someone who openly asked the question, of all Fed spending. Is it worth borrowing money from China (at a very high interest rate), to pay for said program? The answer is likely to be no. This would include, Cash for Clunkers, Unlimited unemployment insurance, and benefits for illegal aliens. A no brainer. This administration, really does practice vodoo economics.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354409356184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:49:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354410527441-10</Id><Topic><Title>Did Anyone See the new Lincoln Movie?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354333696329</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:48:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not many will likely see it, cause it had limited car chase scenes. The opening scene, a far away shot, showed soldiers fighting in the mud. Then they came in tight to show horrible, hand to hand combat. A black soldier, with a 3 foot bayonnett, came down on a Reb, via the top of his shoulder. I expected it, to come out the bottom of his torso. Then, in the next scene the Black soldiers spoke about taking no prisoners, and wiping out everyone at a particular battle. Sure seemed like old Spielberg, like his hero, Barrack, was trying to divide this country among the various groups. Whether it be Black, or White. Rich, or poor. Republican, or Democrat.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354410527441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 20:08:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354411247951-11</Id><Topic><Title>No one sure how Dividend Stocks will fare</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354331405310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:10:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I spoke with my wife's Uncle today. A very rich man. He's a recently retired Doc, who is meeting with his advisor next week. Capital is fleeing our shores cause of this economic fool. If anything, we should be cutting corporate taxes, our taxes are the highest in the World. With the influx of illegal aliens, and all the business cut backs, where are people suppossed to get jobs? The VAT tax is almost a certainity, with all the illegals here (who pay no taxes). Mexico is a very rich country. Why must we support all of their poor? Just because they vote often, and Democratic</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354411247951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 20:20:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354413321028-12</Id><Topic><Title>No one sure how Dividend Stocks will fare</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354331405310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:10:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Capital is fleeing: Wrong. We are flush with cash, that is why interest rates are so low. Check your interest rates at the bank. They do not even want our money. Our taxes are the highest: Wrong. Our taxes are the lowest in the developed world. Vat is a certainity: Wrong. The Vat is a flat tax. The Democrates have always opposed that. ...the illeglas ( who pay no taxes ): Wrong. Gas taxes, property taxes, sales taxes, fees and license are paid by everyone. And if they have a salary paying job Social Security is withheld and they never get a penny of that. Mexico is a very rich country: Wrong. You might want to get out of your basement and take a trip south of the border. If Mexico were so rich why would illegals be risking there lives to get here. Rob Fisk is an idiot.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1354413321028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 20:55:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354422714610-13</Id><Topic><Title>No one sure how Dividend Stocks will fare</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354331405310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:10:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next Divy up 0.45, up a penny-- got to love it</Msg><Username>brat81us</Username><Timestamp>1354422714610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 23:31:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>