<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-22"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356174136388-1</Id><Title>Testing...</Title><Msg>1......2....3....</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1356174136388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 06:02:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356179895867-2</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne La Pierre For President</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356111777788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “I'm surrounded by Police…” – rob Don’t panic and go down in a blaze, rob. It’s only the A.S.P.C.A. there investigating reports that you’re spanking that monkey in your basement. Incidentally, there were no After Hours Quotes last night because this week’s editors were all Mayans, who all week long were like, “why bother?”</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356179895867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 07:38:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356180844225-3</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne La Pierre For President</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356111777788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There was an armed guard at Columbine. How did that work out? Clinton asked for 100,000 increase in policemen and the NRA ridiculed that and the request died. Now the NRA wants 100,000 few police in schools. The Republicans want smaller government but 100,000 new police. What is the total cost of 100,000 police? Stopping the mfg of all pistols and all military type weapons with clips and it cost NOTHING. and without a doubt there will be a huge decrease in murders and armed robberies. That will not end murders and armed robberies but I would guess about 50% decrese in violent crime and the cost is nothing. In fact, soon we would need less policemen.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1356180844225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 07:54:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356184045359-4</Id><Title>New Year!!!</Title><Msg>Hmmm. if you partied up waiting for the Mayan world end.... What do you do differently for New Year's Eve?</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1356184045359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:47:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356184229326-5</Id><Topic><Title>New Year!!!</Title><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1356184045359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:47:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...Did the ball drop yet?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356184229326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:50:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356184295794-6</Id><Title>GOP pulls another Boehner...</Title><Msg>... It would appear to me that the consensus is, that the GOP just pulled another Boehner! Analysis: GOP Policies Led to Fiscal Cliff Blowup By By CHARLES BABINGTON AP “…Such intransigence in the face of a narrowly divided U.S. electorate dismays Republicans who say compromise can be vital to a party's survival. The collapse of Boehner's tax effort ‘weakens the entire Republican Party,’ said Rep. Steve LaTourette, R-Ohio, who is retiring after 18 years. ‘It's the continuing dumbing down of the Republican Party,’ he said, ‘and we are going to be seen more and more as a bunch of extremists that can't even get a majority of our own people to support policies that we're putting forward. If you're not a governing majority, you're not going to be a majority very long.’ Republican consultant and writer Craig Shirley told The Washington Post: ‘The national GOP is now simply a collection of warring tribal factions’.”</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356184295794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:51:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356184412622-7</Id><Title>When will the GOP face reality?...</Title><Msg>... It would appear to me that the consensus is, that the GOP just pulled another Boehner! Analysis: GOP Policies Led to Fiscal Cliff Blowup By By CHARLES BABINGTON AP “…Such intransigence in the face of a narrowly divided U.S. electorate dismays Republicans who say compromise can be vital to a party's survival. The collapse of Boehner's tax effort ‘weakens the entire Republican Party,’ said Rep. Steve LaTourette, R-Ohio, who is retiring after 18 years. ‘It's the continuing dumbing down of the Republican Party,’ he said, ‘and we are going to be seen more and more as a bunch of extremists that can't even get a majority of our own people to support policies that we're putting forward. If you're not a governing majority, you're not going to be a majority very long.’ Republican consultant and writer Craig Shirley told The Washington Post: ‘The national GOP is now simply a collection of warring tribal factions’.”</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356184412622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:53:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356184740259-8</Id><Title>When will GOP face reality?...</Title><Msg>... It would appear to me that the consensus is, that the GOP just pulled another (Speaker of the House.) Yahoo censors Boehner???? They should censure him, not censor his name. Analysis: GOP Policies Led to Fiscal Cliff Blowup By By CHARLES BABINGTON AP “…Such intransigence in the face of a narrowly divided U.S. electorate dismays Republicans who say compromise can be vital to a party's survival. The collapse of Boehner's tax effort ‘weakens the entire Republican Party,’ said Rep. Steve LaTourette, R-Ohio, who is retiring after 18 years. ‘It's the continuing dumbing down of the Republican Party,’ he said, ‘and we are going to be seen more and more as a bunch of extremists that can't even get a majority of our own people to support policies that we're putting forward. If you're not a governing majority, you're not going to be a majority very long.’ Republican consultant and writer Craig Shirley told The Washington Post: ‘The national GOP is now simply a collection of warring tribal factions’.”</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356184740259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:59:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356184873237-9</Id><Title>It would appear that The GOP pulled another...</Title><Msg>... …Boehner. Analysis: GOP Policies Led to Fiscal Cliff Blowup By By CHARLES BABINGTON AP “…Such intransigence in the face of a narrowly divided U.S. electorate dismays Republicans who say compromise can be vital to a party's survival. The collapse of Boehner's tax effort ‘weakens the entire Republican Party,’ said Rep. Steve LaTourette, R-Ohio, who is retiring after 18 years. ‘It's the continuing dumbing down of the Republican Party,’ he said, ‘and we are going to be seen more and more as a bunch of extremists that can't even get a majority of our own people to support policies that we're putting forward. If you're not a governing majority, you're not going to be a majority very long.’ Republican consultant and writer Craig Shirley told The Washington Post: ‘The national GOP is now simply a collection of warring tribal factions’.”</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356184873237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 09:01:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356185008047-10</Id><Title>Like rats fleeing the sinking ship...</Title><Msg>... Analysis: GOP Policies Led to Fiscal Cliff Blowup By By CHARLES BABINGTON AP “…Such intransigence in the face of a narrowly divided U.S. electorate dismays Republicans who say compromise can be vital to a party's survival. The collapse of Boehner's tax effort ‘weakens the entire Republican Party,’ said Rep. Steve LaTourette, R-Ohio, who is retiring after 18 years. ‘It's the continuing dumbing down of the Republican Party,’ he said, ‘and we are going to be seen more and more as a bunch of extremists that can't even get a majority of our own people to support policies that we're putting forward. If you're not a governing majority, you're not going to be a majority very long.’ Republican consultant and writer Craig Shirley told The Washington Post: ‘The national GOP is now simply a collection of warring tribal factions’.”</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356185008047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 09:03:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356186300211-11</Id><Topic><Title>weapons</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1356152166219</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 23:56:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>446 school age children shot in Chicago so far this year with strongest gun laws in country – media silent The cesspool known as Chicago probably has the toughest gun laws in the country, yet despite all the shootings, murders, and bloodshed, you never hear a peep about this from the corrupt state run media. In Chicago, there have been 446 school age children shot in leftist utopia run by Rahm Emanuel and that produced Obama, Jesse Jackson, Louis Farrakhan, etc. 62 school aged children have actually been killed by crazed nuts in Chicago so far this year with almost two weeks to go. So why isn’t this news worthy? Is it because it would embarrass those anti second amendment nuts who brag about Chicago’s tough gun laws? Is it because most of the kids who were shot and killed were minorities? Or is it because the corrupt media doesn’t want to show Chicago in a bad light? Amazingly, no Obama crocodile tears either. For those of you too dense to get the point of this post, it’s to make the point about gun laws. No matter how tough the gun laws are, the crazed, nut jobs will find a way to get them and if they so chose, use them. No draconian law can stop this, no matter how well intentioned the law is, or if it’s just about leftists grabbing power from citizens and taking away their constitutional rights. THE LIST OF MURDERED SCHOOL AGE CHILDREN 2012 18 YEARS OLD- 15 17 YEARS OLD- 16 16 YEARS OLD- 16 15 YEARS OLD- 6 14 YEARS OLD- 4 13 YEARS OLD- 2 12 YEARS OLD- 1 7 YEARS OLD- 1 6 YEARS OLD- 1 446 School Age Children Shot in Chicago so Far This Year THE LIST OF SCHOOL AGE CHILDREN SHOT IN 2012 18 year old- 110 17 year old- 99 16 year old- 89 15 year old- 62 14 year old- 39 13 year old- 21 12 year old- 10 11 year old- 2 10 year old- 3 9 year old- 1 7 year old- 3 6 year old- 2 5 year old- 1 4 year old- 1 3 year old- 1 1 year old- 2</Msg><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1356186300211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 09:25:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356187668488-12</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne La Pierre For President</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356111777788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Columbine and this last instance are anomalies. Tragic to be sure but in both cases they were perpetrated by mentally deranged individuals with the same 'I don't care if I die' attitude of a suicidal terrorist. There is little defense against those sort of people, they are hard to recognize if they don't want to be, their problems are often facilitated by, caused or hidden by their families and others closest to them. To overact to the actions of these demented souls is nearly as unfortunate...the deaths are fewer but the demented actions of large numbers of fools could be even more detrimental in the long run. Changing the gun laws while in such a stressed state of mind is careless at best. People grumble about being able to buy guns at gun shows without adequate background checks but no one has been able to quantify how many criminals or mass killers have actually purchased their weapons in such a manner. The most recent example of insanity used weapons purchased legally by his parent! By a parent how thought that her son has some problems relating properly with society, so let’s go shot guns to bond with each other. I am not sure the shooter was the only mentally troubled soul in that family. Common sense needs to be ruling factor in investigating necessary or adequate and useful guns laws, not panic, anger, or sorrow. Unfortunately our media and government don't understand that sort of common sense. Haste will not lead to good decisions. Restricting the purchase and ownership of weapons on such a drastic basis will only weaken the opportunities of self-defense by a law-abiding society. Such gun law changes will not stop criminals from obtaining weapons and they are the ones that need to be stopped.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1356187668488</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 09:47:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356188190096-13</Id><Topic><Title>Wake up, Mr. Boehner...the clock's ticking...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356010640460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is also ticking on the President. He wants what he wants and he wants right now! That is the typical attitude of the newer generation. He won't compromise, he won, he is the boss, he is the smartest man on the planet...if you don't believe him, just ask him. He is an arrogant SOB that is going to demand that he get his way or else. There is no compromise, there is no 'what is best for the country as a whole', there is only I won and I will get what I want. His demands for increased taxes will not solve the problems we have, it will hardly make a dent in the debt or deficit if we don't cut spending, but he will hold out to get his way or he will hold his breath until he turns blue or will simply stomp his feet and whine until they give him what he wants. He has asked of new plans from the Republicans, has received several, and turned all of them down. He isn’t negotiating; he is having a temper tantrum This is the great example of leadership his is giving to his country.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1356188190096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 09:56:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356188297528-14</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne La Pierre For President</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356111777788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In Baltimore, kids, &amp; parents would welcome more Police. I believe the city has about 50 thousand heroin addicts. These people hang out at schools, and prey on the kids. No plan is perfect. The great things about Officers is they become familar with who belongs, and those who don't. Crime is out of control here cause of the illegal alien problem. They have flooded our communities with cheaper, and cheaper drugs.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356188297528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 09:58:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356188584701-15</Id><Topic><Title>NJ Senator Menedez Should Resign</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356045109532</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:11:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Despite being a Republican, having the illegal alien component trumps this story. As far the big media is concerned, this never happened.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356188584701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 10:03:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356189395761-16</Id><Topic><Title>What a day!</Title><Username>marwinhdj459</Username><Timestamp>1341679545000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-07 12:45:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great move</Msg><Username>williamgoldsmith80</Username><Timestamp>1356189395761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 10:16:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356189456749-17</Id><Topic><Title>Maryland State Police now in Balt City</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356147098552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 22:31:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would occassionaly work late in a bad neighborhood. When I did I put a loaded pistol in my lunch pail. I told my partner to duck back in the corner of the manhole if anything happened. Better to be tried by twelve than carried by six. I'ver had rocks and other things thrown in the M/H in those areas. I used to put a clear plastic tarp across the neck of the M/H for protection. It was the only part of town things like that happened.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1356189456749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 10:17:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356192904206-18</Id><Topic><Title>Wake up, Mr. Boehner...the clock's ticking...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356010640460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's an interesting take on what has happened. What has actually happened is that the Tea Brains just wrote themselves out of any impact on policy whatsoever, with the fiscal cliff and moving forward.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356192904206</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 11:15:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356193054692-19</Id><Topic><Title>Maryland State Police now in Balt City</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356147098552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 22:31:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dealing with getting things fixed in the inner city, like your phone, etc. Is always interesting. I know of TELCO people being told to pack it in. Leave asap by the local drug dealers. Once you've been given the word, you'd be foolish to stick around. A guy who once owned a convience store, told me how cop corruption begins. They start receving gifts around the Hollidays, then they ask that they avoid patrolling on certain streets, between say, 1 to 3. Some. don't believe this is a big deal. Then of course, we have some that steal the drugs, and start selling them. One guy did that, a 1/2 block from the station. He knew that many wouldn't suspect him, being that he was so close to headquarters.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356193054692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 11:17:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356195615627-20</Id><Topic><Title>Wake up, Mr. Boehner...the clock's ticking...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356010640460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The President is hung up on this 'I won' attitude. He won, but he didn't win by such a large majority that he has an unlimited mandate to force his will on every subject that gets discussed. He is a poor leader. The things that have gone on in his administration and have gone unanswered, uninvestigated, and ignored by the media is shameful and precedent setting. His governing agenda is to create a crisis, demand it be resolved to his satisfaction or else. Often in the face of a crisis, he shots off his mouth first and thinks later. His stance on the 'fiscal cliff' is ridiculous, he is not interested in negotiating or finding out what might be best for the majority of the people, he is interested in WINNING. If he doesn't win, the rest of the world is ignorant, incompetent partisan. He never considers that such stiff resistance to anything the Republicans want is simply the reverse of what he claims they do to his wishes. He is too arrogant, lazy, and narcissistic to even think he might be wrong or too stubborn for his own good. He is like the playground bully.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1356195615627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 12:00:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356196212229-21</Id><Topic><Title>Wake up, Mr. Boehner...the clock's ticking...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356010640460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What recovery? GM is planning to buy back a lot of its stock and the government is planning to sell a lot of what they still own...at a loss compared to what we gave GM for that stock. Housing is starting to show some signs of improvement but only because of artificially forced low interest rates and we may be headed for another housing bubble because the jobs picture, in spite of their claims is still failing; that is part of the reason they want the UE benefits extended in any 'cliff' negotiations. The stock market is like a bungee cord with all their manipulations of the media and the stories of failure on the part of the Republicans. If the Democrats are the wise and such great leaders they claim why isn't Dirty Harry presenting some plans that both houses might consider? He has all but disappeared along with Nancy. This has all been between JB and Obama when the laws that govern our spending and taxation must be passed by Congress, the entire Congress, not two people. We cannot continue to spend like we are let alone increase taxes so they can spend more. Rather than spend so much time on the tax rates, just extend the Bush cuts so no one see an increase, other than all the hidden and newly identified Obama Care taxes and work on a budget and some accountability rules on off budget spending. Get a control on the spending and then determine how much income is required to support that instead of increasing the spending when they have no real clue if it will be enough or not. Most noted economists insist that increasing taxes to the levels Obama want won't make a dent in our problems anyway. This negotiation is not trying to find a solution or what is best for the country, it is a political fight, and either way we the people will still lose.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1356196212229</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 12:10:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356196565741-22</Id><Topic><Title>weapons</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1356152166219</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 23:56:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure makes a good case for home schooling. You would think with all that cold weather, shootings would go down. Here, in the People's Republic of Maryland, if we get a cold period, shootings drop off. Our folks are warm weather criminals. But when it warms up the streets come alive. I know there has been a large Police presence, in cities where Air Jordans were dramatically reduced to drive Holliday sales. It seems to attract a lot of gang bangers. People don't understand that if these gangs run across each other, a war can easily breakout.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356196565741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 12:16:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356196659319-23</Id><Topic><Title>Cars versus guns...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355946081474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 14:41:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We have regulations for bomb making ingredients. We have regulations for automobiles. We have regulations for firearms." Then what is the problem and why the hue and cry that the regulations must change immediately? There was recently a 35-car pileup on a freeway that killed several, is anyone in Congress calling for new car, truck, or highway regulations?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1356196659319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 12:17:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356199279736-24</Id><Topic><Title>Cars versus guns...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355946081474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 14:41:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Then what is the problem and why the hue and cry that the regulations must change immediately?" I'd say 20 dead 6 and 7 year olds along with their teachers topping off a long line of shootings is indicative of a problem. You want to think that's not a problem, go ahead. You people are sick. What is the problem? Are you #$%$ kidding me? "There was recently a 35-car pileup on a freeway that killed several, is anyone in Congress calling for new car, truck, or highway regulations?" Because the AAA will push for better regulations to prevent future accidents, in contrast to the NRA which is pushing for an AR-15 in every classroom, a policy which any sane person know would result in more students getting shot. Congress doesn't have to call for new regulations to improve automobile safety over threats that they'll be waylaid by a special interest with far, far too much influence. They'll just improve the regulations. But go ahead and keep up this crazy. Every situation that comes up these days you and your fellow Tea Brains march out the crazy. And now you're done as a political force. Anyone who knows history knows what as small group of committed extremists can accomplish, no matter how demented and outlandish, so in 2010 even I was a little worried. But American Democracy has proven itself again. And you're done. You're just adding nails to the tea brain coffin at this point. And you did it all to yourself.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356199279736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:01:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356199654340-25</Id><Topic><Title>Wake up, Mr. Boehner...the clock's ticking...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356010640460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He won because the Bush tax cuts for the wealthy expire no matter what, and there is absolutely nothing the Tea Brains can do to stop it. That's why he won. Because you tea brains were to d*** dumb to play your hand when you had a good one. And now you're too dumb to even salvage what you can from the situation. And you're done.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356199654340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:07:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356200693197-26</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne La Pierre For President</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356111777788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What is the total cost of 100,000 police?" NPR estimated over $8 billion to put an officer in every school. Note that these same people are also saying we should improve our mental health system (after forcing cuts for decades). How? By cutting the taxes of people with mental disorders and hoping they know what to do with the savings? Hope the market sorts it out? Pray they don't use their tax credits to buy an AR-15 and the latest edition of Grand Theft Auto? These are the consequences of Republican irresponsibility and contempt for public infrastructure. Law enforcement has been cut. Mental health has been cut. Schools have been cut. They have no solutions to the problems they've created. Heck, they don't even see a problem. You really have to question the sanity of people that want to keep s*x education out of schools and bring guns into them.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356200693197</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:24:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356200940668-27</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne La Pierre For President</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356111777788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ricky, You are spot on. Amen brother.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1356200940668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:29:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356201608499-28</Id><Topic><Title>DEAR MR. BOEHNER - Please Consider</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1356092465229</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 07:21:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I prefer the GOP brakes to the GOP gas pedal. Things are still far, far better than the Bush years. And that was pre-Tea Party. Imagine what they'd be like now...</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356201608499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:40:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356202168003-29</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne La Pierre For President</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356111777788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shut up you withered old boob. To the extent you are even capable of thought, nobody cares what you think. December 26 is fast upon us and I still do not have confirmation of your arrival at Red's Java Hut on the wharves of SF for a beer at noon. Could it be that you are an all talk, no do, skinny armed little wussy? Actually, why am I asking, we know the answer. Poor Marjorie! There are ways of tracking people...there are ways of tracking people...there are ways of tracking people...waaahhhhh...</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1356202168003</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:49:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356202702130-30</Id><Title>Could 2013 be the Last Year for Your Employer Paid Plan?</Title><Msg>Starting in 2014, just one year away, millions of ill-informed voters may loose their employer paid healthcare. The fine employers will have to pay, is only $2000. Sounds like a no brainer. Just sent Obama a check, and he'll administer it, fund it, supply it. Elections have consequences, and this healthcare debacle was widely debated. Maybe the average deufus American deserves Cuban healthcare.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356202702130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:58:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356203168005-31</Id><Topic><Title>New Year!!!</Title><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1356184045359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:47:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Celebrate the next prediction.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1356203168005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 14:06:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356203455425-32</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy Hook</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1355979551915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 23:59:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny stuff.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1356203455425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 14:10:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356203600809-33</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy Hook</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1355979551915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 23:59:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bizarre.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1356203600809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 14:13:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356203698983-34</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne La Pierre For President</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356111777788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, hiring legions of Police isn't necessary. All we have to do is assign an existing Officer to each school. We already do that in Baltimore County, for Middle, and High Schoolers. If you think about it, crime goes up dramatically, after 3 pm. That's when school is dimissed. That's exactly why Travon Martin had quite a record. He was a burglar. He was caught with burglary tools, and stolen goods. The media tried to hide this at all cost. So with all the sophisticated crime tracking software, it's unbiased. It clearly shows that schools brings criminals, and victims together each day. Public schools, are the dem equivalent of the watering hole in the jungle. The good, the bad, and the ugly, come together each day. Don't you just love Clint Eastwood.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356203698983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 14:14:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356205412348-35</Id><Topic><Title>Could 2013 be the Last Year for Your Employer Paid Plan?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356202702130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:58:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Could 2013 be the Last Year for Your Employer Paid Plan?" No. "Starting in 2014, just one year away, millions of ill-informed voters may loose their employer paid healthcare." Are you Mayan?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356205412348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 14:43:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356208906389-36</Id><Topic><Title>Wake up, Mr. Boehner...the clock's ticking...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356010640460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “His (Obama’s) stance on the 'fiscal cliff' is ridiculous, he is not interested in negotiating or finding out what might be best for the majority of the people, he is interested in WINNING.” - winjondale Winny, my boy, it would appear to the majority of Americans, now including many of your own, that The GOP has just pulled another Boehner. Analysis: GOP Policies Led to Fiscal Cliff Blowup By By CHARLES BABINGTON AP “…Such intransigence in the face of a narrowly divided U.S. electorate dismays Republicans who say compromise can be vital to a party's survival. The collapse of Boehner's tax effort ‘weakens the entire Republican Party,’ said Rep. Steve LaTourette, R-Ohio, who is retiring after 18 years. ‘It's the continuing dumbing down of the Republican Party,’ he said, ‘and we are going to be seen more and more as a bunch of extremists that can't even get a majority of our own people to support policies that we're putting forward. If you're not a governing majority, you're not going to be a majority very long.’ Republican consultant and writer Craig Shirley told The Washington Post: ‘The national GOP is now simply a collection of warring tribal factions’.” "Dumbing down." Gee, winholder, we've been saying that about you for years.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356208906389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 15:41:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356209193728-37</Id><Topic><Title>Wake up, Mr. Boehner...the clock's ticking...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356010640460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “His (Obama’s) stance on the 'fiscal cliff' is ridiculous, he is not interested in negotiating or finding out what might be best for the majority of the people, he is interested in WINNING.” - winjondale Winny, my boy, it would appear to the majority of Americans, now including many of your own, that The GOP has just pulled another _____________. (Speaker’s name goes here.) Analysis: GOP Policies Led to Fiscal Cliff Blowup By C. BABINGTON (AP) “…Such intransigence in the face of a narrowly divided U.S. electorate dismays Republicans who say compromise can be vital to a party's survival. The collapse of Boehner's tax effort ‘weakens the entire Republican Party,’ said Rep. Steve LaTourette, R-Ohio, who is retiring after 18 years. ‘It's the continuing dumbing down of the Republican Party,’ he said, ‘and we are going to be seen more and more as a bunch of extremists that can't even get a majority of our own people to support policies that we're putting forward. If you're not a governing majority, you're not going to be a majority very long.’ Republican consultant and writer Craig Shirley told The Washington Post: ‘The national GOP is now simply a collection of warring tribal factions’.” Dumbing down? Gee, winholder, we’ve been saying that about your posts here for years.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356209193728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 15:46:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356209849553-38</Id><Topic><Title>I'm scared, Maybe the World is Ending.</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356136633511</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 19:37:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barry was about to leave for his Christmas Vacation. Off to Hawaii. So, they could have been pilot wings. Some type of reward they normally give to the little fellas. I know he set records for flying on Air Force One.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356209849553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 15:57:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356213978265-39</Id><Topic><Title>Wake up, Mr. Boehner...the clock's ticking...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356010640460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “His (Obama’s) stance on the 'fiscal cliff' is ridiculous, he is not interested in negotiating or finding out what might be best for the majority of the people, he is interested in WINNING.” - winjondale Your interpretation of events never fails to be nothing short of light years from reality. You do recall there was an election not long ago, don’t you? The candidates ran on platforms…the people voted…you lost…and in so doing, apparently learned nothing. Here’s an AP story headlined GOP Polices led to Fiscal Cliff Blowup “…Such intransigence in the face of a narrowly divided U.S. electorate dismays Republicans who say compromise can be vital to a party's survival. The collapse of Boehner's tax effort ‘weakens the entire Republican Party,’ said Rep. Steve LaTourette, R-Ohio, who is retiring after 18 years. ‘It's the continuing dumbing down of the Republican Party,’ he said, ‘and we are going to be seen more and more as a bunch of extremists that can't even get a majority of our own people to support policies that we're putting forward. If you're not a governing majority, you're not going to be a majority very long.’ Republican consultant and writer Craig Shirley told The Washington Post: ‘The national GOP is now simply a collection of warring tribal factions’.” Dumbing down? Gee, winholder, we’ve been saying that about your posts here for years.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356213978265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 17:06:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356215586751-40</Id><Topic><Title>Wake up, Mr. Boehner...the clock's ticking...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356010640460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"GM is planning to buy back a lot of its stock and the government is planning to sell a lot of what they still own" The good news is the goofball feds are getting out of the auto business. The bad news is it looks like the boondoggle will cost taxpayers some $5B. I don't have my Christmas card from the UAW yet. How about you?</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1356215586751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 17:33:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356217108802-41</Id><Topic><Title>Wake up, Mr. Boehner...the clock's ticking...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356010640460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So far the government is ahead by about $22 billion for all the bailouts. You jackass Republicans totally wrecked the economy and the Democrats have to bail it out. Four years later the country is ahead by $22 billion, a depression is avoided, unemployment is going down and you fools are complaining. It is OK to be stupid but how about just being quit about it.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1356217108802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 17:58:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356217945204-42</Id><Topic><Title>Wake up, Mr. Boehner...the clock's ticking...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356010640460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We know. You would have let Detroit fail. How much do you think that would have cost? More than $5 billion, that's for sure. Obama found $716 billion savings from Medicare without cutting benefits. Yet you would have Obama reinstate all $716 billion in spending, and decry the AARP for supporting those savings. As long as the government checks go to you, you like high spending. People like you and the Tea Brains have no place in government. You certainly don't deserve a card from anyone.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356217945204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 18:12:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356229046648-43</Id><Title>Benghazi Blamed on Ambassador Stevens</Title><Msg>What a Christmas present for his family. In the final report, it was everyone, but at the same time no one, that failed their duty. It would be unfair, to place blame. In the final determination, after exhaustive review, responsibility rests on the Ambassador's shoulders for the safety of the ground personnel. He didn't ask that the mission be closed, or forcefully enough ask for more boots on the ground. This poor man didn't even fire extinquishers at his disposal. Meanwhile, the man who refused to send aid, Barrack, is on another 20 day vacation in Hawaii. How do these people sleep at night?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356229046648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 21:17:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356229735746-44</Id><Topic><Title>Marine chained to Bed in Mexico, Obama Vacations</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356059387397</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 22:09:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Marine was released. I guess the Mexicans saw there was really nothing to gain by holding him. After several months he is finally free. No one in our government seemed to care. So, perhaps in the Spirit of Christmas, he's back home. Praise the Lord. But it seems Barry did nothing to help. I'm sure if he did, he'd be taking credit.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356229735746</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 21:28:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>