<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351310595865-1</Id><Topic><Title>You didn't build that, you didn't build that</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1351310282706</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 23:58:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cool yo!</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1351310595865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 00:03:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351338588960-2</Id><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Msg>... “No theory, no ready-made system, no book that has ever been written will save the world. I cleave to no system. I am a true seeker.” – Mikhail Bakunin “It takes a good deal of physical courage to ride a horse. This, however, I have. I get it at about forty cents a flask, and take it as required.” – Stephen Leacock "As part of a new 'transparency series,' McDonald's is releasing videos that show how its food is made. It involves horses and bayonets." - Jimmy Fallon “You can safely assume that you've created God in your own image when it turns out that God hates all the same people you do.” – Anne Lamott “More Brandy wine? They were boiling it in Ireland before the snakes left!" – King Henry II, The Lion in Winter “My feeling is religious insofar as I am imbued with the consciousness of the insufficiency of the human mind to understand more deeply the harmony of the Universe which we try to formulate as ‘laws of nature’.” – Albert Einstein "A lot of crazy rumors are starting to surface about the two candidates. A man is claiming that President Obama used and sold c#caine in college. On the bright side, if this is true, it means Obama does have business experience." - Jay Leno “Several people have told me that my inability to suffer fools gladly is one of my main weaknesses.” – Edsger W. Dijkstra “The American elite does not have any real image of peace — other than as an uneasy interlude existing precariously by virtue of the balance of mutual fright. The only seriously accepted plan for peace is the full loaded pistol. In short, war or a high state of war-preparedness is felt to be the normal and seemingly permanent condition of the United States.” – C. Wright Mills “The most savage controversies are those about matters to which there is no good evidence either way.” – Bertrand Russell “Donald Trump says he will reveal big news about President Obama on Wednesday. Trump said he would have announced it sooner, but faking a Kenyan birth certificate is harder than it looks." - Conan O'Brien “We, by our arts may be called the grandsons of God.” – Leonardo da Vinci “It would be frightening to think that in all the cosmos, which is so harmonious, so complete and equal to itself, that only human life is happening randomly, that only one's destiny lacks meaning.” – Mircea Eliade “Endorsements are rolling in. The Atheist Party has endorsed Obama for president. When told the news Obama said, 'Thank God’!” - Conan O'Brien “I decided (after listening to a "talk radio" commentator who abused, vilified, and scorned every noble cause to which I had devoted my entire life) that I was both a humanist and a liberal, each of the most dangerous and vilified type. I am a humanist because I think humanity can, with constant moral guidance, create a reasonably decent society. I am terrified of restrictive religious doctrine, having learned from history that when men who adhere to any form of it are in control, common men like me are in peril. I do not believe that pure reason can solve the perpetual problems unless it is modified by poetry and art and social vision. So I am a humanist. And if you want to charge me with being the most virulent kind—a secular humanist – I accept the accusation.” – James Michener “Have a good weekend, all.” – echo2165 “A voice comes to one in the dark.” – Samuel Beckett</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351338588960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 07:49:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351339012453-3</Id><Title>Never forget: "After my election I have more flexability"</Title><Msg>Just wondering what does more flexability mean to our "Dear Leader"? and What did it mean to President Medvedev? and Does Mr. Putin understand the value of a more flexable POTUS? Wonder why this never came up during the debates? Regardless of the outcome of the election IMHO POTUS will make good on his promise to his friend Mr. Putin. The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351339012453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 07:56:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351341554235-4</Id><Topic><Title>Never forget: "After my election I have more flexability"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351339012453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 07:56:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You do not have the ability to understand the message even if we explained it to you.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1351341554235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:39:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351346454848-5</Id><Topic><Title>Romney lover, explain why he needs a govt funded tax cut from 20% or more, to 14% or less</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351279716123</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 15:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's actually to "fund" Americans - to LOCATE freeloading, bloodsucking "leeches" like you &amp; your group .. to get y'all off of welfare - on to "workfare"" As you spend your day posting messages. The question was why does Romney need a tax cut from the govt, aka handout.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351346454848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351346591374-6</Id><Topic><Title>Never forget: "After my election I have more flexability"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351339012453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 07:56:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again the perfect response from the left, that indicates that those on the right do not have the intellectual capacity to understand the profound statements of their "Dear Leader". I pray that they all go to the polls on November 7 and prove me wrong. Sorry couldn't resist The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351346591374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351349413076-7</Id><Topic><Title>More from The GOP War on Women...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351112943088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It looks like Echo is getting under your skin. "Now as far as myself ... I'm not a follower of anything". Well, that's a lie. We all know you'll follow an open bag of pork cracklin's until your knees give out under your ponderous weight and the sweat drips from your combover into your little piggy eyes. You are an idiot.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351349413076</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:50:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351349836037-8</Id><Topic><Title>Romney lover, explain why he needs a govt funded tax cut from 20% or more, to 14% or less</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351279716123</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 15:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why does Romney need a tax cut from the govt, aka handout.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351349836037</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:57:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351352105967-9</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (cont.)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351300725933</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 21:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Echo. I always look forward to wrapping up the week with five minutes of these: Good for you finding Elbert Hubbard (“The recipe for perpetual ignorance is: be satisfied with your opinions and content with your knowledge.” – Elbert Hubbard); talk about an obscure American sage. We've got his Little Journeys to the Homes of Good Men and Great, and Message to Garcia, which are good for 15-20 minutes of distraction on a rainy winter day.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351352105967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:35:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351354560697-10</Id><Topic><Title>Romney lover, explain why he needs a govt funded tax cut from 20% or more, to 14% or less</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351279716123</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 15:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess you like paying taxes so banksters and the boys that run the military industrial complex can get richer. If you think ANY of the major candidates intend to change this racket you are a fool. They ALWAYS write loopholes in tax law for the people that really run this country. Congress is full of bribe takers in both parties. There's a web site that lists contributions to national offices. By googling around you can find it. I use the example of the Goldman-Sachs PAC. It was the second largest contributor to the Kenyan in 2008. He has collected more money from the 1% than Romney. I'll bet you are to stupid to figure that one out.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351354560697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:16:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351355501925-11</Id><Topic><Title>You didn't build that, you didn't build that</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1351310282706</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 23:58:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Downloaded this rap from itunes to my car stereo and turned it up while filling up with gas with all the windows down. The people filling up next to me started dancing guess they liked it. If Romney wins I'll be dancing too.</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1351355501925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:31:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351356976671-12</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer</Title><Username>ritche1998</Username><Timestamp>1351248370550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 06:46:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes he is!</Msg><Username>borderescalade</Username><Timestamp>1351356976671</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:56:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351357280983-13</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer</Title><Username>ritche1998</Username><Timestamp>1351248370550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 06:46:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Website pls.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1351357280983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 13:01:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351365736352-14</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer</Title><Username>ritche1998</Username><Timestamp>1351248370550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 06:46:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time to buy. Cramer is just trying to help his short selling buddies. They are now following investors/clients/money flow into high yield dividend stocks. The population is getting older and investors are looking for income generating investments. Some see this as an opportunity to rip them off. Also, this dividend paying for valuations concept came from: The Evaluation Of Common Stocks by Arnold Bernhard. He believed that a company's dividend paying ability was the most important metric in the valuation of its stock. I would not place any weight on Cramer's statement. A short seller who has been putting pressure on this stock lately. My guess is Cramer is trying to help his by discouraging retail investors from buying the stock. T is also in better shape than VZ to maintain its dividend. VZ has more debt and a large minority interest associated with its earnings. Also, this neo-communist notion that all stocks should trade at little or no multiples came from a group ( likely short sellers) a few years ago. They tried to persuade investors not to buy stocks with multiples over 10 percent. This was total nonsense. They were only trying to make money on their bets against companies. T trades at about 13.8X forward earnings right now. This is really very conservative for this company. It will likely trade higher 2013 (17 X trailing earnings of about $2.45 per share). This is still pretty conservative for a stable dividend paying stock. Investors may not see many stocks with over 5 percent yields in 2013 and they surely will not see any at 9 percent in this sector ( maybe in their Cramer dreams).</Msg><Username>bass9189</Username><Timestamp>1351365736352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:22:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351369866428-15</Id><Title>How many van loads of Somalians does it take to change the results in Ohio?</Title><Msg>According to the Somali Community Association of Ohio web site over 45,000 Somalis live in the state of Ohio, and about 40% of those are US citizens. You have to hand it the dems they sure know how to get out the vote. The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351369866428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:31:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351373739323-16</Id><Topic><Title>ATT retiree benefits</Title><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1343908864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical ignorant response.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1351373739323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 17:35:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351374205069-17</Id><Topic><Title>that two out of three were censored is frightening...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351301086851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 21:24:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey robfisk, when I looked up "more on" in the dictionary, it had a picture of you mug.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1351374205069</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 17:43:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351374536585-18</Id><Topic><Title>ATT retiree benefits</Title><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1343908864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats #$%$. Obama wants companies to drop their health coverage so we have no choice. He wants the government to own us all. If you think you won't trade your freedom for government healthcare you are fooling yourself. It will cost the working man more and we will get less. If you think Universal healthcare is the ticket you live in an alternate world.</Msg><Username>deebuck53</Username><Timestamp>1351374536585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 17:48:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351374661568-19</Id><Topic><Title>ATT retiree benefits</Title><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1343908864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is true. I have talked to several retirees. If you are married and not on medicare yet and your spouse is not covered at work by their insurance you pay $110.00 for you and $110.00 for the spouse.</Msg><Username>deebuck53</Username><Timestamp>1351374661568</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 17:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351379724460-20</Id><Topic><Title>5%, adding? div going up a penny me thinks :)</Title><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351173167453</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:52:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe the point is who will exit a stock that has a 5 percent dividend yield for lower yielding securities. Few Investors will exit 5 percent to get maybe 2 percent. Also, if the bond yield does increase to over 5 percent price will go down. Anything over 5 percent is also considered high risk in the current bond markets, meaning price could move down even more.</Msg><Username>bass9189</Username><Timestamp>1351379724460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 19:15:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351380864587-21</Id><Title>"Maybe if I Focus on the Big Bird, People Will Forget How Bad of a President I am"</Title><Msg>-Barack Obama</Msg><Username>xtgeminiman</Username><Timestamp>1351380864587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 19:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351380941471-22</Id><Topic><Title>Romney lover, explain why he needs a govt funded tax cut from 20% or more, to 14% or less</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351279716123</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 15:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what is the reason mitt romney needs the 4-5% tax cut from the government, aka a handout, when he already finds every loophole and way of paying a low tax rate. What does he need it for, and why should we give it to him, it's about $1,000,000. The question goes unanswered by the uber intellects here.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351380941471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 19:35:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351386625837-23</Id><Topic><Title>"Maybe if I Focus on the Big Bird, People Will Forget How Bad of a President I am"</Title><Username>xtgeminiman</Username><Timestamp>1351380864587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 19:34:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...How sad. Get well, my friend.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351386625837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351389888354-24</Id><Topic><Title>ATT retiree benefits</Title><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1343908864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the act is not in effect yet.</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1351389888354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 22:04:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351390077636-25</Id><Topic><Title>ATT retiree benefits</Title><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1343908864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree to a Canadian universal health system would be great. But too many skimmers are making money on this system. I have visited Canada 4 times in 5 yrs. and have met zero Canadians who want our health care----they complain about the tax invovled but realize the horrors of our system. If I were young I would head north, but I am old and have cancer.g.l.t.a.</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1351390077636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 22:07:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351390498365-26</Id><Topic><Title>ATT retiree benefits</Title><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1343908864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the proposed voucher system that Romney panders will be a farce. The real issue is all the people who make money off our broken health system---insurance agents,billers,clerks,3rd party billers,etc etc.....the talking heads on national tv sure bash and support selective groups. National healthcare would actually benefit big business because it would level the field.</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1351390498365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 22:14:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351390602224-27</Id><Topic><Title>How many van loads of Somalians does it take to change the results in Ohio?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351369866428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:31:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they live primarily in Columbus,Ohio but who knows their party preference or whether they vote?</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1351390602224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 22:16:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351392875832-28</Id><Topic><Title>Romney lover, explain why he needs a govt funded tax cut from 20% or more, to 14% or less</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351279716123</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 15:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical statement from the 47% who pay no federal tax saying it's not fair to lower the taxes on the rest of us.</Msg><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1351392875832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 22:54:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351393825825-29</Id><Topic><Title>Romney lover, explain why he needs a govt funded tax cut from 20% or more, to 14% or less</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351279716123</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 15:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one seems able to answer why Romney needs his Bush tax cut. This in on top of his normal tax advantages. The answer is there is no reason, he doesn't need it. He has no use for it except it adds to his account balance and the number is bigger. The next question is why do we tax payers and voters give it to him?</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351393825825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 23:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>