<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354281682133-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Get his Money</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354232624025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 18:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...and that explains why the Obama team received rave reviews for getting the "handout" vote energized for this election.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1354281682133</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 08:21:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354282968308-2</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Senate Pounded by John Boehner</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1354240116860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:48:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “…Boehner is a weak cry baby who needs to go…” – geofakeholt Speaking of cry babies, I see you guys were out in force last night. Talk about a bunch of whining sore losers. Summarizing last night’s bawling points: “OH, boo-hoo, those evil poor people are picking on us. The EPA is a communist plot who probably is putting fluoride in our drinking water. Say NO to Obamacare before the death squads come for Grannie. Boehner needs to grow a pair – screw compromise. The DC beltway Democrats are Commies. Good will trump evil, as the President will somehow hang himself. People in cities don’t vote. The ‘haves’ will lose everything. The President has a mandate from the ‘freeloaders’ who voted him in (you mean the 47% of the population who are all bums?) He’ll get our money one way or another…and he’ll give it all to the immigrants and Inner city folks…(again, you mean just like he stole the election with promises of gifts and handouts? Didn’t Newt set you straight on that last week?) Do you fools have any idea how absolutely ridiculous you sound continuing on with this immature incessant, and blatantly racist, tirade, even in the face of your own party telling you that they just learned, the hard way, (in terms the Tea Partiers might understand), “that dog don’t hunt” ? “Romney’s comments that Obama owed his reelection to ‘gifts’ is absolutely wrong” – Jindal “We cannot be ignorant of demography.” – Haley Barbour Hey, Haley…apparently you have a significant enough portion of your base who refuses to accept that. Might being “ignorant of demography” have some inbred racial connotation? BTW, apparently, winnie was MIA yesterday because he was having the Romney/Ryan campaign tattoo removed from his face by laser. Ouch! What do winnie and Mike Tyson have in common? Face tattoos? No, they’re both ugly with a single digit I.Q.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1354282968308</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 08:42:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354283384883-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Get his Money</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354232624025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 18:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...Didn't swanger just tell you those folks don't vote? Of the 65,138,059 citizens (almost 52%) who voted for Obama, are you suggesting they were all looking for handouts? Or just that they don't pay any taxes? Or just that you aren't very happy with the results.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1354283384883</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 08:49:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354284933216-4</Id><Topic><Title>Norquist Popular With Lib. Democrats</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1354046450537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:00:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At this point the fiscal cliff negotiations are all politics. Democrats have proposed the revenue increases (which are very popular), but neither side wants to be the one that proposes cuts. This has been the Republican problem all along--they talk the talk but when it's time to get down to the business of making cuts, they don't walk the walk. Heck, they spent the campaign accusing Obama of cutting Medicare. Well, now they've really backed themselves into a corner. They banked everything on making Obama a one term president. The Democrats are coming off a 2nd win that has serious implications for the electoral college maps (many of those purple states are now decidedly blue). The revenue increases are coming. Republicans are divided. And they're being faced with the spectre of either not being able to come up with the solid spending cut proposals they have repeatedly demanded or being the ones who cut Medicare, which they have also repeatedly demanded. That's why I laughed at winholder when he was complaining about "Congress" never actually dealing with fiscal concerns. Well, now they are. And we see who is walking the walk. It's the ones who found both the spending cuts and the revenue to maintain Medicare.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354284933216</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 09:15:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354285014291-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Get his Money</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354232624025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 18:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe that he should reduce the handouts. That would be prudent. Hire some competent people to root out the fraud. Why should I pay more, when less fortunate folks are not? We all should share in this tax hike. And we should all suffer the ills of cuts in spending. I bet that the poor would be glad to give up something. Right?</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354285014291</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 09:16:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354285374879-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Get his Money</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354232624025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 18:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiot. Be sure to call me a typical lib namecaller, now, after you called over half of America freeloaders looking for handouts. My suggestion to you is to get out of your namecalling mindset, and take a good look at the American people and what we are trying to achieve.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354285374879</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 09:22:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354286612981-7</Id><Title>AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD</Title><Msg>AMD AMD AMD AMD</Msg><Username>powerball754</Username><Timestamp>1354286612981</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 09:43:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354287531191-8</Id><Topic><Title>AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD AMD</Title><Username>powerball754</Username><Timestamp>1354286612981</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 09:43:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be a product of public education. This is the AT&amp;T board. Besides, AMD is in a downtrend for the near term. The rise is just MM's setting the pins up (in order to knock the dumb money out soon).</Msg><Username>coulddobetter</Username><Timestamp>1354287531191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 09:58:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354287955855-9</Id><Topic><Title>Norquist Popular With Lib. Democrats</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1354046450537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:00:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then propose some cuts, and don't attack Obama when he finds $700 billion in savings without cutting benefits.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354287955855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:05:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354288593817-10</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Senate Pounded by John Boehner</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1354240116860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:48:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like cupcakes! No more broccoli! Nonsanctioned broccoli usurps refrigerator space! Recapitalize the fridge with cupcakes! I think this one is my favorite: "Recapitalize Social Security Trust Fund by making many entitlement cuts." It doesn't quite beat "keep your government hands off my Medicare," but it's close.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354288593817</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:16:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354289799710-11</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Senate Pounded by John Boehner</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1354240116860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:48:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mike Tyson" I agree with all you say except that Mike Tyson is as dumb. I wou;ldn't assume that. They also say Obama has no mandate at 3%, whilst GWB strutted around with mandate to spend on a negative number. They also say a man who was a state Senator, US Senator and two terms as President, the highet job in the land ,next to Norquist the Lobbyist that is, is just a ol' communiddy organizer. Good, either they change or keep losing elections. Good.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1354289799710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:36:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354290547979-12</Id><Topic><Title>T is one of top picks like crimson on apex</Title><Username>ethelvillarreal43</Username><Timestamp>1353943269318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:21:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for this awesome report!</Msg><Username>ralphsolo409</Username><Timestamp>1354290547979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:49:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354293350865-13</Id><Title>re; Obama will get our money...</Title><Msg>... “…too many young, not too (politically) savvy students, ETC. - seeing the leaniant (sic) criteria to receive Govt. money, for making their lives better = the same as BUYING votes !! This would account for an easy 10 % of the Obama vote…” – jon the retarded statistician Let’s see here. Obama got 65,138,059 votes, total. (It would have been 65,138,060, but Rob’s Prius broke down on the way to the polls, so Mrs. Fisk couldn’t cast her ballot. Of course, that cost Mitt Rob’s vote, as well, but neither were too important in the grand scheme of things, and at least it got them out of the house for awhile…and having coffee in the repair shop waiting room is a veritable soiree for the Fisks. Plus, free donuts!!! Quite a day, despite not voting!) So, ten percent of that would be 6,513,805 votes that were cast by students looking for handouts, according to Doctor jon. Jon, as I know you’re a stickler for facts and accuracy, would you mind showing us your source for that very questionable number that, along with many other murky theories, suddenly registered in your limited grey matter? The total number of postsecondary students is about 21 million. About one forth of eligible college students are not registered to vote. That leaves about 15.75 million REGISTERED college voters. It’s estimated that about 57% of eligible voters actually turned out in 2012, overall. That leaves under 9 million college voters. Obama got about 52% of the vote total. Fifty-two percent of nine million equals about 4.6 million college voters who voted for Obama. You contend that about 2 million more than that not only voted for Obama, but every single one of them (plus 2 million imaginary others) all did it simply for the freebies. This proves several things about jon’s facts, figures and fantasies. One, it’s impossible to admit that anyone who disagrees with him does so out of thoughtful analysis or that they voted for any number of reasons besides wanting handouts…and, two…most of jon’s incoherent ramblings here, rather than containing any factual relevancy whatsoever, are based solely on whatever strikes his fancy on any given moment. And, three, if he was any decent kind of a guy, he’d have stopped by the repair shop, had a couple donuts with the Fisks, and then driven them to the polls. Geeeez, talk about voter suppression!!!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1354293350865</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 11:35:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354294434866-14</Id><Title>Say it ain't so. A dem wouldn't do this.</Title><Msg>Susan Rice’s foreign investments By: John Hayward Follow @@Doc_0 11/30/2012 08:42 AM In what might turn out to be the final set of nails in the coffin of her Secretary of State ambitions, it turns out that U.N. Ambassador Susan Rice has huge foreign investments, including several companies that are doing business with Iran. She has ties to one company, Royal Dutch Shell, that stands to make a billion dollars if the sanctions against Iran are lifted; as the Washington Free Beacon reports, other Rice investments are currently making big bucks working for the mullahs, to the ostensible displeasure of the Administration: Rice has additional investments in Norsk Hydro ASA, a Norwegian aluminum firm, and BHP Billiton PLC, an Australian-based natural resources company, financial disclosure show. Norway’s Norsk Hydro was awarded in 2006 a $107 million exploration and development contract for Iran’s Khorramabad oil block, according to the Wall Street Journal. Rice’s portfolio includes an investment of up to $15,000 in the company. Norsk acknowledged at the time that it was working in Iran against the wishes of the U.S. government. America is “not happy that we’re there,” Norsk Hydro spokeswoman Kama Holte Strand told the Journal at the time. Holte admitted that the company was working with Tehran because it is “profitable.” Rice has up to $50,000 invested with another Iranian partner, BHP Billiton, which was probed by the Securities and Exchange Commission in 2010 for its dealings with Cuba and Iran, according to reports. The company, which had leased office space in Tehran, admitted to making more than $360 million from the Iranians, according to The Australian. Rice also has big investments with a Canadian oil pipeline company that would make out very nicely if the Keystone XL pipeline ever gets built… something Rice would have influence over, if she became Secretary of State. The Daily Caller has the details: According to her May 2012 financial disclosure, Rice has an investment in TransCanada Corporation worth between $300,000 and $600,000. TransCanada is angling for the State Department’s permission to build the final portion of the Keystone XL pipeline — a 1,700-mile conduit for crude oil between Canadian deposits and Texas refineries. If she were confirmed as secretary of state, Rice would have final authority to green-light the large section of the pipeline project still languishing in regulatory purgatory. “[A]bout a third of Rice’s personal net worth is tied up in oil producers, pipeline operators, and related energy industries north of the 49th parallel,” a [National Resources Defense Council] blogger wrote Wednesday, “including companies with poor environmental and safety records on both U.S. and Canadian soil.” “Rice and her husband own at least $1.25 million worth of stock in four of Canada’s eight leading oil producers, as ranked by Forbes magazine. That includes Enbridge, which spilled more than a million gallons of toxic bitumen into Michigan’s Kalamazoo River in 2010 — the largest inland oil spill in U.S. history.” Republicans generally believe the Keystone XL pipeline should be completed, so there would be applause for Rice if she was able to get it done. (Actually, if she’s really interested in winning Republican support for her prospective nomination, she should start advertising her willingness to do so.) But it’s rather difficult to avoid the clear conflict of interest, and of course her ties to Iranian business are going to be even larger “bumps in the road” on her path to Secretary of State. And her entire portfolio is a rather stunning violation of Democrat Party dogma. Rice is extremely wealthy – she’s worth somewhere between $22 and $44 million, according to her financial disclosures, making her the richest current member of the executive branch. A lot of that money is tied up in the kind of overseas investments that Democrats nearly popped a blood vessel screaming about during the 2012 presidential campaign. She’s even got money in Wal-Mart, the current hate fetish of Big Labor. Susan Rice, in addition to the lingering questions about her role in the Benghazi scandal, is practically a caricature of what Democrat activists think a Republican appointee would look like… except for what she looks like. And that’s all that really matters to a lot of Democrats, isn’t it? That, plus the proper Party credentials?</Msg><Username>coulddobetter</Username><Timestamp>1354294434866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 11:53:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354294561150-15</Id><Topic><Title>Norquist Popular With Lib. Democrats</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1354046450537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:00:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thus far there has been very little walking the walk, just a lot of threats, name-calling, and wasting of time...kind of like this message board. In Congress neither side has done much of anything yet nor neither has Obama outside of participating in the name-calling and threats. He thinks he doesn't have to negotiate because he won and he will go on another campaign tour to convince the American people he is right. It makes little difference if he is right or wrong (which I think he is) because Congress, particularly those up for reelection in two years, will have to make the call. The tax laws are a convoluted, corrupt mess. Who wrote them? The housing and banking industry hit a wall a few years ago. Who wrote the laws that changed their processes that lead to the fiasco that started many of our problems? Medicare, Social Security has been in danger of falling apart for decades now. Who wrote the laws that dictate how they operate and are they are funded? Who has ignored calls from nearly everyone that something needs to be done? The answer to these and many other questions around our financial difficulties is of course CONGRESS! Politics and not the needs or the future of this country will lead to the decision made over this current fiasco and that will not lead to the best outcome for the taxpayers. Wanna bet they go home for yet another recess before they reach agreement?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1354294561150</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 11:56:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354294693934-16</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Senate Pounded by John Boehner</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1354240116860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:48:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ricky, quietly step away from the bottle, it is way too early in the day.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1354294693934</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 11:58:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354294991902-17</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Senate Pounded by John Boehner</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1354240116860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:48:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope, no tattoo removal, just a nice leisurely round of golf with the friends and then a little casino time with the wife...came out a winner as well. Believe it or not I am not obsessed with you, Ricky or the other radical fools like you. I am not obsessed with tracking other posters on this board. I am not obsessed with Obama; he will only be with us for another four years at the most. We have survived worse Presidents, the question is will we survive another sessions or two of Congress. Have a good day Sir Echo, I have another round of golf scheduled for this afternoon, and a lesson from the local club pro…my short game needs some work.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1354294991902</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:03:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354295997127-18</Id><Topic><Title>Pensions</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1353718010663</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:46:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I worked until I was 59 years of age. I retired early because Verizon wanted to cut costs and made an amazing offer to just quietly and quickly go away. No one is paying for my retirement. I am living off the money I saved, invested, and earned for 24 years of service to a company that promised those benefits in return for an honest day’s work. I paid for my education and did it without taking out government-sponsored loans, I didn't even use my VA benefits, I just worked! I could have returned to the workforce, in fact was offered by Verizon to return as a contractor. We made the decisions that with both our retirements and incentive pay to retire, we could live comfortably without doing so. I didn't ask to be forced into Medicare, the government and their rules to companies pushed me there. I had health and life insurance through my past employer, at a higher price than I thought reasonable, but with the government’s assistance and the desire of my employer to reduce costs even further, they both said I had to enroll in Medicare. As a result I am now paying higher deductibles, higher rates to Verizon and paying for Medicare. Neither my doctors, nor my care have changed, I am just paying more to maintain the status quo. I don’t see where any of those decisions is shortchanging you or anyone like you or your future. You have the keep in mind, these boomers you so quickly denigrate, didn’t make these rules…the government did, and please consider that most of the rules you despise were passed by Democrats. In your vernacular, I paid my way. Thank you Congress.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1354295997127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:19:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354296764947-19</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet: cap gain 30%, 50% tax on the rich</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353097971771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh contraire mouth that roars. I am completely aware of my own personality and individuality. I am also aware of the history of the past actions of our duly elected and paid for Congress. I am aware of the philosophies of liberals like you that want the government to control everything, including your personal lives. No thanks, if I have to settle for that to be self-aware in your view that is too high a price to pay. By the way, that really is a dumb, inappropriate comment.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1354296764947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:32:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354298900024-20</Id><Title>Looks Like My Naked Options on T Will Expire Worthless Yet Again</Title><Msg>$300/week for doing literally nothing. What a great company.</Msg><Username>xtgeminiman</Username><Timestamp>1354298900024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:08:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354300377260-21</Id><Title>What ever happened to that "igolf or whatever" poster?</Title><Msg>obnoxious guy. Did he finally pass away, hopefully?</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354300377260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:32:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354301243624-22</Id><Title>Obama will get...</Title><Msg>... “…too many young, not too (politically) savvy students, ETC. - seeing the leaniant (sic) criteria to receive Govt. money, for making their lives better = the same as BUYING votes !! This would account for an easy 10 % of the Obama vote…” – jon the retarded statistician Let’s see here. Obama got 65,138,059 votes, total. (It would have been 65,138,060, but Rob’s Prius broke down on the way to the polls, so Mrs. Fisk couldn’t cast her ballot. Of course, that cost Mitt Rob’s vote, as well, but neither were too important in the grand scheme of things, and at least it got them out of the house for awhile…and having coffee in the repair shop waiting room is a veritable soiree for the Fisks. Plus, free donuts!!! Quite a day, despite not voting!) So, ten percent of that would be 6,513,805 votes that were cast by students looking for handouts, according to Doctor jon. Jon, as I know you’re a stickler for facts and accuracy, would you mind showing us your source for that very questionable number that, along with many other murky theories, suddenly registered in your limited grey matter? The total number of postsecondary students is about 21 million. About one forth of eligible college students are not registered to vote. That leaves about 15.75 million REGISTERED college voters. It’s estimated that about 57% of eligible voters actually turned out in 2012, overall. That leaves under 9 million college voters. Obama got about 52% of the vote total. Fifty-two percent of nine million equals about 4.6 million college voters who voted for Obama. You contend that about 2 million more than that not only voted for Obama, but every single one of them (plus 2 million imaginary others) all did it simply for the freebies. This proves several things about jon’s facts, figures and fantasies. One, it’s impossible for him to admit that anyone who disagrees with him does so out of thoughtful analysis or that they voted for any number of reasons besides wanting handouts (BTW, aren’t capital gains and other favorable tax rates for the one percenters, and coporate welfare and subsidies, handouts, as well?Would it be fair to say, by the same token, Mitt’s voters were also looking for handouts?)…and, two…most of jon’s incoherent ramblings here, rather than containing any factual relevancy whatsoever, are based solely on whatever strikes his fancy on any given moment. And, three, if he was any decent kind of a guy, he’d have stopped by the repair shop, had a couple donuts with the Fisks, and then driven them to the polls. Geeeez, talk about voter suppression!!!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1354301243624</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:47:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354301406972-23</Id><Topic><Title>Pensions</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1353718010663</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:46:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, in 2012. In 2011 it was $76.00 per month. In 2013 will be $270.69 per month.</Msg><Username>frb53</Username><Timestamp>1354301406972</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:50:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354301853381-24</Id><Topic><Title>T is one of top picks like crimson on apex</Title><Username>ethelvillarreal43</Username><Timestamp>1353943269318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:21:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This was really helpful</Msg><Username>davidgarcia640</Username><Timestamp>1354301853381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:57:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354301870454-25</Id><Topic><Title>T is one of top picks like crimson on apex</Title><Username>ethelvillarreal43</Username><Timestamp>1353943269318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:21:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This was really helpful</Msg><Username>davidgarcia640</Username><Timestamp>1354301870454</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:57:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354303721451-26</Id><Title>PROTECT YOUR 401K, RETIREMENT, SAVING NOW!</Title><Msg>FOR YOUR CHILDREND.</Msg><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1354303721451</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 14:28:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354304820840-27</Id><Topic><Title>Pensions</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1353718010663</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:46:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't see your other post. I am working part-time now still paying taxes, just like I have since age 18. Present employees family $81.00 a month, I my case retiree family $270.69 a month. Who is paying their reasonable share? I retired after 30 years of climbing poles ,that was all my knees would take.</Msg><Username>frb53</Username><Timestamp>1354304820840</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 14:47:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354306558652-28</Id><Topic><Title>Buy backs to beat dividend tax?</Title><Username>stonewallneeljac</Username><Timestamp>1353452128897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 17:55:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't hold, let go.</Msg><Username>phypan_99</Username><Timestamp>1354306558652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:15:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354306867076-29</Id><Title>Buying votes...</Title><Msg>... “…too many young, not too (politically) savvy students, ETC. - seeing the leaniant (sic) criteria to receive Govt. money, for making their lives better = the same as BUYING votes !! This would account for an easy 10 % of the Obama vote…” – jon the statistician Let’s see here. Obama got 65,138,059 votes, total. (It would have been 65,138,060, but Rob’s Prius broke down on the way to the polls, so Mrs. Fisk couldn’t cast her ballot. Of course, that cost Mitt Rob’s vote, as well, but neither were too important in the grand scheme of things, and at least it got them out of the house for awhile…and having coffee in the repair shop waiting room is a veritable soiree for the Fisks. Plus, free donuts!!! Quite a day, despite not voting!) So, ten percent of that would be 6,513,805 votes that were cast by students looking for handouts, according to Doctor jon. Jon, as I know you’re a stickler for facts and accuracy, would you mind showing us your source for that very questionable number that, along with many other murky theories, suddenly registered in your limited grey matter? The total number of postsecondary students is about 21 million. About one fourth of eligible college students are not registered to vote. That leaves about 15.75 million REGISTERED college voters. It’s estimated that about 57% of eligible voters actually turned out in 2012, overall. That leaves under 9 million college voters. Obama got about 52% of the vote total. Fifty-two percent of nine million equals about 4.6 million college voters who voted for Obama. You contend that about 2 million more than that not only voted for Obama, but every single one of them (plus 2 million imaginary others) all did it simply for the freebies. This proves several things about jon’s facts, figures and fantasies. One, it’s impossible for him to admit that anyone who disagrees with him does so out of thoughtful analysis or that they voted for any number of reasons besides wanting handouts (BTW, aren’t capital gains and other favorable tax rates for the one percenters, and corporate welfare and subsidies, handouts, as well? Would it be fair to say, by the same token, Mitt’s voters were also looking for handouts?)…and, two…most of jon’s incoherent ramblings here, rather than containing any factual relevancy whatsoever, are based solely on whatever strikes his fancy on any given moment. And, three, if he was any decent kind of a guy, he’d have stopped by the repair shop, had a couple donuts with the Fisks, and then driven them to the polls…talk about voter suppression!!!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1354306867076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:21:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354307177625-30</Id><Topic><Title>Pensions</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1353718010663</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:46:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd say that situation sounds about right--if you want younger workers to be able to get the same deal when their knees go after 30 years. There are few companies around like AT&amp;T to provide those kinds of benefits to workers anymore. Mostly public utilities. The rest have gone bankrupt or moved the good jobs overseas. You can't outsource climbing poles though...</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354307177625</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:26:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354307980446-31</Id><Topic><Title>Say it ain't so. A dem wouldn't do this.</Title><Username>coulddobetter</Username><Timestamp>1354294434866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 11:53:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"is practically a caricature of what Democrat activists think a Republican appointee would look like… except for what she looks like." You mean she looks like Condoleeza Rice? Or Colin Powell You just cannot fathom a group of people that judge leaders based on competence and policy preferences, can you? It's all race and gender and class to you. . . To Democrats, Susan Rice looks more like Christopher Warren than Condi Rice. Can you understand that?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354307980446</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:39:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354309772245-32</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Senate Pounded by John Boehner</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1354240116860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:48:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “…just a nice leisurely round of golf with the friends and then a little casino time with the wife…” – winholder Hey, out of curiosity…do all you Tea Party folks who emphatically reject the notion that your platform was essentially a “War on Women”, call their life’s partner, “The Wife”? Just curious. I wonder if any of the females that the Republicans in the House just appointed to the 19 committee chair positions, would like to be referred to as “The Wife”. Oh, wait a minute…that isn’t an issue, is it? All 19 are white males. Silly me. There are 25 Republican women in the House, but, apparently, none fit to chair a committee. So this is what you learned from the election? Certainly someone must be qualified. Somebody give Speaker Boehner a binder to sift through.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1354309772245</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:09:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354309863183-33</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet: cap gain 30%, 50% tax on the rich</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353097971771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Au Contraire? You can go on tirade after tirade about how Congress ignores the people who vote them into office all you want. But any independent observer is marveling at the change in policy this election has caused from just a year ago, and the change in policy the 2010 election caused. So when an American citizen like you goes on a tear and states: "They for some unknown reason that defies all logic think they are the only ones that can fix our fiscal problems, not being intelligent enough to realize they are the cause of the problems." And constantly deny any responsibility for the negative consequences of government policy, yet claim all credit for his share of the economic strength those policies have fostered, what at all is inappropriate about pointing out that you are completely unaware of your personal role in this political system? It's a democracy. Take some responsibility for your government, please.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354309863183</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:11:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354310115268-34</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Senate Pounded by John Boehner</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1354240116860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:48:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “…too many young, not too (politically) savvy students, ETC. - seeing the leaniant (sic) criteria to receive Govt. money, for making their lives better = the same as BUYING votes !! This would account for an easy 10 % of the Obama vote…” – jon the statistician Let’s see here. Obama got 65,138,059 votes, total. (It would have been 65,138,060, but Rob’s Prius broke down on the way to the polls, so Mrs. Fisk couldn’t cast her ballot. Of course, that cost Mitt Rob’s vote, as well, but neither were too important in the grand scheme of things, and at least it got them out of the house for awhile…and having coffee in the repair shop waiting room is a veritable soiree for the Fisks. Plus, free donuts!!! Quite a day, despite not voting!) So, ten percent of that would be 6,513,805 votes that were cast by students looking for handouts, according to Doctor jon. Jon, would you mind showing us your source for that very questionable number that, along with many other murky theories, suddenly registered in your limited grey matter? The total number of postsecondary students is about 21 million. About one fourth of eligible college students are not registered to vote. That leaves about 15.75 million REGISTERED college voters. It’s estimated that about 57% of eligible voters actually turned out in 2012, overall. That leaves under 9 million college voters. Obama got about 52% of the vote total. Fifty-two percent of nine million equals about 4.6 million college voters who voted for Obama. You contend that about 2 million more than that not only voted for Obama, but every single one of them (plus 2 million imaginary others) all did it simply for the freebies???? This proves several things about jon’s facts, figures and fantasies. One, it’s impossible for him to admit that anyone who disagrees with him does so out of thoughtful analysis or that they voted for any number of reasons besides wanting handouts (BTW, aren’t capital gains and other favorable tax rates for the one percenters, and corporate welfare and subsidies, handouts, as well? Would it be fair to say, by the same token, Mitt’s voters were also looking for handouts?)…and, two…most of jon’s incoherent ramblings here, rather than containing any factual relevancy whatsoever, are based solely on whatever strikes his fancy on any given moment. And, three, if he was any decent kind of a guy, he’d have stopped by the repair shop, had a couple jelly donuts with the Fisks, and then driven them to the polls…talk about voter suppression!!!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1354310115268</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:15:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354310246163-35</Id><Topic><Title>Buy backs to beat dividend tax?</Title><Username>stonewallneeljac</Username><Timestamp>1353452128897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 17:55:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can pee your pants all you want boy</Msg><Username>stonewallneeljac</Username><Timestamp>1354310246163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:17:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354310380093-36</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Senate Pounded by John Boehner</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1354240116860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:48:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “…too many young, not too (politically) savvy students, ETC. - seeing the leaniant (sic) criteria to receive Govt. money, for making their lives better = the same as BUYING votes !! This would account for an easy 10 % of the Obama vote…” – jon the statistician Let’s see here. Obama got 65,138,059 votes, total. (It would have been 65,138,060, but Rob’s Prius broke down on the way to the polls, so Mrs. Rob couldn’t cast her ballot. Of course, that cost Mitt Rob’s vote, as well, but neither were too important in the grand scheme of things, and at least it got them out of the house for awhile…and having coffee in the repair shop waiting room is a veritable night on the town for rob and “The Wife”. Plus, free donuts!!! Quite a day, despite not voting!) So, ten percent of that would be 6,513,805 votes that were cast by students looking for handouts, according to Doctor jon. Jon, would you mind showing us your source for that very questionable number that, along with many other murky theories, suddenly registered in your limited grey matter? The total number of postsecondary students is about 21 million. About one fourth of eligible college students are not registered to vote. That leaves about 15.75 million REGISTERED college voters. It’s estimated that about 57% of eligible voters actually turned out in 2012, overall. That leaves under 9 million college voters. Obama got about 52% of the vote total. Fifty-two percent of nine million equals about 4.6 million college voters who voted for Obama. You contend that about 2 million more than that not only voted for Obama, but every single one of them (plus 2 million imaginary others) all did it simply for the freebies???? This proves several things about jon’s facts, figures and fantasies. One, it’s impossible for him to admit that anyone who disagrees with him does so out of thoughtful analysis or that they voted for any number of reasons besides wanting handouts (BTW, aren’t capital gains and other favorable tax rates for the one percenters, and corporate welfare and subsidies, handouts, as well? Would it be fair to say, by the same token, Mitt’s voters were also looking for handouts?)…and, two…most of jon’s incoherent ramblings here, rather than containing any factual relevancy whatsoever, are based solely on whatever strikes his fancy on any given moment. And, three, if he was any decent kind of a guy, he’d have stopped by the repair shop, had a couple jelly donuts with the rob and “The Wife”, and then driven them to the polls…talk about voter suppression!!!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1354310380093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:19:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354310436813-37</Id><Topic><Title>Norquist Popular With Lib. Democrats</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1354046450537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:00:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Thus far there has been very little walking the walk" Are you kidding? Obama has been making the same concrete revenue proposals related to the Bush tax cuts for four years now. They are going to walk on January 1st no matter what. If Republicans want spending cuts to go along with that, or to close loopholes instead, they need to come up with a proposal. Go on another "I hate Congress" rant if it helps you sleep at night, but realize you've got your head in the sand.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1354310436813</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:20:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354316134086-38</Id><Title>After Hours Quotes...</Title><Msg>... “It is precisely because an ideal is necessary to man that the man without ideals is in permanent danger of fanaticism.” – G. K. Chesterton “Brain-washing starts in the cradle.” – Arthur Koestler “You may delay, but time will not.” – Benjamin Franklin “Be an opener of doors for such as come after thee.” – Ralph Waldo Emerson “The issue which has swept down the centuries and which will have to be fought sooner or later is the people versus the banks.” – Lord Acton “Get out of my way son, you're usin' my oxygen.” – R.P. McMurphy “Nature does nothing uselessly.” – Aristotle "Israel’s Iron Dome defense is intercepting 90% of Hamas' missiles. Usually to see that many interceptions you have to watch Tony Romo play." –Jay Leno “The pulpit only ‘teaches’ to be honest; the market-place ‘trains’ to over-reaching and fraud; and ‘teaching’ has not a tithe of the efficiency of ‘training’. Christ never wrote a ‘Tract’ in his life, but he went about doing good.” – Horace Mann “Not in mine eyes alone is Paradise,” - Dante “Facts and theories are different things, not rungs in a hierarchy of increasing certainty. Facts are the world's data. Theories are structures of ideas that explain and interpret facts. Facts do not go away while scientists debate rival theories for explaining them. Einstein's theory of gravitation replaced Newton's, but apples did not suspend themselves in mid-air pending the outcome.” – Stephen Jay Gould</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1354316134086</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 17:55:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354316145918-39</Id><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Msg>... “The greatest barrier to consciousness is the belief that one is already conscious.” – P.D. Ouspensky “The only perfect and genuine republic is that which comprehends every living being. Those distinctions which have been artificially set up, of nations, societies, families, and religions, are only general names, expressing the abhorrence and contempt with which men blindly consider their fellowmen” – Shelley “The ink of the scholar is more holy than the blood of the martyr.” - Muhammad “He had a face like a benediction.” – Miguel de Cervantes “Yesterday, Barack Obama looked especially good. He looked relaxed and ready to lead, so he took questions from the press for 20 minutes then finished up with a few Al Green songs.” – David Letterman “Never let your sense of morals prevent you from doing what is right.” – Isaac Asimov “Education is the great equalizer, and shouldn’t be limited to the wealthiest few.” – Congressman Jim Clyburn “To me the greatest moment in an experiment is always just before I learn whether the particular idea is a good or a bad one. Thus even a failure is exciting, and most of my ideas have of course been wrong.” – while often attributed to winholder, it was actually Noble Physicist, Ivar Giaever “I’ve said consistently that no employer ever really accepts a union. They tolerate the unions. The very minute they can get a pool of unemployment they'll challenge the unions and try to get back what they call managements prerogatives, meaning hire, fire, pay what you want.” – Jimmy Hoffa "France says the U.S. hacked its government computers. Cyberwar is new to them. France has never surrendered online before." –Jay Leno “We need a renaissance of wonder. We need to renew, in our hearts and in our souls, the deathless dream, the eternal poetry, the perennial sense that life is miracle and magic.” – E. Merrill Root “Before I go on with this short history, let me make a general observation – the test of a first-rate intelligence is the ability to hold two opposed ideas in the mind at the same time, and still retain the ability to function. One should, for example, be able to see that things are hopeless and yet be determined to make them otherwise. This philosophy fitted on to my early adult life, when I saw the improbable, the implausible, often the ‘impossible,’ come true…In a real dark night of the soul it is always three o'clock in the morning, day after day.” – F. Scott Fitzgerald “Have a good weekend, all.” – echo2165 “A man is a very small thing, and the night is very large and full of wonders!” – Lord Dunsany</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1354316145918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 17:55:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354318268054-40</Id><Topic><Title>Norquist Popular With Lib. Democrats</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1354046450537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:00:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, Obama has been making the same demands for four years. How does that equate to 'working' with people to find a common ground? Repeating the same demands over and over does not fit with any definition of 'negotiation'. Good speech, but like your fearless leader and just like your tail wagging posts, but it is meaningless bla, bla, bla. Better luck next time, but this isn't going to fly as a legitmate reason for the lack of progress. It take two to tangle and thus far all Obama and Reid have done is showboat.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1354318268054</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 18:31:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354324597524-41</Id><Topic><Title>Say it ain't so. A dem wouldn't do this.</Title><Username>coulddobetter</Username><Timestamp>1354294434866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 11:53:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know exactly what a "slimeball" is, don't you robfisk.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1354324597524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:16:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354325032716-42</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Senate Pounded by John Boehner</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1354240116860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:48:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are like babies crying for their pacifier.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1354325032716</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:23:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354325112383-43</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Senate Pounded by John Boehner</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1354240116860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:48:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We still have not survived Dubya. That will take generations.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1354325112383</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:25:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354325189190-44</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Senate Pounded by John Boehner</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1354240116860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 20:48:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The republican women belong in the kitchen and the bedroom.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1354325189190</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:26:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354329554599-45</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Get his Money</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354232624025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 18:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My relatives own a plumbing/heating concern. They just let their secretary go. They found out somehow, that she was a closet Obummer supporter. They are not alone. Now their business phone goes directly to their cells. Business had dropped off anyway. Not many folks want to spend thousands of dollars, upgrading equipment, when they are worried about their jobs. I urge all small businessmen to let these these Obama supporters be the first to feel his pain. Even the Chinese are writing editorials calling out Obama for causing a World wide economic turndown.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354329554599</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 21:39:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354331405310-46</Id><Title>No one sure how Dividend Stocks will fare</Title><Msg>It would make me laugh, as I am all in cash, if those Obummer supporters lost some coin, as the dividend tax soars to 42%, from 15%. The Chinese are really worried, they're afraid "The One", may start a Global Recession. Still don't buy it that only 16% of Senior Citizens voted. I think George Soros' voting machines should be thrown away. These election was rigged.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354331405310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:10:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354332244349-47</Id><Title>Will our Enemies Launch a Sneak Attack?</Title><Msg>December 7th, is right around the corner. We are just weeks away from the automatic defense spending cuts. I hope China doesn't try to make a move, while "The One" is destroying Military Morale. Wish I had a bunker to hide in. How many know we are spending more money on this fun loving, Presidental Couple, than the British spend of their entire Royal Family. For a poor girl, the Daughter of a bus driver I believe, Mouchelle sure does have expensive tastes.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354332244349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:24:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354332411552-48</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Get his Money</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354232624025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 18:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He'll get his money, even if it's funny money, right off the printing presses.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354332411552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:26:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354333696329-49</Id><Title>Did Anyone See the new Lincoln Movie?</Title><Msg>They were definitely trying to show comparisons between President Lincoln, and "The One", that we are burdened with today. Spielberg should be ashamed of his one sided portrayal of the ends, justifying the means. The Movie seemed to be laying the ground work, that we will likely need to keep Barry on, (for a 3rd term), that will be probably be needed, thanks to George Bush.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354333696329</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:48:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>