<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-18"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345262659000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Barry Ready to Use Oil Reserve</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345251940000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:05:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He wants to claim that HE lowered gas prices just priot to the election. He is a sleaze ball.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345262659000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:04:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345262823000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Corn Prices up 23% world wide in July</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345252755000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:19:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The blend gets you lower mileage and does not help you engine. It sucks. I rented a U-Haul a month ago for a cross-country trip and they specifically tell you and put it in writing NOT to use any Ethanol fuels. Wonder why?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345262823000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:07:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345262955000-3</Id><Topic><Title>romney will never win</Title><Username>ser3324</Username><Timestamp>1345048976000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No confusion here, all I have to do is read one of you and/or Echo's posts. That solves all the confusion.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345262955000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:09:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345263160000-4</Id><Topic><Title>SSA orders ammo why?</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1345083236000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 22:13:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again, another frivolous attack but no response to the original question. Why are these government agencies buying ammo at all, let alone copious amounts? You don't have a clue so you simply attack the poster instead of addressing the subject matter. Geeez, are you one of Obama's campaign managers? Good job; are they paying you well?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345263160000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:12:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345263300000-5</Id><Topic><Title>EPA wins "Court Battle" - We lose !</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1345238264000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 17:17:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"More frequent Auto repair costs." It's all part of his job stimulus plan. Just more 'created government' jobs. It plays well in the media though, especially when the unemployment reports are issued...just before they are revised.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345263300000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:15:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345288110000-6</Id><Title>Fun Fridays and bad news...</Title><Msg>... My, oh my, another forlorn Friday night locked away in a cubicle. Nice life! I DO see why you’re puttin’ in overtime, however – it’s called desperation. As of yesterday, according to Yahoo, voting prediction percentages for the candidates are as follows (their election model combines polling, prediction markets and historical data). Oh, wait, do you far-right folks count Yahoo among that horrible Main Stream Media that you mistrust and abhor? If you do, who do you spend so much time here? Well, here’s their analysis, and, frankly, kids, it doesn’t look good for you. So gear up, create another alias, have another jolt cola, and fire away more misspelled tales of indignation and phony patriotism. Assuming the other states go as predicted, the race will come down to these key, swing states. For Romney to win, he’ll have to win Florida, Virginia and Ohio, PLUS one other state. I’ll give you Florida. Virginia…possibly. You can do the math. Game over. But keep pluggin’ away here, day after day, alias after alias, mindless messages of hate and fear after mindless message of intolerance and obstructionism. As witnessed by your silly posts from 9 to midnight last night, you apparently have no friends, no life and no place else to go, anyhow. Unfortunately, the one percenters, whose message you are being duped into forwarding, are not in their basements on a Friday night pounding out propaganda like you are. Key Swing States Colorado Obama – 62% Romney – 38% Florida Romney – 62% Obama – 38% Iowa Obama – 55% Romney – 45% Nevada Obama – 73% Romney - 27% New Hampshire Obama – 54% Romney – 45% Ohio Obama - 54% Romney – 46% Virginia Obama – 50.5% Romney – 49.5% Wisconsin Obama - 71% Romney – 29%</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1345288110000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:08:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345288829000-7</Id><Title>does anybody on this board talk about at&amp;t?</Title><Msg>why is this board for at&amp;t only used for political attacks? does anyone care that at&amp;t's stock has not been in the green lately?</Msg><Username>downsout71</Username><Timestamp>1345288829000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345296627000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why they support traditional marriage: Rooster plus Rooster equals Goose Egg Hen plus Hen equals Goose Egg Rooster plus Hen equals Chick-Fil-A</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1345296627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:30:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345299770000-9</Id><Title>Run Forest, Run!</Title><Msg>I recently set up an ATT account for my business. What a disaster. If I had stock in this company I would dump it in a heart beat. I know some are saying "oh, this is just someone paid to write negatively about the company." Wrong! I don't have time to go into all the details. I am trying to run a business and earn a living. Take my advice. Don't do business with ATT and if you own stock - run!</Msg><Username>jme510</Username><Timestamp>1345299770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:22:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345300610000-10</Id><Title>Union is finished in cal and conn</Title><Msg>Hey "striking" union thugs. See what the rank and file approved in the midwest and at the old att? That's all you get too. Stick a fork in it, your done. Unless you clowns still want to play games over stickers. Stickers? Can't believe you forced employees to lose pay over stickers. Stickers? Hahahahahahhaahaha. That's rich. What's next, clickers? Hey, you could change your name to the stickers and clickers union? SCU? Losers.</Msg><Username>freerangeturducker</Username><Timestamp>1345300610000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:36:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345302029000-11</Id><Topic><Title>SSA orders ammo why?</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1345083236000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 22:13:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have heard that it is preparing for what might happen if the new voter id laws get American Voters in an uproar. We have a black Pesident that many want to not have a second term, and on the other hand a man with money hidden all over the World. He and his wife they do not know what they have. Many want to see Obama's birth certificate, also many want to see Romney's tax returns. The GOP is scaring people about their future. The terrorist will get us, Social Security, and Medicare will be broke in a few years. Obama's people say the other are lieing, both sides causing the pot of humanity to start to boil. They are being battered with all these negatives, that a revolution of sort may occur. I hope some of these bullets are rubber bullets. Why, because after I served a year in Vietnam, and was trained for riot control. The year was the Spring of 68, a year before that were the riots in Detroit. People were selected as sniper. Other basic riot control with loaded weapons, and fixed bayonets. The need for this never occured Thanks be to God.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1345302029000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:00:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345302578000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Corn Prices up 23% world wide in July</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345252755000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:19:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sort of like telling Coke or Budweiser that they have to put one can of inferior, offbrand product into every sixpack. You have to guess which one, but it helps some poor Obama led beverage company out.</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1345302578000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:09:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345304950000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Corn Prices up 23% world wide in July</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345252755000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:19:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be a paid poster. Definitly a person who's stocks are related to the carbon industry. Unlimited, as you know how long the Earth will have life. Continued use of these carbon sources of energy will continue the rise in cancer, and respiratory diseases. Your like the farmer who back in the day, he forked hay with a one tined fork. Then he say his neighbor with a three tine. He had the good sense to go out and buy one. We need a multiple spearheaded approach to solve the problem of a World's increasing demand on petro-chemicals. Solar, wind, chemical, tidal, and hydro-electric.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1345304950000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:49:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345305841000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Run Forest, Run!</Title><Username>jme510</Username><Timestamp>1345299770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:22:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are being paid or have too much time on your hands. What's your beef instead go generalities? We have solutions to your complaints by stating them. Allow 24 hours for responses.</Msg><Username>dm74575</Username><Timestamp>1345305841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:04:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345305966000-15</Id><Topic><Title>does anybody on this board talk about at&amp;t?</Title><Username>downsout71</Username><Timestamp>1345288829000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:20:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So why hasn't it been green? Let's hear it.</Msg><Username>dm74575</Username><Timestamp>1345305966000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:06:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345307055000-16</Id><Topic><Title>does anybody on this board talk about at&amp;t?</Title><Username>downsout71</Username><Timestamp>1345288829000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:20:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, basicly the market as a whole has been up. Statistically if it stay up in the three months prior to an election the incumbent wins. Also as a rule over many years the stock market does better with a Democratic President. Ra, ra, go AT&amp;t Forward Obama</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1345307055000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:24:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345307374000-17</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Inc. Best thing Since Sliced Bread...</Title><Username>leonardweber723</Username><Timestamp>1345294804000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:00:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually I love to make bread on the market, as well as the oven. Unsliced bread actually stays fresh longer. I love Black Forest Rye, with caraway. I am lazy though I have them slice it. Good luck, Go AT&amp;T, GO Ctl, go corn and beans. Love that Edamame.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1345307374000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:29:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345312053000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Run Forest, Run!</Title><Username>jme510</Username><Timestamp>1345299770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:22:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No solutions for ATT business customers on the weekend, as ATT's business customer service isn't open on the weekend. Further, you can't even log on to their business website for assistance. The business customer service group that isn't open on the weekend has to set you up. They are set-up for M-F, 9-5 businesses.</Msg><Username>jme510</Username><Timestamp>1345312053000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:47:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345312523000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Amazing !!!</Title><Username>alwynfri027</Username><Timestamp>1345291401000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:03:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>brilliant analysis</Msg><Username>annaliesembj310</Username><Timestamp>1345312523000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345313590000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Corn Prices up 23% world wide in July</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345252755000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:19:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From your words you sound like a angry latino. Wonder if you really are? Or a paid poster. Food Stamp program was initiated by the GOP Sen. Dole. It is a win, win. Feeding needy people, and supporting the prices of America's food producers. I believe for every Amdollar issued in stamps the US realizes 1.60. We Americans eat to much, and excercise very little. Walk, or bycyle to the grocery, etc. Let's get into shape, and we will be less depressed, and healthier than just running our jaws, pointing at the other party.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1345313590000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:13:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345313745000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Cwa D4 ratifies contract</Title><Username>rmg8080</Username><Timestamp>1345246420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:33:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SAD is what it is and pathetic...</Msg><Username>stanleybarrel</Username><Timestamp>1345313745000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:15:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345322426000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Corn Prices up 23% world wide in July</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345252755000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:19:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Minnf lier: You seem to know a lot about "paid posters". How about telling us how you signed on to be one! I could use some extra cash myself! P.S. Thanks for the great tip on pitchforks. I dumped my one tine fork for one of those "three tiners"! What a time saver!</Msg><Username>gms47cb</Username><Timestamp>1345322426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 16:40:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345323663000-23</Id><Topic><Title>does anybody on this board talk about at&amp;t?</Title><Username>downsout71</Username><Timestamp>1345288829000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:20:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When someone buys thousands of shares for between $27.73 and $28.10 per share, continues to collect dividends that annualize over 6.25%, and the stock is currently above $37.00 per share -- it seems plenty green. But, if you find a stock that only goes up, please let us all know!</Msg><Username>gms47cb</Username><Timestamp>1345323663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 17:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345326413000-24</Id><Title>WE NEED HELP</Title><Msg>Please come back jimmy carter. turns out you weren't the worst president after all...</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345326413000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 17:46:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345328399000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Union is finished in cal and conn</Title><Username>freerangeturducker</Username><Timestamp>1345300610000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>im here in connecticut and you are so right ...the unions will never win if the districts all settle without waiting on the other districts.....with cowards in district 4 midwest and in bellsouth land district 3 we will never win.....</Msg><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1345328399000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:19:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345328658000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Corn Prices up 23% world wide in July</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345252755000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:19:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barry is definitely the worst President ever. He is obviously trying to destroy this great country. In Europe now, your plane tickets have an extra surcharge, for the carbon that plane travel puts into our atmosphere. How about grounding Air Force One, and saving the planet. They say Barry is having trouble getting enough people to stand behind him at campaign events. I wonder what the average IQ is for the Obama campaign attendees?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345328658000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:24:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345328689000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Cwa D4 ratifies contract</Title><Username>rmg8080</Username><Timestamp>1345246420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:33:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it sure is here in connecticut district 1 and in california district 9 we fight on without our cowardly brothers and sisters who in the midwest district 4 and bellsouth land district 3 took the offer ...this is not a union larry cohen sold us all out again and once again seth rosen and judy dennis sold us all out ....3 years ago you cowards were the first to settle and once again you did it to us again.....just rememebr this larry cohen is part of the 1 percent he is not one of us...he makes millions of dollars a year on our union dues......for all you yes voters karma is coming your way.....</Msg><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1345328689000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:24:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345328791000-28</Id><Topic><Title>D 4 contract</Title><Username>rmg8080</Username><Timestamp>1345246267000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:31:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>COWARDS.......</Msg><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1345328791000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:26:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345329157000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Run Forest, Run!</Title><Username>jme510</Username><Timestamp>1345299770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:22:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jme. All you're griping about are the hours of operation or no access to the company web site? You are only looking to agitate for whatever your agenda may be. You had your opportunity to state your problems for assistance and resorted to rhetoric. The time for "ignore" is at hand. See ya.</Msg><Username>dm74575</Username><Timestamp>1345329157000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:32:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345329376000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Run Forest, Run!</Title><Username>jme510</Username><Timestamp>1345299770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:22:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Almost forgot. Having been a field tech for the company, it is very easy to set up a "meet" to fix whatever problems you are having. The company is always willing to schedule out of hours tech. meets to resolve whatever it is that you still haven't told us is your problem.</Msg><Username>dm74575</Username><Timestamp>1345329376000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:36:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345330081000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Barry Ready to Use Oil Reserve</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345251940000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:05:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, he might even approve a pipeline or two. He can always change his mind later. Anything Barry can take credit for, right before the election. Interestingly, Rick Edelman, said today that the stock market has done pretty well under Obama. He doesn't want to take credit for it though. Why? It runs counter to his anti 1%, anti Wall Street spiel. Rick's protege, also said after the 2008 meltdown, stocks had no way to go but up. But Rick said something that really makes sense. It might have been a slip up. He said one thing for sure however, if Barry gets a 2nd term. You can be sure, TAXES WILL BE GOING UP UNDER OBAMA! Enough said, if you are an investor, I say just say no to Barry. Anyone but. Remember, Ryan is an economist, and Mitt a businessman. Whereas Barry is trying to redistribute the investor's welth. So, say good bye to Barry. Regime change is just weeks away.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345330081000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:48:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345333264000-32</Id><Title>Our Place in Space Under Obama.</Title><Msg>There isn't one. We have to pay the Russians now to get our people into space. We are loosing our can do attitude, under Obama. We can't continue to be an innovative society, while allowing illegal immigration to turn us into a 3rd World Country. All the innovations brought to us by the space technology. GPS, weather forecasting, or the nano technology, that's driving the electronics of today, is at risk. I hope the people who worked in the space program, and their families vote this Socialist President out of office. Florida, we need you in the Republican column.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345333264000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:41:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345337296000-33</Id><Title>re - SSA orders ammo why?...</Title><Msg>... “Mmm, that our Gov't (sic) would feel the need to re-arm itself, from fear of it's (sic) own citizens “ (sic) Jon, I don’t claim to be an English Professor or anything, but I’d be willing to bet that what you’ve got going on up there, in addition to your normal spelling incompetence, is that you created the first half of a sv clause (subject-verb clause), at which point you apparently nodded off. Would you like to buy a verb? Despite your narcolepsy, I’d like to inquire as to what country you live in. Here in ours, the politicians comprising the duly elected Government ARE the citizens. None of them are perfect, but we do our best to ensure fair elections in accordance with our doctrine of one person, one vote, with the majority ruling (except for that pesky Electoral College). We then accept those results and try to work together for the benefit of all. Oh, and while it hasn’t always been this way, nowadays we encourage ALL citizens to be involved in the election process and we don’t put hurdles in the way to restrict certain blocks of voters’ ease of access to the polls. How’s it work where you live – poll taxes, literacy tests and documentation harassment, or something like armed insurrection, which you seem to be advocating and encouraging?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1345337296000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 20:48:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345341460000-34</Id><Topic><Title>stock picking strategies</Title><Username>marleeneni960</Username><Timestamp>1345300027000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:27:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting</Msg><Username>florisurb473</Username><Timestamp>1345341460000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 21:57:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345343893000-35</Id><Topic><Title>SSA orders ammo why?</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1345083236000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 22:13:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOU PEOPLE AFRAID OF WHAT MAY OCCUR? See previous post by me.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1345343893000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 22:38:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>