<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356866386360-1</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Obama Giving 17 Fighter Jets to the brotherhood?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356619460727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 09:44:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did your mother have any children that lived?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1356866386360</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 06:19:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356866753757-2</Id><Topic><Title>Could 2013 be the Last Year for Your Employer Paid Plan?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356202702130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:58:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>robfisk...jon2retard, same person.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1356866753757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 06:25:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356866934671-3</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1356577227990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 22:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More reich-wing BS.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1356866934671</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 06:28:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356880373444-4</Id><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Msg>“Democrats said they had been told House Republicans might reject a deal until after Jan. 1, to avoid a vote to raise taxes before they had technically gone up, and then vote to cut taxes after they had risen.” (AP) Oh, that’s really mature. More Grover worship. Pathetic.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356882119307-5</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm thinking when we get really serious about addressing out of control spending, we can get serious about not increasing the taxes of everyone.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1356882119307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:41:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356882660780-6</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not pathetic, just modern day politics.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1356882660780</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:51:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356883034853-7</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Latest example: Huffpost (12/28/2012): "Obama Orders Pay Raise For Congress, Federal Workers, Joe Biden While Obama's order made no mention of merit for such a raise, HuffPost's Amanda Terkel reported on Friday that the 112th Congress is set to end the session as the most unproductive since the 1940s, with only 219 bills passed by the body becoming law". Yes, it is true their pay has been frozen for a number of years but that hasn't stopped out of control federal spending. In fact, I'm thinking they are getting the raise in recognition of record spending and a record high deficit level. WASHINGTON CALLING, SEND MORE MONEY</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1356883034853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:57:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356883107097-8</Id><Topic><Title>FACT::House Speaker Ranks Higher than Senate Speaker</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1356786562504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 08:09:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And how many ideas have been presented by the right that the President simply called unacceptable and moved on, no negotiations, no counter offers, just more of I want what I want and I want it right now from the 'me' generation President.</Msg><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1356883107097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:58:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356883548157-9</Id><Topic><Title>Wiretapping</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1356789755503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 09:02:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The media is reporting that the law allows the government to do this wiretapping only of 'foreign citizens'. What is a 'foreign citizen'? If you are a citizen, you're technically not a foreigner, you're a citizen! If you're a citizen, how does the government know you are of foreign origin? Wasn’t this something the Democrats and Obama screamed about being wrong while Bush was President? When did it suddenly become the correct thing to do?</Msg><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1356883548157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:05:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356883891229-10</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congressional pay, at least for the elected officials is regulated by law, not Presidential decree. Congress in their infinite wisdom voted themselves automatic pay increases unless they vote not to accept them. The President has no control over the pay of Congressional pay for elected members. The Federal union employees may be getting raise, while most of the people paying their salaries aren't, if they have are lucky enough to have a job in this #$% house economy. Perhaps the MSM has it wrong yet again, or perhaps the Presidents alligator mouth has overrun his humming bird butt yet again. It is so hard to tell these day.</Msg><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1356883891229</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:11:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356885577094-11</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may be right normally, but according to the report he used his executive order privilege. The order includes members of Congress and federal workers.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1356885577094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:39:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356886877471-12</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From The Foundation of Human Understanding. “Revolutionaries in government have created economic chaos, shortages in food and fuel, confiscatory taxation, a crisis in education, the threat of war, and other diversions to condition Americans for the “New World Order." The technique is as old as politics itself. It is the Hegelian Dialectic of bringing about change in a three-step process: Thesis, Antithesis and Synthesis. The first step (thesis) is to create a problem. The second step (antithesis) is to generate opposition to the problem (fear, panic and hysteria). The third step (synthesis) is to offer the solution to the problem created by step one: A change which would have been impossible to impose upon the people without the proper psychological conditioning achieved in stages one and two. Applying the Hegelian Dialectic, and irresistible financial influence, concealed change agents seek to dismantle social and political structures by which free men govern themselves — ancient landmarks erected at great cost in blood and treasure. Their objective is to emasculate sovereign states, merge nations under universal government, centralize economic powers, and control the world's people and resources.” This is precisely the method being used by Obama and his ‘crisis management’ type governing. Too many things have occurred during his term that had ‘to be resolved immediately’, including problems that Congress or others created decades ago and during the preceding recent months. This is what Obama has done with the ‘fiscal cliff’ situation. This could have been resolved logically and rationally months ago. Instead, he and at this direction, the Democrats have forced this into a ‘crisis’ situation so that the Hegelian principles could be used to find a solution. This is becoming his standard method of governing, create a crisis, build the crisis to even larger proportions, and then force his solution upon the self-created problem.</Msg><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1356886877471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 12:01:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356890812429-13</Id><Topic><Title>Could 2013 be the Last Year for Your Employer Paid Plan?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356202702130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:58:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bet the CEO gets a huge bonus!</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1356890812429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 13:06:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356891291234-14</Id><Title>Finally, Americans are going to get some "skin in the game"</Title><Msg>Back in January of 2009, while appearing on ABC's "This Week" show, our president elect said: "...for a long term economic fix, all Americans will have to sacrifice. Everybody is going to have to give. Everybody is going to have to have some skin in the game," Regardless of what happens with the "fiscal cliff", on January 1, 2013 all Americans are going to get their chance to have more skin in the game with 5 new Obamacare taxes: o Medical device tax o Flex account tax o Surtax on investment income o A new limit on medical itemized deductions o Medicair payroll tax hike These taxes should provide a net $1 trillion of new tax money for the years 2013 thru 2022. If we add in the taxes involved with the "fiscal cliff" it looks like more Americans are going to get their chance "to have some skin in the game" Thank you Mr. President for making all of this possible. "In your heart you know he is right" The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356891291234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 13:14:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356899163777-15</Id><Title>Health Insurance</Title><Msg>No need to have or worry about insurance. I drive by the hospital daily and have never seen a body laying out on the lawn yet!</Msg><Username>northbadger</Username><Timestamp>1356899163777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 15:26:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356903610859-16</Id><Title>Dear Progressives</Title><Msg>You're just Communist SOBs in sheeps clothing! Progressivism,Communism it's all the same sht! Betrayers and Benidict Arnolds all of you. And now you and your kind have infiltrated the highest offices in the land. Washington's Progressive Policies will not sustain itself and the whole thing will eventually come crashing down in front of us because of your misguided beliefs about wealth redistribution. Your totalitarian vision of a future America will be clouded in corruption and eventual collapse of the state. Your ignorance will bring an end to the greatest nation the world has ever seen or will ever see again in human history. You are the BETRAYERS and history will never look at you as anything else but that!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1356903610859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 16:40:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356905483768-17</Id><Topic><Title>Dear Progressives</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1356903610859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 16:40:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does your platitudes mean?? Say what you mean and stop preaching drival.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1356905483768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 17:11:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356908873927-18</Id><Topic><Title>Could 2013 be the Last Year for Your Employer Paid Plan?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356202702130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:58:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the USA Today, they are scrubbing the term Obamacare. They prefer to call it ACA (The Affordable Care Act). And like so many things is Washington, the name means exactly the opposite. We can't possibly afford this. The article from 12/28, of USA Today, warns that employers who still provide health care, may give a fixed dollar amount. It's called a premium reimbursement. YOU CAN USE THAT MONEY AT THE STATE EXCHANGE. Problem is, many states refuse to set up exchanges. A big catch 22. Many dems up for election, are now introducing bills to delay Obamacare. Or dramatically reduce it. Call your elected officials today. Maybe we can roll this back.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356908873927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 18:07:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356910219550-19</Id><Topic><Title>Might be time for a moment of prayer for the good people of Chicago</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356789009225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 08:50:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More proof of MSM's selection process in reporting tragedy. On Sunday December 17, 2012, 2 days after the CT shooting, a man went to a restaurant in San Antonio to kill his X-girlfriend. After he shot her, most of the people in the restaurant fled next door to a theater. The gunman followed them and entered the theater so he could shoot more people. He started shooting and people in the theater started running and screaming. It’s like the Aurora, CO theater story plus a restaurant! Now aren’t you wondering why this isn’t a lead story in the national media along with the school shooting? There was an off duty county deputy at the theater. SHE pulled out her gun and shot the man 4 times before he had a chance to kill anyone. So since this story makes the point that the best thing to stop a bad person with a gun is a good person with a gun, the media is treating it like it never happened. Only the local media covered it. The city is giving her a medal next week. Just thought you’d like to know.</Msg><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1356910219550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 18:30:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356911029658-20</Id><Title>Get on with it.</Title><Msg>The Republicans have made a reasonable offer, but Harry say's the Democrats are not in a position to make a counter offer. What the &amp;^%^ does that even mean? Has he not been paying attention? Has he not been in the meetings? Does he not understand the problem? There is a simple, non-political solution to protect all the middle class taxpayers that both sides say they are dearly concerned about...pass a bill tonight that extends the Bush tax rates and then work on the rest of the issues. Leave the top rate taxes as they are, leave spending as it is and then negotiate those items without any lame duck members of Congress being involved. Protect the people, that is the major function of the government from top to bottom. Get over yourselves and do something useful, do something about the points they both agree upon and set a program in place to address the other issues. Forget the political game for leverage and protect the American taxpayers from your own stupidity. This isn't rocket science and that is a good thing, because the IQ's of the folks claiming to lead this country isn't high enough for simple math, let alone rocket science. All this I won and I am going to win #$%$ needs to be sent to the corner with a dunce cap. These guys are like kids at recess!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1356911029658</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 18:43:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356914830936-21</Id><Topic><Title>Dear Progressives</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1356903610859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 16:40:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What war? ...on what you've voted for? Do either of you have enough sense to write clearly what you are talking about?</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1356914830936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 19:47:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356926494028-22</Id><Topic><Title>Betcha Barry Will settle Dockworkers Strike.</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356653762613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 19:16:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's been put off until sometime in February or March. Of course Barry told them to stand down.</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1356926494028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 23:01:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>