<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351569729360-1</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Scripture speaks of a depracatory prayer for those being much reprooved that don't change their ways. You pray that the Devil takes them. Think about it. It also says that if you bless those that hate your God you are a partaker with them in their evil deeds.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351569729360</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:02:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351573652340-2</Id><Topic><Title>About Retiree Benefits</Title><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1351472730322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 21:05:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi Bob.......yes, it seems most people do have to apply for A and B. A has no costs (hospitalization) and B is for physicians, tests, etc. In my research, it seems the federal retirees can only apply for A and not B, and use their federal insurance as the primary. It seemed that way though I didn't spend much time since it didn't seem to pertain to me. It's B that costs so much money. I'm not sure how the railroad retirement or teacher's retirement systems work, exactly. I know they are very different. I do know that everyone is not the same. Quite frankly, I'm worn out just trying to figure this all out. I don't feel there was enough information available to us to work through this, but maybe I just didn't know where to look.</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1351573652340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 01:07:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351608563121-3</Id><Topic><Title>I have to laugh</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564720588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Laugh away you loony old crackpot! You were ignorant and foolish enough to post these personal things about yourself in the first place. You've got your neofacist, racist, antisemitic views spread all over the internet with your name and street address loonily attached to them ("My Life" probably wasn't the smartest thing you've signed up for). Then you lie, lie, lie about all of your exploits against "communists". The best whopper was the one about beating up Harry Bridges and his boys...the year you were born! Nobody is threatening you, you lying coward ("runner"...that makes ME laugh). Maybe you should be spending more time helping your ill wife (whose illness YOU posted about) instead of spinning your go nowhere conspiracy theories, fantasizing about your "Big Brother" in heaven punishing everyone who calls you out for the the lying, pansy tool you are, and posting to the T Board and "Jew Watch" - the latter, now there's a quality site.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351608563121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:49:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351615014311-4</Id><Topic><Title>I have to laugh</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564720588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting about "Jew Watch". It's operated by a "Jew". Seems as though you've spent a lot of time researching me. I have a very good friend that works for a large software company. Perhaps I should have him do a little tracing of you. You have it wrong about the "year I was born" and Harry Bridges. My good friend from the 101st Airborne and a handful of others did a number on Bridges boys in 1967. Took ones picket stick with it's commie slogan and rammed the broken end into his belly and left him in the street. They paraded with bailing hooks. I was in on the "punch In" in L.A. in 1967. It was really fun. Interesting too is that most of the rank and file cops were with us too. Yes, "Runner". I've been a fair runner most of my life and run every distance from one mile to one hundred miles. I've done triathlons and even boxed some. I worked with amateur boxing for a number of years. Could still get in the ring in my late forties and hold my own with some pretty good boxers. James Foreman was kinda my favorite, getting back in the ring at 50. He also flew the American flag in the Mexico City Olympics while the dips gave the commie salute. The clinched fist raised to heaven.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351615014311</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:36:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351618866692-5</Id><Topic><Title>T could burst tomorrow! This is how come.</Title><Username>robertportillo90</Username><Timestamp>1351602368302</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:06:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've known these guys. Extremely legitimate with their writeups. I'm going to now subscribe.</Msg><Username>abdocharles445</Username><Timestamp>1351618866692</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351620305708-6</Id><Topic><Title>T could burst tomorrow! This is how come.</Title><Username>robertportillo90</Username><Timestamp>1351602368302</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:06:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>markets will decide where each stock will go</Msg><Username>garyfritch489</Username><Timestamp>1351620305708</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:05:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351620830943-7</Id><Topic><Title>Echo/ "yourenohelp" ABSOLUTE DISGUST !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1351614901051</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:35:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's spelled "banter" you fat fool.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351620830943</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:13:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351621145045-8</Id><Topic><Title>I have to laugh</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564720588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh no, LARDQUAKE! I can see your chins flapping in umbrage. Fight the good fight fatboy!</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351621145045</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:19:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351623043435-9</Id><Topic><Title>I have to laugh,</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564514347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:35:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Johnny Lardcakes and the neo-facist in bed together. Isn't that lovely? Jonny, I know you're desperate but you need to pay a bit more attention to who you decide to make butt babies with.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351623043435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351623343510-10</Id><Topic><Title>I have to laugh</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564720588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “James Foreman was kinda my favorite…” Wow, you’re very knowledgeable. James Foreman, huh? Any relation to George? You’ve obviously taken a few too many punches over the years. Nice to see that you’re bragging about a group of ignorant vigilante hill-billies stabbing a demonstrator and leaving him to die in the streets. How brave – you should be very proud. Now, there’s some real patriotism for ya’. Another chicken-hawk tough guy living his meager existence vicariously through the anonymous wonders of psyberspace. James Foreman…nice. How many of these other famous boxers did you like?: Ricky Marciano Jake “Raging Hormones” Lamotta Oscar de la Meyer Jack Dorsey Ponce de Leon Spinks Rubin “Sandwich” Carter Ray “You Boom-Boom #1, Mama-san?” Mancini Max Schlemiel Hector “Nacho” Camacho Roberto “Una mas, por favor” Duran Sugar Ray Charles Gene Tierney Salt Ray Leonard “Delaware” Joe Walcott Buzzard Charles “Marvelous” Marvin Hamlisch Thomas “Doorman” Hearns James “Cluster” Douglas Floyd “The Barber” Mayberry, Jr. Manny “Mario Brothers” Pacquaio jonretard L. Sullivan U. R. Anidyit</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351623343510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:55:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351623676243-11</Id><Topic><Title>I have to laugh</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564720588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oscar de la Meyer besides being an excellent boxer also invented the Oscar de la Meyer "beiner"!</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1351623676243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:01:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351623885904-12</Id><Topic><Title>I have to laugh</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564720588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Love it! Sorry that Johnny Lardcakes obsession with us being the same drew you into my being taken to the woodshed by the fine, upstanding moral guardian of the T board!</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351623885904</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:04:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351624841888-13</Id><Topic><Title>I have to laugh,</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564514347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:35:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fat fool.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351624841888</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:20:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351625115237-14</Id><Topic><Title>I have to laugh,</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564514347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:35:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's spelled "illegitimate" you illiterate fat fool.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351625115237</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:25:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351625211154-15</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you VOTE "skin color" over qualifications - For A Reason !! @@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@ One of the best lines heard lately was from Izzy Kapp, a now retired shop foreman from the old Republic Steel Plant in Cleveland. At 17 Izzy immigrated to the USA from England after his family escaped from Poland when he was 12. A more proud American can not be imagined. He often said, "I am overwhelmed by the opportunities my county offers me!" All five of his children graduated from college. One got an MS, another got a JD, and the third an MD degree. It took Izzy 13 years of night school to get a college degree. When a young Black kid was being laid off at the end of his 90 day evaluation period he confronted Izzy in the huge Republic Steel Plant break room at lunch and tried to intimidate him with all sorts of NAACP / ACLU / Etc threats. "I want this on-the-record in front of everybody." the young man said. "You' firin' me 'cause I'm Black!" Without even looking up from his sandwich the foreman said, "No. We hired you because you're Black. We're firing you because you're useless." 'Great slogan for the 2012 election: They Voted You In Because You're Black. We're Voting You Out Because You're Useless.</Msg><Username>happygambler34</Username><Timestamp>1351625211154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:26:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351626646266-16</Id><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Msg>What Romney believes! 1 Reducing taxes and regulations will create jobs. This was the policy under Bush that took our country from a budget surplus to a budget deficit and failed to sustain a vital growing economy. 2. Only those individuals currently covered by medical insurance should be covered for pre-existing conditions. 3. Competition between the insurance companies will reduce medical costs. Isn’t this what we have today for everyone under the age of 65? Have you premiums gone up and health care improved? 4. The current Social Security system should be changed to allow individuals to invest their retirement funds in the stock market in hopes of getting a higher return. How much money would you have lost if you had sold the stocks in your retirement fund at the bottom of the recession? 5.You believe that higher income earners (those in the top 10%) should pay taxes at lower rate than Warren Buffet’s secretary or the average wage earner. 6. Taxes and regulations, not the lack of demand, were the major cause of the recession. 7. That the banking and financial industry does not need to be regulated. What do you think caused the housing industry to collapse and the banks to need financial aid from the government to survive? 8. Women should be paid less than men for the same job. 9. That the United States should increase its military spending even though the U.S. already spends more on defense than the next 13 countries with the highest defense budgets. 10 That companies are people and should be allowed to make unlimited political contributions without disclosure. It is your vote. This former Republican is voting for Obama</Msg><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>20</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351626760245-17</Id><Topic><Title>I have to laugh</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564720588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I ran into Leon Spinks in a St. Louis bar some 20 years ago. The poor guy was penniless, living in a downtown flop house and signing autographs for drinks. Very sad because he was a good kid.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1351626760245</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:52:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351628963340-18</Id><Title>Why I can't vote for "O"</Title><Msg>From The Washington Times web site: New Obama slogan has long ties to Marxism, socialism The Obama campaign apparently didn't look backwards into history when selecting its new campaign slogan, "Forward" — a word with a long and rich association with European Marxism. Many Communist and radical publications and entities throughout the 19th and 20th centuries had the name "Forward!" or its foreign cognates. Wikipedia has an entire section called "Forward (generic name of socialist publications)." "The name Forward carries a special meaning in socialist political terminology. It has been frequently used as a name for socialist, communist and other left-wing newspapers and publications," the online encyclopedia explains. The slogan "Forward!" reflected the conviction of European Marxists and radicals that their movements reflected the march of history, which would move forward past capitalism and into socialism and communism. The Obama campaign released its new campaign slogan Monday in a 7-minute video. The title card has simply the word "Forward" with the "O" having the familiar Obama logo from 2008. It will be played at rallies this weekend that mark the Obama re-election campaign's official beginning. There have been at least two radical-left publications named "Vorwaerts" (the German word for "Forward"). One was the daily newspaper of the Social Democratic Party of Germany whose writers included Friedrich Engels and Leon Trotsky. It still publishes as the organ of Germany's SDP, though that party has changed considerably since World War II. Another was the 1844 biweekly reader of the Communist League. Karl Marx, Engels and Mikhail Bakunin are among the names associated with that publication. East Germany named its Army soccer club ASK Vorwaerts Berlin (later FC Vorwaerts Frankfort). Vladimir Lenin founded the publication "Vpered" (the Russian word for "forward") in 1905. Soviet propaganda film-maker Dziga Vertov made a documentary whose title is sometimes translated as "Forward, Soviet" (though also and more literally as "Stride, Soviet"). Conservative critics of the Obama administration have noted numerous ties to radicalism and socialists throughout Mr. Obama's history, from his first political campaign being launched from the living room of two former Weather Underground members, to appointing as green jobs czar Van Jones, a self-described communist.</Msg><Username>bullbear308</Username><Timestamp>1351628963340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351629344007-19</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good summary, there're a lot more but that's enough. Same here almost always voted republican, never again not now not this time especially. We have a good man in there, romney is dishonest, acts like a used car salesman with shoe polished hair. Santorum was right, romney is the worst one they could pick to run. Besides all that, it looks like romeny is mentally unable. Vote American values and for a great American, President Obama.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351629344007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:35:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351630254140-20</Id><Topic><Title>I have to laugh</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564720588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Other people's abilities of logic." Good lord, what an illiterate nightmare of a clause that is.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351630254140</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:50:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351630496635-21</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem is that a lot of what you wrote as Romney beliefs is not factual. They are the talking points of the Democratic Party. You need to find out a bit more about what you’re told than to just buy into it. It is people like you that are voting when you don't truly comprehend what you're voting for or against that puts idiots in office and keeps them there. You need to stop listening only to the sound bites in the campaign ads and do a little research and reading.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1351630496635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:54:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351630754173-22</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for "O"</Title><Username>bullbear308</Username><Timestamp>1351628963340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are many good reasons NOT to vote for Obama. Use of the work forward is a weak reason. If that is the best you have, then vote for him. Those voting against Obama for reasons they think they have learned from the MSM are as bad as those voting for and against Romney for those same simpleton reasons. If you’re voting for or against a candidate for one single reason…shame on you.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1351630754173</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:59:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351630870951-23</Id><Topic><Title>I have to laugh</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564720588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “…you under estimate (sic) other peoples abilities of logic” – jon at recess Believe me, jon, thanks to the voluminous nature of your repetitive error-filled posts, absolutely, positively, NO ONE here underestimates YOUR abilities of logic (one word, bonehead, but if you add a bunch of quotation marks, question marks and parenthesis you’ll feel better about it…something like this: ((??...”under” ? !(tee-hee) “es’ (smiles) ti - - -“mate!!”?????? (giggles, chuckle, guffaw, ) I really didn’t think it was possible, but your posts have become nothing but sophomoric, scatological, error-laced, playground trash-talking as though you were in elementary school…although many suspect you didn’t get that far. It would appear that your fixation on totally unsophisticated bathroom humor probably stems back to your lifelong addiction to whoopee cushions as your only source of originality. Well, that and the fake plastic dog turds. I suppose, having been being kicked out of Sunday school for saying to Sister Esther “pull my finger” has affected you, as well. Then again, terminal flatulence in those dingy cubicles where you work probably adds to you unpopularity. Anyhow, your posts have become (well, they always were, actually) totally irrelevant, and, simply belittling defenseless and ignorant people like you really offers no challenge. But speaking of challenges...regarding your repeated attempts at the deflection of who has multiple-aliases…you know the offer…you, win, dale, et. al… Put up or shut up. What a shallow, lightweight you are.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351630870951</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:01:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351631015799-24</Id><Topic><Title>I have to laugh</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564720588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“…you under estimate (sic) other peoples abilities of logic” – jon at recess Believe me, jon, thanks to the voluminous nature of your repetitive error-filled posts, absolutely, positively, NO ONE here underestimates YOUR abilities of logic (one word, bonehead, but if you add a bunch of quotation marks, question marks and parenthesis you’ll feel better about it…something like this: ((??...”under” ? !(tee-hee) “es’ (smiles) ti - - -“mate!!”?????? (giggles, chuckle, guffaw, ) I really didn’t think it was possible, but your posts have become nothing but sophomoric, scatological, error-laced, playground trash-talking as though you were in elementary school…although many suspect you didn’t get that far. It would appear that your fixation on totally unsophisticated bathroom humor probably stems back to your lifelong addiction to whoopee cushions as your only source of originality. Well, that and the fake plastic dog t#rds. I suppose, having been being kicked out of Sunday school for saying to Sister Esther “pull my finger” has affected you, as well. Then again, terminal flatulence in those dingy cubicles where you work probably adds to you unpopularity. Anyhow, your posts have become (well, they always were, actually) totally irrelevant, and, simply belittling defenseless and ignorant people like you really offers no challenge. But speaking of challenges...regarding your repeated attempts at the deflection of who has multiple-aliases…you know the offer…you, win, dale, et. al… Put up or shut up. What a shallow, lightweight you are.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351631015799</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:03:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351631139057-25</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is still a cover up ongoing. They still haven't told the truth about what happened, what they knew about what and when it was happening and why they didn't send help. If you believe otherwise, you need mental help. Either that are you are simply not paying attention to the world around you.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1351631139057</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:05:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351631187286-26</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good points. Notice Republicans rebutals resort to name calling and little or no substance. Still, I'm holding my nose while voting for Obama. We needed a sea change and he's caked in to the conservatives. Medical insurance companies wrote Obamacare except for pre-existing conditions. He's increased drone attacks. Done nothing to stem gun violence.</Msg><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1351631187286</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351631670260-27</Id><Title>The Canned Food Is On It's Way, New Jersey</Title><Msg>What a laugh. Romney is collecting canned food and he isn't sure where it's going, but he thinks it's New Jersey. Better check because geography is one of Romney strong suites. When he went to Israel a few weeks ago to look presidential he said Jerusalem was the capitol of Israel. Anyway, they need power before they can cook the stuff and transportation up and running more than a food drive. Romney, a president needs to be a leader, not a volunteer.</Msg><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1351631670260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:14:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351632977178-28</Id><Topic><Title>The Canned Food Is On It's Way, New Jersey</Title><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1351631670260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:14:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not if Christie gets to it first. I must give credit to Christie for PRAISING OBAMA'S GOOD WORK today, it was great.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351632977178</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:36:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351633431217-29</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually you need mental help. It is all your own little idea, there is an investigation going on now, not a cover up. That's how it works. The judge doesn't decide before the evidence. The camera is still on Romney and his big mistake at the debate, this faux news story is just a cover up to hide Romney's blunder. That's what's called a cover up.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351633431217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351638000079-30</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you list or take exception to the points that I stated?</Msg><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351638000079</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:00:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351638957297-31</Id><Title>Philadelphia Freedom</Title><Msg>Pennsylvania is trending for Romney. On Rush's show today, he said the Republicans are sending money into Philadelphia. Here in the People's Republic of Maryland, many working people plan to retire in Pa. Please consider contacting our friends to the north, we need you. Man phone banks. MARYLAND IS SAID TO BE LOST, BUT DON'T BELIEVE IT. WE CAN STOP DUTCH RUPPERSBERGER, &amp; O'MALLEY'S 7 QUESTIONS. Vote against everyone. Yes, we can. Don't forget what Eric Holder, and Obama did to the elderly people in Philadelphia. Allowing black panthers, with bats to intimidate voters, and not prosecuting, despite the video proof, is just plain wrong. THIS IS AMERICA, DON'T LET A CHICAGO MOBSTER STEAL THIS ELECTION!!! Regime change is just days away.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351638957297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351639357428-32</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you go to a left wing site, copy and paste talking points, and post them here. Why debate them when everyone knows that you and your left wing buddies won't consider the facts? That's nothing but a waste of time. What's even worse is that you clowns fail to realize that no one even takes you seriously.</Msg><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1351639357428</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:22:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351639429508-33</Id><Title>Mayor Doomberg should Step Down</Title><Msg>The stock market closed for several days, electrical substations flooded. Fires destroying entire neighborhoods. Subways closed. And this guy is running around the Country (most recently here in Maryland), telling how to vote on Gay Marriage?? Passing laws on how big my soft drink should be??. This guy is definitely a DEMOCRAP. We need Guliani back, asap!!</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351639429508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:23:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351639775313-34</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Doomberg should Step Down</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351639429508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I forgot Hospitals evacuated. This should be a wake up call. This guy, like Obama, just isn't up to the job. Clint, get your chair. If a guy can't do a job, he has to go.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351639775313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:29:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351640206621-35</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One point of your story I take issue with. I calculated what I would have had in SS had I just invested all of what I and my employer paid in since I started working up to when I retired at age 65 in 1998. By simply putting it in the DOW which has averaged a 8% return over the years I would have had $250,000 in the account. Using actuarial tables for a 65 year old man at that time you find that even with health insureance I would be drawing more that way than with the gummint taking care of me. I havn't voted for a major party candidate in years as they are all in bed with the thieves that run things. Demon Rat LBJ stole money from SS to finance his illegal war in 'Nam. Others have done the same since. People that support them are one of two things, a gullible fool or a paid shill that profits from the thieving.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351640206621</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:36:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351640508087-36</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for "O"</Title><Username>bullbear308</Username><Timestamp>1351628963340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's the biggest liar we've ever had in National office. He watched in real time, via a drone, those brave Seals fighting to the bloody end. They perished in a mortar attack, the machine gun they manned, caked in their own blood. How anyone who ever wore the uniform can vote for this guy, is beyond me. They defied orders to stand down, and saved 30 Americans, from this well planned, 911 Anniversary attack.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351640508087</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:41:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351640831771-37</Id><Topic><Title>The Canned Food Is On It's Way, New Jersey</Title><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1351631670260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:14:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Hopefully .. you'll also be too lazy to "vote" !!" I already voted. I must give credit to Christie for PRAISING OBAMA'S GOOD WORK today, it was great. Live on TV, there's no denying it, no denying, it's great. Worse he chastised romeny for wanting to make a photo op out of new jersey and Christie let romney's camp have it on that side to. It's so great.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351640831771</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:47:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351641072966-38</Id><Title>Big Bird, Binders, &amp;Bu!!</Title><Msg>Is the media ever going to get to any serious subjects in this campaign? Why is the Dead Seals Dad, Mr. Woods invisible? His son Tyrone, and his fellow Patriots, saved 30 Americans, by refusing orders to stand down. The media couldn't get enough time with Cindy Sheehan. Mr. Woods has a real story to tell. He will not be silenced.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351641072966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:51:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351641391321-39</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for "O"</Title><Username>bullbear308</Username><Timestamp>1351628963340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In this case forward means what it says, moving us up and out of this recession. That's all, great slogan. I suppose when you can connect unrelated dots in your mind anything is possible. My lawn mower has a forward setting on it, I suppose my lawn mower is commie to those unrelated dots connecting minds.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351641391321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:56:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351641727210-40</Id><Topic><Title>Why did they Take away the Plane?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351047019924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:50:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More facts are starting to leak out. Barry watched the entire attack on drone video. These seals refused to stand down. By disobeying orders, they saved 30 Americans by preventing their certain slaughter, from a well trained 911 Anniversary attack force. Their machine gun was reported to be caked in their blood. This makes Watergate look like child's play. This is the biggest coverup in American history, and the Dem infused media, could care less. But, we won't forget these real heroes at the ballot box.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351641727210</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:02:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351642025469-41</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can agree with your point regarding Social Security. However, as I'm sure you are aware for each buyer there is also a seller. So while you might have made money in the market someone else was a loser. Unfortunately a lot of individuals as well as fund managers sell towards the bottom of a correction and fail to buy back into in a timely manner. These individuals are the ones that benefit most from Social Security.</Msg><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351642025469</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:07:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351642378543-42</Id><Topic><Title>Philadelphia Freedom</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351638957297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a silly old fool.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1351642378543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:12:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351642606571-43</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you so dumb that you think the stock market is a zero sum game?</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1351642606571</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:16:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351642745918-44</Id><Topic><Title>Philadelphia Freedom</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351638957297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Grey Panthers, (the old folks), will counter your black panthers (thugs), this time at the polls.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351642745918</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:19:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351644405039-45</Id><Title>Teachers Should Go For Mitt</Title><Msg>Mitt has promised to dramatically cut the Fed Education Department. The savings is supposed to be plowed into Teacher's salaries. We don't need layer, upon layer, of fat cat bureaucrats, sucking up money that those who do the real work need. See the article on Dick Morris' website.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351644405039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351645565401-46</Id><Topic><Title>Philadelphia Freedom</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351638957297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I use that phrase, (courtesy of WCBM's Tom Marr. His 9am morning talk show has listeners world wide. He frequently sits in for Mark Levine. This state is so liberal, with all the freebies, we attract legions of illegals. This is addition to all the Fed, &amp; State employees, we constantly re-elect leaders that are clearly socialists and communists.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351645565401</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:06:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351647228199-47</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot Mitt's latest lie about Jeep sending jobs to China!</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1351647228199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351647507016-48</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To list all that nonsense tells me you were NEVER a republican. Nice try.</Msg><Username>dave_martin_2244</Username><Timestamp>1351647507016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>