<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-15"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347687050185-1</Id><Title>U S credit rating cut to AA-</Title><Msg>Egan-Jones Cuts U.S. Rating to AA- After Fed Adds to Stimulus By John Detrixhe - Sep 14, 2012 2:55 PM CT Egan-Jones Ratings Co. cut its credit rating for the U.S. one level to AA-, citing the potential for the Federal Reserve’s third round of large-scale asset purchases to weaken the dollar and drive up inflation. U.S. debt to gross-domestic-product has risen to 104 percent from 66 percent in 2006, Egan-Jones said today in a report. The firm lowered the U.S. to AA in April. Yields on 10- year Treasuries have fallen five basis points since the end of that month to 1.86 percent. The Fed’s latest program will “stoke the stock market and commodity prices, but in our opinion will hurt the U.S. economy and, by extension, credit quality,” Egan-Jones said. “The increased cost of commodities will pressure profitability of businesses, and increase the costs of consumers, thereby reducing consumer purchasing power.” The Fed yesterday announced its third round of large-scale asset purchases since 2008, saying it will buy $40 billion of mortgage debt a month. The central bank didn’t set any limit on the ultimate amount it would buy or the duration of the program. Policy makers also extended the prospect of near-zero interest rates until mid-2015 and said policy will stay accommodative “for a considerable time” even after the economy strengthens. . .</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1347687050185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 01:30:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347688968777-2</Id><Topic><Title>What's fueling the GOP decline?...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347546435275</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:27:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My facts are straight. I do not need a reference when I have personal knowledge. You are far left, I am center right and love my country. My impression is that you hate this country and very much like Obama and what he stands for, including his communist/socialist worldview, which you seem to have.That is my opinion. You are about to go the way of Obama and all the destruction he has brought into this country. The GOP in decline? Hardly. Obama refuses to release his records, but people were around him and they talk. All will come out eventually. Who are you to say it"s not so? You apparently know little about Obama. Do not assume I am as unknowing as you...and assuming is what you're doing. Do not tell lies about me, I've been on this board much longer than you and my reputation is not for telling "whoppers".</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1347688968777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 02:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347690943554-3</Id><Topic><Title>Why isn't Barry attending the Daily Whitehouse Briefings?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347587447741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama wants out. It's the democratic party who wants him in. He's doing everything he can to make himself un-electable.</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1347690943554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 02:35:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347693253529-4</Id><Topic><Title>What's fueling the GOP decline?...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347546435275</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:27:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok, I'll bite.......what are you talking about? Unless you're a breeder, why are bloodlines so important to you? We are not in the United Kingdom where bloodlines matter for leadership. The fight for America specifically stopped that sort of thing. However, if you're concerned with Ronald Reagan's bloodline, how can you be so sure Michael Reagan is not the blood of Ronald Reagan? I don't believe his so called birth father's name has EVER been released or his so called birth mother's name has EVER been released. I still don't know what your point is and what it's relevance is to anything.</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1347693253529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 03:14:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347709828218-5</Id><Topic><Title>U S credit rating cut to AA-</Title><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1347687050185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 01:30:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Egan-Jones Cuts U.S. Rating to AA- After Fed Adds to Stimulus” Oh, I see you’d like Wall Street to run the country, without any of those pesky regulations getting in the way. Ah, yes, an unfettered, Laissez-faire environment for Mitt’s vision of the Oligarchy of the ruling class. There’s one problem with that - Greed tends to bend the rules. But, then again, that’s what you want. No rules. Charges Pending Against Egan Jones “The SEC warned Egan-Jones in October 2011 of a possible enforcement action. On April 24, 2012, the SEC charged Sean Egan with numerous offenses including: making false and misleading statements in the firm's application to become a Nationally Recognized Rating Agency, violations of conflicts-of-interest and record keeping, and falsely stating that he was unaware if his paid clients were long or short specific securities that Egan-Jones rated. The Securities and Exchange Commission issued charges against the company, and its founder Sean Egan for ‘material misrepresentations and omissions in the company’s July 2008 application to register as a Nationally Recognized Statistical Rating Organization (NRSRO) for issuers of asset-backed securities (ABS) and government securities’ as well as ‘material misrepresentations in other submissions furnished to the SEC and violations of record-keeping and conflict-of-interest provisions governing NRSROs’.” – Wikipedia “...the firm’s lawyer has denied the allegations stating that ‘it’s clear the SEC has a bias against independent firms’...” As well they should. They (falsely) claimed they didn’t know if their paid clients were long or short on the very securities they were rating???????? You want guys who are trying to make profits for themselves and are “wholly investor-supported” making decisions on credit worthiness????? Obviously you do, but the majority of Americans don’t. And this post is the perfect metaphor of what this election is all about. And, say what you will, but this one’s over, boys and girls.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347709828218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 07:50:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347711637703-6</Id><Title>AT&amp;T is showing historic technical movement</Title><Msg>AT&amp;T looks really unstable right now. Check out this site for the latest updates in AT&amp;T goo.gl/LpGh3</Msg><Username>karimahewes</Username><Timestamp>1347711637703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 08:20:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347722774226-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With talk radio, Fox and the internet we can get the truth. Liberal media is paying the price for biased untruthful reporting with massive declining subscribers and viewership. People are want the truth the national media no longer has a monopoly on how information and what information is delivered.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347722774226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 11:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347724819319-8</Id><Topic><Title>Is AT&amp;T about to plunge? I think I have figured it out</Title><Username>madiebrighenti</Username><Timestamp>1347723448756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 11:37:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gullible Obama people jump on this</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347724819319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347727276735-9</Id><Topic><Title>Why isn't Barry attending the Daily Whitehouse Briefings?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347587447741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it really too much, to ask our Presidente to do his job? Clint is right, if you can't do the job, you got to let him go. PRETTY HARD TO DO THIS WHEN YOU'RE ON THE GOLF COURSE TRYING TO LINE A PUTT UP.....IT'S TIME FOR OUR DEAR LEADER TO MOVE ON....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1347727276735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347728733761-10</Id><Title>Christians fight HHS mandate</Title><Msg>Angry about the HHS mandate and wonder what you can do Join us begining sept 29th 2012 for 72 hours of continuous prayer and arrests at The White House We Must Obey God Rather Than Men! The future of religious freedom in America is at risk! With the recent Supreme Court ruling affirming Obamacare, the future of religious freedom in America is at risk, and in grave danger of being entirely wiped out. Obamacare will force institutions, churches and individuals to purchase abortion-inducing drugs, and pay for sterilization and abortion in direct opposition to their beliefs, conscience and historic teachings of the Church. For the first time in our nation’s history, our government is forcing people of faith and conscience to abandon their deeply held values and core beliefs. The President is now “dictating” to Christians how they are to live their faith. The government is replacing the teachings of Scripture, the Church, and our conscience, demanding that we bow down before their dictates. If the Christian community does not take a stand and send a powerful message to President Obama that we “must obey God rather than man,” and we “will never comply” with immoral and unjust government mandates that violate our faith — religious freedom and the First Amendment will be trampled before our very eyes. Beginning at 5:00 p.m. on September 29, 2012 we will engage in 72 hours of continuous prayer and arrests in front of the White House. We will prayerfully and peacefully assemble and the only grounds for arrest will be that our location is often a “restricted” zone for free-speech, so our defiance of the HHS Mandate will be taken as unprotected speech. Martin Luther King - During the Civil Rights movement, MLK worked tirelessly for the cause of equal rights amongst all citizens of the United States, regardless of skin color. In Birmingham, Alabama, he lead a massive event of civil disobedience, an event which captured the eyes and hearts of the country, and landed him — and many others — in jail. In jail for justice. In jail for standing up for the rights and liberties of his fellow men and women. In jail, with his brothers in what he called the “coalition of conscience”. Again, the government is threatening to take the freedoms of its people — of the preborn, and of the multitude who in good conscience cannot and will not participate in their killing. This is our Birmingham. We must risk arrest, or we must resign ourselves to the betrayal of our fellow men, of our God. 5:00 P.M. Actsfive 29 officially begins. What a powerful and prophetic way to begin the event: People will walk over to the White House and risk arrest, speaking a prophetic word to President Obama and our elected officials that we will “obey God rather than man” and “we will not comply” with any mandate or law which forces us to violate our conscience and our core faith beliefs and values. This will begin a 72 hour vigil of prayer, public witness and arrests at the White House. From this point on, there will be a continual presence at the White House.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347728733761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 13:05:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347729645505-11</Id><Topic><Title>Is AT&amp;T about to plunge? I think I have figured it out</Title><Username>madiebrighenti</Username><Timestamp>1347723448756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 11:37:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Historically, this is the time of year for a major decline in the entire market. Late September, early October.</Msg><Username>fivelinesfourspaces</Username><Timestamp>1347729645505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 13:20:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347735750872-12</Id><Title>Technical Chart Shows Upside on AT&amp;T, Inc.</Title><Msg>Im in shock!AT&amp;T, Inc. is on the verge of a major change in trend. Check out this site goo.gl/JCFKy</Msg><Username>liliaschrecongost</Username><Timestamp>1347735750872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 15:02:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347737396219-13</Id><Topic><Title>Why isn't Barry attending the Daily Whitehouse Briefings?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347587447741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barry is ignoring this. Voting present, like he did in the Illinois legislature. The only interview he gave that I'm aware of, is his one with Telemundo. This is America, we may have a foreign born Presidente, but not for long. Does the average American care what Mexicans think? I think not. Instead of this lap dog media going after Romney, they should be going after Obama, who's policies are costing American lives. Instead of questions of who is more talented, Jay Zee, or Beyonce? We need to know why the Marine Embassy Guards weren't allowed to use live ammo.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347737396219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 15:29:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347738203248-14</Id><Topic><Title>First Time Ever, An Illegal Alien Addresses DNC</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347500758778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:45:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I always recall the first cut I ever heard that Barry planned, it was against the Vets. He wanted to drastically cut their medical benefits. It was around the time they closed Walter Reed. He had to put these cuts on the back burner, so many came out against it .He had to change his mind. You watch, if he somehow he gets a 2nd term, Vets will pay. Illegals with be the big winner in his 2nd term.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347738203248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 15:43:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347739167038-15</Id><Title>Does Barry Believe in God?</Title><Msg>Real journalists have found that Barry has quoted this Bible verse over 50 times, "We are our Brother's Keeper". However, Obummer has a half brother named George. He is living in terrible conditions, and needs help. He is not good at making speeches, raising campaign money, and is just trying to get by. Does anyone know how we can help this poor man? Why does Barry hate him so?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347739167038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 15:59:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347739488940-16</Id><Title>Obama, The Movie 2016 winning fans.</Title><Msg>This is the 2nd biggest documentary film of all times. Michael Moore, is paraded as the 2nd coming. His films are fictional. He actually claims Cuba has better health care than the United States. How silly</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347739488940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 16:04:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347740878916-17</Id><Topic><Title>Christians fight HHS mandate</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347728733761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 13:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know, you’re entitled to worship whoever you want to, whenever you want to, wherever you want to and however you want to. Believing superstitious nonsense, however, doesn’t give you any legitimate justification to make up your own laws. Sadly the lunatics on the other side are saying the same thing about their version of god, and just like you, suggesting they have some divine calling and justification for doing whatever they want to do. I wish you both would grow up. And BTW, while you’re trying to drag Dr. King’s name into your “let’s tell women what to do” nonsense, you really should study history and stop embarrassing yourself. “In 1966, Planned Parenthood® Federation of America inaugurated the PPFA Margaret Sanger Award to honor the woman who founded America's family planning movement. The PPFA Margaret Sanger Award is given annually to individuals of distinction in recognition of excellence and leadership in furthering reproductive health and reproductive rights.” Guess who was one of the recipients in 1966? “This award is presented to the Reverend Martin Luther King Jr., for his courageous resistance to bigotry and his lifelong dedication to the advancement of social justice and human dignity. In the tradition of all great humanitarians who have seen that human life and progress are indeed indivisible, Dr. King has lent his eloquent voice to the cause of world-wide voluntary family planning.” Please stop denigrating Dr. King. He wouldn’t like your gig in Washington, and he wouldn’t like you. He would, however, just like me, love to see you get arrested. Good luck with that.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347740878916</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 16:27:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347753734140-18</Id><Topic><Title>Christians fight HHS mandate</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347728733761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 13:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dr. King would not have accepted any award that contained the name of Margaret Sanger had he understood this woman was a racist. In 1966 PP represented itself, at least on the surface, as being anti-abortion. Dr. King being a Christian leader would have fought for the rights of the unborn and if he were alive today would be proud to stand with those trying to protect the freedom of religion. It doesn't suprise me that you Echo bring up the name of Margaret Sanger since you both share a common thread of atheism and racism. At a March 1925 international birth control gathering in New York City, a speaker warned of the menace posed by the "black" and "yellow" peril. The man was not a Nazi or Klansman; he was Dr. S. Adolphus Knopf, a member of Margaret Sanger's American Birth Control League (ABCL), which along with other groups eventually became known as Planned Parenthood. Margaret Sanger aligned herself with the eugenicists who strongly espoused racial supremacy and “purity,” particularly of the “Aryan” race. Eugenicists hoped to purify the bloodlines and improve the race by encouraging the “fit” to reproduce and the “unfit” to restrict their reproduction. They sought to contain the “inferior” races through segregation, sterilization, birth control and abortion. that's you ECHO Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., stridently denounced abortion as a form of genocide in many speeches. Dr. King did in fact receive the Margaret Sanger Award in 1966. But it is also a fact that in 1966, Planned Parenthood was still (at least publicly) anti-abortion. They were still using a pamphlet they wrote and published in 1963 titled Is Birth Control Abortion?. The pamphlet read: Is birth control abortion? Definitely not. An abortion kills the life of a baby after it has begun. In 1966, and before, Planned Parenthood was publicly against abortion. So was Dr. King; so it shouldn’t be surprising that he accepted an award from them. Dr. King did not know (as most people even today don’t know) that Margaret Sanger was a racist, elitist, and eugenicist. She knew that if he hopes for a controlled black population were to be realized then PP would have to enlist the help of black ministers. On January 17, 2000, Martin Luther King Jr.s niece, Alveda King, spoke at a pro-life meeting at Faneuil Hall of Boston University. She said: " If Martin Luther King’s dream is to live, our babies must live. We have been fueled by the fires of women’s rights. What about the rights of the baby who is artificially breached. We can’t sit idly by and allow legal murder.”</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347753734140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 20:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347755023339-19</Id><Topic><Title>Christians fight HHS mandate</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347728733761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 13:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is true. Also this is why the GOP has the stand on getting rid of abortion. Too, many GOPers having abortions. This will take votes from the GOP. GOPer's are born you know. This is probably the last election if they can get a low turn out from the other side, or restrict their voting somehow. Four years from now Texas is reported to become a possible DNC win. All , I can say to advise is the GOP needs to screw more, and try to out number us. Or continue to ruin public education so even some Democrats will vote against themselves. Many are already doing this. It really amazes me, but some people near welfare, vote GOP.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1347755023339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 20:23:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347755545814-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, The Movie 2016 winning fans.</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347739488940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 16:04:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For what it costs they do a much better job than here. We have the most expensive healthcare system in the World. Not the best how ever. Just Google it.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1347755545814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 20:32:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347766282375-21</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, the drone attack is the reason. Obama openly brags about having total control of the drone hit list. So the movie excuse isn't plausible. These rioters aren't fooled by Barry's double speak. Like GM in alive, &amp; O$ama is dead. Then he says, I support you, and whatever Government you choose. Also, this joke of a movie is at least six months old. The main stream media believes if they repeat this movie myth frequently enough, most will believe it. However, no one not under the control of this administration believes this for one second. See the Fox interview with the retired guy who was in charge of the O$ama kill unit These attacks came on 9/11, and the attackers had top shelf weapons, and were well trained. These weren't kids throwing a couple stones at the Embassy. I know many Libs knock Fox, but you'll get the real scoop there. I watch msnbc, just to try to understand why anyone would still vote for Obummer</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347766282375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 23:31:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>