<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-08"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354985949790-1</Id><Title>Tax churches that run non-church businesses</Title><Msg>There are millions, if not billions, of tax dollars that could help this country that are in the name of churches, but actually have nothing to do with religion other than the tax-exempt status they have. This is wrong. I've thought so for years, but at this difficult time in history, I believe it is time to say this and get it out there because I know many other Christians who feel the same but are afraid to say. Since every entity that signs up for tax exempt status gets that status, no one knows for sure how much money they are making and how much in tax revenue would be owed to the local, state, and federal governments. One huge example I will give: TRINITY EPISCOPOL CHURCH IN NYC, own ALL of Manhattan, NY. Wallstreet, what was the twin towers, all the major banks there in the financial district, is leased to Trinity Episcopol Church NYC. The church "got" this land early on in somewhat of a controversial way (stole it probably), and leases it out. How many millions of dollars do you think this church owes if a new law separating these entities as businesses would bring in? This church exists for the sole purpose of leasing this property in Manhattan. That's just one. Think of all the churches that own businesses in the name of "church" that do not conduct worship services or bury their dead on that land. It's huge. Yet, we say nothing. It has caused much bitterness over the years. It is time the churches have church, and have true separation of church and state. I believe it could be the answer to many problems. I bring this up because one of my old telephone friends just married a minister, and they are using their "tax exempt status" to start a business. She feels as long as it's going to the church (and into their pockets, some not all because she is investing some of her inheritance in it), that it's OK and that I'm terrible to say it is not a good thing.</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1354985949790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 11:59:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354986742486-2</Id><Topic><Title>Tax churches that run non-church businesses</Title><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1354985949790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 11:59:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I meant to say leased from Trinity Episcopol, not leased "to".......my point is that church is making a fortune off of non church business and pay not one dime in taxes. They are fat cat churches, at our expense.</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1354986742486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 12:12:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354987234150-3</Id><Title>Where did my post go?</Title><Msg>I posted an important post on separating churches from the tax-exempt status and taxing those entities and named a church in NYC that is filthy rich because of this........where did it go?</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1354987234150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 12:20:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354987423078-4</Id><Topic><Title>Where did my post go?</Title><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1354987234150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 12:20:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK. Sorry, I'm used to having my posts deleted. I can see it's there.</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1354987423078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 12:23:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354988515798-5</Id><Topic><Title>Is it time we Punish Single Women?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354844143546</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 20:35:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dastardly! I wonder how he ever came up with such a clever idea...I bet he thinks he's pretty smart fooling all the rest of us that way.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1354988515798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 12:41:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354988601984-6</Id><Topic><Title>Where did my post go?</Title><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1354987234150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 12:20:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whew. I know I can move on with my day with a profound sense of relief.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1354988601984</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 12:43:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354988742832-7</Id><Topic><Title>Quit your whining and let T fall lower then buy the krapski out of this dividend winner</Title><Username>born_in_a_cage</Username><Timestamp>1354846510280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 21:15:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When did you get a "friend"? Is he a big white bunny named "Harvey"?</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1354988742832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 12:45:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354991063372-8</Id><Topic><Title>Is it time we Punish Single Women?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354844143546</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 20:35:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Sharia law should ever become the law of the land, single women would no longer be a problem, nor would homosexuals, nor would thieves or liars. I'm told they have strong "penalties" for such situations. When the Iranian president told Columbia University students, "There are NO homosexuals in Iran", he wasn't lying. However, I have friends who lived extensively in the Middle East and the women from Americans lived in a certain compound while their husbands worked in the oil industry, they were asked to act and do certain things which they respected, and these women say you could not expect any people to be nicer or more respectful anywhere in the world. One friend told me she wanted to live there and not come back to America. Many of the Americans had lived there for more than twenty years and raised their children there. They provided help to clean their homes and do their clothes. The wives virtually had to do nothing but raise their children, which they also were provided babysitters to help. They provided Christian pastors and churches to worship their Christianity and did not interfere with their beliefs in any way. However, haven't talked to her lately. I do assume she will defend the Middle East and their way of life. She clearly did love those people and had no problem with their requirements. It was a "live, and let live" situation. However these women followed "their rules". They had drivers appointed for them and they did not go out shopping alone. They always wore scarves on their heads, and they did not use profanity or speak loudly or obtusely. They did not speak to other men in a "chatty way", if at all, and basically the women just did what they wanted to do......shop. Saudi Arabia was where these families worked and lived for the time I have knowledge. I once asked the one friend if she was ever afraid, and she said Never. She said nothing was ever stolen from her or her home, and she felt safer there than in the United States. Her husband retired from the oil company and they had to come back to the U.S. facing taxes, mortage payments, doing her own housework, and having to drive to the grocery store and worry about getting mugged or hit by a drunk driver.</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1354991063372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 13:24:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354992593680-9</Id><Topic><Title>Is it time we Punish Single Women?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1354844143546</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 20:35:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I, for one, would prefer Sharia Law over the insanity that has gripped Washington in the past few decades.</Msg><Username>thecrap0n</Username><Timestamp>1354992593680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 13:49:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354998318920-10</Id><Topic><Title>Tax churches that run non-church businesses</Title><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1354985949790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 11:59:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I care. I don't like it either. Envy has nothing to do with some churches making out like bandits. Render unto Caesar what is Caesar's and unto God what is God's. It's time to pay Caesar his part which will help everybody else.These churches will still be very rich, even having to pay taxes.</Msg><Username>collarbitreign</Username><Timestamp>1354998318920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:25:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354998461452-11</Id><Topic><Title>Tax churches that run non-church businesses</Title><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1354985949790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 11:59:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Caesar only helps himself. You must be quite deluded if you think otherwise.</Msg><Username>thecrap0n</Username><Timestamp>1354998461452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:27:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355016813253-12</Id><Title>ATT is doing NOK and MSFT a disservice</Title><Msg>They should take all their phones out of ATT stores and they are NOT SUPPORTING THEIR PHONES and THEIR SALES PEOPLES GIVE A RATS #$%$ ABOUT THEM</Msg><Username>todlondon</Username><Timestamp>1355016813253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 20:33:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355017207404-13</Id><Title>Kissinger and the NEW WORD ORDER</Title><Msg>The Bilderberg group has stated that the human world population needs to decrease to 500 million people. We are currently at 7 billion. Decreasing to this level would put the earth back in biological balance and save it from ecological disaster. Mother nature however has a way of doing this through starvation as resources vanish and starvation occurs through famine.</Msg><Username>todlondon</Username><Timestamp>1355017207404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 20:40:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355017976521-14</Id><Topic><Title>Kissinger and the NEW WORD ORDER</Title><Username>todlondon</Username><Timestamp>1355017207404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 20:40:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is "The New Word Order?" Is that like writing correctly, putting the subject first and then the verb. What is the correct word order? I know Kissinger still has an accent, but I think he gets his words in the right order. Please explain.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1355017976521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 20:52:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>