<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351915370634-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama betrays Benghazi</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1351871675167</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:54:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One doesnt need to know a lot given the corruption the last 4 years. I thought the same thing day 1. Long history of scandal Chi-Town style. Us Indies are scratching our heads at the knee jerks.</Msg><Username>telluride15</Username><Timestamp>1351915370634</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 00:02:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351918257424-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama betrays Benghazi</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1351871675167</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:54:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Obama admin are liars, they tried to convince Americans this was all the result of a video. Communications that reveal the Obama administration turned it's back on these people and got them killed. Hillary Clinton deserves no respect remember her claim of being under sniper fire during a trip to Bosnia which she later had to admit was a lie. Hillary and the Obama admin have betrayed America</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1351918257424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 00:50:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351918658802-3</Id><Topic><Title>Gov Cumo tries to justify Gas shortage</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351908058390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:00:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Obama administration has failed the people impacted by this hurricane. These people are hurting and Obama just seeks photo ops no real help from his administration.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1351918658802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 00:57:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351926801660-4</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy creates change for VOTING Dates !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1351910268529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:37:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH, teehee. Mommy's fat greasy little baby thinks he made a funny (grins) (??)</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351926801660</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 03:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351926899307-5</Id><Topic><Title>I wish PBS would be defunded</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1351914895627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish you'd die a long, slow, lonely death in a great deal of pain. I bet I'll get my wish before you get yours, dungball.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351926899307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 03:14:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351938955109-6</Id><Topic><Title>I wish PBS would be defunded</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1351914895627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Defund the communist EPA and Dept of Education ! ! Communist big wig Carol Browner was EPA Director (forever) before becoming present Director of US Dept of Energy ! !</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1351938955109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 06:35:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351944290786-7</Id><Topic><Title>I wish PBS would be defunded</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1351914895627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “Communist big wig Carol Browner was EPA Director (forever) before becoming present Director of US Dept of Energy ! !” Carol Browner is not now, nor has she ever been, the Director of The US Dept. of Energy. But thanks for further revealing your ignorance. (And, incidentally, she was the best EPA Director of all time.) Now go back to telling us that global warming is a hoax and the planet is only 6000 years old. Tee Partee Untie!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351944290786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 08:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351945283660-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obummer Needs To Return to NYC</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351911840747</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:04:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If he is in NY then he is a distraction ; if he is not in NY he is negligent. What can Obama do in New York to help????</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1351945283660</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 08:21:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351945522628-9</Id><Topic><Title>I wish PBS would be defunded</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1351914895627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And don't forget the classical music. They seldom play Hank Jr. Or the writers almanac. Or Masterpiece Theater but never wrestling. Don't you get it? PBS is not for idiots.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1351945522628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 08:25:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351947943027-10</Id><Topic><Title>Obummer Needs To Return to NYC</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351911840747</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:04:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's not forget, this story will be covered. It can't be swept under the rug for a few more weeks, like Bengazi. Unfortunately, Barry has encouraged deivisions in this Country over the last four years. Union, over non-Union. Gay, over straight, Minority, over Mainstream. If the restoral effort fails, who is going to get most of the blame. It is Obami my friend. I for one would have a lot of respect if he would just roll up his sleeves, and take control. No one is going to tell the President of the United States no. I really believe Barry is missing the opportunity of a lifetime. In the next couple days we have a big decision to make. Throw politics aside, which of these two men do you believe can get a job done? Romney, a businessman, or Barry. Which one would you rather be in a fox hole with? The answer is clear, for me at least. Teleprompters will not correct this problem. Only action, will put the Greatest City, in the Greatest Country, back on it's feet again.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351947943027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:05:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351948393451-11</Id><Topic><Title>Gov Cumo tries to justify Gas shortage</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351908058390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:00:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's sad. If we can't defeat a little wind, and water under this Administration, what chance do we have, if we have to go to war with China? Maybe God, Allah, or someone is trying to send us a message. We should make a better choice, on who is going to lead us for the next four years. Teleprompter reading will not make this catastrophe go away.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351948393451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:13:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351949083168-12</Id><Topic><Title>Staten Island becomes Satan's Island</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351912922610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:22:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a crying shame. Seriously, so many Billions in stimulus money has been funneled by Obama to his friends. All those funds stolen, and sqandered. That money was borrowed from the Chinese, our kids, and several generations of their kids, will be paying this back. Now, it's undeniable. We need some of those funds. Lucy, this skinny President has some explaining to do. We can pass judgement on this telepromper reading fool, in just a few days. Yea, or Nay. How can anyone answer that gold standard of a question. Especially these poor victims. Are you better off than you were FOUR years ago?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351949083168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351949394148-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obummer Needs To Return to NYC</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351911840747</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:04:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lose the election!</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1351949394148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351950962334-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obummer Needs To Return to NYC</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351911840747</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:04:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More #$%$ from jon2retard, the only black man in America driving a Prius. Where in Ohio did Romney have a 50,000 person crowd?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1351950962334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:56:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351951190593-15</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy creates change for VOTING Dates !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1351910268529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:37:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical robfisk post, unintelligent.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1351951190593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351952387655-16</Id><Topic><Title>And they wonder why people are leaving their states</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351864409249</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:53:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My wife works with illegals here in the Peoples Republic of Maryland. We are awash in illegals, taking all of the contruction jobs here. The vast majority in her program love to visit Fla. on the holidays. They love the warm weather. The only reason you don't have more is because of your dismal employment possibilities. These people love money, and most have two, or three jobs. So, the only hope we have is Mitt. I believe he is a fair man. He understands the economy, and won't dismiss our concerns (both Black &amp; White), on where our folks are going to be able to get jobs. God luck, hang in there. Please urge everyone you know to vote Barrack out of office. If you want to see an interesting piece on immigration, check out PBS. I don't know the title, but it's an hour on the coming war between brown, and white. Why is Big Bird trying to divide our folks? But the overwhelming message is. Why should we ask these young Latinos to fund the retirement of our elderly? It plays the race card, explaining that 80% of our elderly are white. It's must see tv. Please try to have your friends check it out. At the very least Mitt, wiill seal the border. If we start taxing their money transfers, many will self deport. If Barry gets a 2nd, you can bet we will become a welfare state for these law breakers. God Bless.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351952387655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 10:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351952731730-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obummer Needs To Return to NYC</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351911840747</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:04:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not exactly sure. I think it was Finlay, but don't hold me to it. Who is Jon? I only use my name, Rob. Who would post as a retard?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351952731730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 10:25:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351953651788-18</Id><Topic><Title>I wish PBS would be defunded</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1351914895627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I recently saw a piece on PBS that was a real eye opener. Unfortunately, I don't recall the title. It was an hour on the upcoming war between Brown, &amp; White. I don't understand why Big Bird would try to divide our Country, but he is. The main question raised, was how can we ask all these young Latinos to pay for our elderly retirees. It showed that 80% of our retired, living off of Social Security (and therefore off the backs of young illegal immigrants), WERE WHITE! But the reality is the other way around, these young illegals are living off of our retired folks. America's Greatest Generation, is just trying to stay in their homes, and are paying very high property taxes, cause of all these freeloaders in the underground economy. So, please vote your pocketbook. A Romney-Ryan victory means a return of fiscal sanity. Mitt is an honest man, and understands the economy. He'll seal the border, and tax money transfer back to these crooked countries. These people will self deport, and create jobs for our citizens, both Black, and White. Ebony, and Ivory, as Paul McCartney used to sing about.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351953651788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 10:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351956562133-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama betrays Benghazi</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1351871675167</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:54:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both American and British sources said, at the very least, the security situation on the ground and the lack of proper response were the result of "complete incompetence by the Obama administration."</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1351956562133</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:29:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351957293704-20</Id><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Msg>GOOGLE THE ABOVE, and you will find a former Mormon, and their recruiting practices. Lieing is involed, and the Bible is True only if viewed by Mormon interpretations. Now, I know why Mitt finds it so easy to lie.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351957575200-21</Id><Topic><Title>I wish PBS would be defunded</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1351914895627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I worked with a lot of ex-military over the years. Those from Viet Nam, always had good rebutals. One guy (a Marine quipped), mostly to big guys. Thank Goodness, I didn't have to serve with you. I would have hated to have to see you drop your death turd.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351957575200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:46:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351957859049-22</Id><Title>Most Blacks now support gay marriage</Title><Msg>Blacks didn't always feel this way but now that BO has said he likes it so do his strongest supporters who will vote for him based only on skin. Going forward America no longer needs to feel it is wrong to use skin color as a criteria in selecting their leaders blacks are leading the way in setting an example. America can now point to BO that voting based on skin color is OK</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1351957859049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:50:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351958726835-23</Id><Topic><Title>I wish PBS would be defunded</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1351914895627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lav, you should read scripture. Not the lies that organized religion has built out of it and erroneous interpretations. It has been foretold that this would happen because his people (not the counterfeits) turn away from him. The same thing happened in OT days. "Brotherhood" with the Satan worshipping Canaanites brought the ancint (and true) kingdom of Israel down. One verse says; "Strangers (aliens) eat their sustenance and they know it not." The end isn't going to be pretty but it will end and I believe very soon. Read the Mayflower Compact. They knew who they were and quoted a verse from Revelations.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351958726835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351958811969-24</Id><Topic><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...."But the fearful, and unbelieving, and the abominable, and murderers, and fornicators, and sorcerers, and idolaters, and all liars, shall have their part in the lake which burns with fire and brimstone: which is the second death."...... Revelation 21:8</Msg><Username>coulddobetter</Username><Timestamp>1351958811969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:06:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351959060943-25</Id><Topic><Title>I wish PBS would be defunded</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1351914895627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You quote fools that do not understand scripture. The word for "day" in the creation story actaually means an indeterminate time. Notice the progression on each "day" of creation. It fits exactly what they find in the fossil record. "The" Adam was placed here 6,000 years ago. The earth had others here before him. "Man Made" global warming is a hoax but you and others are too stupid to figure it out or are part of the gang that wants to promote their anti-human agenda.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351959060943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351959136119-26</Id><Topic><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google the White Horse Prophecy, that will explain the Bishop's run for President.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1351959136119</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:12:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351962904973-27</Id><Topic><Title>I wish PBS would be defunded</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1351914895627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ooooh...here comes Runaway's ("spewmor", "screwhor", or whatever the demented old fantasist is calling himself now) angry sky fairy (his "Big Brother")...boom...boom...kaboom! Funny, how the closer death comes, the more you nut jobs think you're going to mitigate and erase all the damage you've done to others in your life by dripping your senile spittle on the pages of a screwy Bronze Age work of fiction... Good luck with that! If there is a hell, it is yawning wide at this very moment to receive your lying soul with its sick violent fantasies. Soon! Very soon!</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351962904973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:15:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351963053130-28</Id><Topic><Title>I wish PBS would be defunded</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1351914895627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whatever that means, Lardquake. Apparently, just like you, your alter egos are incapable of writing anything sensible. I wish I could feign surprise.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351963053130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351963279527-29</Id><Title>"Romney Calls His Campaign a Movement"</Title><Msg>This is the first thing I've agreed with Bishop Magic Pants on - it is definitely a "movement". Excuse me, I'll be right back; after a couple of cups of coffee, I have to go pinch a Romney Campaign.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351963279527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351963362066-30</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy creates change for VOTING Dates !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1351910268529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:37:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It takes even less intelligence to understand that you are not funny, which is, I supposed, why you are utterly challenged on this front. Though you are not funny, you are an IDIOT!</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351963362066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351963693301-31</Id><Topic><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are an atheist and like almost all atheists align yourself with liberal democrats. You are unqualified to discuss relgion.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1351963693301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:28:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351964102011-32</Id><Topic><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody is qualified to discuss "relgion", since it doesn't exist. Oh wait a minute, maybe you deluded sheep who believe in the angry sky fairy are qualified, since you spend a lot of time discussing things that don't exist and arguing about, and killing each other for, that which doesn't exist more. Discuss away...baaa...baaa...baaa! And you thieving little sheep, I used to exchange posts with the real geoff_holt on this board, and let me tell you, you are no geoff_holt. He was fierce and you're just a nattering little p*ssy. What do your kiddie stories in the bible tell you about people who steal? What happens to them? You both a hypocrite and a thief.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351964102011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:35:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351964639874-33</Id><Topic><Title>Our dispossession in our own lands</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1351906080156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 21:28:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Radix", the journal of the uneducated, unemployed and irrelevant. I doubt there will be a second issue, so don't take out a long term subscription. Save your SSI payments for something important like the casino or the lottery. You poor ignorant thing, the world you thought you knew has moved on and forward; you were uneducated, unmotivated and unequipped to keep pace, so you're still sitting in next to the broken appliances in your front yard in your dirty diaper, with a filthy snot smear under your nose whining about it instead of pulling your ignorant #$%$ out of the dirt and doing something about it. Go away already!</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351964639874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:43:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351966660254-34</Id><Topic><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are there any democrats who post on this board that are not atheist? gay liberal and atheist = democrat</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1351966660254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 14:17:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351968061274-35</Id><Topic><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I neither know nor care. I don't memorize peoples' posts. It's wonderful that you do, however. It must fill a void, give you the illusion of your life having purpose and, hopefully, occupies time you would otherwise spend leering at children at the playground. So, please, knock your stupid, illiterate self out with your hobby. Before I forget. You are an IDIOT.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351968061274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 14:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351968144815-36</Id><Title>disitrict 3 vote no</Title><Msg>to all my cwa union brothers and sisters in district 3/bell south who voted down att;s last offer...vote no again and get rid of judy dennis your vp....we in district 1 and 9 thought it would be all of us together ...once again she has let you down.....</Msg><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1351968144815</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 14:42:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351970035019-37</Id><Topic><Title>"Romney Calls His Campaign a Movement"</Title><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351963279527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yah it was refreshing to see romney not lying or forgetting what he said the last speech. A bowel movement it is, so true.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351970035019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 15:13:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351974085587-38</Id><Title>In Maryland, Just Say No</Title><Msg>The crazies are all about. I saw several bus loads near the Chick Filet. There are 7 questions on the ballot here, Tuesday in Maryland. All about State Government borrowing money, to waste more of our tax dollars. WE HAVE TO DEEP SIX, ALL SEVEN. Another incentive. All these O'Mally sponsored questions, if passed could get O'Malley elevated to the Presidency one day. JUST A LITTLE SWEETNER TO GET YOU OUT. Can you imagine, allowing him to do to the Nation, what he's done to Maryland!. The two ballot questions that are the worse ones, allow in-state tuition, for illegal aliens, and GAY Marriage. All of these ballot questions, are thinly disguised, taxpayer subsidies. Illegals deserve no in state break. They were born out of the good old USA. Be you Ebony, or Ivory if this bill passes it will pull in illegals from all over this Country. Bottom line, we pay for their education, and they take ebony, and ivory slots. Gay marriage is about getting the tax breaks when you file your yearly taxes. Again, asking me to subsidize, carpet cleaners, and pole swallowers. I don't care what they do behind close doors, just don't ask me to pay for it.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351974085587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 16:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351974647382-39</Id><Topic><Title>Most Blacks now support gay marriage</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1351957859049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:50:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, many Blacks are insulted when anyone compares gay issues, to their civil rights struggles. Many of us know that Barry has had special male friends, in the past. The most famous, or infamous is that guy named Larry Sinclair. They will turn out to support Barry, here in Maryland in high numbers. Well into the 80% range. Don't forget Barry got 93% in 2008. They problem the Gay lobby has here, they will also vote down gay marriage while they are at the polls.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351974647382</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 16:30:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351976847933-40</Id><Topic><Title>Biden admits he has never been proud to be BO's vice president</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1351879096787</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 13:58:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It could happen</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1351976847933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:07:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351977153775-41</Id><Topic><Title>Most Blacks now support gay marriage</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1351957859049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:50:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorrty but you are all wet. Most Blacks DO NOT support same sex marriage. Many Black preachers are excoriating the Kenyan for doing so. The Kenyan has flip flopped on the subject because he wants the "Gay?" vote. By the way, did you lose your job at Finnochios when they closed?</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351977153775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:12:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351978282885-42</Id><Topic><Title>Most Blacks now support gay marriage</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1351957859049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:50:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please rewrite that paragraph. It makes no sense. Your writing would be bad for a high school dropout. Pitiful. And to think you have the right to vote.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1351978282885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:31:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351978821583-43</Id><Topic><Title>Most Blacks now support gay marriage</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1351957859049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:50:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I watched a Black preacher voice his opposition to gay marriage but admitted he and his congregation would be voting for BO, I leave this open to your own interpretation.</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1351978821583</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351979893361-44</Id><Topic><Title>Most Blacks now support gay marriage</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1351957859049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:50:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gay marriage is not that big an issue among black people</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1351979893361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:58:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351980755483-45</Id><Topic><Title>I wish PBS would be defunded</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1351914895627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So defund PBS, but don't cut big oil federal gov't. subsidies? Wow!</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1351980755483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:12:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351982613670-46</Id><Title>Obama Gets a Photo Op, Then Goes AWOL</Title><Msg>I know New Yorkers aren't that stupid. They know when they've been played. Did Barry go back to DC to kick start FEMA, or pull back some National Guard from their overseas deployment? No, he flew into Vegas for yet another fundraiser. The election is just hours away, whatever money he raises won't help. These victims of Sandy need help now. ASAP! Is this guy really that uncaring? Maybe he just doesn't care what people think!</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351982613670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:43:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351995119961-47</Id><Title>Just Send the Check</Title><Msg>Say the Democrats. For some reason, history is being revised to state that there never was a struggle to achieve a living wage by Americans prior to, and post the "World War Era' of this country. I mean, there was no welfare then folks. Now, if things don't work out for you, you can depend upon the working taxpayer to bail you out, especially the entitlled "takers". When all the great Americans of that long past era are gone, all we will have left is an entire segment of Americans who feel they are due the good life withourt struggling for it. The old folks I know are ashamed of what is going on now. I'd hate to wake up in the morning as a Democrat, praying that I will be fed, nursed, and housed by their Government.</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1351995119961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:11:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351995833058-48</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Gets a Photo Op, Then Goes AWOL</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351982613670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:43:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea, I saw Romney manning a shovel. He quit campaigning and is help the poor in a soup kitechen in NY. ( Not ) He is a regular Mother Teresa. Or was that Romney on the news today making four stops in three states. Why is he not helping the New Yorkers?????</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1351995833058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:23:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351996052886-49</Id><Topic><Title>Just Send the Check</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1351995119961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell the old folks you know who are ashamed to send back their social security checks and stop filing for medicare. When they do that I will become a believer. Otherwise they just have their hand out like everyone else.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1351996052886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>