<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352011814821-1</Id><Topic><Title>OH MY - So Tired Of Class Envy Politics !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1351987843182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 20:10:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH MY - so tired of you. What sort of fat, idiotic pig says that he wants to vomit on the President of the US - whoever occupies the office? Who raised you? You are an IDIOT!</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1352011814821</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 01:50:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352012349656-2</Id><Topic><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thereby confirming you are posting under at least five aliases, because nobody but you, if they were in their right mind, would give a good GD about that post. If it's not all big fat illiterate coward jon2retarded's aliases, stand up and be counted.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1352012349656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 01:59:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352018500193-3</Id><Topic><Title>"Romney Calls His Campaign a Movement"</Title><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351963279527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I take my Romney every morning after a few cups of java myself. Will be taking a BIG one on Nov 7.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1352018500193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 03:41:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352023158908-4</Id><Topic><Title>Just Send the Check</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1351995119961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Tell the old folks you know who are ashamed to send back their social security checks and stop filing for medicare." "Otherwise they just have their hand out like everyone else" The difference is they paid their share out of their own pocket. It is a not so subtle difference that is obviously lost on you.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1352023158908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 04:59:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352024894545-5</Id><Title>Thanks For Another Dividend!</Title><Msg>Not buying at these levels, but certainly like that cash flow.</Msg><Username>tropazzz</Username><Timestamp>1352024894545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 05:28:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352030988456-6</Id><Topic><Title>Just Send the Check</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1351995119961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the old people are 75 or older they paid about 30% of what they are taking EVEN if you allow for compounding of their contributions. I do not begrudge them their checks. My Mom is 92 and lives in her own house, etc. However for the old people to #$%$ about others trying to have a quality of life as provided by Obamacare is just hypocritical. " I got mine and f*** everyone else " is a sad commentary for this country.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1352030988456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 07:09:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352032905706-7</Id><Topic><Title>Just Send the Check</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1351995119961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “…you can depend upon the working taxpayer to bail you out, especially the entitlled ‘takers’…Americans who feel they are due the good life withourt struggling for it. I'd hate to wake up in the morning as a Democrat, praying that I will be fed, nursed, and housed by their Government…” – cmontx Waking up in general would be a good goal for you. You are either totally ignorant of reality, or simply another spokesperson for the “privileged” class. For all you mouth pieces of the 2%, who attempt to lie and deceive the rest of us about the evils of those lazy, drunkard, welfare bums (add your own racial implication) who are stealing from you “hard working”, patriotic, moralistic, citizens,…it’s time to wake up. The system is rigged. Social welfare pales in comparison to corporate welfare. Romney’s closed door comments about the 47% was by no means a mistake. Stop blaming the middle class in defense of the greed of the select few. From “Think by Numbers” “Government Spends More on Corporate Welfare Subsidies than Social Welfare Programs About 59 billion is spent on traditional social welfare programs. 92 billion is spent on corporate subsidies. So, the government spent 50% more on corporate welfare than it did on food stamps and housing assistance in 2006. Before we look at the details, a heartfelt plea from the Save the CEO’s Charitable Trust: There’s so much suffering in the world. It can all get pretty overwhelming sometimes. Consider, for a moment the sorrow in the eyes of a CEO who’s just found out that his end-of-year bonus is only going to be a paltry $2.3 million. “It felt like a slap in the face. Imagine what it would feel like just before Christmas to find out that you’re going to be forced to scrape by on your standard $8.4 million compensation package alone. Imagine what is was like to have to look into my daughter’s face and tell her that I couldn’t afford to both buy her a dollar sign shaped island and hire someone to chew her food from now on, too. To put her in that situation of having to choose… She’s only a child for God’s sake.” It doesn’t have to be this way. Thanks to federal subsidies from taxpayers like you, CEO’s like G. Allen Andreas of Archer Daniels Midland was able to take home almost 14 million in executive compensation last year. But he’s one of the lucky ones. There are still corporations out there that actually have to provide goods and services to their consumers in order to survive. They need your help. For just 93 billion a year the federal government is able to provide a better life for these CEO’s and their families. That’s less than the cost of 240 million cups of coffee a day. Won’t you help a needy corporation today? The Traditional Welfare Queen When one thinks about government welfare, the first thing that comes to mind is the proverbial welfare queen sitting atop her majestic throne of government cheese issuing a royal decree to her clamoring throngs of illegitimate babies that they may shut the hell up while she tries to watch Judge Judy. However, many politically well-connected corporations are also parasitically draining their share of fiscal blood from your paycheck before you ever see it. It’s called corporate welfare. The intent here is to figure out which presents the greater burden to our federal budget, corporate or social welfare programs. There are, of course, positive and negative aspects to this spending.The primary negative aspect is that you have to increase taxes to pay for it. Taxing individuals lowers their standard of living. It reduces people’s ability to afford necessities like medical care, education, and low mileage off-road vehicles.The common usage definition of social welfare includes welfare checks and food stamps. Welfare checks are supplied through a federal program called Temporary Aid for Needy Families. Combined federal and state TANF spending was about $26 billion in 2006. In 2009, the federal government will spend about $25 billion on rental aid for low-income households and about $8 billion on public housing projects. For some perspective, that’s about 3 percent of the total federal budget TANF (Temporary Aid to Needy Families) Another negative aspect relates to the fact that social welfare programs reduce the incentive for recipients to become productive members of society. However, in 1996, Congress passed a bill enacting limited welfare reform, replacing the Aid to Families with Dependent Children (AFDC) program with the new Temporary Aid to Needy Families (TANF) program. One key aspect of this reform required recipients to engage in job searches, on the job training, community service work, or other constructive behaviors as a condition for receiving aid. The bill was signed by a man named Bill Clinton, who is much better known for an act of fellatio which, of course, had far greater societal implications. Regardless, the success of this reform was pretty dramatic. Caseloads were cut nearly in half. Once individuals were required to work or undertake constructive activities as a condition of receiving aid they left welfare rapidly. Another surprising result was a drop in the child poverty rate. Employment of single mothers increased substantially and the child poverty rate fell sharply from 20.8 percent in 1995 to 16.3 percent in 2000. The Corporate Welfare Queen Now, let’s consider the other kind of welfare. Definition: corporate welfare n. Financial aid, such as a subsidy, provided by a government to corporations or other businesses. The Cato Institute estimated that, in 2002, $93 billion were devoted to corporate welfare. This is about 5 percent of the federal budget.To clarify what is and isn’t corporate welfare, a “no-bid” Iraq contract for the prestigious Halliburton, would not be considered corporate welfare because the government technically directly receives some good or service in exchange for this expenditure. Based on the Pentagon’s Defense Contract Audit Agency (DCAA) findings of $1.4 billion of overcharging and fraud, I suppose the primary service they provide could be considered to be repeatedly violating the American taxpayer.On the other hand, the $15 billion in subsidies contained in the Energy Policy Act of 2005, to the oil, gas, and coal industries, would be considered corporate welfare because no goods or services are directly returned to the government in exchange for these expenditures. Tax breaks targeted to benefit specific corporations could also be considered a form of welfare. Tax loopholes force other businesses and individual taxpayers without the same political clout to pick up the slack and sacrifice a greater share of their hard-earned money to decrease the financial burden on these corporations. However, to simplify matters, we’ve only included financial handouts to companies in our working definition of corporate welfare. Whenever corporate welfare is presented to voters, it always sounds like a pretty reasonable, well-intended idea. Politicians say that they’re stimulating the economy or helping struggling industries or creating jobs or funding important research. But when you steal money from the paychecks of working people, you hurt the economy by reducing their ability to buy the things they want or need. This decrease in demand damages other industries and puts people out of work. Most of the pigs at the government trough are among the biggest companies in America, including the Big 3 automakers, Boeing, Archer Daniels Midland, and now-bankrupt Enron. Farm Subsidies However, the largest fraction of corporate welfare spending, about 40%, went through the Department of Agriculture, most of it in the form of farm subsidies. (Edwards, Corporate Welfare, 2003) Well, that sounds OK. Someone’s got to help struggling family farms stay afloat, right? But in reality, farm subsidies actually tilt the cotton field in favor of the largest industrial farming operations. When it comes to deciding how to dole out the money, the agricultural subsidy system utilizes a process that is essentially the opposite of that used in the social welfare system’s welfare system. In the corporate welfare system, the more money and assets you have, the more government assistance you get. Conversely, social welfare programs are set up so that the more money and assets you have, the less government assistance you get. The result is that the absolute largest 7% of corporate farming operations receive 45% of all subsidies. (Edwards, Downsizing the Federal Government, 2004) So instead of protecting family farms, these subsidies actually enhance the ability of large industrial operations to shut them out of the market. Wal-Mart. Always high subsidies. Always. The same is true in all other industries, too. The government gives tons of favors to the largest corporations, increasing the significant advantage they already have over smaller competing businesses. If, in the court of public opinion, Wal-Mart has been tried and convicted for the murder of main street, mom-and-pop America, then the government could easily be found guilty as a willing accomplice. Wal-Mart receives hundreds of millions of dollars of subsidization by local governments throughout the country. These subsidies take the form of bribes by local politicians trying to convince Wal-Mart to come to their town with the dream of significant job creation. Of course, from that follows a larger tax base. For example, a distribution center in Macclenny, Florida received $9 million in government subsidies in the form of free land, government-funded recruitment and training of employees, targeted tax breaks, and housing subsidies for employees allowing them to be paid significantly lower wages. A study by Good Jobs First found that 244 Wal-Marts around the country had received over $1 billion in government favors. The Big Picture So now let’s look at the big picture. The final totals are $59 billion, 3 percent of the total federal budget, for regular welfare and $92 billion, 5 percent of the total federal budget, for corporations. So, the government spends roughly 50% more on corporate welfare than it does on these particular public assistance programs. Should we spend less on corporate welfare and/or social welfare programs? Or should we spend even more? It’s up to you. A bunch of people died horrible deaths to make sure this country remained a democracy, so if you feel strongly about this issue you owe it to them to call or write your congressman and senators and give them a piece of your mind.” Think By Numbers Why Think by Numbers? Numbers cannot lie. A world without disease, starvation, violence, and suffering is the ultimate destination of humanity. Getting there will require voters to base their decisions on statistical cost-benefit analyses instead of irrational emotions. The power of numbers can make utopia a reality.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1352032905706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 07:41:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352033153543-8</Id><Topic><Title>I wish PBS would be defunded</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1351914895627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gop's plan is dumb down america. look at the bald assed lies they tell now. Getting rid of pbs will get rid of 85 to 90 of the intellectual conversation about politics. instead we should get rid of station like fox the spread lies.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1352033153543</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 07:45:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352033289596-9</Id><Topic><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bully what did you call the kids on your corner? bet you threw a rock and ran. come out with facts, enough of this name calling.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1352033289596</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 07:48:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352033366273-10</Id><Topic><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another name calling post. do you get paid for this crap. better keep pbs maybe it would educate you.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1352033366273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 07:49:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352034337089-11</Id><Topic><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... "I do not consider it an insult, but rather a compliment to be called an agnostic. I do not pretend to know where many ignorant men are sure - that is all that agnosticism means." - Clarence Darrow</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1352034337089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 08:05:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352034961282-12</Id><Topic><Title>Just Send the Check</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1351995119961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess I am not eloquent enough to make my real point. When the Oldtimers all die off, the struggle to achieve a "living status" through hard work will have no spokesman. I feel that the Democrats don't want to let their minions know that you have to work to survive, not just kick back and draw cash, vouchers and checks. Once you are on the "Dole",you are forever on the dole, and that is a travesty to anybody who works for a living. Take a look at what is happening in Greece. That is our blueprint to avoid. Even the oldtime Greeks are rolling over in their graves.</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1352034961282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 08:16:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352035060097-13</Id><Topic><Title>"Romney Calls His Campaign a Movement"</Title><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351963279527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, it is. google the white horse prophecy in this you will see why other than thinking he is a finnancial whiz, how the mormons will save the country.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1352035060097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 08:17:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352036683236-14</Id><Topic><Title>Just Send the Check</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1351995119961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When they die off there will be more money to siphon off to the boomers like ME! LOL</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1352036683236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 08:44:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352045831427-15</Id><Topic><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The rank and file of most organizations are just followers that know little except what they are fed by their leaders. Deceit is common among ALL leaders of most groups, religious . political and economic. Scripture tell us that Satan rules this world and gives power to those that do his bidding. This won't last very much longer. It's all going to end "with great violence" as scripture foretells. Be sure you choose the right side when that time comes.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1352045831427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:17:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352046159574-16</Id><Topic><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And, ou of course, believe everything came from nothing. Know anything about probabilities? Get a book written by a French mathematician titled "Human Destiny." The mathematics of evolution simply don't add up. Something odd too is that many top scientists are theorizing that we exist in an artificial matrix. Some sci-fi writers proposed that many years ago. Perhaps it is basic training for things in the future . If you wash out you don't have a future.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1352046159574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:22:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352046657855-17</Id><Topic><Title>I wish PBS would be defunded</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1351914895627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big oil does not need our monies. The federal monies were put in place over 100 years ago to promote oil production. With big oil making huge profits now, they no longer need taxpayer money.</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1352046657855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:30:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352047376934-18</Id><Topic><Title>OH MY - So Tired Of Class Envy Politics !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1351987843182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 20:10:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, it all depends on how much of an illiterate failure you are, so in the present case, I'd say it is "yo". Definitely "yo". You are a mouthbreathing IDIOT!</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1352047376934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:42:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352048801599-19</Id><Title>LARDQUAKE finally...finally posted something funny</Title><Msg>Let's all congratulate baby jonny and his alter egos. After his seemingly never ending failed efforts, he finally posted something absolutely hilarious. "We all make mistakes, but just slow down .. get your thoughts together, then you'll be able to post a coherent rebuttal (smiles)" Considering the endless spew of unreasoned, illiterate prattle and minstrel show nonsense baby jonny posts, his presuming to advise another on achieving clarity has got to sit at the pinnacle of lack of self-awareness. Congratulations, baby jonny, you have now shown yourself to be both stupider and less evolved as a sentient being than ever before - and that, well that, is an accomplishment indeed! You are an IDIOT!</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1352048801599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:06:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352048928222-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Gets a Photo Op, Then Goes AWOL</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351982613670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:43:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The power of the Presidency is almost limitless. Even on MSNBC they poked fun at the amount of travel miles logged by Air Force One. They renamed Ohio, as the new base of Air Force One. People/Victims should come before elections, The Military, something Barrack will dramatically cut, has tons of equipment at their disposal. How about an Air Craft Carrier being brought in, at least those poor victims could be brought in out of the cold. Times like these, you need a business man like Mitt. Not someone from Central Planning, like Barrack. Living large on the taxpayer, saying one thing, and doing something completely different.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352048928222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:08:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352049216657-21</Id><Topic><Title>OH MY - So Tired Of Class Envy Politics !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1351987843182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 20:10:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you see the problem LARDQUAKE. If you could write even at a third grade level, your terribly clever, playground insult might have been intelligible. You need adult remedial education in basic skills. I am sorry that the schools of Vaginny have failed you so badly, but it's up to you to get the help you need. I've been meaning to thank you for all the interesting information you voluntarily shared on the web (i.e., with the world) about your birth date, location and birth certificate. I found a couple of interesting things in about 4 minutes on the web. Do you want to post any more personal information about yourself on the board? Social Security number would be fun ! On a daily basis, you make it abundantly clear you're stupid, but that was a high-water mark even for you. You are an IDIOT!</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1352049216657</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:13:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352049389166-22</Id><Topic><Title>And they wonder why people are leaving their states</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351864409249</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:53:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We always joke in my shop, whenever work picks up, shop stewards, and those higher up the Union ladder, all of the sudden have pressing Union business to attend to. I'm sure many of those in the Union shop, weren't at work many days cause of Union business. Some higher elected Union officials, only have to show up once a month to keep their employers happy.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352049389166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:16:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352050802378-23</Id><Topic><Title>And they wonder why people are leaving their states</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351864409249</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:53:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You couldn't possibly heave your vast, sweating carcass out of your dilapidated K Car to pump gas, so this is all theoretical for you, anyway. You are an IDIOT!</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1352050802378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:40:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352051129695-24</Id><Title>Biden Draws 900 at his Latest Rally</Title><Msg>I forced myself to listen to this guy, just to understand his twisted take, on the current state of America. One repeated statement, and the related rhetoric, centered on their desire to "Level the Playing Field". Class envy. I am constantly asked at work, by other Blacks why I am conservative? They say you aren't a rich man. You've had to take loans out to send your kids to college. The Union has carved out an exception for you on Obamacare. You are solidly in the Middle Class. You'll never be rich. True, unless I hit the lottery. But, I understand the promise of America. One day my kids could become rich, not that money is the end all. (That's another reason why I support Mitt. He's given Millions to those in Need). I don't want to deny that to my kids, or anyone elses. My Dad taught me from an early age, to be responsible, and to help others in need. Which I have always tried to do. He hated con men, beggars, and thieves. Those who for some reason, or another, "Thought the World Owed Them a Living". It sounds like a marketing theme. But that kind of sums it up. The Dem party has become a bunch of Con Men, Beggars, and Thieves. I feel like Ronald Reagan's statement, "I didn't leave the Democratic Party, They left me". Really says it all. Probably sums it up best, in a nutshell, why we must get rid of Obama!</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352051129695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:45:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352052352270-25</Id><Topic><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting, no takers evey single democrat on this MB is an atheists what does that tell you about the democrat party as a whole.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1352052352270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 13:05:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352052556330-26</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Draws 900 at his Latest Rally</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352051129695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:45:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden was in Florida last week....saw about 15 people jumping up &amp; down waving signs outside a campaign office where Joe wasted an hour of his day. He stopped in at a cafe' for lunch and talked to 4 senior citizens for an hour. The less he talks the better the message.</Msg><Username>commishfree1</Username><Timestamp>1352052556330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 13:09:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352052667226-27</Id><Topic><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why (??)..."don't" YOU lede "us" off hear, since you are such a "FONT" of originality (!!).. What "new: and IDIOTic thing will you "Come" up with "next"... (!!!) (teehee) You are an IDIOT!</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1352052667226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 13:11:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352052686971-28</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Draws 900 at his Latest Rally</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352051129695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:45:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If MR did give millions to others then why are they so quiet about it. Those supposed millions came from taking jobs from America and sending them overseas. Perhaps a little"guilt money" makes him feel better about what he has done to the workers in states like Ohio and Michigan. As you know Obama will be re elected and the sad sack Republicans will see the errors of their way and be more willing to compromise on key issues.</Msg><Username>blair.wagner</Username><Timestamp>1352052686971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 13:11:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352053125959-29</Id><Topic><Title>And they wonder why people are leaving their states</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351864409249</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:53:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are looking for construction work why didn't you say so. I have a leaking roof and the only people who will get on my roof are Mexicans. If you want the job come to North Carolina. Can I expect you tomorrow? I didn't think so.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1352053125959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 13:18:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352055141664-30</Id><Topic><Title>Is it a sin for a Mormon to LIE???</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351957293704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No more of a sin than for the 'Christian' Obama to lie. Or Harry Reid, or Nancy Pelosi, or… Harry by the way is also a Mormon.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1352055141664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 13:52:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352055584368-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Gets a Photo Op, Then Goes AWOL</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351982613670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:43:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hopefully Obama got the heck of the way due to some intelligent thought. Why the MSM demands that a President shows up at all major disaster areas is beyond reason. The President shows up and work stops, police, and other recourses are wasted in traffic control, security, and press events that get in the way of the real recovery work. There are people in the government that are responsible at a level that will actually help in recovery efforts and get paid handsomely for that work. Let them do their work. The President can watch on TV like the rest of us not actually in the damaged area. A smart President, not a media seeking President would stay abreast of the work being done, or not done and give directions to make good things happen. Showing up and slowing work isn't one of the things he needs to do to help.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1352055584368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 13:59:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352055840027-32</Id><Topic><Title>Just Send the Check</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1351995119961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As one of those getting a SS check, I will start sending back the return of my SS taxes when those collecting while not paying any taxes or working start working for their care and well being...oh wait, they can't...there are no jobs for them to apply for, plus they have few if any marketable skills to be paid for.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1352055840027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:04:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352055978749-33</Id><Topic><Title>Most Blacks now support gay marriage</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1351957859049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:50:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If black gay marriage or simply gay marriage is a defining problem in this economy and job crisis that this country is trying to dig its way out of, we are indeed an ignorant population of fools.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1352055978749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:06:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352056144565-34</Id><Title>Drugg Cowboys Hope Obama Hangs On</Title><Msg>Note:Spelling Errors to Avoid Yohoo Sensoars. I've decided to try to tune into the liberal media. I have to try to understand their mindset. I watched Current TV today. I believe this is Al Gorr's channel. They had a show that aired around 13:30 Eastern Standard Time. The young oriental journalist was in the Golden Triangle, on Mexico's Gold Coast, on the beautiful Pacific Ocean. Here, in the Druug controlled coastal area, where our illegal druug imports begin, the economy is booming, (Druug dealers are buying Hummers, &amp; Mansions are being built), cause of America's inner cities desire to escape our economic realities. No jobs, no hope, no change here. Just the cheap poison being peddled on our Nation's streets to our young folks, who have no way out. Our people have no boom, the only people working are illegals. Mit is the only hope we have. At least he'll seal the border, and provide jobs to our people.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352056144565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:09:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352056368979-35</Id><Topic><Title>Classified Cable exposes Obama admininstraion responsible for American deaths in Benghazi</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1351872580091</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:09:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Obama administration is doing all they can to delay the truth of this incident coming out. They know that if the truth is told prior to the election, they are finished and so is Billary. They screwed the pooch on this one and they can't figure out how to get out of it. Obama is forgetting one the fundamental truths of politics...when you find yourself in a hole, STOP DIGGING! If the truth of this failure is ever known, one might think many heads would roll, but if Obama is reelected, it will be swept under the rug much faster than Fast and Furious.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1352056368979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:12:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352056666532-36</Id><Topic><Title>Gov Cumo tries to justify Gas shortage</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351908058390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:00:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did the governors of these states think they would sail through this without problems? They knew the power was going to out, they knew gas was going to be scarce. Why weren't there more plans for extra mobile generating power? Why weren't there more plans for transporting fuel into the regions? It seems again, though not on the scale of New Orleans those local governments have not properly planned for coming, known disasters. Good work guys. That they even considered for a day of allowing the marathon to continue was simply stupid.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1352056666532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:17:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352056778993-37</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Gets a Photo Op, Then Goes AWOL</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351982613670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:43:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, but the proof is in the pudding. After being asked by Doomberg, and not encouraged by Cuomo, to show. Only Christie was left. Barry, ever the media/ Hollywood type, knew he'd get at the very least some great pics out of this. It worked, a slight bump up in the polls. But in hindsight (from the victims point of view), most agreed a helicopter fly over, and then some real help would have been better. NY is still waiting.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352056778993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:19:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352057548432-38</Id><Topic><Title>Gov Cumo tries to justify Gas shortage</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351908058390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:00:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, they have drills, they practice. The amount of money that is spent to deal with man made disasters is astronomical. Of course, natural disasters are no different. People need help. But common sense is in short supply. Even the thought of using 400 badly needed generators, for the marathon, instead of the victims is insane. Instead of getting, normally slow to react Government agencies in gear ASAP, the NY Gov. is wasting time gathering info to file suit. Going after those perceived to be price gouging.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352057548432</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:32:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352057972166-39</Id><Topic><Title>Drugg Cowboys Hope Obama Hangs On</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352056144565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:09:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I remember early on in the campaign Mit saying, he would not forget Detroit. He mentioned making an economic empowerment zone, to jump start business there. If you've ever been to Michigan, these people need something. One thing for sure, the Dems have done nothing for this State. Don't forget Mit grew up there. He won't put you on ignore after the election.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352057972166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:39:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352058525358-40</Id><Topic><Title>Drugg Cowboys Hope Obama Hangs On</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352056144565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:09:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea, he grew up in Michigan And got the hell out as quick as he could. Where does Mitt live? Not Michigan that is for damn sure.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1352058525358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:48:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352058741171-41</Id><Topic><Title>Drugg Cowboys Hope Obama Hangs On</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352056144565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:09:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tool!</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1352058741171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:52:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352058981644-42</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Draws 900 at his Latest Rally</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352051129695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:45:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...simply "fascinating" (!!)..please tell us more about your scintillating existence and your outings for "Skillets" at Dennys. It must be stories like this that make you the chick (??) maggot (grins) you are today (!!)</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1352058981644</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:56:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352059551236-43</Id><Topic><Title>In Maryland, Just Say No</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351974085587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 16:21:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Gay marriage protection bill, I found out is actually allowing state filers, ( who are gay), to get a bigger tax break than a traditional married couple. I don't know how Gov O'Malley was able to get that written into the legislation, but it was slipped in. I guess it was to makeup for the past, as what he perceives as, tax inequities. Now I understand why his Brother, (a traditional Catholic), no longer allows his campaign signs on his lawn. Also, be aware that on In-State Tuition for Illegals, those not born here, who start in the 2 year/Community College, are guaranteed transfer into the 4 Year School ( ie, Univ of Md). PLEASE REALIZE PARENTS- Only 10% of applicants get into our highly sought after Colleges. Even if these illegals got a 4 year college degree, they can not work here legally. Don't take lightly, the years of your hard earned taxpayer dollars, being wasted. It's your child, who will likely come up short on this fraudulent legislation.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352059551236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 15:05:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352060297703-44</Id><Topic><Title>Teachers Should Go For Mitt</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351644405039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My wife who is a Teacher, always spends close to a thousand dollars a year for her classroom. We have yet another Casino Bill pending this cycle, that the Fraudulent Gov. O'Malley swears will benefit education. Owe Malley last years raided $350 MILLION DOLLARS from our kids education money. By now, we should have the most educated kids in the universe. PLEASE, FBI, Investigate Governor O'Malley, if this isn't illegal, it should be!</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352060297703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 15:18:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352060374053-45</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Draws 900 at his Latest Rally</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352051129695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:45:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jon2retard aka robfisk, talking to himself. How many alias's does this clown have? Does he really own a Prius?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1352060374053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 15:19:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352060539461-46</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Draws 900 at his Latest Rally</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352051129695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:45:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has the Bishop released his? How about his tax returns? Where's the birth certificate?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1352060539461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 15:22:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352061258433-47</Id><Topic><Title>Classified Cable exposes Obama admininstraion responsible for American deaths in Benghazi</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1351872580091</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:09:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, this makes Watergate look like a non-event. It appears Obama will be able to evade, brush off, and deflect, any real investigation on this, till well after the election. Imagine if a Man of Honor, like Mit, had this Press Corp protecting him. He could be elevated to Sainthood within a month of taking office. Whereas Barrack, should be impeached, and is one step ahead of having to resign, for incompetence. That would leave Biden in charge. And that is way too scary to even think about. Joe, and his 900 person crown at his latest Ohio campaign stop. I wonder if they included the press corp in that 900 number?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352061258433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 15:34:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352061334865-48</Id><Title>NY Daily News Endorses Mitt Romney</Title><Msg>Sunday, 04 Nov 2012 10:19 AM By Patrick Hobin The New York Daily News, the country’s fifth largest newspaper, endorsed Mitt Romney on Sunday, joining the ranks of more than a dozen papers that have turned away from Barack Obama after endorsing his candidacy in 2008. The paper's endorsement came as a surprise: the News has a staunchly Democratic editorial viewpoint. The Daily News is also owned by one of the country's most respected and influential Democrats, Mort Zuckerman, the billionaire real estate mogul. But the New York daily staked its arguments against Obama not on politics but the economy, charging that President Obama’s promises went unfulfilled. “Revival of the U.S. as a land of opportunity and upward mobility is the central challenge facing the next president,” the paper wrote. “The question for Americans: Who is more likely to accomplish the mission — Barack Obama or Mitt Romney?” “Four years ago, the Daily News endorsed Obama, seeing a historic figure whose intelligence, political skills and empathy with common folk positioned him to build on the small practical experience he would bring to the world’s toughest job. We valued Obama’s pledge to govern with bold pragmatism and bipartisanship. The hopes of those days went unfulfilled.” The Daily News argued that Obama inherited a difficult economic situation but did not provide the right guidance to lead an economic revival. “The trend over the Obama years: Goodbye to middle- and high-income jobs in New York City; hello to positions that pay less than $45,000 a year,” the paper wrote. “Recovery from the disaster that Obama inherited was going to take time. But four years is a long, long slog. Had the president guided a typical upswing, America would by now have regained essentially all its lost jobs. At his present pace, Obama would reach that milestone in the third year of a second term. The regrettable truth is that Obama built a record of miscalculations and missed opportunities,” the Daily News editorial said. The paper, which is considered the publication of working class New Yorkers, even took Obama to task for Obamacare. “After originally projecting that the program would produce 4 million more jobs than the country now has, along with a 5 percent jobless rate, Obama pleads that he saved Americans from more dire straits,” it wrote. “Next came Obamacare. While the country bled jobs, the president battled to establish universal health insurance — without first restraining soaring medical bills. Then he pushed one of the largest social programs in U.S. history through a Democratic-controlled Congress without a single Republican vote. R.I.P. and never to be resurrected — Obama’s promised bipartisanship.” The Daily News said Romney’s approach to fix the economy would be “stronger” “Critically, he has tailored his policies to create jobs, jobs, jobs,” the Daily News wrote. “The centerpieces of Romney’s plan call for spending restraint and rewriting the Internal Revenue code to lower rates by 20 percent. He would make up much of the lost revenue by eliminating deductions and loopholes that have made the tax system a thicket of strangling complexities. On its own, paring the personal and corporate rules to the basics would catalyze business and consumer spending.” In the end, the paper’s endorsement came down to who could better get the country back on sound economic footing. It concluded its editorial with: “The presidential imperative of the times is to energize the economy and get deficits under control to empower the working and middle classes to again enjoy the fruits of an ascendant America. “So the News is compelled to stand with Romney.” © 2012 Newsmax. All rights reserved.</Msg><Username>demsdontgetitever</Username><Timestamp>1352061334865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 15:35:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352063383943-49</Id><Topic><Title>Classified Cable exposes Obama admininstraion responsible for American deaths in Benghazi</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1351872580091</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:09:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>W's fecklessness is responsible for 3000 deaths on US soil and you guys are #$%$ about 4 that occured in one of the most dangerous places on earth. How can you keep a straight face?</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1352063383943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:09:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352065347145-50</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Draws 900 at his Latest Rally</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352051129695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:45:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was be good if we stuck to the point. MR is the biggest con job to come along in american politics in a long long time. Talk about being a phony, he tops them all. His aim has always been to take care of the insiders and his 1% buddies. Did you not listen to him when he thought he was off the record? Wise up and look out for your own best interest. The Democrats have done more for the middle class over the last 50 years than any republican ever thought of doing. If MR had his way there would be no auto industry in this country,all the hard working immigrants would have been sent packing(and who would have done your dirty work then?),and all women would be on notice to submit as the Mormon women do to whims of their men. America is going to say "no thanks"</Msg><Username>blair.wagner</Username><Timestamp>1352065347145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:42:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352065606150-51</Id><Topic><Title>Classified Cable exposes Obama admininstraion responsible for American deaths in Benghazi</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1351872580091</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:09:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There isno consulate in Benghazi. Just oner more lie to add to the many others. It was a CIA "safe house". I think they hung the Ambassador out to dry because he knew too much about the gun smuggling to Al Queda in Libya. He was involved in it when it started. We are doing the same thing in Syria. Pure insanity, or? something else.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1352065606150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:46:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352065726387-52</Id><Topic><Title>Teachers Should Go For Mitt</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351644405039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fools prattle on and on while the rest of us are happy to pay our taxes and be glad that we live in this great country where any common person (not just the wealthy) can be come president. Again pay your taxes and be glad.</Msg><Username>blair.wagner</Username><Timestamp>1352065726387</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:48:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352067227752-53</Id><Topic><Title>Just Send the Check</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1351995119961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am going to leave my money to a whole bunch of great looking women, a little at a time. To heck with the poor people.</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1352067227752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 17:13:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352073037494-54</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Draws 900 at his Latest Rally</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1352051129695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:45:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that the Ronald Reagan with the oatmeal running down his chin and Nancy asking if he needs to use the bathroom?</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1352073037494</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 18:50:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352073390656-55</Id><Title>The republicans are the "enemy".</Title><Msg>These words were straight from the President's mouth a long time ago. Now he tells his sheeple to vote for "revenge". These words from the the most divisive President in our history. Vote this miserable pos out before he divides this country so badly it will never recover.</Msg><Username>plsnomorobama</Username><Timestamp>1352073390656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 18:56:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352076105383-56</Id><Topic><Title>Teachers Should Go For Mitt</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351644405039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Little boy...my wife is a state wide teacher of the year...what, exactly do you do? Growing up would be a start.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1352076105383</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 19:41:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352077195252-57</Id><Topic><Title>Teachers Should Go For Mitt</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351644405039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pure #$%$ rising tide lifts all ships. We can not even afford a small boat.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1352077195252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 19:59:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352077313913-58</Id><Topic><Title>Just Send the Check</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1351995119961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The difference is they paid their share out of their own pocket." No. The difference is they're old. When they were young many many more of them took advantage of a much more robust social safety net than young people experience now. But in the course of their lives they contributed--just as young people who use the safety net will today. You pretend this is a class war to make yourself feel better. But this is a generational war. The boomers stealing from their children and grandchildren, and using the government to do it. Young people have a right to be angry and to ask you to pay for your stuff.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1352077313913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:01:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352077451125-59</Id><Topic><Title>Just Send the Check</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1351995119961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Once you are on the "Dole",you are forever on the dole" Absolutely false. There are work requirements for all safety net programs and lifetime limits. The average length of time that a person receives food stamps is nine months. The idea of cradle to the grave welfare is a lie--part of the class war waged by Republicans on working people.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1352077451125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:04:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352077525143-60</Id><Topic><Title>Just Send the Check</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1351995119961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd prefer you just pay for your stuff.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1352077525143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:05:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352079807163-61</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama's Top 50 AccomplishmentsDuring His 1st term in Office</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1352075809626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 19:36:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This colossal spam political ad got all of 5 thumbs down. What a shame to attribute Paul Revere's name to it.</Msg><Username>dave_martin_2244</Username><Timestamp>1352079807163</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:43:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352084040984-62</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama's Top 50 AccomplishmentsDuring His 1st term in Office</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1352075809626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 19:36:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did you only give yourself three thumbs up? Your post was such a paragon of illiterate, meaningless, drooling idiocy that I was tempted to give you a thumbs up just to confirm for you that nobody can do stupid the way you do stupid. You are an IDIOT. I'm in Europe for the next couple of weeks, so you'll have to stutter along without me. I'll check back in with you in the early weeks of President Obama's second term. Remember to chew and try not to choke to death on a turkey or a ham in the meantime, because that would make me "SAD" (!!). I assume there will be someone nearby to regularly slap the back of your fat, greasy bald head and remind you to breath (??). (grins) You are an IDIOT.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1352084040984</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 21:54:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352085431865-63</Id><Topic><Title>NY Daily News Endorses Mitt Romney</Title><Username>demsdontgetitever</Username><Timestamp>1352061334865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 15:35:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Iowa's largest newspaper has endorsed Mitt Romney, delivering a blow to President Barack Obama, who it endorsed in 2008. The Des Moines Register's editorial board wrote that Obama's "best efforts to resuscitate the stumbling economy have fallen short. Nothing indicates it would change with a second term in the White House." Romney becomes the first Republican the paper has endorsed since 1972. AND THIS: According to Editor &amp; Publisher, Republican Mitt Romney is stunning the newspaper world, earning 112 endorsements from editorial boards around the country compared to the President’s 84. Most large market newspapers like the The New York Times and The Washington Post have stuck with Obama, but have run less than glowing assessments of his accomplishments. So while a newspaper endorsement may not mean what it once did, these conversions could be telling of a national trend.</Msg><Username>coulddobetter</Username><Timestamp>1352085431865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 22:17:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352086473339-64</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama's Top 50 AccomplishmentsDuring His 1st term in Office</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1352075809626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 19:36:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leave me alone LARDQUAKE. I'm packing. Like I told you, you are just going to have to find a new friend (grins) for a couple of weeks (!!).. I know it won't be easy to find someone else who is willing to waste time to help you better yourself, but you'll just have to try. It's "riddance" you fat, festering, illiterate asshat. You are an IDIOT.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1352086473339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 22:34:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352087802581-65</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy creates change for VOTING Dates !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1351910268529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:37:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was a butt baby and that explains it all.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1352087802581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 22:56:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>