<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349011275824-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, Best President Ever!!!!</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1348972931710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NEW ANT and the Grasshopper, Two Versions: The ANT AND THE GRASSHOPPER This one is a little different.... Two Different Versions ... Two Different Morals OLD D VERSION The ant works hard in the withering heat all summer long, building his house and laying up supplies for the winter. The grasshopper thinks the ant is a fool and laughs and dances and plays the summer away. Come winter, the ant is warm and well fed. The grasshopper has no food or shelter, so he dies out in the cold. MORAL OF THE OLD STORY: Be responsible for yourself! MODERN VERSION The ant works hard in the withering heat and the rain all summer long, building his house and laying up supplies for the winter. The grasshopper thinks the ant is a fool and laughs and dances and plays the summer away. Come winter, the shivering grasshopper calls a press conference and demands to know why the ant should be allowed to be warm and well fed while he is cold and starving. CBS, NBC, PBS, CNN, and ABC show up to provide pictures of the shivering grasshopper next to a video of the ant in his comfortable home with a table filled with food. America is stunned by the sharp contrast. How can this be, that in a country of such wealth, this poor grasshopper is allowed to suffer so? Kermit the Frog appears on Oprah with the grasshopper and everybody cries when they sing, 'It's Not Easy Being Green...' Occupy the Anthill stages a demonstration in front of the ant's house where the news stations film the SEIU group singing, We shall overcome. Then Rev. Jeremiah Wright has the group kneel down to pray for the grasshopper's sake, while he damns the ants. President Obama condemns the ant and blames President Bush 43, President Bush 41, President Reagan, Christopher Columbus, and the Pope for the grasshopper's plight.. Nancy Pelosi &amp; Harry Reid exclaim in an interview with Larry King that the ant has gotten rich off the back of the grasshopper, and both call for an immediate tax hike on the ant to make him pay his fair share. Finally, the EEOC drafts the Economic Equity &amp; Anti-Grasshopper Act retroactive to the beginning of the summer. The ant is fined for failing to hire a proportionate number of green bugs and, having nothing left to pay his retroactive taxes, his home is confiscated by the Government Green Czar and given to the grasshopper. The story ends as we see the grasshopper and his free-loading friends finishing up the last bits of the ant's food while the government house he is in, which, as you recall, just happens to be the ant's old house, crumbles around them because the grasshopper doesn't maintain it. The ant has disappeared in the snow, never to be seen again. The grasshopper is found dead in a drug related incident, and the house, now abandoned, is taken over by a gang of spiders who terrorize the ramshackle, once prosperous and peaceful, neighborhood. The entire Nation collapses bringing the rest of the free world with it. MORAL OF THE STORY: Be careful how you vote in 2012.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349011275824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:21:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349014379981-2</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Should The Rich Pay In Taxes ??</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1348871759337</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 18:35:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the long term capital gains tax rate should go back at least to where it was under Reagan, and to where it was prior to the Bush tax cuts: 20%. This is what we would get if we let the Bush tax cuts for the wealthy expire, as Obama is trying to do. It would still be the lowest it has ever been, except for the Bush era, and well below what regular people pay on their salaries, wages and business profits. And remember, capital gains are not subject to the payroll tax.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349014379981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349014731558-3</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Should The Rich Pay In Taxes ??</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1348871759337</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 18:35:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"However, it isn't 47% of America's households." You're right, it's not. 47% of households pay no federal income tax. It is a much smaller number, however, if you include the payroll tax. The 47% also includes seniors and the disabled--people without income for a reason. As the boomers retire, that figure may rise.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349014731558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:18:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349014829209-4</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Should The Rich Pay In Taxes ??</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1348871759337</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 18:35:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, you still haven't answered.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349014829209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349018024220-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, Best President Ever!!!!</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1348972931710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is there one where the grasshopper impersonates the ant?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349018024220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:13:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349018220479-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correcting the falsehoods posted on this board, and pointing out the hypocrisy of the posters, gives me great pleasure. I do find it interesting that you consider facts and data Democratic talking points. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349018220479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:17:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349020851976-7</Id><Topic><Title>Are the killers of the Libyan embassy staff Obama's bin laden</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348624875142</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:01:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congress is calling for more and complete answers about the attack on the U.S. Consulate in Libya -- where four Americans were killed – the administration’s response so far bizarre. It seems that with each passing day, the situation surrounding the administration’s response to the terrorist attack on the U.S. Consulate in Libya becomes more bizarre. The United States Congress and the American people are still waiting to get straight answers. the strike a “deliberate and carefully planned terrorist attack. Rep. Peter King who heads the House Homeland Security Committee, on Friday called for Rice to resign over her "misleading" statements. The consulate, as well as U.S. Ambassador J. Christopher Stevens and the three other Americans killed, did not have adequate security and why FBI investigators have yet to reach the crime scene. Just 18 days ago the administration judged that it was appropriate for our consulate to be lightly guarded and it was safe for our ambassador to come through the city with a small security detail. What has changed in Libya in such a short time that even FBI agents, our most elite investigative personnel, cannot safely enter the city? What has led to such a precipitous decline? America wants answers.</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349020851976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:00:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349021600189-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama keeps secret thousands of Union worker jobs to be lost under his policies</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348962259803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:44:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Defense contractors are bracing for a blow to business. And newly emerging studies are starting to show which states will be hit hardest. For some, the budget ax amounts to billions of dollars in lost income over the next decade. The cuts will cause dramatic program and personnel dislocation. Maryland is one of several states expected to take a heavy hit. The Center for Security Policy recently outlined, state by state, the potential impact of the cuts. The five that would be hit worst are Virginia, California, Texas, Maryland and Florida. In Virginia, defense contractors could be looking at a $9.9 billion hit every year -- that includes the impact of both the so-called "sequestration" cuts and budget cuts already planned that likely will not be averted. Tthat could mean more than 122,000 private-sector jobs. In California, the projected impact is $7.9 billion. In Texas, it's $6.5 billion. The "sequestration" cuts are what lawmakers and contractors are all worried about. They were triggered by lawmakers' failure to reach a deficit-reduction plan on their own, following last summer's deal to raise the nation's debt limit. But if the Obama administrations does nothing, then more than $500 billion in defense cuts over the next decade are set to go into effect. On top of that are another $500 billion in non-defense cuts. The defense portion of that could cost more than 1 million jobs. Contractors are warning that the job-loss potential is no bluff. Sikorsky Aircraft Corp., maker of the Black Hawk helicopter, recently announced the elimination of 570 jobs, from the closure of a plant in upstate New York. And Northrop Grumman recently announced it was cutting 600 aerospace jobs "Who knows what's going to happen," said Scott Pattison, executive director of the National Association of State Budget Officers. "On the defense side, there are quite a number of states that will be impacted." Pattison said the defense cuts won't just hit the companies -- they'll hit, over time, the budgets of the states that rely on tax revenue from those companies. Tough decisions will have to be made at the state level to determine do you raise taxes? Do you continue to cut?" "You want a strong national defense for this country? I need to have some stability," Panetta said Thursday. "That's what I'm asking the Congress to do. Get me some stability with regards to the funding of the Defense Department for the future."</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349021600189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:13:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349022431625-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, Best President Ever!!!!</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1348972931710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very good ricky glad to see you have crawled out to your liberal fantasy world.</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349022431625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349022614421-10</Id><Topic><Title>Are the killers of the Libyan embassy staff Obama's bin laden</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348624875142</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:01:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bin Laden died in 2001. Bush and now the Kenyan kept the fairy tale alive to further their NWO agenda and have an excuse for the massive police state they've built. Suggest too that you do some checking on the "Ambassador" that was killed. Apparently his Ambassadorial duties entailed the delivery of weapons to those that killed Khadaffi. If so, then he got what he deserved.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1349022614421</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:30:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349023414295-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, Best President Ever!!!!</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1348972931710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell us ricky what changed your mind about our worthless president?</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349023414295</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:43:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349030944789-12</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Should The Rich Pay In Taxes ??</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1348871759337</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 18:35:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On further reflection IMHO it should be noted that the notion of taxes may be taken out of our hands by the UN. Recently the UN has noted the need for additional and more predictable financing which has led for a search for new sources. According to the UN, finding these necessary resources will be necessary to achieve the Millennium Development Goals and meet other global challenges, such as addressing climate change. The UN has suggested "various ways to tap resources through international mechanisms, such as coordinated taxes on carbon emissions, air traffic, and financial and currency transactions,” They further state: “Such taxes also make economic sense, as they help stimulate green growth and mitigate financial market instability. In short, such new financing mechanisms will help donor countries overcome their record of broken promises to their own benefit the world at large.” It should be clear (to anyone who has been paying attention over the last few years) that one of the two political parties (through their actions) has embraced the UN goals and has shown that they are more than willing to give the UN athority in matters that were formerly only held by the American people. So in November the choice should be very clear: o Vote for the party that desires to increase the athority of the UN over the United States, or o Vote for the party that doesn't</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349030944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:49:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349033974660-13</Id><Topic><Title>CWA</Title><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1348965079793</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:31:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the union stinks......period</Msg><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1349033974660</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:39:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349034549571-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama keeps secret thousands of Union worker jobs to be lost under his policies</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348962259803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:44:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Also keep in mind ... this is National Defence.” – jonwindandale And keep in mind, Dale, as you’ve been told repeatedly when you get sloppy, here in the United States, we spell it defenSe. Lay off the cheap plonk, mate, eh?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1349034549571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349038090305-15</Id><Topic><Title>CWA</Title><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1348965079793</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:31:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bob, do what I did... give the CWA a list of what needs to be corrected and a time line,, if they don't correct it, drop out and take 10% of your co-workers with you. if enough of us drop out because of unsatisfactory representation, eventually the CWA will see it in their pocket books,, or you could go 1 step further and join a different union to negotiate for you. Good luck.</Msg><Username>dondavid60</Username><Timestamp>1349038090305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349044784393-16</Id><Topic><Title>Like a Replacement Ref, Barry is so Wrong</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348626911097</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:35:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The main Dem handler is dramatically trying to keep debate expectations for Obama low. They say that Mitt will no doubt have some snappy lines. So, how can Barry defend his terrible record. We will have to tune in to see.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1349044784393</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:39:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349047171380-17</Id><Title>Hugo Chavez Endorses Obami</Title><Msg>Known in many parts of the World, as Mr. Anti-American, Chavez's endoresement should get everyone's attention. I guess he's really worried about America becoming energy independent, under a Romney-Ryan administration. Remember, Obama gave him Billions of taxpayer money for Chavez to drill for oil. Now, this oil is being sold to the Chinese. Thanks Obami for putting us further in debt, by borrowing money from China, then funding CHINA'S ECONOMY.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1349047171380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:19:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349050903126-18</Id><Title>Mouchelle Meals Minting Young Republicans</Title><Msg>It's unamious, every kid knows their lunch should be hands off from the Govment. Kids are notoriously bad eaters. So now they go around hungry, and tasty food brought from home has become contrband.. And they aren't happy, they know who brought this pain, Big Butt Mouchelle. They won't forget. I recall, way back in the 6th grade, even then, my friend Dave's tuna sandwiches were very valuable. The cafeteria food was very good, however Dave's Mom's tuna sandwiches were the best.. Dave, skinny as a rail, always brought three tuna sandwiches. Some days he only ate two. He could always sell one to Darrell. Darrell's Mom never packed him a lunch. So Darrell had to eat cafeteria food. It was mostly good, but not like gourmet tuna sandwiches. Dave used Darrell's money to by butter baked cookies, not like the healthy ones Mouchelle is hawking, that taste like cardboard.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1349050903126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 20:21:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349052455616-19</Id><Title>The Romney-Ryan Cuts, I'm in.</Title><Msg>The one that exceited me the most, getting Federal Govment Employess to pay their back taxes. The complete list of cuts is on Mitt's site. Just this one's projected savings, 1 BILLION Dollars. If that don't fire you up, nothing will. Bringing the pain being forced on us by Obami's policies, and forcing it on the deadbeats. These people don't pay, cause they don't have to. Federal workers never spent one day in the unemployment line. Your vote can make them pay. You gotta love Romney-Ryan, a team willing to crack down on this insanity.. Regime change is just weeks away.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1349052455616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 20:47:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>