<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-05"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346840015958-1</Id><Title>Real battle-Cowboys vs Giants</Title><Msg>Line is NY -4 over Dallas! What say you? Politics are boring!</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1346840015958</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 06:13:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346845707021-2</Id><Topic><Title>Real battle-Cowboys vs Giants</Title><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1346840015958</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 06:13:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not betting against NY. Dallas is accumulating a growing history of underachieving. NY by 14. I'll be happy to eat my view, but that's the way I see it.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1346845707021</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 07:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346846214570-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We gather to reclaim the basic bargain that built the largest middle class and the most prosperous nation on Earth – the simple principle that in America, hard work should pay off, responsibility should be rewarded, and each one of us should be able to go as far as our talent and drive take us,” the platform now reads. You might revise it to read: "We gather to reclaim the basic bargain that built the largest middle class and this declining nation – the simple principle that in America, sitting on your tail should pay off, responsibility should not be rewarded, and each one of us should be able to go as far as our government will take us,”</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1346846214570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 07:56:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346847994461-4</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346638429000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:13:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney a successfull business man. Obama never ran anything. you choose</Msg><Username>ls3487</Username><Timestamp>1346847994461</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:26:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346852529477-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"God is no longer part of the Democratic Party platform." Speaking of god, OMG!!!! You people have gone from fabricated distortions to outright pathological prevarication. Is your god the officially sanctioned god of the Republican platform, and, if so, does she tolerate and encourage these continued lies? Just who do you people think you are to call other people godless? That shows true desperation on your part. Perhaps, the DNC platform goes to great lengths to protect the First Amendments doctrine of separation of church and state. To say that Democrats have foregone God, however is as asinine as the Scopes Monkey Trial, to which Clarence Darrow responded, “We have the purpose of preventing bigots and ignoramuses from controlling the education of the United States.” Again, you can lie all you want, but this is straight from the Democratic platform - verbatim: “Faith We honor the central place of faith in our lives. Like our Founders, we believe that our nation, our communities, and our lives are made vastly stronger and richer by faith and the countless acts of justice and mercy it inspires. We believe that change comes not from the top-down, but from the bottom-up, and that few are closer to the people than our churches, synagogues, temples, and mosques. To face today’s challenges–from saving our planet to ending poverty—we need all hands on deck. Faith-based groups are not a replacement for government or secular non-profit programs; rather, they are yet another sector working to meet the challenges of the 21stcentury. We will empower grassroots faith-based and community groups to help meet challenges like poverty, ex-offender reentry, and illiteracy. At the same time, we can ensure that these partnerships do not endanger First Amendment protections – because there is no conflict between supporting faith-based institutions and respecting our Constitution. We will ensure that public funds are not used to proselytize or discriminate. We will also ensure that taxpayer dollars are only used on programs that actually work.” And here are comments from last night’s speakers, all mentioning God. If God punishes liars, you are totally screwed – then again, it can’t get much worse than what you’re already doing here. Julian Castro comments - “As my grandmother got older, she begged my mother to give her grandchildren. She prayed to God for just one grandbaby before she died. You can imagine her excitement when she found out her prayers would be answered—twice over...And I can still remember her... making the sign of the cross behind us, saying, ‘Que dios los bendiga.’ (‘May God bless you.’) A couple of Mondays ago was her first day of pre-K. As we dropped her off, we walked out of the classroom, and I found myself whispering to her, as was once whispered to me, ‘Que dios te bendiga.May God bless you.’ It begins with re-electing Barack Obama. It begins with you. It begins now. May God bless you, and may God bless the United States of America.” Michelle Obama’s closing remarks: “...and we must once again come together and stand together for the man we can trust to keep moving this great country forward…my husband, our President, President Barack Obama.Thank you, God bless you, and God bless America.” Lily Ledbetter’s closing remarks: “Thank you very much. God bless America.” What show were YOU watching last night – the Fox special, “Hank Williams, Jr., Ted Nugent and The Mormon Tabernacle Choir Performing Hits from the Crusades?”</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346852529477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:42:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346856296984-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOD cares even when the Demoncrats don't.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1346856296984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:44:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346856911842-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just who do you people think you are to call other people godless? There is no denying Obama had God deliberately removed from the democrat platform. You try to scold republicans for pointing this out but there is no disputing this fact. Why did Obama have God removed? Maybe Julian Castro didn't get the memo that God is no longer part of the democrat party. Julian Castro is a hypocrite he doesn't follow God's word when it comes to his support abortion and gay marraige.</Msg><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346856911842</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346857032819-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If God punishes liars, you are totally screwed". GOD does punish liars and Obama is the prince of liars. His book, "Dreams from My Father", is a total fabrication to divert attention from the fact that his REAL father was a top Communist of the past century and had a major influence on Obama from age 9 to 18. He mentions "Frank" 22 times in his book but never admits that he was his real father.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1346857032819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346857157111-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is everyone so surprised about these revelations about Obama. Anyone paying attention would have realized his extremism when he started campaigning for president the first time. The American voting public needs to wake up and discern the truth about this guy (i.e., vote for Romney).</Msg><Username>kulglw</Username><Timestamp>1346857157111</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346857332824-10</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346638429000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:13:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney is a REAL Mormon; Obama is a fake Christian to get votes. He is a REAL Muslim.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1346857332824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:02:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346857688164-11</Id><Topic><Title>San Antonio mayor Castro</Title><Username>plsnomorobama</Username><Timestamp>1346805985889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:46:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most hispanics are Catholic, the Catholic church is clear about their anti-abortion stance and the DNC has sent a message they favor abortion. Puzzling how mayor Castro and many hispanics values their political affilation over their faith</Msg><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346857688164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:08:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346858881008-12</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346638429000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:13:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has run this country into the ground.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1346858881008</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:28:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346859464265-13</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346638429000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:13:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BOTH surround themselves with anti-Christians in direct violation of Christian doctrine. Read scripture and see what it says about those that do so.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1346859464265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:37:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346860162485-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we really need change now, and that's a businessman, named mitt.</Msg><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1346860162485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346861082834-15</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Out of the 40 pages that make up the platform, Obama is cited by name on 38 of them. He is cited over 200 times throughout the document. The Democrat party's platform is really Obama's manifesto," Much like the days of Hitler, huh! Romney with his vast business experience knows how to create jobs, Owe-Bama has no clue. His golf game is getting better though!</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1346861082834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:04:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346863949645-16</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Julian Castro is a hypocrite he doesn't follow God's word when it comes to his support abortion and gay marriage…there is no disputing this fact. Why did Obama have God removed?” – the poor soul portraying himself as obombed Well, there was a LOT disputing that fact which I just mentioned, but you simply chose to ignore it. So, let’s see, why did Obama have God removed? I’m really not certain, but let’s venture some guesses: 10. Dress code violation. God forgot his coat and tie. 9. Unruly behavior. God was interrupting the speeches with thunderous applause. 8. Smuggled a flask onto the convention floor for alleged communion service. 7. Upstaged the candidates by riding in on the Democratic donkey. 6. Distracted others in the audience with constant tweetings of forgivness. 5. God admitted he was a Socialist. 4. Was preaching to welfare recipients to “be fruitful and multiply”. 3. Caught performing a faith healing during Obamacare discussion. 2. Ejected from the hall for throwing peanuts at Fox cameraman. And the number one reason Obama had God removed 1.God was making wagers on the floor of the convention that you couldn’t find any reference, anywhere, to “God’s word on abortion or gay marriage.” – and She should know!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1346863949645</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:52:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346865796883-17</Id><Title>Every redesign of this board gets worse</Title><Msg>It is now almost useless. Oh well, it is mostly about politics anyway. I can get plenty of politics elsewhere.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1346865796883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:23:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346866194575-18</Id><Topic><Title>Every redesign of this board gets worse</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1346865796883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. I think they use mokeys for their focus groups.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1346866194575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346866526836-19</Id><Title>$16 Trillion</Title><Msg>Well, we just blew through $16 Trillion. How appropriate that it is achieved during the DNC. Wonder if the Dems will include that milestone among their list of accomplishments during events today?</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1346866526836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:35:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346866618253-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, fess up, which Democratic website did you get this post from because I know you didn't write it yourself, you're not that smart. Also, during his the story about his grandmother's desire for grandkids, did they even mention who the father of the twins is? You're so lost in the muck and mire of the liberal morass you can't see the forest for the trees.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1346866618253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:36:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346868919970-21</Id><Topic><Title>$16 Trillion</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1346866526836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actual , % per President per Snopes. Reagan 189%, 55%GHWB, Clinton 37%, GWB 86%, Obama, 35%</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346868919970</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:15:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346869237067-22</Id><Topic><Title>$16 Trillion</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1346866526836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also, old is what our Founding Father said, and stated in our Constitution. Yet, they are truths, the truth is what we live by, and what we use to make tomorrow's decisions. The truth is the truth, and it never gets too old least we forget.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346869237067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:20:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346869663207-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By God Given. I think you are referring to the help a out of luck American would receive from the GOP if they had their way. Pray to God, and see what he gives you!</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346869663207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346870081772-24</Id><Topic><Title>$16 Trillion</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1346866526836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When the absolute figures are crushing, use percentages. Nice try. Bush added nearly $5 Trillion to the deficit in 8 yrs. That was a killer to be sure. Not to be outdone, Obama added a like amount ($5 Trillion) in less than 4 yrs. How is that for momentum?</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1346870081772</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346877902135-25</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Out of the 40 pages that make up the platform, Obama is cited by name on 38 of them. He is cited over 200 times throughout the document. He's actually cited 141 times, but you can't help lying, can you? This is common practice for the party with an incumbent President. The RNC platform in 2004 cited Bush 250 times. See here: presidency.ucsb.edu/papers_pdf/25850.pdf But I'm sure this fact won't keep you hacks from making the "Obama Manifesto" claim ad infinium. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346877902135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:45:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346878312117-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama didn't have God removed from the Democratic platform any more than Romney had the exception for rape and incest removed from the Republican platform. These things are written from the ground up, and often include things party leaders might not want.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346878312117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:51:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346882557168-27</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why are you so bitter and want America to fail. You clearly don't believe that "hard work should pay off, responsibility should be rewarded." Why</Msg><Username>rcub5d</Username><Timestamp>1346882557168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346884144775-28</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Article 6 Section 3 of our Consitution, Also no religious test shall ever be required as a qualification to any office or public service trust under the United States of America. In fact the words Jeus, Chritianity, Creator, Divine, or God are ever mentioned in our Constitution no not even once.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346884144775</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:29:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346884979116-29</Id><Topic><Title>$16 Trillion</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1346866526836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not true. Not all the money alloted has be spent. The money spent was to get our economey going, pay for two previously unpaid for Wars, plus the unpaid for GOP donut hole. Many other hole in your "facts"</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346884979116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346886783530-30</Id><Title>Wiped my "HANDIE", Pass me a BeeR - Just finished laying my Boss.</Title><Msg>Working HARD - in the DLLSTXNOC! My work appraisal was all Exceptional. Wonder what it would be if anyone besides my bossgirlfreind knew that I cut the red read to the ringer, drank everclear from a flask while reading the News all day while punching the silence button for alarms. I work real HARD ask my boss.</Msg><Username>noccentertimmy</Username><Timestamp>1346886783530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:13:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346888246338-31</Id><Topic><Title>Every redesign of this board gets worse</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1346865796883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just tried to post on another board. Kept asking for my pass word. Gave them the correct one and than nothing. Happened over and over again. Bunch of incompetants. Recently moved from AT&amp;T's area. Spent 4-1/2 hours on the phone and spoke to at least 8-10 people to get phone service, TV and DSL. The two techs that came took about an hour apiece. American business has turned into a nightmare if you want any service from some of them. Never had a problem with AT&amp;T.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1346888246338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:37:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346888330560-32</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tommy Lee Jones said the guy that came down the mountain with the stone slabs did not build a country, people did itperiod!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! God has no business in politics. This country was founded so that everyone can practice their religion and not try to subject people to their to beliefs</Msg><Username>chgjt</Username><Timestamp>1346888330560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:38:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346888378610-33</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean the ones over seas. Like he did in Massachusetts</Msg><Username>chgjt</Username><Timestamp>1346888378610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346888550044-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You nitwits are arguing over something that has no business in politics . Practice your beliefs you heathens because you sure in hell don't express them</Msg><Username>chgjt</Username><Timestamp>1346888550044</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346888737101-35</Id><Title>Lanny Davis, Clinton's Lawyer Goes after Barry</Title><Msg>On Lou Dobbs tonight he had an interview with Davis. He didn't have to, but he did it anyway. Lanny ran down the bad blood between Bill, Hill, and Barry. Just in case someone missed it. He ended by saying it's no way one could argue that they are better off now, than they were 4 years ago. So they should stop arguing the obvious. Can't wait for Bill's speech. Maybe he'll see the light, and be a Republican by 2016. He did say the era of BIG GOVERMENT was over. It's ok, Barry wants REALLY BIG GOVERNMENT. There is a difference. THIS PREZ WANTS TO SUPERSIZE IT.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346888737101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:45:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346889628865-36</Id><Topic><Title>$16 Trillion</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1346866526836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Not true. Not all the money alloted has be spent." Hogwash. Even the Dems are reluctantly acknowledging it today.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1346889628865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346889850065-37</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The change of venue, and the program changes for Barry, has really upset some people. They know the real reason, it's the problem of filling the seats. I guess I'd be mad too. It must of cost a pretty penny to get a hotel room. I'm sure they jacked up the price, and cancellations are limited. WHY COULDN'T THEY HAVE THIS IN A UNION STATE? It's a shame when people think of manufacturing in North Carolina. It's all gone. Barry hates tobacco, though he loves the taxes. If you recall, all the furniture, carpet mills, and clothing factories that have been run out by the unfair, Chinese backed competition. Didn't Barry promise he would do something about that? Yea, run the tape. We know, the Obama's hate NASCAR. Mouchelle get booed there. In hindsight, Charlotte, may have been a bad choice. Just like Barry.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346889850065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:04:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346890089764-38</Id><Topic><Title>The Socialist Party endorses President Obama</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1346578990000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 05:43:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barry will wipe out all the stock market gains in his 2nd term. He'll let Wall Street really knows how he feels. It's time to redistribute some wealth Mouchelle. You go, El Presidente.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346890089764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:08:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346890609453-39</Id><Topic><Title>Maryland's O'Malley tripped up?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346726286000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 22:38:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm serious. When will Biden speak at the Convention? Are they really going to keep this guy under glass for the next couple of months</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346890609453</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:16:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346892154842-40</Id><Topic><Title>Maryland's O'Malley tripped up?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346726286000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 22:38:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>back to some real entertainment!</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1346892154842</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:42:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346898456632-41</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346210905000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 23:28:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>try truth ... who is telling the truth?... let God's word be our truth....Did u read the Mormon bible that teaches Jesus and Satan r brothers? A lie str8 out of Hell... Pastor who endorsed Perry on Friday says Romney is a cultist By Chris Moody | Dr. Robert Jeffress, the influential pastor of a Dallas-based megachurch, offered his formal endorsement of Texas Gov. Rick Perry Friday at the Values Voter Summit in Washington, D.C. Friday, shortly before he explained why Perry's opponent atop the GOP field, former Massachusetts Gov. Mitt Romney, is a cultist. Jeffress introduced Perry before he addressed the annual gathering for social conservatives, making a special point to emphasize Perry's Christian faith--as opposed to Romney's, who a Mormon, which Jeffress said was a "cult." "We understand Mormonism is not Christianity and thus the difference between somebody who's moral and good like Mitt Romney and a true born-again follower of Christ," Jeffress said after Perry's speech, adding that Perry had welcomed his endorsement. "I really think the decision for conservative evangelical Christians right now is going to be, do we prefer somebody who is truly a believer in Jesus Christ, or somebody who is a good moral person but he's a part of a cult." "It's not politically correct to say, but it's true. Mormonism is a cult. And for those reasons, besides Governor Romney's lack of consistency on social issues, I think Rick Perry is the most electable choice among Christian conservatives," he went on. Jeffress' views, however, do not reflect Perry's, his campaign spokesman told The Ticket. "The governor does not believe Mormonism is a cult," Perry Communication Director Mark Miner said in an email. Labeling Mormonism as a cult does not put Jeffress outside of the Southern Baptist mainstream. The denomination officially recognizes Romney's church as a cult, and has done so for years. Jeffress's views also should not come as a surprise to Perry's camp, since the preacher has publicly called Mormonism a cult in the past. "The Southern Baptist Convention has officially labeled Mormonism as a cult, so this is not some right-wing extremist view. It's a view of the largest Protestant denomination in the world," he said. "I think there are a lot of people who will not publicly say that's an issue because they don't want to appear to be bigoted, but for a lot of evangelical Christians, that is a huge issue, even if it's unspoken.</Msg><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346898456632</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:27:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346898724684-42</Id><Title>Hey Demoncrats .... don't lecture to me about paying more taxes</Title><Msg>A-holes Democrats are hypocrites when it comes to paying taxes They say taxes are a patriotic duty. So why did Geithner and Daschle have trouble paying them?</Msg><Username>ru14u23nk</Username><Timestamp>1346898724684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:32:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346899074093-43</Id><Topic><Title>Obama removes God from democrat platform</Title><Username>obombed</Username><Timestamp>1346805849716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So when you demoncrats going to start allowing christians to practice their beliefs? Hmmmm</Msg><Username>ru14u23nk</Username><Timestamp>1346899074093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:37:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346900019997-44</Id><Title>Demoncrats are hypocrites</Title><Msg>I propose all entertainers and wealthy demoncrats give up half their net worth to support their constituents! If they want to give other people's money away they should provide leadership! Correct? A series of tax reforms, generous exemptions and tax credits, including last year’s economic stimulus bill, have dropped millions of Americans from the federal tax rolls. Huge numbers of Americans are simply no longer affected by the federal income tax. The Tax Policy Center projects that 47 percent of all U.S. households will pay no federal income tax for 2009. And, the bottom 40 percent of income earners actually receive a cash payment from the government at tax time. This cash payment is styled as a “refund” but it is actually a net cash transfer from the government--not a refund of taxes actually withheld on income. And for many Americans, this cash transfer from Uncle Sam actually exceeds all federal, state and local taxes that they pay in any form during the year including sales taxes and social security taxes. Of course, we are accustomed to the idea that high income earners pay more in taxes both in absolute terms and as a percentage of their incomes. But taxing only the top half of a society is not normal progressive taxation. Instead, the recent changes to our tax system are an example of politicians using the tax code for their own political ends. In this case, the so-called progressive Democratic politicians are using “tax reform” to grow their political base by creating a group of Americans that pay no federal income tax The people who don’t pay federal income taxes are, as the phrase goes, “rational economic actors” just as much as anyone. Like all people, non-taxpayers respond to economic incentives. Their demand for entitlements and government programs is naturally insatiable because they don’t care at all about the cost. Non-taxpayers don’t have any “skin in the game” and are completely indifferent to the government raising income taxes. So they will always support increasing government programs as a long as they get even a small benefit from them because it does not cost them a cent. It’s also perfectly rational for non-taxpayers to support politicians who favor more spending. Non-taxpayers get something for nothing, at least until the country becomes insolvent.</Msg><Username>ru14u23nk</Username><Timestamp>1346900019997</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:53:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346900725520-45</Id><Topic><Title>San Antonio mayor Castro</Title><Username>plsnomorobama</Username><Timestamp>1346805985889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:46:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>reason Obama picked Castro to speak- this guy was raised in a home that harbored a lot of anti-American sentiment he draws political inspiration from his mother – who is a member of a very radical movement. The 37-year-old Hispanic mayor told New York Times Magazine that upon being elected mayor in 2009 he promptly hung in his private office a La Raza (meaning "the race") poster. Maria del Rosario Castro, the mother of San Antonio Mayor Julian Castro, told New York Times Magazine when speaking about a historic Ameican landmark “I can truly say that I hate that place and everything it stands for.”</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1346900725520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:05:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>