<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-11"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344694485000-1</Id><Title>ROMNEY-RYAN</Title><Msg>Let the fun begin.</Msg><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1344694485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:14:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344695603000-2</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY-RYAN</Title><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1344694485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WE NEED TO BE HEARD!!! I am a member of golf's lower 99%. I am an indifferent golfer, and there's no way I could ever make it to the professional level. I will never put in the practice time to be the best. I will never have the shots, skills, or mental toughness to make it in the sport. I just never felt like working all that hard at it. However, I am a part of the golfing community and, as such, feel I should be paid by the top 1% of golfers for what I do. It isn't fair that those players who have worked harder, have studied the game, have better equipment and are more skilled and dedicated should make all that BIG money. Where's my share? I'm a Victim! The top 1% should pay for my club memberships and green fees and lessons, buy me new clubs, balls, clothes and shoes, and pay me some of their winnings. They can afford it. They are "The Rich". The whole system should be changed to accommodate people like me. I think we should get together and occupy a golf course and demand that those who are better at what they do, pay for us who generally suck. Whining should get us something - maybe we'll make the cover of Time Magazine, garnish some public sympathy. Heck, during this election year we may even get a law or two passed by legislators who want our votes. PS. Don't mention this to tennis players. We thought of it first.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1344695603000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:33:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344695849000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Economic Fairness in Obummer's 2nd Term</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1344517169000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 08:59:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How's the only black man in America driving a Prius doing?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1344695849000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:37:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344696269000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Strike in DIST 9?</Title><Username>josieinib</Username><Timestamp>1344298108000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 20:08:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a fair assessment. It's my opinion as well that Mobility depends on the legacy landline facilities- otherwise, anyone could do it....and do it better. T's top-heavy, overcompensated, clawback free management structure still lives in the 19th century- and only survives by virtue of the work done by predecessors who better understood and better managed T's landline backbone.</Msg><Username>n1tr0x3n</Username><Timestamp>1344696269000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:44:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344700274000-5</Id><Title>GREAT CHOICE...</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan will be the quintessential Americans like George Patton and Joe DiMaggio. They will attack the usurping tyrant boldly on all fronts and at all times and at this this they will not flag nor fail. They will never succumb to the siren call of the regime’s propaganda ministers that will permeate the television waves. They will not bargain with this tyrant and his propaganda ministers and gutter rats. They will not try to reason with them as the tyrant and his gaggle of lying lackeys and dirty dingbats will grant no quarter for them and if they can, they will destroy them and their families and all of America without remorse. Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan will follow the tyrant Hussein Louie Benito Hugo Isuzu Obama to the inmost recesses of his mind and make him fear and dread the very sight and sound of them. Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan will never let up and they will make the Child Emperor’s fear of them permeate his thoughts from when he rises in the morning until he retires at night, where he will be allowed only a brief respite in between his nightmares as his day of reckoning approaches. they will make him howl.</Msg><Username>cavuto_jr</Username><Timestamp>1344700274000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344701433000-6</Id><Topic><Title>GREAT CHOICE...</Title><Username>cavuto_jr</Username><Timestamp>1344700274000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm from Wisconsin and have met Paul. He is great in all areas. I'm afraid however that we've gone beyond the tipping point. Romney/Ryan are behind in the polls right now.</Msg><Username>crazyhorse1786</Username><Timestamp>1344701433000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344704042000-7</Id><Topic><Title>GREAT CHOICE...</Title><Username>cavuto_jr</Username><Timestamp>1344700274000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't wait to see a Paul Ryan/Joe Biden debate. It would only be better if it was with West Coast Nancy.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344704042000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344708031000-8</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY-RYAN</Title><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1344694485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>B.... S.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1344708031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:00:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344726697000-9</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY-RYAN</Title><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1344694485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go ahead many believe you golfers are lazy ....'s the course will grow up in weeds, and revert to a natural habitat.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1344726697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 19:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>