<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-29"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351488515256-1</Id><Topic><Title>I've never seen that level of corruption on any scale!</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351476541727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 22:09:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is the most corrupted man in the Free World. He is America's version of the betrayer of Jesus!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351488515256</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 01:28:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351517685450-2</Id><Topic><Title>More from The GOP War on Women...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351112943088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Echo is paid to be here.</Msg><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1351517685450</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:34:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351519328710-3</Id><Topic><Title>How many van loads of Somalians does it take to change the results in Ohio?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351369866428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:31:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>45,000 X 40%= 18,000, 18,000/15 per van(maxi vans assumed)= 1,200 van loads of Somalians to vote for Obama to change the results in his favor.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351519328710</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:02:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351519693161-4</Id><Topic><Title>How many van loads of Somalians does it take to change the results in Ohio?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351369866428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:31:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oops, forgot those 40% of Somalians are citizens, they can vote how they want unless you feel you rwnj's should impose your views on them. Oops, thought you rwnj's didn't like others imposing their views on you, so must be you would never do that to others, either. Oops, wrong, rwnj's do impose their views without liking others to impose on them. Oh well</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351519693161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:08:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351521285221-5</Id><Topic><Title>More from The GOP War on Women...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351112943088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is from this Sunday's Parade Magazine, the Ask Marilyn column. I think if perfectly describes echo/Ricky, etc. The question: Why do people believe something to be true about a political figure or party, even after they see credible evidence to the Contrary? Answer: You've just stated a fine example of bias, probably caused by an aversion to accepting the likelihood that one can be wrong. Why, if you're wrong about one thing, you might be wrong about other things. It's a scary thought all right, especially if you've built your attitude about life around the philosophy of a particular party. Some people are so biased that they tend to agree with most or all of the positions taken by their own parties, and if you agree with a position taken by a different party, they assume you must be a member of the opposing party. That the epitome of political bias. Meet the echo twins.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1351521285221</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:34:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351521625421-6</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins</Title><Username>freakedout35</Username><Timestamp>1351454377244</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:59:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Barack Hussein Obama, is sitting right in front of you. A true Christian he is." Really? Then to what church does he claim membership and attend? The last one he attended regularly was headed by an out-and-out racist, radical, nut job preacher. Most of his ministering brethren likely would not consider Rev. Wright a true Christian. You’ve been paying way too much attention to MSM sound bites. If you tried reading more than a paragraph at a time and you might learn something.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1351521625421</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351521859302-7</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (cont.)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351300725933</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 21:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps Mr. Popper's quote should be altered a bit to best desciribe your political philosophy echo. Perhaps it shoud read “True ignorance is not the absence of knowledge, but the refusal to acknowledge it.”</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1351521859302</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351522105867-8</Id><Title>Another Fine Weekend...</Title><Msg>... Information you know you can trust…from jon… a fellow American and outstanding, unbiased citizen, who is a devoted family man and involved member of the community, proud of his self-sacrifice with his relentless volunteer efforts each weekend to the many charitable organizations with which he is involved…just like many of you out there who have enjoyed the weekend with friends, family and …uh, oh, wait a minute here. How many of you were preoccupied over the weekend, with making 36 posts to a stock message board?…that’s right…count ‘em…36. That’s our boy, jon. Let’s see here: Friday night: 8 posts, from about 6:00 p.m. (with more earlier in the day) until about 10:30…hmmm, that puts a pretty good dent in Friday night, although, maybe he’s a night owl. Saturday: back at it at 9:45 a.m., and I doubt the family did much in the way of farmer’s markets, or other autumn events, because from 10 in the morning, until past midnight, jon was very busy, thinking up, putting into words and otherwise creating another 13 posts…that’s right, thirteen, more. Note, that having posted 13 posts over the course of 14 hours, one might have thought he’d have time to spell-check some of them…but, well, that’s jon…writing to the level of the Tea Partiers. Now, Sunday morning, he probably was in church, where he both sings Soprano in the choir, and is the church’s oldest alter-boy. However, he was back at his posting duties by about 3:00, where for the next 8 hours he churned out another 15 posts…that’s right, fifteen more until 11:00 p.m. And keep in mind, all of these are strictly with the retarded jon alias. So, with all of the others, he probably didn’t have time to even eat over the weekend, much less say hello to his family. I suppose many of you find it extremely odd, that a grown man with a family spends each and every weekend sending out anonymous messages to complete strangers. But remember…jon is here only for your best interest. The information he shares with you is timely, relevant and tremendously useful. For example, a few highlights from his 36 weekend posts. “Well .. We elected a ‘cult’ Moos-lem (in denial)” “…try going to a REAL psyciatrist (sic)” (Hey, jon, try going to a REAL dictionary) “…youz is really dum as a doe knob” “how many were ‘waived’ off of the Terrorist Watch List .. so they could come over here and ‘vote’ for Obammy” “…go back to your basement and talk to that "empty chair" (ya chithead)” “remember, racist blame (??) will get you racism back in your face ... I'm your example !!” “…that's fine as longs as no ‘chiggas’ like you come floating by” “ya little two faced jerk !!” “…quit acting like a used rubber ... (snark)” “It's that little glossy ‘comic book’…in two languages (Arabic &amp; Kenyan) - I even had my Moos-lem Brotherhood rush the printing - Signed - B. H. Obammy” “Obama really sucks !!” Jon, you are a true scholar and valuable asset to undecided voters everywhere. Keep up these fine weekend efforts. (Don’t look now, but your family abandoned you several months ago, although I’m certain you’ve been too busy posting to notice. All kidding aside, you probably are, in fact, influencing some voters… influencing them to ask why on earth would they want ignorant, racist fools like you, who have absolutely no life, to be in charge of this country. Maybe next week, you could take some time off…go mow a few lawns, make a few bucks, and go out and get yourself the spelling version of Hooked on Phonics. It’ll be a nice change of pace for you…you’re obviously cracking under the pressure of all that cubicle stress.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351522105867</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:48:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351522447624-9</Id><Topic><Title>Another Fine Weekend...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351522105867</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:48:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suppose many of you find it extremely odd, that a grown man with a family spends each and every weekend sending out anonymous messages to complete strangers. And I suppose that you assume a grown man that spends his time tracking the posts of other anonymous messages is completely sane and rational?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1351522447624</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:54:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351523022729-10</Id><Topic><Title>More from The GOP War on Women...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351112943088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “This is from this Sunday's Parade Magazine, the Ask Marilyn column.” Whoa, winny, I’m so happy to see you’ve branched out from your normal Fox diet to get some additional, intellectually stimulating input from another credible source. Ask Marilyn, huh? Can’t wait to see Miss Manners’ take on the subject. So, you think The New York Times is biased, but you get your news from Ask Marilyn???? I would think that would be troublesome to sane people. Sadly, I didn’t catch the article, but I’d be willing to bet she was talking about you birthers.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351523022729</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 11:03:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351530435249-11</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins</Title><Username>freakedout35</Username><Timestamp>1351454377244</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:59:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and the other atheists who post on this MB do not have any business telling us who to choose based on religion. BO sat in the pew of a church for 20 years listening to a guy who preached racisms and hatred.</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1351530435249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:07:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351531591967-12</Id><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Msg>God bless Tyrone Woods and his family, a true American hero. His story should be told loudly and often, and he should never be forgotten. The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351534059372-13</Id><Topic><Title>Another Fine Weekend...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351522105867</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:48:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Strange things happen in war!</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1351534059372</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:07:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351534425725-14</Id><Title>If Obama had a daughter</Title><Msg>It would look like Sandy. Oh, wait he has daughters. If Obama had an economic plan it would look like Sandy.</Msg><Username>crazyhorse1786</Username><Timestamp>1351534425725</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:13:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351534744717-15</Id><Topic><Title>How many van loads of Somalians does it take to change the results in Ohio?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351369866428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:31:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oops, forgot those 40% of Somalians are citizens, they can vote how they want unless you feel you rwnj's should impose your views on them. Oops, thought you rwnj's didn't like others imposing their views on you, so must be you would never do that to others, either. Oops, wrong, rwnj's do impose their views without liking others to impose on them. Oh well</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351534744717</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:19:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351535362722-16</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one in romney's family has served this country in the military, they belong to a polygamy first cult. romeny went to france and cheered the other boys his age going to Vietnam to die by the tens of thousands. that's a coward if there ever was one, in action. So sorry if the truth rains on your parade of lies about a man who makes this country safer, by his actions. Now that's a great American hero, President Obama.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351535362722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:29:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351538197278-17</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear peppeek, I must admit (after reading your post) that my first instinct was to point out how sad and pathetic I find you and people like you, but then I thought about the words that I heard from Tyrone's father George (over the weekend) where instead of lashing out with vitreal or blame, Mr. Woods chose to forgive those who were responsible for the death of his son and pray for a change in their hearts. So like Mr. Woods I choose to forgive you and people like you for your insensitivity and lack of compassion for your fellow man, and pray that God someday will change your heart and help you see the error of your ways. God Bless The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351538197278</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:16:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351538696749-18</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whatsamatter I been raining on your romeny love parade too much?. I don't want your prayers, pray for romney that he listens to Jeezus, pays caesar his taxes, and takes to heart a rich man no more will get to heaven than a camel can go through the eye of a needle..</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351538696749</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:24:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351538798374-19</Id><Topic><Title>ATT retiree benefits</Title><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1343908864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A follow-up on my original post......I retired from ATT- in Ohio.-2012. Our meeting w/ the union informed us that NOTHING is in place for our healthcare in 2014- the company and the union have agreed to "TALK" about it next fall (2013). How do you think that will go with the contract settled and signed????? Do you really think that any employees on the payroll will stand up for retirees? Not a chance. It's a my, me, world, But wait till they get to retirement age, (if they make it that far). My worst case worry is no benefits or premiums that are so high that your pension cannot cover them. Put your house and money in a trust, go to the hospital like 3/4 of the population, and pay $10 a month toward your bill.......you will get the same care with insurance or no money..... Worked all those years and now they screw us.... cancel your u-verse, landline, and cell/dsl. Sign up with another company. Why support them when they don't live up to the promises of benefits???</Msg><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1351538798374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:26:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351540860156-20</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “God bless Tyrone Woods and his family, a true American hero. His story should be told loudly and often, and he should never be forgotten.” - gremlin I suppose Sean Smith, Glen Doherty, Ambassador Stevens and the two other Americans and seven Libyans injured in the attack are of no concern to you because their relatives haven’t attempted to politicize the events like disgusting people like you have done. Oh, wait a minute, some of them did say something…I believe we covered that here already. I guess you conveniently missed it with your Rush Limbaugh reposts.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351540860156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:01:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351541023823-21</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: Tyrone's father's name is Charles my error</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351541023823</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:03:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351541647383-22</Id><Topic><Title>How many van loads of Somalians does it take to change the results in Ohio?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351369866428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:31:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"YES, I do feel that fraudulant, mis-leading people "like you" .. should squalor in their own "POOP" you taliking again? most excellent opinions, tells a lot about character and maturity. The van loads of Somalians are fraudulent? I thought they were real. You're a 63 yr old angry red faced guy? That's too bad. I'm older than you and much more relaxed. Settle down it isn't good for the pressure. You'll need your ObamaCare. That's funny.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351541647383</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:14:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351542606308-23</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"their relatives haven’t attempted to politicize the events like disgusting people like you have done" It's not just politics Echo: 10/26/2012 "Earlier this month, after President Obama told Comedy Central’s Jon Stewart, ”If four Americans get killed, it’s not optimal,” the mother of Libya victim Sean Smith, angrily replied, “My son is NOT very optimal… he is very dead.” Pat Smith, 72, went on to say more in her interview with The Daily Mail: “It’s insensitive to say my son is not very optimal – he is also very dead. I’ve not been ‘optimal’ since he died and the past few weeks have been pure hell. I am still waiting for the truth to come out and I still want to know the truth. I’m finally starting to get some answers but I won’t give up. ‘There’s a lot of stupid things that have been said"</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1351542606308</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:30:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351545289057-24</Id><Topic><Title>How many van loads of Somalians does it take to change the results in Ohio?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351369866428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:31:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did Bush the younger and Karl Rove reach across the aisle? No</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1351545289057</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:14:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351548100122-25</Id><Title>Air Force 1 was seen in new close up photos</Title><Msg>two days ago, the pics show Obama seeding clouds by dumping bags out of the cargo bays. On his ring it was zoomed in to see the arabic words, I love my birthplace Kenya. He'll try anything that guy. I got this from a good source.</Msg><Username>lithiumniobate</Username><Timestamp>1351548100122</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:01:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351549242002-26</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does Romney's family military duties have to do with the President and the State Department lying to cover of a total screw up? What does any part of your post have to do with the ongoing cover up?</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1351549242002</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:20:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351552679448-27</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no cover up, never has been, never will be, it's in your imagination. My accurate statement pertains to the subject of this thread, obviously. Romney said the President said spontaneous demonstration in the rose garden, which of course was false and a complete error. Lie is what Romney did. That's your boy. Not Romney's family military duties, but their lack of miltary service duty. Yet Romney seems to promote war and others going into war.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351552679448</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 19:17:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351554241627-28</Id><Topic><Title>About Retiree Benefits</Title><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1351472730322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 21:05:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Military retirees also must apply for Medicare A and B</Msg><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1351554241627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 19:44:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351561794028-29</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There is no cover up, never has been, never will be, it's in your imagination." If so, please try to explain why Ambassador Rice who, by the way, is a member of Obama's Cabinet (I'll assume you know what that means) went on 5 networks saying it was not a terrorist attack several days after Obama says he said it was. And for the record, if you listen carefully to what the President said in the Rose Garden he did not say DIRECTLY that IT was a terrorist attack. Rice is not some underling 20 levels below the President who is simply out of control. She was sent out on the media circuit to get the "it wasn't a terrotist attack" message out and she was a good soldier. So, someone of the two if not both are full of it or are simply inept and it doesn't take an overly bright person to clearly see it. Believe what you like, but I'm predicting some heads are going to roll before this one is over. The loved ones of these dead heros are still looking for answers and they are not going to be bought off.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1351561794028</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 21:49:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351564137294-30</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LEAVE HER ALONE! PeepPeep is probably someones grandmother! She can't help herself! It's all Bushes fault! Just ask PeepPeep. Barry is a nice man, he wants to give you things, like health care and free food, unemployment money Chevy Volts Cell phones</Msg><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1351564137294</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:28:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351564514347-31</Id><Title>I have to laugh,</Title><Msg>because a boob on this board thinks he can intimidate me by posting certain personal facts. I mentioned once that doing things like that is a two way street. I havn't even bothered to copy his handle down it scares me so much. But, I guarantee that if any real problem comes from his comments or snooping he, she? will be talking to a very good attorney. Or quite possibly someone else.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564514347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:35:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351564720588-32</Id><Title>I have to laugh</Title><Msg>Someone thinks they can scare me by posting certain personal things on this board. It won't work friend and if any real problem come from it you will be talking to a very good lawyer. Remember that sort of thing is a two way street.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564720588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351564780643-33</Id><Title>testing</Title><Msg>testing</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351564780643</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:39:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351569510178-34</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A great many like him have been sacrificed on the altar by the "New World Odor" crowd. It's time it changed.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351569510178</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 23:58:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>