<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347250981166-1</Id><Topic><Title>Donna Brazile face of the democratic party</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347201077813</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 10:31:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you see the women at the dnc? they are not interested in men. the democrat party is largely just a collection of bitter old angry lesbians screeching like nails dragged accross a chalk board.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347250981166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 00:23:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347278164517-2</Id><Title>Romney Only Tweak Obama Care NOW</Title><Msg>I feel companies knowing this alone, would be a good beginning. This plus some tax loop hole closings would get the economy going. Just, knowing a version of Obama Care will be their should really help companies, including AT&amp;T, and it's customers. The rest wil be good old Capitalism, their are companies with plans to start, grow, develop. Best get it done before the other guy does.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1347278164517</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 07:56:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347278257412-3</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, Slick Willie was Impeached !</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1347243288590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 22:14:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ask the bounce he gave Obama. What other off base opionions do you have?</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1347278257412</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 07:57:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347279777719-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama today again admits his desire to raise taxes</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347219657100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"be specific about what you would cut to balance the budget" EPA, NPR, NEA to begin with Oh, G-O-O-O-O-O-D answer!!!!! EPA? Good idea. Let’s just turn the environment over to you corporate denizens of the world who have done such a terrific job self-regulating the planet into a cesspool for quick profit. No big deal. Global warming is a socialist conspiracy, anyhow. NPR? Well, the Federal, State and local government funding of NPR’s budget is less than 5%. Of course when all you watch is FOX news and Real Housewives with Toddlers &amp; Tiaras from the Jersey Shore home of Jerry Springer &amp; the Kardashians, you, no doubt won’t miss NPR. The N.E.A.? Another splendid idea. In order to miss the NEA, one would have had to had some encounter with some rudimentary elements of education at some point in his life. Obviously, that isn’t you – but let’s privatize education so only the rich learn anything, and keep the working class ignorant so they’ll believe nonsense from fools like you.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347279777719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 08:22:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347288332521-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama today again admits his desire to raise taxes</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347219657100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama signed a government takeover of healthcare into law. Below is a list of new boards and commissions created in the bill: 1. Grant program for consumer assistance offices (Section 1002, p. 37) 2. Grant program for states to monitor premium increases (Section 1003, p. 42) 3. Committee to review administrative simplification standards (Section 1104, p. 71) 4. Demonstration program for state wellness programs (Section 1201, p. 93) 5. Grant program to establish state Exchanges (Section 1311(a), p. 130) 6. State American Health Benefit Exchanges (Section 1311(b), p. 131) 7. Exchange grants to establish consumer navigator programs (Section 1311(i), p. 150) 8. Grant program for state cooperatives (Section 1322, p. 169) 9. Advisory board for state cooperatives (Section 1322(b)(3), p. 173) 10. Private purchasing council for state cooperatives (Section 1322(d), p. 177) 11. State basic health plan programs (Section 1331, p. 201) 12. State-based reinsurance program (Section 1341, p. 226) 13. Program of risk corridors for individual and small group markets (Section 1342, p. 233) 14. Program to determine eligibility for Exchange participation (Section 1411, p. 267) 15. Program for advance determination of tax credit eligibility (Section 1412, p. 288) 16. Grant program to implement health IT enrollment standards (Section 1561, p. 370) 17. Federal Coordinated Health Care Office for dual eligible beneficiaries (Section 2602, p. 512) 18. Medicaid quality measurement program (Section 2701, p. 518) 19. Medicaid health home program for people with chronic conditions, and grants for planning same (Section 2703, p. 524) 20. Medicaid demonstration project to evaluate bundled payments (Section 2704, p. 532) 21. Medicaid demonstration project for global payment system (Section 2705, p. 536) 22. Medicaid demonstration project for accountable care organizations (Section 2706, p. 538) 23. Medicaid demonstration project for emergency psychiatric care (Section 2707, p. 540) 24. Grant program for delivery of services to individuals with postpartum depression (Section 2952(b), p. 591) 25. State allotments for grants to promote personal responsibility education programs (Section 2953, p. 596) 26. Medicare value-based purchasing program (Section 3001(a), p. 613) 27. Medicare value-based purchasing demonstration program for critical access hospitals (Section 3001(b), p. 637) 28. Medicare value-based purchasing program for skilled nursing facilities (Section 3006(a), p. 666) 29. Medicare value-based purchasing program for home health agencies (Section 3006(b), p. 668) 30. Interagency Working Group on Health Care Quality (Section 3012, p. 688) 31. Grant program to develop health care quality measures (Section 3013, p. 693) 32. Center for Medicare and Medicaid Innovation (Section 3021, p. 712) 33. Medicare shared savings program (Section 3022, p. 728) 34. Medicare pilot program on payment bundling (Section 3023, p. 739) 35. Independence at home medical practice demonstration program (Section 3024, p. 752) 36. Program for use of patient safety organizations to reduce hospital readmission rates (Section 3025(b), p. 775) 37. Community-based care transitions program (Section 3026, p. 776) 38. Demonstration project for payment of complex diagnostic laboratory tests (Section 3113, p. 800) 39. Medicare hospice concurrent care demonstration project (Section 3140, p. 850) 40. Independent Payment Advisory Board (Section 3403, p. 982) 41. Consumer Advisory Council for Independent Payment Advisory Board (Section 3403, p. 1027) 42. Grant program for technical assistance to providers implementing health quality practices (Section 3501, p. 1043) 43. Grant program to establish interdisciplinary health teams (Section 3502, p. 1048) 44. Grant program to implement medication therapy management (Section 3503, p. 1055) 45. Grant program to support emergency care pilot programs (Section 3504, p. 1061) 46. Grant program to promote universal access to trauma services (Section 3505(b), p. 1081) 47. Grant program to develop and promote shared decision-making aids (Section 3506, p. 1088) 48. Grant program to support implementation of shared decision-making (Section 3506, p. 1091) 49. Grant program to integrate quality improvement in clinical education (Section 3508, p. 1095) 50. Health and Human Services Coordinating Committee on Women?s Health (Section 3509(a), p. 1098) 51. Centers for Disease Control Office of Women?s Health (Section 3509(b), p. 1102) 52. Agency for Healthcare Research and Quality Office of Women?s Health (Section 3509(e), p. 1105) 53. Health Resources and Services Administration Office of Women?s Health (Section 3509(f), p. 1106) 54. Food and Drug Administration Office of Women?s Health (Section 3509(g), p. 1109) 55. National Prevention, Health Promotion, and Public Health Council (Section 4001, p. 1114) 56. Advisory Group on Prevention, Health Promotion, and Integrative and Public Health (Section 4001(f), p. 1117) 57. Prevention and Public Health Fund (Section 4002, p. 1121) 58. Community Preventive Services Task Force (Section 4003(b), p. 1126) 59. Grant program to support school-based health centers (Section 4101, p. 1135) 60. Grant program to promote research-based dental caries disease management (Section 4102, p. 1147) 61. Grant program for States to prevent chronic disease in Medicaid beneficiaries (Section 4108, p. 1174) 62. Community transformation grants (Section 4201, p. 1182) 63. Grant program to provide public health interventions (Section 4202, p. 1188) 64. Demonstration program of grants to improve child immunization rates (Section 4204(b), p. 1200) 65. Pilot program for risk-factor assessments provided through community health centers (Section 4206, p. 1215) 66. Grant program to increase epidemiology and laboratory capacity (Section 4304, p. 1233) 67. Interagency Pain Research Coordinating Committee (Section 4305, p. 1238) 68. National Health Care Workforce Commission (Section 5101, p. 1256) 69. Grant program to plan health care workforce development activities (Section 5102(c), p. 1275) 70. Grant program to implement health care workforce development activities (Section 5102(d), p. 1279) 71. Pediatric specialty loan repayment program (Section 5203, p. 1295) 72. Public Health Workforce Loan Repayment Program (Section 5204, p. 1300) 73. Allied Health Loan Forgiveness Program (Section 5205, p. 1305) 74. Grant program to provide mid-career training for health professionals (Section 5206, p. 1307) 75. Grant program to fund nurse-managed health clinics (Section 5208, p. 1310) 76. Grant program to support primary care training programs (Section 5301, p. 1315) 77. Grant program to fund training for direct care workers (Section 5302, p. 1322) 78. Grant program to develop dental training programs (Section 5303, p. 1325) 79. Demonstration program to increase access to dental health care in underserved communities (Section 5304, p. 1331) 80. Grant program to promote geriatric education centers (Section 5305, p. 1334) 81. Grant program to promote health professionals entering geriatrics (Section 5305, p. 1339) 82. Grant program to promote training in mental and behavioral health (Section 5306, p. 1344) 83. Grant program to promote nurse retention programs (Section 5309, p. 1354) 84. Student loan forgiveness for nursing school faculty (Section 5311(b), p. 1360) 85. Grant program to promote positive health behaviors and outcomes (Section 5313, p. 1364) 86. Public Health Sciences Track for medical students (Section 5315, p. 1372) 87. Primary Care Extension Program to educate providers (Section 5405, p. 1404) 88. Grant program for demonstration projects to address health workforce shortage needs (Section 5507, p. 1442) 89. Grant program for demonstration projects to develop training programs for home health aides (Section 5507, p. 1447) 90. Grant program to establish new primary care residency programs (Section 5508(a), p. 1458) 91. Program of payments to teaching health centers that sponsor medical residency training (Section 5508(c), p. 1462) 92. Graduate nurse education demonstration program (Section 5509, p. 1472) 93. Grant program to establish demonstration projects for community-based mental health settings (Section 5604, p. 1486) 94. Commission on Key National Indicators (Section 5605, p. 1489) 95. Quality assurance and performance improvement program for skilled nursing facilities (Section 6102, p. 1554) 96. Special focus facility program for skilled nursing facilities (Section 6103(a)(3), p. 1561) 97. Special focus facility program for nursing facilities (Section 6103(b)(3), p. 1568) 98. National independent monitor pilot program for skilled nursing facilities and nursing facilities (Section 6112, p. 1589) 99. Demonstration projects for nursing facilities involved in the culture change movement (Section 6114, p. 1597) 100. Patient-Centered Outcomes Research Institute (Section 6301, p. 1619) 101. Standing methodology committee for Patient-Centered Outcomes Research Institute (Section 6301, p. 1629) 102. Board of Governors for Patient-Centered Outcomes Research Institute (Section 6301, p. 1638) 103. Patient-Centered Outcomes Research Trust Fund (Section 6301(e), p. 1656) 104. Elder Justice Coordinating Council (Section 6703, p. 1773) 105. Advisory Board on Elder Abuse, Neglect, and Exploitation (Section 6703, p. 1776) 106. Grant program to create elder abuse forensic centers (Section 6703, p. 1783) 107. Grant program to promote continuing education for long-term care staffers (Section 6703, p. 1787) 108. Grant program to improve management practices and training (Section 6703, p. 1788) 109. Grant program to subsidize costs of electronic health records (Section 6703, p. 1791) 110. Grant program to promote adult protective services (Section 6703, p. 1796) 111. Grant program to conduct elder abuse detection and prevention (Section 6703, p. 1798) 112. Grant program to support long-term care ombudsmen (Section 6703, p. 1800) 113. National Training Institute for long-term care surveyors (Section 6703, p. 1806) 114. Grant program to fund State surveys of long-term care residences (Section 6703, p. 1809) 115. CLASS Independence Fund (Section 8002, p. 1926) 116. CLASS Independence Fund Board of Trustees (Section 8002, p. 1927) 117. CLASS Independence Advisory Council (Section 8002, p. 1931) 118. Personal Care Attendants Workforce Advisory Panel (Section 8002(c), p. 1938) 119. Multi-state health plans offered by Office of Personnel Management (Section 10104(p), p. 2086) 120. Advisory board for multi-state health plans (Section 10104(p), p. 2094) 121. Pregnancy Assistance Fund (Section 10212, p. 2164) 122. Value-based purchasing program for ambulatory surgical centers (Section 10301, p. 2176) 123. Demonstration project for payment adjustments to home health services (Section 10315, p. 2200) 124. Pilot program for care of individuals in environmental emergency declaration areas (Section 10323, p. 2223) 125. Grant program to screen at-risk individuals for environmental health conditions (Section 10323(b), p. 2231) 126. Pilot programs to implement value-based purchasing (Section 10326, p. 2242) 127. Grant program to support community-based collaborative care networks (Section 10333, p. 2265) 128. Centers for Disease Control Office of Minority Health (Section 10334, p. 2272) 129. Health Resources and Services Administration Office of Minority Health (Section 10334, p. 2272) 130. Substance Abuse and Mental Health Services Administration Office of Minority Health (Section 10334, p. 2272) 131. Agency for Healthcare Research and Quality Office of Minority Health (Section 10334, p. 2272) 132. Food and Drug Administration Office of Minority Health (Section 10334, p. 2272) 133. Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services Office of Minority Health (Section 10334, p. 2272) 134. Grant program to promote small business wellness programs (Section 10408, p. 2285) 135. Cures Acceleration Network (Section 10409, p. 2289) 136. Cures Acceleration Network Review Board (Section 10409, p. 2291) 137. Grant program for Cures Acceleration Network (Section 10409, p. 2297) 138. Grant program to promote centers of excellence for depression (Section 10410, p. 2304) 139. Advisory committee for young women?s breast health awareness education campaign (Section 10413, p. 2322) 140. Grant program to provide assistance to provide information to young women with breast cancer (Section 10413, p. 2326) 141. Interagency Access to Health Care in Alaska Task Force (Section 10501, p. 2329) 142. Grant program to train nurse practitioners as primary care providers (Section 10501(e), p. 2332) 143. Grant program for community-based diabetes prevention (Section 10501(g), p. 2337) 144. Grant program for providers who treat a high percentage of medically underserved populations (Section 10501(k), p. 2343) 145. Grant program to recruit students to practice in underserved communities (Section 10501(l), p. 2344) 146. Community Health Center Fund (Section 10503, p. 2355) 147. Demonstration project to provide access to health care for the uninsured at reduced fees (Section 10504, p. 2357) 148. Demonstration program to explore alternatives to tort litigation (Section 10607, p. 2369) 149. Indian Health demonstration program for chronic shortages of health professionals (S. 1790, Section 112, p. 24)* 150. Office of Indian Men?s Health (S. 1790, Section 136, p. 71)* 151. Indian Country modular component facilities demonstration program (S. 1790, Section 146, p. 108)* 152. Indian mobile health stations demonstration program (S. 1790, Section 147, p. 111)* 153. Office of Direct Service Tribes (S. 1790, Section 172, p. 151)* 154. Indian Health Service mental health technician training program (S. 1790, Section 181, p. 173)* 155. Indian Health Service program for treatment of child sexual abuse victims (S. 1790, Section 181, p. 192)* 156. Indian Health Service program for treatment of domestic violence and sexual abuse (S. 1790, Section 181, p. 194)* 157. Indian youth telemental health demonstration project (S. 1790, Section 181, p. 204)* 158. Indian youth life skills demonstration project (S. 1790, Section 181, p. 220)* 159. Indian Health Service Director of HIV/AIDS Prevention and Treatment (S. 1790, Section 199B, p. 258)*</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1347288332521</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347288677558-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obama today again admits his desire to raise taxes</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347219657100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How come I never get granted anything?</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1347288677558</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:51:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347289570139-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obama today again admits his desire to raise taxes</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347219657100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, let’s raise taxes by cutting out many of the corporate tax loopholes, the loopholes that keep Congressional campaign contributors contributing. Let's raise some taxes, but let’s also get serious about spending reductions and finally, finally, get serious about the waste and fraud in our government spending. Raising taxes so the Democrats can give more away to their favorite voting blocs is not the answer and Sorry Lord Barry, but Harry is wrong, compromise is not doing what you want and getting everyone else to kowtow to your wishes. It means working out deals that will actually accomplish something good for this country and our finances. Creating new commissions, new departments, new Czar positions, ignoring government waste and not just flat out firing the cheaters and the wanna be kings is wrong and always should be. We have to stop the government sponsoring of unions and their corrupt leaders, let the unions survive or fail based on their own activities and value.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1347289570139</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:06:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347290220255-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama today again admits his desire to raise taxes</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347219657100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“How come I never get granted anything.” CK That’s not true. You were granted asylum in Delaware. You’ve been granted a pardon from your excesses of the 70’s. Your family takes you for granted all the time. Granted, not the best grants, I’ll grant ya’, but whadyawant? Immunity &amp; Absolution?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347290220255</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:17:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347294285609-9</Id><Title>Re: Obama today again admits his desire to raise taxes</Title><Msg>Yahoo is now taking me for granted with this farkakte msg board. I didn't get a reply button for your post!</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1347294285609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:24:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347294522162-10</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Obama today again admits his desire to raise taxes</Title><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1347294285609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:24:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney admits he is going to raise taxes on the high, high income people, with money , still in the USA. I think he should raise the tax on people with money overseas. Give the date for the big increase, write it down as a memo. Then make sure his blind trust invester gets the memo.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1347294522162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:28:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347295707530-11</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Obama today again admits his desire to raise taxes</Title><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1347294285609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:24:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently, someone gave you a 'thumbs down' rating to your post and the 'reply' button is blocked. Hmmm!</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1347295707530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347295874850-12</Id><Title>Read this new report on AT&amp;T</Title><Msg>I cant believe what this analyst just told me about AT&amp;T . Check it out! goo.gl/t0566</Msg><Username>ellacagney</Username><Timestamp>1347295874850</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347298360974-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama today again admits his desire to raise taxes</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347219657100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you will be joined by many others. So much so that raising the rates will reduce the amount of tax collected. However the Communist goal is a 100% rate and then they give you back what they say you need.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1347298360974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:32:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347298713108-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama today again admits his desire to raise taxes</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347219657100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Corporate taxes should be cut to zero. They just pass it on to their customers so we end up paying it. At the same time, dividends and capital gains should not get any preferential treatment.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1347298713108</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:38:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347300213042-15</Id><Topic><Title>Obama today again admits his desire to raise taxes</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347219657100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes "And if we go back to the tax rates for folks making more than $250,000 a year, back to the rates that we had under Bill Clinton," he continued, "we can close the deficit, stabilize the economy, keep taxes on middle class families low, provide the certainty that I think all of us would be looking for."</Msg><Username>popndrop</Username><Timestamp>1347300213042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:03:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347300266549-16</Id><Topic><Title>DNC delegate threatens to kill Romney</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347149662196</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:14:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama supporters are out of control also threatening republican Rep. Trey Gowdy with a gun. A 52-year-old Atlanta woman was charged on Sunday with pointing a gun at U.S. Rep. Trey Gowdy while he sat in his car. Gowdy was waiting in his car when a woman “pointed the weapon at him with a threatening gesture said Spartanburg Public Safety Director A. Tony Fisher. Fisher said Spartanburg officials are working with the FBI and others federal authorities about possible federal charges. Gowdy was not injured, Fisher said. As Gowdy drove away, the suspect sprinted across the parking lot, but did not catch up to him, Fisher said. Gowdy then drove to the police station to report the matter. Police “conducted an intense search” to find the woman, Fisher said. She surrendered without incident.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347300266549</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:04:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347301238102-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obama today again admits his desire to raise taxes</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347219657100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee, Winjon, It would appear that you’re so out of ammo that you’ve taken to posting Republican talking points that are over two and a half years old. I’d post the link, but, well, you know...board improvements. Those points have been on numerous right-wing websites, but originated with GOP.gov on February 25th, 2010. (“Courtesy of the Senate Republican Policy Committee.”) They didn’t help you back then, and regurgitating them now won’t either. Affordable Health Care has come to America and it’s not going away. Frankly, the rest of the civilized world has viewed the fact that the richest country on the planet could outspend the next 17 countries combined on defense and wars, but couldn’t provide universal affordable health care to its citizens, as greedishly archaic. You can keep pimpin’ for the Insurance industry, but the American public is no longer buying your act.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1347301238102</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:20:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347301701701-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama today again admits his desire to raise taxes</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347219657100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As of this moment the MB show 15 replies I only see 7 what is going on?</Msg><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347301701701</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:28:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347303165334-19</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Only Tweak Obama Care NOW</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1347278164517</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 07:56:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The insureance companies wrote "Obama Care" and don't doubt it. It DID NOT originate in Congress as our laws are supposed to be. The con men in Congress hadn't even seen a copy of it when they voted for it. The Kenyan reminds me of "Br'er" Rabbit when the Fox and Bear were going to throw him in the Briar Patch. He makes a lot of noise about opposing the rich and the corporations they run but he is actually in bed with them. Check out the 50 or so appointments he's made from Goldman-Sachs into government offices handling public money. A very unfunny joke.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1347303165334</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:52:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347303756665-20</Id><Title>Who companies mahallisi?To report!</Title><Msg>Offer value what is it? In the past, no one has proposed this idea, but a lot of people in the application, but they will sell the value used in the wrong on the buy. Assessed to the company’s future cash flows, discount rates value, in fact, even at a substantial discount to buy, and still there is no margin of safety. because of the intangible assets of the enterprise in the majority of cases, very unstable, unable to provide investors with a true margin of safety. But offer value for selling a good reference. Following example: Respectively Firm A and B, the total share capital of 100 million shares of the enterprise, A company’s annual net profit of $ 5 million, an annual growth rate of 30% in the next 20 years, the price per share of U.S. $ 5 million, City win was 100 times. B corporate annual net profit was $ 30 billion, 5% in the next 20 years, the annual growth rate of 5%, the price per share of $ 3,000, the market win rate of 10 times So 20 years later, the enterprise’s net profit A $ 950 million, to 8.24 percent as the discount rate, the next 20 years, after a reasonable enterprise value ceiling of $ 11.5 billion, now valued at $ 2.306 billion, the enterprise value per share $ 23.06 20 years later, B Enterprises net profit of $ 79.5 billion, to 8.24 percent as the discount rate, the enterprises of the next 20 years after the reasonable price ceiling of $ 954 billion, the present value of $ 195.8 billion, the enterprise value per share $ 1958. When investors sell operations in A Company of the 100 times City win rate, sold obviously not rational. Room for improvement because there is a great value. B enterprises reached before 10 times City win rate, investors should take to sell the operation. The black spider Fund website there are more corporate valuation article</Msg><Username>fengjie583</Username><Timestamp>1347303756665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:02:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347307989285-21</Id><Title>Read this new report on AT&amp;T</Title><Msg>I cant believe what this analyst just told me about AT&amp;T . Check it out! goo.gl/t0566</Msg><Username>moiracremer93</Username><Timestamp>1347307989285</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347311400855-22</Id><Topic><Title>Read this new report on AT&amp;T</Title><Username>moiracremer93</Username><Timestamp>1347307989285</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:13:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what did he say? I don't see any link.</Msg><Username>goldiehaunt</Username><Timestamp>1347311400855</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 17:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347328537283-23</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, Slick Willie was Impeached !</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1347243288590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 22:14:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean your hero GWB did'nt lie? Oh and what about the 4000 plus soldiers that got killed for. All clinton did was get a BJ and your wonderful commrads that hate him made a mountain out of a mole hill. Your kind is what I say is F_ll of S__T.</Msg><Username>chgjt</Username><Timestamp>1347328537283</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:55:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>