<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351742905256-1</Id><Topic><Title>Philadelphia Freedom</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351638957297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know why the New Black Panthers go around mouthing off, but I can tell you, for sure, they are all talk and no do. In Texas, the phrase would be, "all hat and no cows". They are from Texas and they took their show on the road. They did get "called out" in Texas, and they ran. The most they are guilty for is hate speech, other than that, they have never committed any crimes. If they don't shut up their stupid mouthes, sometime who doesn't know better will carry them to glory. If they should show up where you're voting, just walk around them.</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1351742905256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 00:08:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351745847809-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama goes to Church?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351732107030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama will either be voted out or he will be impeached. Either way, he's gone.Climate change? Manmade climate change has been proven hocus pocus by the scientists who actually know. It's Al Gore's imagination that keeps that illusion going.The climate is always in constant change and cycling. Manmade, no. Gore is worried that he has been forgotten.He's right.</Msg><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1351745847809</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 00:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351770883200-3</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Doomberg should Step Down</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351639429508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea, maybe you guys can bring back W. We need help with a hurricane and the economy. Why do you Repuklicans never mention the last guy you elected?</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1351770883200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 07:54:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351775748759-4</Id><Topic><Title>Teachers Should Go For Mitt</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351644405039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vote for Ron Paul!</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1351775748759</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:15:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351776305329-5</Id><Topic><Title>Teachers Should Go For Mitt</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351644405039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not voting is a vote.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1351776305329</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:25:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351776485252-6</Id><Title>Dividend</Title><Msg>Where is it, Chuck???</Msg><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1351776485252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351776950617-7</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Peppeek's investigation isn't going well: "The U.S. Mission in Benghazi convened an “emergency meeting” less than a month before the assault that killed Ambassador Chris Stevens and three other Americans, because Al Qaeda had training camps in Benghazi and the consulate could not defend against a “coordinated attack,” according to a classified cable reviewed by Fox News. Summarizing an Aug. 15 emergency meeting convened by the U.S. Mission in Benghazi, the Aug. 16 cable marked “SECRET” said that the State Department’s senior security officer, also known as the RSO, did not believe the consulate could be protected. “RSO (Regional Security Officer) expressed concerns with the ability to defend Post in the event of a coordinated attack due to limited manpower, security measures, weapons capabilities, host nation support, and the overall size of the compound,” the cable said. According to a review of the cable addressed to the Office of the Secretary of State Hillary Clinton, the Emergency Action Committee was also briefed "on the location of approximately ten Islamist militias and AQ training camps within Benghazi … these groups ran the spectrum from Islamist militias, such as the QRF Brigade and Ansar al-Sharia, to ‘Takfirist thugs.’” Each U.S. mission has a so-called Emergency Action Committee that is responsible for security measures and emergency planning."</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1351776950617</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:35:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351777267532-8</Id><Topic><Title>Philadelphia Freedom</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351638957297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “I understand that a Company in Spain, (headed by George Soros), makes most of the voting machines” Rob, it seems one of your side’s tactics is to constantly accuse the opposition of doing something that you know full well you, yourselves have been doing all along or again plan to. That’s not unlike most of the banter on this board, which, generally results in your responses being the political equivalent of “So’s your Mother!” While that’s an expedient and curt resource on the playground, it’s a bit juvenile for the political arena, depending, of course, on what base of the electorate you are targeting. Unfortunately, the Tea Party has consistently answered that question, as do you guys with your rants of ignorance and racism. From GlobalResearch – “While the story (about Soros), spread first by public airwaves clown and radio host Michael Savage and, naturally, Fox ‘News,’ is completely false, the general concern at the heart of it is not. Indeed, it underscores, yet again, the very point we’ve been making on this topic here for years… …several large Romney campaign donors and Romney's own son Tagg have financial ties to voting machine producer Hart InterCivic, Hamilton County, Ohio's voting machine provider…two of its parent corporation’s executives have directly contributed to the Romney campaign despite being board members at an organization that must, by its nature, remain neutral in campaigns. When you put together the Hart executives' obvious bias toward Romney, the opportunities for manipulation of election results, the fact that Ohio is a key battleground state, and the reciprocation of investments between the capital firms, it's not hard to feel a certain note of disconcert. This appears to be a repeat of the infamous former CEO of Diebold Wally O’Dell, who raised money for Bush while his company supplied voting machines and election management software in the 2004 election.” And we in Ohio remember it well, because O’Dell even had the audacity to send a fund raising letter on behalf of George W. Bush in ‘03 stating that he was committed to “to helping Ohio deliver its electoral votes to the President.” Talk about flagrant, and you have the audacity to criticize others? Keep in mind, O’Dell also later left the company when being investigated by the SEC for insider trading…but, of course, you guys don’t want any regulations on Wall Street, either. Gee, there seems to be a pattern there. “Today, my family (wife &amp; kids), and I participated in early voting, here in the People's Republic. The lines were out the door, and snaked around the building asked several people what made them turn out. None appeared to be Barry's supporters” – more rob Yeah, rob, sure you did. Everybody goes to the polls and asks others for their political philosophy on why they showed up. I can see it now. Rob and family (apparently he took the girls out of college to go vote): to a crowded polling place of predominantly African-Americans (none of which, according to rob “appeared to be Barry’s supporters”????? What did they appear to be, then, rob? The John Birch Society??): “Excuse me, but my family and I were wondering if you, like us, are voting for Romney because you’re fed up with crime and illegal immigration. You know, the GOP and the Tea Party are terribly concerned with the well being of we people of color.” Response: “Are you talkin’ to me, you jive-a#S Uncle Tom? What the fock is that you’re driving??? Oh, man, oh, man…look at this fool…he’s drivin’ a Prius…what’s wrong with you, Oreo? Don’t be askin’ me who I vote for, fool. I vote you get your sorry Herman Cain butt outta’ here!!!” Incidentally, rob, while you’re complaining about the lines you had to stand in at your “family outing”…you know in Maryland you could have requested an absentee ballot long ago (up until yesterday, as a matter of fact) and mailed it in, like most smart people have already done. I guess you guys just needed to get out for awhile. “We still could loose (sic) though.” Yes, indeed, you certainly could. That’s because you are a “looser”. Down with pubic educashun…Tee Partiers Untie!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351777267532</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:41:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351777716536-9</Id><Title>Things we can all learn from Senator Bob</Title><Msg>If you agree to pay two #$%$ $500 each and you only pay them $100 each, then don't be surprised if they rat you out. If you tell two #$%$ how beautiful and nice you think they are, and then you disrespect them after you have your way with them, then don't be surprised if they rat you out. If you treat your constituents like you treat #$%$, then don't be surprised if they rat you out. The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351777716536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:48:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351779201741-10</Id><Topic><Title>Obama goes to Church?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351732107030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a fine Christian man and attends church regulary. Although many so called Christians go to church, then come home to spout hatred and lies. In that case better to stay home as Jeezus doesn't say that, or like that either.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351779201741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351781819038-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama goes to Church?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351732107030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>really? ever heard reverend wright's hateful sernons? obama sat in that racists church for 20 years. no wonder he said "the police acted stupidly" before he had any facts. no wonder he said "if i had a son he'd look like that" when referring to trayvon martin. real nice guy, a bit racist but you think he's a great guy.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351781819038</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:56:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351781849516-12</Id><Topic><Title>Teachers Should Go For Mitt</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351644405039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wasted vote</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351781849516</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:57:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351783149892-13</Id><Topic><Title>penson fund needs money?</Title><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1351716964970</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:56:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On October 19th, T announced: AT&amp;T to Place $9.5 Billion in Equity in Pension Plan. By googling the announcement, there are several articles with additional detail. The most informative appeared to be from Morningstar.</Msg><Username>bruce.knapp</Username><Timestamp>1351783149892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351783540959-14</Id><Title>same ole same ole.. MMs run up the market and then FLEECE!!! over n over again!!</Title><Msg>amazing!</Msg><Username>rmbdata</Username><Timestamp>1351783540959</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351785177311-15</Id><Topic><Title>Things we can all learn from Senator Bob</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351777716536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:48:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As I understand the story it went something like this: o Bill and Hill learned before the convention in 2008 that the party and the MSM were all in for the man from Chicago o At that time they were given the option to either continue the fight or support the party, have your debts paid off, and take Secy. of State o Bill and Hill took the later option o Now that we are at the end of the first term, and Bill and Hill have held up their part of the bargain, and there is a strong possibility that the man from Chicago might not get a second term, Bill and Hill are still looking to get the money that they have earned, so they will continue to play nice until next wednesday, after that all bets are off Just my humble opinion The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351785177311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351785242752-16</Id><Title>GREEDDINESS MADE ME LOOK STUPPIDDD!</Title><Msg>AND YOU??</Msg><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1351785242752</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351788392899-17</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend</Title><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1351776485252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:28:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already banked. THANKS T.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1351788392899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:46:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351788782206-18</Id><Topic><Title>penson fund needs money?</Title><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1351716964970</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:56:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think you must be too dumb to get a "penson" fund. You might want to get a GED instead. I hope investors who look at this MB aren't revolted by the irrelevant, political, and just plain dumb input. While I put him on IGNORE, Jon is among the worst offenders, but has a lot of company in the "spam department".</Msg><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1351788782206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351789828260-19</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend</Title><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1351776485252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:28:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dividend Declaration Date: Sep-29-2012 Dividend Ex Date: Oct-05-2012 Dividend Record Date: Oct-10-2012 Dividend Pay Date: Nov-01-2012</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351789828260</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 13:10:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351789845622-20</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend</Title><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1351776485252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:28:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>where is the penny? I expect it soon.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351789845622</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 13:10:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351793456121-21</Id><Topic><Title>Just checked my UHC insurance from T</Title><Username>snakehead_billy</Username><Timestamp>1351460021026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 17:33:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And folks wonder why our health care is so expensive. They used to jail those kind of devients a few years back.</Msg><Username>bedwetters99</Username><Timestamp>1351793456121</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:10:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351796589159-22</Id><Topic><Title>Gawdawful!</Title><Username>timetraveler2u</Username><Timestamp>1351737050352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 22:30:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's like panning for gold here timetraveler. Gotta sift through a lot to get the gold.</Msg><Username>dave_martin_2244</Username><Timestamp>1351796589159</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:03:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351796647676-23</Id><Topic><Title>Teachers Should Go For Mitt</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351644405039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Compared to the other 2 running? Don't think so.</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1351796647676</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:04:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351796837188-24</Id><Topic><Title>Teachers Should Go For Mitt</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351644405039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh yeah, get rid of the one advocate teachers have left. The states are stripping salaries and teacher numbers. Without Obama's support and the national focus on education, you might as well go back to the day where teachers were not considered a profession or a viable career for men. Mitt Romney couldn't care less about teachers. They are in his 47%. A drain of tax dollars that could be kept at home with his corporate buddies. You are absolutely nut if you vote for Mitt Romney, whether you are a teacher, woman, student, worker, or business person making less that $250,000. Now if you make over $250,000 then have at it, but don't be surprised when you get screwed too.</Msg><Username>thedukeintexas</Username><Timestamp>1351796837188</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351797149050-25</Id><Topic><Title>Va. Election VOTES Will Not Be Released Till Fri.</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1351724256139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:57:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does that amount to? 14 voters?</Msg><Username>thedukeintexas</Username><Timestamp>1351797149050</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:12:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351797590577-26</Id><Topic><Title>Teachers Should Go For Mitt</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351644405039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't get it. RP has no chance, I don't care if he is the best choice(and he isn't). Ron Paul is a screaming wacko lunatic who embarrasses himself when he speaks, he gets all emotional and goes high-pitched. A kook! But voting for him means you don't care if Obama gets a 2nd term. Handouts will continue to rise and so will the debt. And I was no fan of GWB either. Obama is absolutely for wealth redistribution and that won't work. Unemployment will stay high if he sticks to that plan. He can shift people from unemployment to disability roles but it won't make us a better country. What happened to "transparency"? He favors unions to an extreme, Boeing plant? Pipeline from Canada? He is awful on economics.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351797590577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351798400677-27</Id><Topic><Title>Things we can all learn from Senator Bob</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351777716536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:48:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “If you treat your constituents like you treat (blank), then don't be surprised if they rat you out.” – frog clown “In interviews, the two women said they met Menendez around Easter...They claimed Menendez agreed to pay them $500, but in the end they each received only $100. The women spoke through a translator in the company of their attorney, Melanio Figueroa. Both asked that their identities remain obscured for fear of reprisals in the Dominican Republic. When shown a photograph of Sen. Menendez, the women said they recognized him as the man with whom they’d had s--ual relations...Neither knew the identity of the man at the time. Both claimed to recognize him later as Sen. Menendez.” Hey, gremlin...Is this really your best shot? Two anonymous #$%$ who refuse to be identified making claims about something that happened last Spring in the Dominican Republic? Whether or not a single politician on vacation (he’s not cheating, as he’s divorced) paid for a prostitute in the Dominican is really not any of my business nor my concern. You probably would have spent more money trying to wine them and dine them, lavish them with gifts, dinner and dancing ‘til the wee hours, simply hoping they might blow the warts off your tadpole...same difference, more expensive. Hey, if you really want to make an argument, why not defend them with Lily Ledbetter pay discrepancies? Funny how, in the midst of your War on Women, you somehow turn into a total hypocrite like Henry Hyde and Newt Gingrich while they were going after Clinton with their overzealous moral fervor: “Former House Speaker Newt Gingrich said on Fox news (March, 2011) that it wasn't hypocritical of him to lead impeachment proceedings against President Bill Clinton in the 1990's, even though he was having an extramarital affair at the time, because the impeachment case was ‘not about personal behavior.’ So, if a spokesperson and potential candidate for your cause says it’s not about personal behavior, what’s your point? Oh, silly me... of course...pointless propaganda when there’s not much else left.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351798400677</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351798570109-28</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend</Title><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1351776485252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:28:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've owned these shares for 3 years. Where's my money, Chuck?</Msg><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1351798570109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:36:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351801613098-29</Id><Title>let's see now, 1. powell, 2. christie, 3 bloomberg</Title><Msg>all endorse or praise President Obama's good job and work, all republicans. Gee, how come RWNJ's? Got a THEORY CONNECTING UNRELATED DOTS ABOUT THAT TOO? Isn't it Great?</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351801613098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351802364596-30</Id><Topic><Title>Things we can all learn from Senator Bob</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351777716536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:48:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow echo, you sure did tell me off, and I am sure that Senator Bob will appreciate the fact that you got all of the facts and his full name out there for everyone to see. Good going guy. I know this won't fit your narrow view of hypocracy, but I seem to remember Senator Bob calling for the firing of some Secret Service agents back in April for their unpardonable sins. Wow echo, you sure did tell me off, The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351802364596</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:39:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351804050620-31</Id><Topic><Title>let's see now, 1. powell, 2. christie, 3 bloomberg</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351801613098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I don't care", always an immature child's last response when they know they're wrong, and they have no answers.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351804050620</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:07:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351804855704-32</Id><Topic><Title>Things we can all learn from Senator Bob</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351777716536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:48:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “…you got all of the facts and his full name out there for everyone to see” Uh, excuse me? What is that supposed to mean? How many Senator Bob’s have been accused of cavorting in the Dominican in the past few days? So, why don’t you explain to everybody why you brought it up in the first place? Now suddenly you’re trying to protect the guy’s I.D.? I swear, you guys just type for the sake of typing…no thought behind it, at all. “I know this won't fit your narrow view of hypocracy (sic), but I seem to remember Senator Bob calling for the firing of some Secret Service agents back in April for their unpardonable sins.” Do you suppose anybody at all, other than you phony, fundamentalist, moralistic-hypocrites, would criticize those agents about anything if they were off on their own vacation? They were on assignment, you simpleton. “Wow echo, you sure did tell me off, “ What is that…the complimentary close of a letter? You punctuate and spell like jon, and your “Bill &amp; Hill”* routine is rob’s normal gig. Honestly, the people you represent who think Americans are stupid, really shouldn’t send out people to make their pitch who are stupider than their target audience. * Speaking of your “Bill &amp; Hill” story, you began with, “As I understand the story it went something like this:” So your inference is that you have some actual source to explain what you are about to tell us. You then give your opinion of the inside workings of the Democratic Party, with absolutely no basis for reality, followed with, “Just my humble opinion.” And you wonder why Middle America isn’t buying your repetitive fractured logic? Ribbit.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351804855704</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:20:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351805097360-33</Id><Title>Anyone heard any news about an announcement coming from T on Wed. 11-7???</Title><Msg>I heard from someone there is an announcement coming from T on Wed. 11-7, anyone heard anything???</Msg><Username>dewydale</Username><Timestamp>1351805097360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:24:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351807011227-34</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone heard any news about an announcement coming from T on Wed. 11-7???</Title><Username>dewydale</Username><Timestamp>1351805097360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:24:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Randy speaks, we listen. Do goggle or Yahoo search for Nov7 and wireline. It's out there on the web</Msg><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1351807011227</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:56:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351807258948-35</Id><Topic><Title>Teachers Should Go For Mitt</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351644405039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When will Ron Paul throw his support behind Mitt? There are no perfect candidates. I would think Paul would take Mitt, over the wreckless spending of Obama. We have absolutely nothing to show for BILLIONS wasted by Barry. It's so obvious, Barry is using to Green movement to funnel money to his partners in crime. I think if you were an environmentalist, you'd be upset with the 38 solar companies, Obummer has torpedoed.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351807258948</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351808060384-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obama goes to Church?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351732107030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forgot the obvious, I should have paid more attention to Barry's Grant Park speech. People were crying, fainting, so caught up in the rhetoric. Now they realize he's just another Chicago gangster, who can read a teleprompter. To be kind, I could say he over promised, and under delivered. But, in his speech in front of the Greek columns, as I recall, he said the rising tides would cease, the planet would start to heal. I guess Owl Gore believed that spiel too.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351808060384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:14:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351808823169-37</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Doomberg should Step Down</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351639429508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I must admit George wasn't very good in all areas. I believe however, as Clint would say, Barry needs to be let go. I'm going to get alot of people exceited, but I am a registered Dem. This is Maryland after all, I have to try and limit the damage from Gov. O'we Malley. I promise to vote for Hill, if Mitt miscues. I hate the way she was Barracked, by Barry. All I am saying, is give Mitt a chance. Can anyone tell me of anything good that would come out of a 2nd Obama administration?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351808823169</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:27:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351810892940-38</Id><Title>go mobile infront of the holidays and recoup your exc losses ina few weeks</Title><Msg>T VZ CLWR...join the party! GL</Msg><Username>rmbdata</Username><Timestamp>1351810892940</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351815350996-39</Id><Topic><Title>Things we can all learn from Senator Bob</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351777716536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:48:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “cause stupider .. ain't in the dictionary (chuckles)” – jon’s part-time research assistant from the carwash on acid (note spelling) Stu-pid (The Free Dictionary) adj. stu•pid•er, stu•pid•est (wait…what was that first one?) 1. Slow to learn or understand; obtuse. 2. Tending to make poor decisions or careless mistakes. 3. Marked by a lack of intelligence or care; foolish or careless: a stupid mistake. 4. Dazed, stunned, or stupefied. 5. Pointless; worthless: a stupid job. n. A stupid or foolish person. 6. jon3retired – Hey, jon, what’s that adjective up there? Right; had you read further, you’d have seen: Ex: adj. : jon was stupider than rob, who’s stupider than windalefrogg, who’s stupider than those thinking America is stupid. Stupid, insipid, morbid, limpid, devoid, sordid, overpaid, putrid, paranoid, flaccid, rabid, unlaid, lurid, and did we say stupid? Common denominator? ID - Freudian uncontrollable chaotic drive for power (some say neurosis), in constant struggle with the ego.(The part of humans from which the basic animal instincts derived) Achieving Super Ego status to counter the ID, is something lacking in the far right ideology. Why bother progressing? We’re happy where we are. Serfs, bring us the wine and the ladies. (Wow, Ann Coulter tapping a keg!)…ID…get lucid, idiots.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351815350996</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:15:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351815467832-40</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone heard any news about an announcement coming from T on Wed. 11-7???</Title><Username>dewydale</Username><Timestamp>1351805097360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:24:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Conflicting articles. Basically, T will divest or invest in wireline.</Msg><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1351815467832</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351816143424-41</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Doomberg should Step Down</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351639429508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>..."I'm not a registered anything, (except conceal carry)"...oh, and pedophile, but that was a bad rap. And it wouldn't surpise any of you out there if I told you I'm not even really registered to vote. Somebody told me there was a test involved, and I don't test well. Well, I don't test.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351816143424</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:29:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351816215965-42</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend</Title><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1351776485252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:28:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mid to late Dec. as usual.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1351816215965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:30:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351816275678-43</Id><Topic><Title>Gawdawful!</Title><Username>timetraveler2u</Username><Timestamp>1351737050352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 22:30:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right buddy!</Msg><Username>catfisherman201</Username><Timestamp>1351816275678</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351816721735-44</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Doomberg should Step Down</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351639429508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You GOPers are going down. GOP party may be gone in 10 years unless they can relate to the people.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351816721735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:38:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351816787648-45</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Doomberg should Step Down</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351639429508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can buy all the liter bottles of "soft drinks" at walmart you want, the whole shelf if you like, and nobody asks why or says no. What ARE you babbling about?</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351816787648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:39:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351817148468-46</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Doomberg should Step Down</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351639429508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you have gulanesia?</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1351817148468</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351817429843-47</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Doomberg should Step Down</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351639429508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bring up Bush because it is folks like you that elected him. Voting for Bush was a sanity or intelligence test and you flunked. You have proven you have no judgment so why not just sit in the corner and be quiet. I can't believe the same folks who voted for Bush are now running around tell the rest of us how to vote this time. Don't you get it. You are a proven idiot.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1351817429843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:50:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351818128639-48</Id><Topic><Title>Obama goes to Church?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351732107030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reverend Wright seems to have dropped off of the face of the earth. You would think he'd say something about the Bengazi 9/11 anniversary attacks. Like the chickens are coming home to da crib. The guy who masterminded the attacks is really frustrated with Obama, and his coverup. This guy is all over the Middle East saying, that these were pre-planned, by him. But many deufus Americans refuse to believe that Obummer would lie about such a thing.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351818128639</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:02:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351818519005-49</Id><Topic><Title>Sorry Shorty</Title><Username>shipleyinsuranceservices</Username><Timestamp>1351709624100</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:53:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not short but I do believe T will rise only for another session or two and then continue downward trend. Just the cycle of most stocks at some point. That's my thinking.</Msg><Username>coulddobetter</Username><Timestamp>1351818519005</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:08:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351818930884-50</Id><Topic><Title>Teachers Should Go For Mitt</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351644405039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not true, and you are forgetting that Mitt plans to do away the tax on dividends, and capital gains. for those making under $250k a year. Think what a boost that would give to our economy. That is the difference when a businessman is President, as opposed to a Socialist. Someone always trying to get even with those creating wealth, not only for themselves, but others. As Reagan would say, a rising tide lifts all boats. Whereas Barrack is acting as our economic Captain (like the Titantic). Full speed ahead (keep spending, and borrowing), and the ship will right itself.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351818930884</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351820191135-51</Id><Title>Clint Eastwood on FOX NEWS (now)</Title><Msg>Vote Tea Party, GOP !</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1351820191135</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:36:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351820367898-52</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood on FOX NEWS (now)</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1351820191135</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:36:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clint blows away libtards.</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1351820367898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351820532745-53</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Doomberg should Step Down</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351639429508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>then the utility board that sets rates should look into this. I liked it when all utilities were regulated monopolies. Things works and rates were steady----no off hour peak kw demand scams,etc. Thanks</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1351820532745</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:42:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351820773079-54</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood on FOX NEWS (now)</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1351820191135</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:36:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a man. A more hip, smaller version of The Duke, John Wayne.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351820773079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:46:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351820894390-55</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Doomberg should Step Down</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351639429508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a cousin that worked in a responsible position in the New York City Administration. You should hear what they say. I can't say too much as it might repurcuss even though they are retired. One thing they told me was that there were ten Wall Street banks that pretty much run the whole country. I always suggest to anyone interested to google the Council on Foreign Relations and look at the membership list. Look up thir charter and find what the purpose of it's founding in 1923 was.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351820894390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:48:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351821714187-56</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood on FOX NEWS (now)</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1351820191135</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:36:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How does Clint stomach Liberal Hollywood? I guess they know better than to attack him.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351821714187</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 22:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351821719900-57</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Doomberg should Step Down</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351639429508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We haven't needed to bring Bush up .. cause Obama has been doing that, for over 3 years .. blaming him for everything" Here we go again. When did Obama ever blame Bush? He was most respectful and praising of Bush at the portrait ceremony at the White House. I'm sure more people than myself noticed the lack of blaming. What Obama, the President, says is he inherited a mess, a fact. You must know that's true if you were in America in Oct 2008. Blaming is more the republican game, just look at yourself blaming Obama for everything. Big difference in meaning what Obama says and does and your interpretation of what he says and does.. Let the flame throwing begin.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351821719900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 22:01:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>