<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356589526200-1</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne La Pierre For President</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356111777788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that worthy of a death penalty sentence carried out by a vigilante, in your warped little brain? No, but perhaps his physical assault of that 'vigilante' might have been. Keep thinking his kid was an innocent little boy until they prove different, which I am confident they will. The media has not always told the truth in this matter, let alone the whole truth.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1356589526200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 01:25:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356613244412-2</Id><Topic><Title>Sidwell Friends School sounds like a very safe place for children</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356558043024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:40:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “As far as the quote ‘In your heart’…I believe most conservatives know the quote” - froggie Of course they do, gremlin. As do all the liberals, centrists, Democrats, moderate Republicans and otherwise sane people from 1964, who recognized the campaign slogan of Barry Goldwater for what it was… “…his slogan ‘In your heart, you know he's right’ was successfully parodied by the Johnson campaign into ‘In your guts, you know he's nuts’, or ‘In your heart, you know he might’ (as in push the nuclear button), or even ‘In your heart, he's too far right’…” I find it fascinating (but not at all surprising) that you’re here promoting an election slogan from a guy who opposed the Civil Rights Act of 1964. The slogan you admire so much, helped contribute to his losing the biggest landslide in the popular vote history, with a lopsided victory for Johnson by over 61% to Goldwater’s 38%. The man you apparently admire so much, carried only his home state of Arizona (barely), and the five Dixie states of SC, GA, AL, MS and LA, mainly because those states in ’64 were still largely an all-white electorate, united against civil rights…not at all unlike the very small contingency of racist, intolerant remnants of that movement – The Tea Party – who you represent today. It is mind boggling that you folks have apparently learned nothing at all from that era, yet continue longing for a bygone political atmosphere equivalent to the “good ol’ boys’ club.” Worse yet, you also apparently learned nothing from the recent election that repudiated your extremist views. Even Goldwater, mellowed in his old age, acknowledged that his party had strayed way too far to the right by saying, “Do not associate my name with anything you do. You are extremists, and you've hurt the Republican Party much more than the Democrats have.” That’s even more applicable today, but somehow the powers that you represent refuse to permit you shills to speak the truth. Instead, you keep heading down that path of extinction, not unlike the many endangered frog species of the world…although in your case, froggie, it’s suicide by politics. RIBBIT!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356613244412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 08:00:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356613861777-3</Id><Topic><Title>ricky</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1356292032094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 14:47:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Do you really think the success of your investment in a PUBLIC utility company does not depend on government?" Your statement above tells anyone who understands T who the fool is.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1356613861777</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 08:11:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356614582703-4</Id><Topic><Title>Sidwell Friends School sounds like a very safe place for children</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356558043024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:40:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"He (Orwell) is one of my political heroes" Political language... is designed to make lies sound truthful and murder respectable, and to give an appearance of solidity to pure wind. George Orwell A bit harsh, but your hero may have seen you coming.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1356614582703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 08:23:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356614875031-5</Id><Title>pinhighshot...</Title><Msg>,,, “Keep thinking his kid was an innocent little boy until they prove different” – pinhighshot (you know, it may be “pin high”, but if it’s still leaving a 60 foot, double-breaking, down hill putt, it’s nothin’ to write home about.) Ah, yes, vigilante justice in the minds of the bar room posse…”Guilty until proven innocent.” More warped logic of American justice from a boiled over and cracked Tea Pot.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356614875031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 08:27:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356619327688-6</Id><Topic><Title>Sidwell Friends School sounds like a very safe place for children</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356558043024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:40:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You choose a line from "Politics and the English Language" to describe me? You'd do better to read that essay than to select quotes from internet searches. Immediately following that sentences is his criticism of "worn-out and useless phrases"--the very grist of conservative writing these days. Look at Froggie's post. It is little more than a litany of conservative buzzwords that would make Orwell cringe. Orwell's thesis is that imprecise and poor language skills lead to imprecise and poor thinking. People who do not speak clearly become victims of the political language Orwell described. In other words, they fail to recognize #$%$. You should not look to me for that. You should look to Jon, robfisk, winholder and Froggie. You should demand precision and clarity in language and shun those who cannot or will not provide it.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356619327688</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 09:42:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356619460727-7</Id><Title>Why is Obama Giving 17 Fighter Jets to the brotherhood?</Title><Msg>Aren't they members of the religion of peace? Do you know how expensive these things are? Why not lend them Air Force One? The election is over. You have no reason to go back to Ohio.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356619460727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 09:44:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356620088611-8</Id><Topic><Title>Sidwell Friends School sounds like a very safe place for children</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356558043024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:40:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I was attempting to point out the intellecual dishonesty of those on the left (Mr. Gregory) who spent 30 minutes on his TV show (Meet The Press) attempting to discredit conservatives for having the temerity to desire the same level of security enjoyed by Mr. Gregory's children and the children of our "dear leader"." Hilarious. Do these same conservatives have the temerity to desire the same level of *education* enjoyed by Mr. Gregory's children and the children of our "dear leader"? Nope. It never occurred to you that "Equalizer" and "Peacemaker" were ironic names for guns, not descriptive names. It is not guns that make people equal. It is education. Again, I question the sanity of people who make equal access to guns into a noble cause, but who believe the Department of Education is "socialism". "I believe most conservatives know the quote" A source for the quote does not make your post any more comprehensible.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356620088611</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 09:54:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356620800975-9</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne La Pierre For President</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356111777788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"perhaps his physical assault of that 'vigilante' might have been." Vigilante is the correct word. Zimmerman had no place following and harassing Martin. Perhaps if he was not armed he would not have made that mistake, and Martin would have walked home and grown up to become a mature adult. The difference between you and I is that you think Zimmerman was a good guy with a gun defending his neighborhood. I think he was a fool with a gun likely to get someone killed. It turns out I was right. The last thing we need is more "good guys" like Zimmerman, armed with AR-15s, roaming the streets.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356620800975</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 10:06:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356621914237-10</Id><Topic><Title>New Year!!!</Title><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1356184045359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:47:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I drink so much I see more than one ball. Double the fun.</Msg><Username>crazyhorse1786</Username><Timestamp>1356621914237</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 10:25:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356622497460-11</Id><Topic><Title>Sidwell Friends School sounds like a very safe place for children</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356558043024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:40:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"and otherwise sane people from 1964, who recognized the campaign slogan of Barry Goldwater" That was a decade before I was born. Froggie apparently associates "conservatives" with "old people". I can't say he's wrong to do so. But he is definitely dating himself and his way of thinking-- a way of thinking that was rejected in 1964, as you point out.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356622497460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 10:34:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356622588470-12</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne La Pierre For President</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356111777788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zimmerman had as much right to be looking out to protect his property and his neighborhood as did the kid that didn't live there out walking around with burgular tools! Zimmerman was attacked for his efforts, by Martin. Part of the reasons many own guns is because like Zimmerman stated, the police don't show up when we call them and then they just let the guys go.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1356622588470</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 10:36:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356623164657-13</Id><Topic><Title>Bullish still</Title><Username>dwczmfbapu1125</Username><Timestamp>1336659467000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-05-10 10:17:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I AM UP TODAY!</Msg><Username>jmicheal17</Username><Timestamp>1356623164657</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 10:46:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356623216525-14</Id><Topic><Title>Sidwell Friends School sounds like a very safe place for children</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356558043024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:40:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well golly gee Ricky, I must have hit a nerve, and for that I will appologize, but as far as the Civil Rights act of 1964 is concerned most Republicans (that I know) are proud of the members of their party and the votes that they made during that time, because were it not for Republican votes in the Senate and the leadership of Senator Everett Mckinley Dirksen (a Republican from the state of Illinois) the filibuster by democrats would never have been broken. A couple of facts that may have slipped by you: o 71 senators voted to invoke cloture o 67 votes were needed o 44 democrats and 27 Republicans joined together to bring the bill to a final vote o Of those voting "nay" 80% were democrats including Robert C. Byrd and former vice president Al Gore's father I realize that race baiting is one of the favored tactics used by the folks on your side, and I know that for the most part the left and their willing partners in the main stream media get away with providing their version of the truth, but I am sorry Ricky you are not entitled to your version of the facts. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356623216525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 10:46:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356623299872-15</Id><Topic><Title>Sidwell Friends School sounds like a very safe place for children</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356558043024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:40:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Orwell's thesis is that imprecise and poor language skills lead to imprecise and poor thinking. People who do not speak clearly become victims of the political language Orwell described. In other words, they fail to recognize #$%$." You fit perfectly into that realm, because you fail to recognize the #$%$! Old George is one of your hero's, but at the same time statements like the one above if submitted by anyone else, you would have branded that person as a racist. I think I have been very clear in my use of the language; you just disagree with the words and the concepts and pretend that anyone that is disagreeable with your standards and beliefs is a fool. Not so! Throughout history, liberalism has lead to the downfall of many empires and great civilizations as it will the United States and democracy if we continue present trends. Our current leader is a narcissist that thinks he was sent to save the world, not just the U.S. while not having the leadership skills to run a mid-sized company, let alone a nation. His desire is to fundamentally change this country if we want it or not because he has a vision of 'fairness' that is incompatible with reality. You need to get over yourself and look around. Try considering the other points of view before condemning them to the scrap heap of liberalism's hatred. You’re a living, breathing hypocrite.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1356623299872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 10:48:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356623685669-16</Id><Topic><Title>Sidwell Friends School sounds like a very safe place for children</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356558043024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:40:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are involved in a conversation I have no part in about things which occurred 10 years before my birth. I am not sure why you are including me in this conversation, which is a conversation that says more about your age than anything else.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356623685669</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 10:54:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356623845225-17</Id><Topic><Title>Sidwell Friends School sounds like a very safe place for children</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356558043024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:40:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice deflection...the subject was the relationship of 'security' that they enjoy while those same people are disparaging as foolish the idea of armed guards at their children’s schools, yet you opt to attempt to change it to the level of education they deserve or desire. Everyone wants his or her children to enjoy a good education, well most people do, not all. They also wish for their children to be safe in receiving that education. Some obviously have more resources to obtain that level of education and security, but should not go about intimating that only some should be so privileged.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1356623845225</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 10:57:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356624079820-18</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Obama Giving 17 Fighter Jets to the brotherhood?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356619460727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 09:44:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Useless assets. The military can't afford to run them anymore after the budget cuts are made. Why not give them to a "worthy cause" like the Muslim Brotherhood? Like spitting on the American flag</Msg><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1356624079820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 11:01:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356624475899-19</Id><Topic><Title>pinhighshot...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356614875031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 08:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is as much evidence that he was 'not' the blameless kid they showed pictures of as there is that Zimmerman unashamedly shot him because he was a black kid. I guess the point is that before you run off at the mouth about how terrifying Zimmerman is/was perhaps you should allow the justice system to run its course. You sure don't want to follow in the footsteps your hero and call the police stupid before you have all the facts, or perhaps you do. Also, when did protecting your home and families become a vigilante action? You and your alter ego complain about want to know what Zimmerman was doing out at night with a gun, but I don’t see similar questions or complaints about Martins actions or reasons for being there. Why?</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1356624475899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 11:07:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356625041863-20</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1356577227990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 22:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"My goal is that whatever the government spends is financed by taxes, not debt. I think that is the best way to moderate spending. " Unfortunately that is not the goal of and hasn't been the goal of Congress for decades, particularly the 40 years the Democrats ruled Congress. I think that is what several of the Republicans are asking that they attempt for a change...change, you know that favorite subject of our current President. Perhaps starting to starve the beast would encourage the beast to begin a weight reduction program on its own. Besides, who cares what your goals are, you are simply an indistinctive poster on a Yahoo message board. You don’t make policy, create, or pass any laws. You’re just sharing your opinions and going out of your way to demean any that doesn’t agree with yours. You don't discuss, you mock, annoy, make fun of, and refuse to consider any that are not of the same thinking. Basically you’re just selfish and mean. .</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1356625041863</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 11:17:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356627189385-21</Id><Topic><Title>Weaver grip</Title><Username>josieinib</Username><Timestamp>1356564095100</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 18:21:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The government trusted a great many men in the service with many types of weapons. We were trained in their use and safety procedures. Now they say we can't be trusted. The ones I don't trust are those that run this government. Many in the military feel the same way.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1356627189385</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 11:53:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356629198909-22</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Obama Giving 17 Fighter Jets to the brotherhood?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356619460727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 09:44:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a member of the Muslim Brotherhood and has financed much of the takeover of Egypt and Libya by the Brotherhood. The Fighter Jets are needed by the Brotherhood to take over Syria. Obama has already provided stinger missiles to the Brotherhood so they could defend against Syria's air-force. You are now living in a country ruled by the Muslim Brotherhood. Either do something about it or get used to it.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1356629198909</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 12:26:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356630136111-23</Id><Topic><Title>pinhighshot...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356614875031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 08:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Martin was living there and going home from the store. A trigger happy, coward with a gun, fool murdered him for nothing. Martin was convicted, and given the death penalty for doing nothing. The cowardly self made vigilante zimmerman couldn't use his fists and go home a little beat up after the fight HE started, like a man, he had the gun, and guns kill.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1356630136111</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 12:42:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356630418990-24</Id><Topic><Title>pinhighshot...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356614875031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 08:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad to see your appointment as judge, jury, and executioner has been confirmed. Did they also crown you king of the fools, or have you just been paying too much attention to Sir Echo?</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1356630418990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 12:46:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356630767736-25</Id><Topic><Title>Weaver grip</Title><Username>josieinib</Username><Timestamp>1356564095100</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 18:21:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the press wants to 'out' legitimate gun owners that have legally purchased and registered their guns, why not publish the percentage of those that have ever been convicted of a crime against another person? Compare that to the general population and those that get their guns illegally. I'll bet the differences would be staggering. Legal gun owners are by and large not criminals, before or after obtaining their guns. Restricting gun ownership more than it is today only allows the criminals to allay their fears of being shot by their victims. Chicago has some of the toughest gun laws in the nation and a high crime rate.</Msg><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1356630767736</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 12:52:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356630861968-26</Id><Title>AT&amp;T Chart looks ominous</Title><Msg>About a week ago the 50 DMA crossed below the 200 DMA and T has been dropping ever since. Now T is trading below the lower Bollinger Band which is at $33.48. At $33.33, only 15 cents under the band, it is not yet a panic and volume is below average so don't rush out and sell. However a stop loss at $32.96 might be a good idea. Bollinger theory holds that, when the bands get close together, a breakout up or down is indicated. Often the initial breakout is swiftly reversed and a breakout occurs in the opposite direction. My point is, AT&amp;T should be watched very closely for the rest of the year. A month ago I predicted a flat December and that has certainly occurred. I also predicted a jump to $40 starting in February. It now looks as if that might start in January. http://finance.yahoo.com/echarts?s=T#symbol=t;range=1y;compare=;indicator=dividend+bollinger+sma%28200%29+ema+volume+stochasticslow+rsi;charttype=candlestick;crosshair=on;ohlcvalues=1;logscale=off;source=undefined;</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1356630861968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 12:54:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356631150686-27</Id><Topic><Title>Sidwell Friends School sounds like a very safe place for children</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356558043024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:40:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ricky says; You are involved in a conversation I have no part in about things which occurred 10 years before my birth. I guess unless it supports his points, he has no interest in or knowledge of history. How convenient!</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1356631150686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 12:59:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356633448795-28</Id><Topic><Title>Sidwell Friends School sounds like a very safe place for children</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356558043024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:40:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It may be physically safe but I bet the curriculum is very slanted toward Communism. I wouldn't want my kid going there.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1356633448795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 13:37:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356634909703-29</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Chart looks ominous</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1356630861968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 12:54:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, if no one else is watching the chart, let me report that T dropped as low as $33.26 and volume remains low. However there is a report that insider trading volume is running high. Does anyone know where I can find out if they are buying or selling?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1356634909703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 14:01:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356635451398-30</Id><Topic><Title>Sidwell Friends School sounds like a very safe place for children</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356558043024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:40:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again, winholder, I question the priorities of people who are willing to pay to bring guns into schools but not teachers. I question the sensibilities of people who discuss inequality in education and focus on armed guards over the quality of education provided. There is something fundamentally wrong with that viewpoint. The wild west is not a model for our schools. You are not willing to invest in schools, teachers, computers, head start, mental health, STEM labs or anything else that will improve our society. But a bunch of armed guards? Gotta have that. A war on drugs? Gotta have that. A military twice the size of the rest of the worlds? Gotta have that. A giant prison population? Gotta have that. It is reflective of everything that is wrong with your way of thinking. Get the guns off the streets. Stop the shooting. Stop the killing. That is a better society. Not turning our classrooms into the OK Corral.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356635451398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 14:10:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356637404527-31</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Chart looks ominous</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1356630861968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 12:54:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The last couple of days of 2012 are going to smack T down but good unless the fiscal cliff is avoided. This could drop a couple of more $$ by New Years Day. Nobody wants to pay a 40% dividend tax. The rest of the stuff (DMA's,etc.) is irrelevant right now until the cliff issue is settled.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1356637404527</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 14:43:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356637822406-32</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne La Pierre For President</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356111777788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zimmerman followed, harassed and shot an innocent kid who did NOT have burglary tools. He was told to not follow and harass the kid by police. Martin was visiting a friend in the neighborhood, he was not committing any crime. Zimmerman behaved recklessly, went out looking for trouble, and he found it. He ended up killing a teenager and ruining his own life. We do not need more "good guys" like Zimmerman thinking they're keeping people safe. Trayvon Martin is dead and he should not be dead. The more Zimmerman's we have in our schools or in our neighborhoods, armed with assault rifles no less, the more that story will be repeated, and the more innocent blood will be spilled by the the "good guys". Y'all watched too many John Wayne movies in your youth.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356637822406</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 14:50:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356638609879-33</Id><Topic><Title>Sidwell Friends School sounds like a very safe place for children</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356558043024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:40:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I bet the curriculum is very slanted toward Communism." I'll take that bet.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356638609879</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 15:03:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356640223170-34</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1356577227990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 22:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 40 years the Democrats ruled Congress? You mean from 1955 to 1995? Winholder, Federal spending as a proportion of GDP was pretty stable until Reagan took office, when it began to grow and deficit spending became the norm. It declined again under Bush I &amp; Clinton, who insisted on closing the deficit by paying for our spending. Spending began to grow as a percentage of GDP under Bush II and a Republican Congress--who again financed this spending through debt instead of taxes. Borrowing and spending leads to higher spending overall. When deficit spending is the norm spending goes up no matter who controls what branch of government. Spending moderates when their is a commitment to paying as you go. Pay for your stuff as you go and you will have less spending overall. The idea that we should shrink government by deficit spending the country into bankruptcy is insane. This is why I mock you. You deserve it. You should be used to it by now, as I'm sure I'm not the only one who mocks you. If anything, I do not mock you enough, and should redouble my efforts.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356640223170</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 15:30:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356640660222-35</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Obama Giving 17 Fighter Jets to the brotherhood?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356619460727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 09:44:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why wouldn't he?</Msg><Username>stuf3131</Username><Timestamp>1356640660222</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 15:37:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356640853063-36</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Chart looks ominous</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1356630861968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 12:54:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just bought at 33.24, and I am here to make money. Actually, I am not optimistic on stocks overall, so I'm looking for safety and dividends, not the short term. You can do a lot worse than T.</Msg><Username>stuf3131</Username><Timestamp>1356640853063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 15:40:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356645442416-37</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Obama Giving 17 Fighter Jets to the brotherhood?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356619460727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 09:44:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another person who should not have access to an AR-15.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356645442416</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 16:57:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356649001395-38</Id><Title>did you add today? 5.4% div was there for a minute or 2</Title><Msg>AT&amp;T Inc ( NYSE : T ) Year Declaration Date Ex-Dividend Date Record Date Payable Date Dividend $ Amount 2013 Nov 07, 2012 Jan 08, 2013 Jan 10, 2013 Feb 01, 2013 0.4500 2013 Total: 0.4500 2012 Sep 29, 2012 Oct 05, 2012 Oct 10, 2012 Nov 01, 2012 0.4400 2012 Jun 29, 2012 Jul 06, 2012 Jul 10, 2012 Aug 01, 2012 0.4400 2012 Mar 30, 2012 Apr 05, 2012 Apr 10, 2012 May 01, 2012 0.4400 2012 Dec 16, 2011 Jan 06, 2012 Jan 10, 2012 Feb 01, 2012 0.4400 2012 Total: 1.7600 2011 Sep 30, 2011 Oct 05, 2011 Oct 10, 2011 Nov 01, 2011 0.4300 2011 Jun 24, 2011 Jul 06, 2011 Jul 08, 2011 Aug 01, 2011 0.4300 2011 Mar 25, 2011 Apr 06, 2011 Apr 08, 2011 May 02, 2011 0.4300 2011 Dec 17, 2010 Jan 06, 2011 Jan 10, 2011 Feb 01, 2011 0.4300 2011 Total: 1.7200 2010 Sep 24, 2010 Oct 06, 2010 Oct 08, 2010 Nov 01, 2010 0.4200 2010 Jun 25, 2010 Jul 07, 2010 Jul 09, 2010 Aug 02, 2010 0.4200 2010 Mar 26, 2010 Apr 07, 2010 Apr 09, 2010 May 03, 2010 0.4200 2010 Dec 18, 2009 Jan 06, 2010 Jan 08, 2010 Feb 01, 2010 0.4200 2010 Total: 1.6800 2009 Sep 25, 2009 Oct 07, 2009 Oct 09, 2009 Nov 02, 2009 0.4100 2009 Jun 26, 2009 Jul 08, 2009 Jul 10, 2009 Aug 03, 2009 0.4100 2009 Mar 27, 2009 Apr 07, 2009 Apr 09, 2009 May 01, 2009 0.4100 2009 Dec 12, 2008 Jan 07, 2009 Jan 09, 2009 Feb 02, 2009 0.4100 2009 Total: 1.6400 2008 Sep 26, 2008 Oct 08, 2008 Oct 10, 2008 Nov 03, 2008 0.4000 2008 Jun 27, 2008 Jul 08, 2008 Jul 10, 2008 Aug 01, 2008 0.4000 2008 Mar 28, 2008 Apr 08, 2008 Apr 10, 2008 May 01, 2008 0.4000 2008 Dec 11, 2007 Jan 08, 2008 Jan 10, 2008 Feb 01, 2008 0.4000 2008 Total: 1.6000 2007 Sep 28, 2007 Oct 05, 2007 Oct 10, 2007 Nov 01, 2007 0.3550 2007 Jun 29, 2007 Jul 06, 2007 Jul 10, 2007 Aug 01, 2007 0.3550 2007 Mar 30, 2007 Apr 05, 2007 Apr 10, 2007 May 01, 2007 0.3550 2007 Dec 15, 2006 Jan 08, 2007 Jan 10, 2007 Feb 01, 2007 0.3550 2007 Total: 1.4200</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1356649001395</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 17:56:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356652886970-39</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Obama Giving 17 Fighter Jets to the brotherhood?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356619460727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 09:44:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought Obama won the Peace Prize. They admitted, they were a little bit early, but he would eventually live up to the award. Giving crazy zealots access to these weapons of mass destruction, can't lead anywhere good. Does Barry remember what happened on 9/11?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356652886970</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 19:01:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356653762613-40</Id><Title>Betcha Barry Will settle Dockworkers Strike.</Title><Msg>Why? His handlers, the Chinese demand it. Or else, no more loans for his redistribution/welfare programs. Plus, no one will be able to buy all that quality merchandise.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356653762613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 19:16:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356653911378-41</Id><Topic><Title>Could 2013 be the Last Year for Your Employer Paid Plan?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356202702130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:58:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, Illegal Mexicans will be covered. One way, or another, on that you can be sure.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356653911378</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 19:18:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356656606349-42</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Obama Giving 17 Fighter Jets to the brotherhood?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356619460727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 09:44:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Al Queda and the Muslim Brotherhood are and have been fronts for our and Britains intelligence agencies. The Muslim Brotherhoods sponsorship goes back to the 1920's. All part of the NWO's plans for the global plantation.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1356656606349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 20:03:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356658965528-43</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Obama Giving 17 Fighter Jets to the brotherhood?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356619460727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 09:44:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love the phrase "weapons of mass destruction". That says it all especially when used with "Does Barry remember what happened on 9/11". W was reading Billy the Goat. Then he attacks Iraq based on the report about weapons of mass destruction when the enemy was, in fact, in Afganistan. Instead of paying for the war with a war tax, W decreases taxes, mostly for the rich, and allows the banks complete freedom and no regulation. Once Barry is elected but not yet sworn in he tries to get him involved in the bank bailout. So now, let's all be critical of the President. We should have elected another Republican. Have you, at long last, have no.........</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1356658965528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 20:42:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>