<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-17"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355754257952-1</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355537341551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:09:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In my opinion there is an important difference between a mentally unstable person and a mentally unstable person with access to AR-15 M4 .223 Bushmaster semi-automatic assault rifles. The difference is that a mentally unstable person with access to an AR-15 M4 .223 Bushmaster semi-automatic assault rifles can kill 20 children and 6 adults in a little over 2 minutes, as demonstrated in the attack in Newtown on Friday. A plain old mentally unstable person cannot. Try as you might, you cannot wrest this horror from the weapon that made it possible. This is the price we pay for having an armed citizenry. You should be thinking about whether that price is worth it, not pretending there is no price to pay. Republicans these days want to pretend that everything is free and there are no consequences. You're dominated by single interests, whether it be the NRA or Grover Norquist. It is time for you to start thinking about your country and its children. Not your guns and your tax bill.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355754257952</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 09:24:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355755044313-2</Id><Topic><Title>Many that commit this sort of act have had their brains fried on various types of dope.</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355562036359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 04:00:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My response was deleted. You can and will be traced.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1355755044313</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 09:37:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355755659390-3</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355537341551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:09:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Republicans these days want to pretend that everything is free and there are no consequences" A very, very bizarre statement given your team of lilberals!</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1355755659390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 09:47:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355756436217-4</Id><Topic><Title>Amazing !!!</Title><Username>orlandoorlando034</Username><Timestamp>1341145210000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-01 08:20:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will take a look at this.</Msg><Username>louisestephen288</Username><Timestamp>1355756436217</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 10:00:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355758460747-5</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355537341551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:09:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People have a constitutional right to possess firearms. People also have the burden to bear to be responsible for those guns. If you have small children or mentally unstable people near or with access to those weapons, you're not being responsible unless they are secured. Yes, guns will kill you but they need to be operated by SOMEONE in order to do so. If they begin to prosecute those responsible for allowing access to weapons by people that should have no such access, perhaps they will begin to be more responsible. But it isn't just guns used irresponsibly that kill people, auto's, drugs, fire, etc. can and are used as well. It is not the weapon of choice but the responsibility to prevent those who are not stable access to such weapons. You cannot legislate away stupidity, mental illness, or just plain evil. Don't get me wrong, this is a terrible tragedy and should not have happened, but if mom had kept her collection locked away from her unstable son, perhaps he would have only ended his life.</Msg><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1355758460747</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 10:34:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355758591658-6</Id><Topic><Title>Many that commit this sort of act have had their brains fried on various types of dope.</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355562036359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 04:00:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Recess is over children, the teacher is calling you back into class. You had better hurry before you end up in the principal’s office.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1355758591658</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 10:36:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355759467747-7</Id><Topic><Title>Many that commit this sort of act have had their brains fried on various types of dope.</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355562036359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 04:00:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ooooohh! Terrel, more lies and fantasies. You really should spend more time in church...you're way too far down Satan's path "my friend". And germane to lv66vette's question, what do you propose to do with the information once "Raptor" ("Marvin" from Geek Squad) finds it for you? Shake your knobby little fist at me and cry out, "Vendetta"? Why not go ahead and post another of your charming little violent threats on here for public consumption? Marvin's time would likely be more productively spent helping you remove from the internet all of the absurdly personal information you have connected with your Yahoo ID. Then you should stop playing with the computer. It's too complicated for you. If you do think that you want to find me - I know that you are too much of a neutered old blow hard to actually show up to our meeting - let Marvin know that I use an anonymizer for all my internet traffic.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355759467747</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 10:51:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355759755593-8</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355537341551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:09:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “SO FAR .. you, like the "media" are falsly (sic) reporting !!” – jon the gun runner From your own gospel news source, Fox News, Dec. 15, 11:27 p.m “NEWTOWN, Conn. (AP) — The gunman in the Newton, Conn., school shooting was prepared for a massacre... The murder weapon: — Bushmaster .223-caliber: lightweight with a high capacity The medical examiner in Connecticut said it appeared all the children and school staff were shot with the same high-powered rifle, some repeatedly, some at close range.” Hey, jon boy. Guess what, pal? It’s time. Fock you, the tea party and the NRA!! Enough is enough. The President’s speech last night was prophetically inspirational. Not unlike the other issues he deals with in attempting to make America a better place for ALL Americans, the gun laws are now in his sights. You crack pot survivalists can cry Constitutional infringement all you want. The 2nd Amendment states the following: “ A well regulated militia being necessary to the security of a free state, the right of the people to keep and bear arms shall not be infringed.” Besides skin-heads and white supremacists survivalist types, who among us claims to be part of a militia, well-regulated or otherwise? They were talking about single shot blunderbuss’s, not today’s semi-and fully-automatic killing machines. Compare our gun control laws with almost any other country on the planet, and you’ll see why we are still looked at as wild-west, lunatic cowboys by the civilized nations of the world. I lived in England in the 70’s when the Bobbies didn’t even carry weapons, and in countries like Japan, the safety of the citizenry is insured by making it difficult to get access to weapons. The argument that only criminals will then have guns is #$%$. Change the law, and ENFORCE serious consequences for possession of illegal firearms. Stop this foolishness...Let the gun legislation debate begin. We should take a serious look at mental health legislation at the same time.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355759755593</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 10:55:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355760439898-9</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355537341551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:09:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jon, AR-15s were used in this shooting, and in the theater shooting in Aurora CO and in the recent mall shooting in Portland OR. The simple fact that I have a list of mass shootings to give you should give you pause. Stop with your mindless partisanship, please.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355760439898</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 11:07:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355760526102-10</Id><Topic><Title>T is one of top picks like crimson on apex</Title><Username>ethelvillarreal43</Username><Timestamp>1353943269318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:21:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Helpful</Msg><Username>ralphlee519</Username><Timestamp>1355760526102</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 11:08:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355762030967-11</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1355761404951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 11:23:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This guy, for instance, should never, ever have access to an AR-15. He's looney toons. Yet he could probably buy one easily and legally for less than $500. Granted, cowards like Lavendar are also known to run over children with trucks. But they cannot kill 26 people in a little over 2 minutes with a truck. Might he find another way? Certainly, if he had the brains and consistent drive to do so and could do so alone and without tipping anyone off. It takes little by way of brains, collaboration or consistent effort to buy and use an AR-15. That makes the AR-15 a perfect weapon for delusional, moronic losers like Lavlew. This is a problem. BTW, thanks for being so ridiculously predictable, Lavlew.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355762030967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 11:33:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355763412370-12</Id><Title>This has become one tough stock to move up..</Title><Msg>..continued dumping through the rest of the month/year likely.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1355763412370</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 11:56:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355763590651-13</Id><Topic><Title>Will T ever see $38 again?</Title><Username>icdcweb</Username><Timestamp>1355320645525</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 08:57:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>probably 28 before 38</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1355763590651</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 11:59:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355763632172-14</Id><Topic><Title>T WILL SEE $68.00 IN THE NEXT 2 YEARS</Title><Username>blackoilpeaking</Username><Timestamp>1355341935051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 14:52:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1355763632172</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 12:00:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355769408438-15</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355537341551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:09:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>50% of this board shouldn't be licensed for a water pistol!</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1355769408438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 13:36:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355771700749-16</Id><Title>Ascending Triangle</Title><Msg>It's do or die time this week for big T.</Msg><Username>xtgeminiman</Username><Timestamp>1355771700749</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 14:15:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355772295841-17</Id><Topic><Title>Ascending Triangle</Title><Username>xtgeminiman</Username><Timestamp>1355771700749</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 14:15:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Descending share price.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1355772295841</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 14:24:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355773297330-18</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355537341551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:09:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The largest school killing in American history was in the late 20's and he didn't use a gun, he used dynamite. Mass killings in this country, while the media won't report this, are actually down over the past decade from many years in the 30's and 50's. Illegal’s walk into this country every day and we can't stop them. Guns, if they are prohibited in this country, will do the same and then only the police and the bad guys will have guns. The police are not plentiful enough to stop all the bad guys with guns, but a bad guy will think twice if he fears that a citizen might have a gun and doesn't have to follow the same rules of engagement as the police. They are legalizing pot and that will slow the smuggling from Mexico and other places. Pot growers make millions off what they ship to the U.S. They will simply replace their pot with guns. They will run a Fast and Furious coming in our direction. That is not acceptable. Tragedies happen around the world on a regular basis and we will never be able to stop them. A fool, head case, or just plain idiot with bad intentions will find a way.</Msg><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1355773297330</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 14:41:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355773528785-19</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1355761404951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 11:23:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The media, which you liberals think are the truth masters have also reported that the killer tried to buy a weapon and was turned away because of the current gun laws. The fact that his mother was apparently a fool or just plain stupid is not being reported. She has a kid with mental issues and her way of bonding with him is shooting guns????? She is dead of course, but where is her accountability in this situation?</Msg><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1355773528785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 14:45:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355773672810-20</Id><Topic><Title>Many that commit this sort of act have had their brains fried on various types of dope.</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355562036359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 04:00:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah and my dad can whip both your dads. Geez, grow up.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1355773672810</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 14:47:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355773790719-21</Id><Title>I'm going to bite the bullet, too!!!!</Title><Msg>I'm going to bite the bullet, too!!!! Obama ordered the cabinet to cut $100,000,000.00 ($100 million) from the $3,500,000,000,000.00 ($3.5 trillion) federal budget. I'm so impressed by this sacrifice that I have decided to do the same thing with my personal budget. I spend about $2,000 a month on groceries, household expenses, medicine, utilities, etc., but it's time to get out the budget cutting axe, go through my expenses, and cut back. I'm going to cut my spending at exactly the same ratio (1/35,000) of my total budget. After doing the math, it looks like instead of spending $2,000 a month, I'm going to have to cut that number by six cents. Yes, I'm going to have to get by with $1999.94, but that's what sacrifice is all about. I'll just have to do without some things, that are, frankly, luxuries – six cents worth. Did Obama actually think no one would do the math? "There are two ways to conquer and enslave a nation... One is by sword...the other is by debt." John Adams 1826</Msg><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1355773790719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 14:49:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355775553893-22</Id><Topic><Title>Show Me The Money! T Style!</Title><Username>esthershannon539</Username><Timestamp>1354972028259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 08:07:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good alert</Msg><Username>allensolo</Username><Timestamp>1355775553893</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 15:19:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355781510444-23</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355537341551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:09:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"he used dynamite" Do you know why they don't use dynamite anymore? It's illegal for most people to purchase dynamite. If your argument is we shouldn't do anything about mass killing of children because we have an irrational immigration policy, a pointless war on drugs and we have gutted our public sector law enforcement I don't know what to say to that except you have again reaped the wages of policies most conservatives support. I do not support any of those policies and certainly am not willing to pay for them with children's lives.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355781510444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 16:58:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355781760733-24</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355537341551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:09:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"So one can imagine the "political spin" afterwards - to re-define the actual crime scene !!" I am arguing with nutjobs. Complete paranoid delusional nutjobs. Jon, you are another person who should not have access to AR-15s, ever.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355781760733</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 17:02:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355782175162-25</Id><Title>Wack job, jon...</Title><Msg>... “So one can imagine the ‘political spin’ afterwards - to re-define the actual crime scene !!” – retarded jon the wacko conspiracy theorist “The Connecticut state medical examiner revealed that the suspect in the shooting deaths of 26 people at an elementary school used the most powerful weapon at his disposal “The .223 Bushmaster rifle, once thought to be recovered in the suspect’s car, was the main weapon in the fatal shootings. All the victims died as a result of gunshot wounds from the rifle, and all the students were in the first grade. Chief Medical Examiner H. Wayne Carver II said during a news conference.” Jon, you need help, son. You don’t know what happened there, I don’t know what happened there and, obviously, the news sources have delivered different versions of events, people and time lines. Above is what the Chief Medical Examiner is saying happened. But for you to continue to pretend you’re some kind of mouthpiece of the far right by suggesting that this is all a conspiracy by the Main Stream Media (which exists only in your demented view of the world) to promote gun control legislation, is beyond preposterous. You are one sorry individual…like the pimply-faced, 98 pound illiterate losers suffering from total lack of self-esteem who hang around gun shows in cammies with white power tats and a mullet. Take your garbage talk up to Newton, talk to some grieving parents and tell them your insidious, nutball theory, you pathetic little dipstick.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355782175162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 17:09:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355783896089-26</Id><Topic><Title>Many that commit this sort of act have had their brains fried on various types of dope.</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355562036359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 04:00:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny how my answers are deleted. There are ways of tracing people.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1355783896089</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 17:38:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355786168086-27</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355537341551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 21:09:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ricky, Why are you more upset and obsessed with AR-15's than the fact that these precious children were killed at all? Two Glock 22, .40 caliber handguns could have done this damage and more, and they'd be infinitely more concealable. A demented individual will find a way to do his evil regardless of your selective type of gun control on AR-15 rifles. By all means, please share with us your "list of mass shootings". And then, compare your list to the number of automobile related deaths in the U.S. Every year for the last 62 years those deaths have exceeded 32,367 each and every year. There have been well over 2 MILLION of them since 1950! Do you also advocate "automobile control" too? After all, if there were no cars = no car deaths. Same illogical argument as your gun control fantasy! P.S.: When you and your fellow leftists come to try and take the AR-15 from my house, I suggest y'all better be wearing your "big boy pants"!!!</Msg><Username>gms47cb</Username><Timestamp>1355786168086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 18:16:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355786466568-28</Id><Topic><Title>Reply to ricky...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355182398460</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 18:33:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Best in progressive thought available daily at MoveOn's website. Today: Joe Scarborough, long time gun advocate, changes his mind about gun control. It's time to regain our school yards, movie theaters, and college campuses from users of assault weapons having the ability to shoot multiple victims in a few seconds.</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1355786466568</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 18:21:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355797362236-29</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1355761404951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 11:23:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"where is her accountability in this situation?" Dead. But even if she was alive and being persecuted would it make a difference? If your plan to prevent mass killings with assault rifles is that 315 million Americans be 100% responsible 100 percent of the time, I think that may be prone to failure. What do you think is the difference between an assault rifle and, say, dynamite, grenades or claymores? Why is even a single shot gun with a caliber over .50 illegal, but an assault rifle not legal? What is the difference, or do you think these should be legal too?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355797362236</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 21:22:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355805876865-30</Id><Topic><Title>T is one of top picks like crimson on apex</Title><Username>ethelvillarreal43</Username><Timestamp>1353943269318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:21:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ethel, I nominate you to be the next US Secretary of State for your clarity and comprehensive reporting.</Msg><Username>jpmax6</Username><Timestamp>1355805876865</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 23:44:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>