<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344088869000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Telecom DD/ Research/ Homework</Title><Username>vwdiesel10</Username><Timestamp>1344025788000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:29:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10-k and 10-q for T and VZ (invested in both, but interested to see dynamics between the two). I read the write-ups done on any new programs or fees as they come along the news wire. I read the industry write-ups on Telecom providers and the equipment manufacturers written up and found through access to the Standard and Poors and FirstResearch databases, as well as the ValueLine company and industry specific quarterly reports. Anything else that I would be missing?</Msg><Username>vwdiesel10</Username><Timestamp>1344088869000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344091223000-2</Id><Title>OWS and SEIU protesters turn on Obama</Title><Msg>OWS joined by SEIU protesters fed up with controlling democrat political one percenters take out frustration on Obama's Okaland campaign office. OAKLAND, Calif. – Police say protesters marching through downtown Oakland smashed a window at President Barack Obama's campaign office. Officials say the window at Obama's office at 16th Street and Telegraph Avenue was broken as more than 100 protesters marched around 9 p.m. Friday. Read more: http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/08/04/protesters-smash-window-at-obama-oakland-office/?utm_source=feedburner&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+foxnews%2Fpolitics+%28Internal+-+Politics+-+Text%29&amp;utm_content=My+Yahoo#ixzz22aX1Fgix</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1344091223000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:40:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344099788000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Read this new report on AT&amp;T</Title><Username>ermelindaarcia</Username><Timestamp>1344091577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SCAM...........</Msg><Username>catspaw33129</Username><Timestamp>1344099788000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:03:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344100215000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Paused, consolidated, and resuming the move higher now!</Title><Username>sblowmeh</Username><Timestamp>1344006058000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:00:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will make new high this coming week. The volume yesterday was the lowest in over two weeks. Institutions love this stock and investors looking for a high dividend ALS o will push it higher. Money went into stocks that were oversold on Friday. T &amp; VZ will move up this coming week. After new highs we may have a small correction. The dividend keeps coming!</Msg><Username>catspaw33129</Username><Timestamp>1344100215000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344103340000-5</Id><Title>Chart Pattern - Acceleration from $35 to $38 per share</Title><Msg>What do you make of the recent acceleration in price from $35 to $38 per share? The slope of the rise is quite steep and probably not sustainable. Also note the outperformance relative to the S&amp;P 500. http://finance.yahoo.com/q/bc?s=T&amp;t=6m&amp;l=on&amp;z=l&amp;q=l&amp;c=^GSPC Possible factors could be the recent article in Barron's, along with the popularity of large cap stocks and high dividend paying stocks. What about the Telecom ETFs? If money is coming into those funds, they have to buy AT&amp;T at whatever price is offered. I guess the question is whether Telecom continues to outperform or whether traders rotate to other sectors in the market.</Msg><Username>KAWill</Username><Timestamp>1344103340000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 14:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344103897000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Chart Pattern - Acceleration from $35 to $38 per share</Title><Username>KAWill</Username><Timestamp>1344103340000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 14:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is a link that should work showing performance relative to the S&amp;P 500 Index. http://finance.yahoo.com/q/bc?t=6m&amp;s=T&amp;l=on&amp;z=l&amp;q=l&amp;c=VFINX%2C+&amp;ql=1 This chart compares AT&amp;T to the Vanguard S&amp;P 500 Index Fund.</Msg><Username>KAWill</Username><Timestamp>1344103897000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 14:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344114057000-7</Id><Topic><Title>I REMEMBER BACK IN THE 90'S WHEN ATT</Title><Username>gay_blew</Username><Timestamp>1343948781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:06:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And then at&amp;t proceeded to claim medical costs were soaring out of control. Thats when coverage started costing more and covering less. I think the unions were backing the same sex coverage for some reason.</Msg><Username>gay_blew</Username><Timestamp>1344114057000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:00:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344117347000-8</Id><Topic><Title>I REMEMBER BACK IN THE 90'S WHEN ATT</Title><Username>gay_blew</Username><Timestamp>1343948781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:06:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"AT&amp;T PROCEEDED TO CLAIM MEDICAL COSTS WERE SOARING OUT OF CONTROL." It can't be lost on you that medical costs indeed are soaring. Surely you can't believe it is primarily a result of covering same sex marriage. Medicaid and Medicare are killing the American taxpayer and reeking havoc on the federal budget (if one existed) and deficit. The difference between the Feds and T is that T has the will to do something about it. Cities are going down in part because they provide "free" health care to city employees along with other lavish benefits. A growing number of states are also headed for trouble. Now private sector taxpayers are saying enough is enough. Simply put, the "free" health care model doesn't work and it is going down everywhere because nothing is free. The good ol' days are over.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344117347000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:55:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344120505000-9</Id><Topic><Title>I REMEMBER BACK IN THE 90'S WHEN ATT</Title><Username>gay_blew</Username><Timestamp>1343948781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:06:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GB, I think you are trying to make orange juice with out oranges. Does not matter if spouse or partner, same coverage. And, if you buy a child or have one the old fashion way, same covrage. T like the Big 3, is having issues with "legacy" cost. Once appon a time, retirees did not live to 75-80 years of age. Go back over the last 10 years and see how muchnthe UAW have "gave back". Basically, retirees paying for health care. Throw in how many T employees are old with knee, hip, and back problems...And in the Big CA how many are FLMA kings and queens. Ya ya ya, migrains and stress. Being gay with a same sex partner is not one of T big issues. Actually, it is so common, no one cares No one</Msg><Username>josieinib</Username><Timestamp>1344120505000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:48:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344129144000-10</Id><Topic><Title>I REMEMBER BACK IN THE 90'S WHEN ATT</Title><Username>gay_blew</Username><Timestamp>1343948781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:06:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But something clicked In my mind .. going into a store, finding a baby that you want..going to checkout .. swiping it's "butt" across the scanner and - ching ching." Hopefully you're in the 10 or less line.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1344129144000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 21:12:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>