<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348113757591-1</Id><Topic><Title>COULD WE POSSIBLY WANT A MUSLIM PRESIDENT</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1347982764850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:39:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get rid of OBlammer!</Msg><Username>jotrout</Username><Timestamp>1348113757591</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348113849469-2</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Media &amp; Yahoo (??) "Romney Poll"</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1347981999544</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:26:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get rid of OBlammer!</Msg><Username>jotrout</Username><Timestamp>1348113849469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:04:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348136142603-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obamcare Tax increase hits Middle and lower income earners hard</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348106076765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you cut and paste, it wouldn’t kill you to include the part that addresses what you are constantly complaining about – you know “subsidizing those who can afford to pay but don’t” Aha, creative editing done by the “fair and balanced” people, as usual. From the article you quote: “A spokesman for the Obama Administration said 98 percent of Americans will not be affected by the tax penalty — and suggested that those who will be should face up to their civic responsibilities. ‘This (analysis) doesn't change the basic fact that the individual responsibility policy will only affect people who can afford health care but choose not to buy it,’ said Erin Shields Britt of the Health and Human Services Department. ‘We're no longer going to subsidize the care of those who can afford to buy insurance but make a choice not to buy it.’ The budget office said most of the increase in its estimate is due to changes in underlying projections about the economy, incorporating the effects of new federal legislation, as well as higher unemployment and lower wages.”</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348136142603</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348136481497-4</Id><Title>Re - redistribution...</Title><Msg>“Obama wants to take your money you worked hard for and give it so someone else. Obama tells the audience he believes there has been ‘a propaganda campaign against the possibility of government action and its efficacy.’ Here’s what he said 14 years ago, about seven years prior to the time Mitt Romney was doing the same thing by inventing Obamacare (Universal Health Care) in Mass. ‘I think that what we're going to have to do is somehow resuscitate the notion that government action can be effective at all,’ Obama says. ‘I think the trick is figuring out how do we structure government systems that pool resources and hence facilitate some redistribution -- because I actually believe in redistribution, at least at a certain level to make sure that everybody's got a shot.’ Now if you paid shills want to construe that as something that today’s sitting President of the United States said 14 years ago as him being a “communist, socialist, illegal immigrant attempting to take over the government” or your other silly claims, go with it. You apparently are incapable of fathoming that this demagoguery is taking you down the road of defeat. We, of sanity, understand it to be a plea to have some fiscal responsibility with our tax dollars, with the extremely wealthy paying their fair share, and with redistributing the way our tax dollars are spent. That does not imply the Robin Hood concept of taking from the rich to feed the poor. It DOES, however mean making Government run efficiently, without the corporate special interest subsidies that do nothing for the average American, while lining the pockets of the privileged few. Contrary to what you right-wing, self-interested crackpots believe, most Americans would rather see our taxes going to rebuilding this country and providing jobs for our own citizens...not a bloated defense budget based on you war-mongering, profit driven, self-interested two percenters, who would deny equal educational opportunities and health benefits to the vast majority of Americans, while using Bogey-Man scare tactics into fooling Americans to line your pockets. If someone really wants to complain about the violence in the world, one need only examine where the ARMS INDUSTRY resides. In your back yard, brother. We are not only the hands down defense spender by some 17 fold, but we are also the largest exporter of weapons to friends and foe, alike. Do I, and many others like me who have seen this insidiousness up-close and personal and been fooled into participating in it, feel that redistributing our priorities to benefit more Americans than the good old boy network of the status quo makes sense? Yes, indeed, we do. And do we feel that the extremely small percent at the top who have benefited by corporate welfare and special interest subsidies should pay their fair share, rather than putting the burden of a social safety net solely on the backs of the middle class? You better believe we do! And if you want to call that “redistribution” to add another buzz word to your propaganda arsenal along with “socialist”, “liberal” “Kenyan” and the rest of the birther nonsense, be my guest. The real America sees through who’s really behind all this regardless of the Citizens United decision which, essentially, enabled the auctioning off of political power in this country. You can continue to attempt to lie, deceive and cheat Americans as you will, but your reign is over. This is a done deal. Thanks tea-party, thanks bigots, thanks intellectual lightweights, for showing the way to moderately sane people concerned about each other. Clearly, you are not concerned about America.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348136481497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:21:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348138987306-5</Id><Title>Razz... where are you!</Title><Msg>I need some sanity on this board and can't wait until the elections is over! I hope you and yours are OK!</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1348138987306</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:03:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348146762143-6</Id><Title>Planetary Alignment</Title><Msg>Three key alignments on Sept. 21 2011 (Jupiter-Venus-Sun), (Saturn-Mercury-Sun) and (Mercury-Earth-Uranus) as well as other significant astrological aspects involving Uranus and the Moon which may represent a possible 6.9 Magnitude earthquake on this day.. ====================================== Will this effect cell phones?</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1348146762143</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348150521038-7</Id><Topic><Title>Re - redistribution...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348136481497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well put. Most on here are bigots, and don't see most of these Republicans are screwing them also. They are in office to protect the interests of corporations and the ultra rich. They con them with the old wedge issues of the 3 G,s...God, Guns and Gays. Get ready for four more years of a black family in your White House. Ha! Ha!</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1348150521038</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348151675261-8</Id><Title>Can you get free cell phone service with food stamps ?</Title><Msg>I was told if you get food stamps you get 250 min different companies. If you get free lunch at school you get free DSL, $250 for a PC and $150 for a modem.</Msg><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1348151675261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348151729887-9</Id><Topic><Title>As usual</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1348086025591</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:20:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trying 38.00 again Mike. Will it hold?</Msg><Username>dave_martin_2244</Username><Timestamp>1348151729887</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:35:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152614876-10</Id><Topic><Title>Can you get free cell phone service with food stamps ?</Title><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1348151675261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:34:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a country!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348152614876</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:50:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348153300071-11</Id><Topic><Title>Can you get free cell phone service with food stamps ?</Title><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1348151675261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:34:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It does not stop there. The Y what used to be the YMCA costs $800 per year plus $80 for paper work. If you get food stamps you get full membership free. They show up after 11 AM with 6 shorties. They put them in Y daycare and sit in the hot tub. They play get to do all teams for free but for members you have to pay $70 per activity. We left. The average IQ was 50. People in the parking lot are having sex and using drugs. You smell pot all the time.</Msg><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1348153300071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:01:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348153587569-12</Id><Topic><Title>Re - redistribution...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348136481497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ha, Ha. Get ready for a total collapse of this economy. Brought on by people such as those that run Goldman-Sachs. Goldman-Sachs is one of the largest contributors to Liver Lip's campaigns. Liver Lips is also in bed with international currency manipulator George Soros. Soros and Liver Lips have been in bed together for ten years. Their first association came through ACORN which Soros founded. When the war starts in the Middle East your freedoms will be gone. You will either knuckle under to the self styled "elite" that run BOTH parties or you might grow some ouvos and resist.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348153587569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348155432467-13</Id><Topic><Title>Can you get free cell phone service with food stamps ?</Title><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1348151675261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:34:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who do you think those folks will be voting for in November?</Msg><Username>dave_martin_2244</Username><Timestamp>1348155432467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:37:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348156102105-14</Id><Topic><Title>Re - redistribution...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348136481497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Most on here are bigots" I would agree that you are a bigot, but just because many of us don't think as you do please don't include us in your bigot pool.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348156102105</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348157432687-15</Id><Topic><Title>Re - redistribution...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348136481497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got it figured you bigot whiteys do not like Barry, or Eric Holderman, who was promoted by your idol Ron Reagane. Do not know why do you? The 50k plate fundraiser tape has one in the group deriding Holderman, by the way did not see any blacks in the room. I believe Holderman would make a great addition to the Supreme Court, in Barry's second term. Oh, by the way whitey bigots this will most likely be the last major election that you can control. Even Texas is looking like a swing State. Also I might add you people are doing a damned good job of destroying the GOP.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1348157432687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:10:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348157432844-16</Id><Topic><Title>Re - redistribution...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348136481497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got it figured you bigot whiteys do not like Barry, or Eric Holderman, who was promoted by your idol Ron Reagane. Do not know why do you? The 50k plate fundraiser tape has one in the group deriding Holderman, by the way did not see any blacks in the room. I believe Holderman would make a great addition to the Supreme Court, in Barry's second term. Oh, by the way whitey bigots this will most likely be the last major election that you can control. Even Texas is looking like a swing State. Also I might add you people are doing a damned good job of destroying the GOP.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1348157432844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:10:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348157539274-17</Id><Topic><Title>Can you get free cell phone service with food stamps ?</Title><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1348151675261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:34:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Copy Cat. NO, you get it with no new taxes for the bigots.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1348157539274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348157672206-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obamcare Tax increase hits Middle and lower income earners hard</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348106076765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"“A spokesman for the Obama Administration said 98 percent of Americans will not be affected by the tax penalty " Enough said anything coming out of the mouth of Obama or someone who represents him is probably lying. evidence - The numbers from the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office are significantly higher than a previous projection by the same office in 2010, shortly after the law passed. "‘This (analysis) doesn't change the basic fact that the individual responsibility policy will only affect people who can afford health care but choose not to buy it" Who will determine if you can afford healthcare? Obamacare is extremely expensive and built on the idea everyone needs to pay for insurance or it won't work. Low income people are going to be fined if they don't pay for insurance under this plan.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348157672206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:14:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348157805356-19</Id><Topic><Title>9/11 attack designed by former Gitmo detainee</Title><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1348110435607</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:07:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Man, you should work for the FBI your great. No should tape is to be found. Plus if you were in a crisis doubt if you could save or find your posterior.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1348157805356</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:16:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348158089937-20</Id><Topic><Title>As usual</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1348086025591</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:20:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's hope so - but it's already into its daily give back routine.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1348158089937</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:21:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348158567144-21</Id><Topic><Title>Re - redistribution...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348136481497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Here’s what he said 14 years ago" So what he said it then and has not changed his beliefs. "most Americans would rather see our taxes going to rebuilding this country and providing jobs for our own citizens...not a bloated defense budget" What do you mean by bloated defense budget? Cutting healthcare our vets were promised, having ill equiped forces using outdated equipment. Americans want both jobs and a strong defense and with the right leadership we can have both.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348158567144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348158624352-22</Id><Topic><Title>As usual</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1348086025591</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:20:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least it got through 37.80 for the time being. Are you in 11374?</Msg><Username>dave_martin_2244</Username><Timestamp>1348158624352</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:30:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348159214750-23</Id><Topic><Title>Re - redistribution...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348136481497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is Ryan's plan to cut the VA. Obama has raised spending on Veteran's health, notably a $4.6 billion infusion for mental health in 2009. Obama has also vowed that Veteran's benefits will be protected if the tea party's fiscal cliff isn't fixed before 2013.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348159214750</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:40:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348160031438-24</Id><Topic><Title>Re - redistribution...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348136481497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Senate just yesterday lost some Vet Votes, They filibustered a jobs bill which we had bipartisan support on. Five GOPer crossed, but they want to stop Obama's jobs plans. VET"S vote and VOTE for your benefit. VOTE OBAMA</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1348160031438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348160031618-25</Id><Topic><Title>Re - redistribution...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348136481497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Senate just yesterday lost some Vet Votes, They filibustered a jobs bill which we had bipartisan support on. Five GOPer crossed, but they want to stop Obama's jobs plans. VET"S vote and VOTE for your benefit. VOTE OBAMA</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1348160031618</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348161017133-26</Id><Title>Obama reveals he doesn't know what national debt is and it is not his problem.</Title><Msg>Letterman conducts what Obama considers a press conference. Obama answered questions his office provided to Letterman in front of a hand picked audience. While appearing on a late night talk show, President Barack Obama displayed a contemptuous lack of concern for the significant number of Americans who care about runaway federal spending by saying that he was simply unaware of the record amount of federal debt. During the president’s appearance on CBS’ Late Show with David Letterman on Tuesday night, Obama was asked about the debt clock prominently featured at the Republican National Convention. America’s national debt exceeded $16 trillion that week – more than the nation’s GDP. Letterman asked if Obama knew the nation’s debt. “I don’t remember what the number was precisely,” Obama replied. President Obama addressed the debt and deficit, saying it is not a problem in the "short term," In other words he doesn't consider it his problem but it will be dealt with after he leaves office. The Obamas have done very well taking advantage a variety of government programs not available to everyone that have made them multi-millionaires. Whatever happens to middle income Americans does not concern them, their massive wealth will see them through whatever lies ahead. After the Letterman show President Obama capped the evening with Beyoncé, Jay-Z, and about 100 wealthy supports who each paid $40,000 for the privilege of his company at Jay-Z’s 40/40 Club where they drank $800/bottle Champagne.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348161017133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:10:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348161072917-27</Id><Topic><Title>Obamcare Tax increase hits Middle and lower income earners hard</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348106076765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obamacare is extremely expensive" With the ACA, you have a much broader choice of private insurance plans than you had previously, and more information to help you choose a plan. If you do not get insurance through your employer you will now be able to enjoy the same group pricing through the exchanges. Direct competition based on price &amp; quality in the exchanges, along with the medical loss ratio and new payment schemes leading to new efficiencies, are also likely to slow the growth of premiums, or lower them on a real basis. If you STILL cannot afford insurance, the ACA provides subsidies and expanded access to Medicaid. The ACA takes a dysfunctional market that serves no one well and begins the process of turning it into a functioning one geared towards improving health. But you do have to participate in that market. You can't just freeload at the ER every time you get sick. You are a useless person, Lavendar. You probably think the government should just provide you with free stuff because you are white. You need to stop being so lazy and dependent on the government.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348161072917</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:11:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348161350517-28</Id><Topic><Title>Can you get free cell phone service with food stamps ?</Title><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1348151675261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:34:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've never understood why people support a side they have to lie to defend. Can you explain it to me? I imagine it's mostly bitterness.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348161350517</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:15:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348161439274-29</Id><Topic><Title>Can you get free cell phone service with food stamps ?</Title><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1348151675261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:34:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am sorry you fall under the broke I need food stamp bracket. I have a lot of money Obama wants to give you via food stamps. You played the fool in school and now you are broke.</Msg><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1348161439274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348161828121-30</Id><Topic><Title>Obamcare Tax increase hits Middle and lower income earners hard</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348106076765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good, the idea was republican to get freeloaders to pay, those waiting for medicare etc to pay their expensive delayed procedures, to save themselves a few bucks in premiums. For once I agree with a republican idea. 6 billion income from it? Not bad at all. In MA it seems to be working, very few are paying the penalty. Obama, does it well every time, the guy is great..</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1348161828121</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348162089338-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obamcare Tax increase hits Middle and lower income earners hard</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348106076765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But you do have to participate in that market. You can't just freeload at the ER every time you get sick." Those who show up in the ER for free care are for the most part poor. Glad to see that you agree the poor will now have to pay for insurance or be fined "With the ACA, you have a much broader choice of private insurance plans than you had previously" The ACA is designed to drive private health insurers out of business and force everyone to a government run single payer system</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348162089338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:28:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348162481295-32</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he believes in redistribution</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348073752677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:55:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm interested to know how low you think taxes for the wealthy should be? 10%? 5%? 1%? How little should the likes of Mitt Romney and Oprah Winfrey pay? How much government support do they need before they start creating jobs? The Bush tax cuts for the top 5% already redistribute $200 billion up the income scale annually, and that's just the top 5%. Are we talking a trillion more in special tax breaks annually? Or just hundreds of billions?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348162481295</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348163055445-33</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he believes in redistribution</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348073752677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:55:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It vote for Obama or later as the rich get richer, and the poor get left behind more and more. WE WILL HAVE A BIGOT SPRING, GET READY!</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1348163055445</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348163288960-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obamcare Tax increase hits Middle and lower income earners hard</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348106076765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, we are really starting to see positive results from Romneycare in Massachusetts. You need several years to get a really good grasp on what is going on for a broad program like this, and the first analyses of Romneycare are looking pretty good. It's really Romney's signature accomplishment. It's a shame he hasn't chosen to use it to his advantage in this campaign. Romney/Obamacare is really a bipartisan policy that would benefit from broad consensus. America would benefit if leaders of both parties would embrace it. Instead, politicking by the right has turned their own policy into a well of uncertainty and distrust-- because it was embraced by the other side.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348163288960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:48:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348163938070-35</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he believes in redistribution</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348073752677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:55:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How little should the likes of Mitt Romney and Oprah Winfrey pay? As long as you are refering to the rich please don't forget to include the Obama's. Removing Bush tax cuts will impact all Americans not just the rich. What you liberal #$%$ fail to admit or realize is that taking all the wealth of the rich will not fix the problem. America needs more tax payers not taxing everyone at a higher rate. Any tax increase to just the rich will be short lived and find its way to middle class as well. The way to get more tax payers is by putting people back to work. Obama's pie in the sky shovel ready and green jobs plan was a hoax to get himself elected, he does not have a plan. We need those shovel ready jobs to dig out of the #$%$ that comes from of his administration.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348163938070</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:58:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348163946466-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obamcare Tax increase hits Middle and lower income earners hard</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348106076765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. Those who show up in the ER and can't pay are for the most part uninsured. Poor people have access to Medicaid. Even more poor people will have access to Medicaid with the expansion (unless your governor happens to be a partisan Republican--but you can change that.) "The ACA is designed to drive private health insurers out of business and force everyone to a government run single payer system" Hogwash. There is not even a public option in the ACA. Remember the last ditch Republican alternative the the ACA--expand Medicare to everyone? Medicare IS government run single payer systems. And it is very popular. But it is not part of the ACA. If you are worried about government run single payer health care, worry about Medicare and its popularity. The ACA is based on private insurance traded in market exchanges.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348163946466</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:59:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348164844200-37</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he believes in redistribution</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348073752677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:55:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"that taking all the wealth of the rich will not fix the problem." I never said it would "fix the problem". I said a reasonable tax policy, combined with spending restraint, while also using the tools we have to grow the economy at the right time would "fix the problem". Remember that Democrats support a Grand Bargain"\ that includes spending cuts and revenue increases at a 6:1 ratio. That proved to be too much for the tea party-led Republican party. It goes without saying that continuously piling tax cuts on the wealthy is nothing close to a reasonable tax policy--it is a ludicrous tax policy. And it seems that spending restraint is a Chimera Republicans trot out, but back away from when the rubber hits the road. You only have to look at the last decade to see that, but you can also look at the Republicans right now backing away from the spending cuts they demanded during the debt ceiling debacle. I want what we had under Clinton. So do most Americans. And so does Obama.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348164844200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:14:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348167154853-38</Id><Topic><Title>Obama reveals he doesn't know what national debt is and it is not his problem.</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348161017133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:10:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow... this is what i am talking about! By josephjohn157</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348167154853</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348167544942-39</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By johnjoseph997 Excellent commentary!</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348167544942</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:59:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348167773790-40</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Obama administration's account of what may have happened in the attack on the U.S. Consulate in Benghazi last week has evolved by the day. At first, officials were reluctant to say whether the strike that killed four Americans including the U.S. ambassador to Libya was premeditated. Top-ranking officials ranging from White House Press Secretary Jay Carney to U.S. Ambassador to the United Nations Susan Rice subsequently gave briefings and went on television to claim they had no evidence the strike was pre-planned. Carney and others then began to open the door to other possibilities, as accounts emerged that there could be an Al Qaeda connection. After more than a week, Carney said Thursday it was "self evident" the strike was terrorism. He and others continue to stick by claims, though, that there's no evidence the attack was pre-planned.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348167773790</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:02:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170827855-41</Id><Topic><Title>Obama reveals he doesn't know what national debt is and it is not his problem.</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348161017133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:10:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem is, he's not playing!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348170827855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:53:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170957593-42</Id><Topic><Title>Obamcare Tax increase hits Middle and lower income earners hard</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348106076765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“We're no longer going (sic) SUBSIDIZE the care… That's the ‘CAT out of the bag’(sic) Obama socialism plan that got caught(sic)... "pill-osi"= we've got to pass it to see what's in it. - AND the Democrats (majority controlled) passed it, blah, blah, blah…” – jonthepaptest I don’t know how to tell you this, jon, but your tired cache-phrase refrains are Nero fiddling while Rome burns. Not to mention, that you write with all the clarity of Professor Irwin Corey. Perhaps you could help prep Mitt for the debates, what with your vast Miss Teen South Carolina-like knowledge of world events. Perhaps to help him in the debates, you could make little signs for him to hold up that say “smiles” or “tee-hee” or “chuckle-guffaw’ or your other little girlie emoticons. Listening to you talk back and forth to yourself is like eavesdropping on Dan Quayle and George W. Bush discussing quantum physics, drunk in a booth at Hooters. “Echo .. this is the beginning of the END.” Well, jon, now THERE’s something we can agree on…it is, indeed, the beginning of the end. Fox News released a new poll Thursday – Let me repeat. FOX NEWS released a NEW poll THURSDAY…that’s FOX NEWS…YOUR go-to source…the only NON Main Stream Media you trust and to whom you turn for your Gospel Truth…Fair and Balanced…that’s THURSDAY…that would be TODAY, jon, if you have no calendar in that cubicle… The results? Ohio – Obama 49% - Romney 42% Virginia – Obama 50% - Romney 43% Florida – Obama 49% - Romney 44% If I’m not mistaken those are three key battleground states, are they not, jon? Other polls say that Romney’s also getting clobbered in Michigan (by 8 points – gee, wasn’t his Dad Governor there and didn’t he live there????) and Wisconsin (by 14 – Gee, isn’t that where Paul Ryan’s from?) There is good news on the horizon, however. I understand he’s holding his own in Utah and running particularly strong among Mormons out there. Imagine that. Now, if there were only about a gazillion more Mormons in this country, you might be alright.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348170957593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:55:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348171296593-43</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No he didn't. Neither Obama nor Bush knew any attacks were coming. Responding to crazy with crazy does not sanity make.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348171296593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:01:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348171391930-44</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing but seniles in this thread.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348171391930</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348171889451-45</Id><Title>Pawlenty quit the twit?</Title><Msg>Like Scooby Doo would say, "wuh-oh".</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1348171889451</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:11:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348173704049-46</Id><Topic><Title>As usual</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1348086025591</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:20:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>once again gave back 50% of it's gains today. can't gain traction. is it shorts? profit taking?</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1348173704049</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348174057647-47</Id><Topic><Title>Obamcare Tax increase hits Middle and lower income earners hard</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348106076765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats adopted the Republican position. Liberal democrats wanted single payer, most Democrats wanted a public option. The initial compromise was the creation of private consumer cooperatives (like electric cooperatives). However, even this was scrapped and essentially what was adopted was Romneycare--the Republican plan for healthcare. Yet Republicans STILL refused to cooperate and have worked to kill their own policy, solely for political partisanship. Just as Romney is doing now.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348174057647</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:47:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348174468380-48</Id><Topic><Title>Obamcare Tax increase hits Middle and lower income earners hard</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348106076765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the stark policy choices outlined in the conventions have made the difference. It's all fun and games to register dissatisfaction with the economy. But when the alternative shouts "even more tax breaks for the wealthy!" it becomes a choice, and one that's easy to make.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1348174468380</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:54:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348175415535-49</Id><Topic><Title>Re - redistribution...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348136481497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Their first association came through ACORN which Soros founded." You guys always have to resort to distortions and out right lies. That's the only way Republicans can win. ACORN was founded by Wade Rathke.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1348175415535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348178265848-50</Id><Topic><Title>Ordered New Iphone 5, Dumped ATT for Verizon</Title><Username>uncletizz</Username><Timestamp>1348074378001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:06:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you sure the grass is greener? You may regret that move. Of course that would depend a lot on how you use it and where.</Msg><Username>bampa3</Username><Timestamp>1348178265848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:57:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348178401293-51</Id><Topic><Title>Re - redistribution...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348136481497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is his name Liver Lip's or Liver Lips? At least be consistent in your stupidity.</Msg><Username>rcub5d</Username><Timestamp>1348178401293</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 18:00:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348178842663-52</Id><Topic><Title>Obamcare Tax increase hits Middle and lower income earners hard</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348106076765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you forgot the :) and the ?:) and the ; ) . Who dat?</Msg><Username>rcub5d</Username><Timestamp>1348178842663</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 18:07:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348180055567-53</Id><Topic><Title>Obamcare Tax increase hits Middle and lower income earners hard</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348106076765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Havn't figured it out yet? "Liberals" ALWAYS lie about everything. They say they are for the little guy but check into it and most are in bed with the billionaires that really run this country. Just like the "Great Society" fraud created by LBJ. He lied about the "Tonkin Gulf Incident" as an excuse to send more little people to 'Nam. He then proceeded to use Soc. Sec. funds to finance an illegal and un-Constitutional war. All the while he was building a multi million dollar fortune through manipulation of government. His favorite Texas contractor, Brown &amp; Root got all the big contracts in 'Nam. Brown &amp; Root later merged with Halliburton, Dick Cheney's "pet" company that got all the fat contracts in the illegal war in Iraq. The Kenyan is in bed with the same types and is still pursuing another illegal war in Afghanistan and getting ready to be involved in the whole Middle East. How many know of the several thousand Special forces troops deployed to Central Africa? Welcome to the New World Odor.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348180055567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 18:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348186661251-54</Id><Topic><Title>Re - redistribution...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348136481497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get rid of O'bamah!</Msg><Username>jotrout</Username><Timestamp>1348186661251</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:17:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348186724490-55</Id><Topic><Title>Obamcare Tax increase hits Middle and lower income earners hard</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348106076765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get rid of O'bama!</Msg><Username>jotrout</Username><Timestamp>1348186724490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:18:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348197023682-56</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just the tip of the iceberg, Obama knew and did nothiing to protect our embacy staff, he tried to cover it up by using a bogus movie protest excuse along with all the liberal media. Obama is changing his story. Sad we need to get the truth from foriegn sources the liberal media all lied to protect Obama. Obama is pathetic, this could be his undoing</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348197023682</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 23:10:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348197963173-57</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Obama administration is now running “apology” ads in Pakistan. The ads include both Hillary Clinton and Barack Obama apologizing for an obscure YouTube video that is blocked in Pakistan. So let’s get this straight: The State Department spent seventy grand of taxpayer money to have the Secretary of State and the President of the United States apologize for a film they “allegedly” had nothing to do with. Well it’s nice to know our money is being spent so wisely by Hussein and his administration as they continue to apologize for someone simply exercising their First Amendment rights, instead of reprimanding those who have been attacking the U.S. embassy there in Pakistan.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348197963173</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 23:26:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>