<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348296693350-1</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt has Super Energized his Base</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348016247399</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Ricky, You got it right, the election is over, it's a done deal, Obama wins, no problem. And I'm an old white guy who can see the writing on the wall, its a slam dunk.</Msg><Username>ezduzitherb</Username><Timestamp>1348296693350</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 02:51:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348312662976-2</Id><Title>AHQ (cont.)...</Title><Msg>“A democratic government is the only one in which those who vote for a tax can escape the obligation to pay it.” – Alexis de Toqueville “There’s something terribly incongruous about the fact that we select 50 contestants to compete for Miss America, but only two to run for president.” – anonymous "I'm watching the news, and I see these protesters in countries like Egypt, Afghanistan, Tunisia. They're all burning American flags. Where are they getting all these flags? If you hate us so much, how do you have a large supply of flags on hand?" –Jay Leno “Congress should not establish a religion and enforce the legal observation of it by law, nor compel men to worship God in any manner contrary to their conscience, or that one sect might obtain a pre-eminence, or two combined together, and establish a religion to which they would compel others to conform.” - James Madison, summary of the first amendment, Annals of Congress, August 15, 1789 “I always thought of losing my virginity as a career move.” – Madonna "It's Opening Day of the U.N in New York...Mahmoud Ahmadinejad is here. He says he hates gay people and he hates J#ws. Boy is he in the wrong town." – David Letterman “My books are water; those of the great geniuses is wine. Everybody drinks water.” – Mark Twain “I was once thrown out of a mental hospital for depressing the other patients.” – Oscaer Levant “It is only by dispelling the clouds and phantoms of Religion, that we shall discover Truth, Reason and Morality.” – Richard Carlile “Mitt Romney was here meeting with the Hispanic Chamber of Commerce. He's looking for a housekeeper for his place in La Jolla." - Jimmy Kimmel “The human race's prospects of survival were considerably better when we were defenseless against tigers than they are today when we have become defenseless against ourselves.” – Arnold Toynbee “Every time we are confronted with a new revolution we take to the opium pipes of our own propaganda.” – I.F. Stone “Paul Ryan said that he and Mitt Romney won't reveal their tax plan to the public until after the election. Other politicians couldn't believe it. They were like, 'At least do the honorable thing and lie’.” – Jimmy Fallon “In all the human societies we have ever reviewed, in every age and every state, there has seldom if ever been a shortage of eager young males prepared to kill and die to preserve the security, comfort and prejudices of their elders, and what you call heroism is just an expression of this fact; there is never a scarcity of idiots.” - Iain Banks</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348312662976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 07:17:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348316033174-3</Id><Title>Winholder's Friday night monologue...</Title><Msg>Wow, winholder, that was quite a soliloquy last night. Seven rambling posts all criticizing the President out of desperation, including: “…this lying, stupid, fool is the person for responsible for the economy we have today and for the past three years.” Man, windandale, you, of all people, suggesting that someone is lying!! You’ve been caught in more lies on this board than Paul Ryan at a convention! You also said, “He knows what the deficit is. He knows what the debt is. He knows where it is headed in the future.” Yes, indeed, he does. Oh, and btw, so does Romney…Consider this remarkable exchange between Romney and conservative radio-host Laura Ingraham earlier this year. “INGRAHAM: You’ve also noted that there are signs of improvement on the horizon in the economy. How do you answer the president’s argument that the economy is getting better in a general election campaign if you yourself are saying it’s getting better? ROMNEY: Well, of course it’s getting better. The economy always gets better after a recession, there is always a recovery. INGRAHAM: Isn’t it a hard argument to make if you’re saying, like, OK, he inherited this recession, he took a bunch of steps to try to turn the economy around, and now, we’re seeing more jobs, but vote against him anyway? Isn’t that a hard argument to make? Is that a stark enough contrast? ROMNEY: Have you got a better one, Laura? It just happens to be the truth.” My goodness, winny my boy, it would appear that your candidate, like many experts today, believes that the economy IS getting better…and, as Mitt said, it just happens to be the truth, no matter what you say. One last point. You also said, “The rich didn't create this problem by being intelligent, talented, or hardworking.” Well, again, you generalize. That certainly is true in many cases, but I also know many, many people who are very wealthy and have never worked a day in their life. Regardless, your tired refrain is hypocritical. You constantly contend that the rich are all intelligent, talented and hardworking while suggesting that the poor, therefore, are unintelligent, have NO talent and are lazy. And, sadly, your candidate puts about half of all Americans in that category. Unfortunately for him, the electorate knows neither of your generalities is true. You know, win, you really should get out more on a Friday night.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348316033174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 08:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348318140674-4</Id><Topic><Title>Look for close around $38.26 as T always..</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1348240712903</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:18:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Long as it ends up green</Msg><Username>slipeh</Username><Timestamp>1348318140674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 08:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348321560153-5</Id><Topic><Title>Are you firing obama?</Title><Username>obomaisaclown</Username><Timestamp>1347925812596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 19:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He can not be fired. He has union representtion. The unions always protect the weak and lame performers. Just look to T's technicians, or SEIU, teachers union's, etc...</Msg><Username>josieinib</Username><Timestamp>1348321560153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 09:46:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348323856122-6</Id><Topic><Title>Are you firing obama?</Title><Username>obomaisaclown</Username><Timestamp>1347925812596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 19:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another comment from the low informed...aka Fox sheep</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1348323856122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:24:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348323977196-7</Id><Topic><Title>Winholder's Friday night monologue...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1348316033174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 08:13:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't Friday night his Log Cabin Republican meeting?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1348323977196</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:26:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348324181088-8</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt has Super Energized his Base</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348016247399</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bishop Robme is done, you can stick a fork in him.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1348324181088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348331236507-9</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt has Super Energized his Base</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348016247399</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This post is pitiful (truth be told, all your posts are pitiful so this isn't a standout). You will never begin to think. You're incapable of it. What you mistake for thought is merely you regurgitating what you're told and decorating every other word with "quotation marks", while breathing through your fat, flabby mouth full of half chewed pork rinds. You are an idiot!</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1348331236507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 12:27:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348333358469-10</Id><Title>Obama appologizes to Mooslums but not Christians</Title><Msg>Religious groups are blasting President Obama for not condemning am anti-Christian art display set to appear in New York City Christians are fed up with the administration’s double standard and religious hypocrisy. Religious groups and some lawmakers have already started sounding off – and making comparisons to the controversy over a recent anti-Muslim film. The low budget movie “Innocence of Muslims” sparked violent and deadly clashes across the globe. It also brought strong rebukes, condemnations and apologies from President Obama, Secretary of State Hillary Clinton and a host of administration officials. The Obama administration’s hypocrisy and utter lack of respect for the religious beliefs of Americans has reached an all-time high, Obama should stand up for America’s values and beliefs and denounce the anti-Christian display that has offended Christians at home and abroad. So will the Obama Administration condemn the anti-Christian art display? Will they air a television ad denouncing the exhibit? Will the Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff ask the gallery to cancel the exhibit? The White House did not return calls seeking comment. Neither did the Pentagon. The lack of response from the White House is unacceptable. Perhaps they’ve forgotten the controversy that surrounds this deplorable piece depicting a crucifix submerged in the artist’s urine. It outraged Christians in American and throughout the world. The anti-Christian display is vulgar and offensive, just as many in the Islamic world found ‘Innocence of Muslims’ to be highly offensive. this administration has yet to echo these views in regards to the religiously offensive ‘art’ here at home.” “I would like to find out what my government is going to say about this,” said Bill Donohue, president of the Catholic League. “We have the United States government making apologies and some very critical statements about the abuse of freedom of speech because it might offend Muslims.” Donohue said the Obama administration seems to have a double standard when it comes to incidents that might offend the Christian community. “It seems like we have a protected class for Muslims as well as some other segments of our population,” he said “But when it comes to Christians, it’s an all-out war.” But Donohue questions the timing of the exhibit. “The timing is not a mistake,” he said. “The obvious reason is not because it’s something new – it’s the idea of throwing more salt of Christians. This is a pattern that’s calculated, it’s deliberate and it’s time the elites spoke out on this.” Tony Perkins, president of the Family Research Council, said the two incidents show a clear contrast between Islam and Christianity. “You won’t have to worry about a mob of people storming the gallery after Sunday school lets out,” Perkins said. The lack of response from the White House over the anti-Christian display provide an unintentional recognition. “It’s a recognition of the contrast between Christianity and Islam,” he said. “You don’t have to plead with Christians not to riot and burn and storm buildings simply because they are offended. That’s the difference. That’s why Christianity moves nations forward and Islam moves nations backwards.”</Msg><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348333358469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348340053258-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama appologizes to Mooslums but not Christians</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348333358469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By johnjoseph997 Excellent commentary!</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1348340053258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 14:54:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348340098553-12</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt has Super Energized his Base</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348016247399</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By johnjoseph997 Excellent commentary!</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1348340098553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 14:54:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348340143649-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By johnjoseph997 Excellent commentary!</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1348340143649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 14:55:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348340189372-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he believes in redistribution</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348073752677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:55:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By johnjoseph997 Excellent commentary!</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1348340189372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 14:56:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348340239206-15</Id><Topic><Title>Obama reveals he doesn't know what national debt is and it is not his problem.</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348161017133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:10:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By johnjoseph997 Excellent commentary!</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1348340239206</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 14:57:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348340289362-16</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, The Movie 2016 winning fans.</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347739488940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 16:04:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By johnjoseph997 Excellent commentary!</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1348340289362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 14:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348340345190-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obamcare Tax increase hits Middle and lower income earners hard</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348106076765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By johnjoseph997 Excellent commentary!</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1348340345190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 14:59:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348340394738-18</Id><Topic><Title>Christians fight HHS mandate</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1347728733761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 13:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By johnjoseph997 Excellent commentary!</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1348340394738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 14:59:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348340430832-19</Id><Topic><Title>NY State "busted"in $15 B Medicare Fraud !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1348243694812</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:08:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By johnjoseph997 Excellent commentary!</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1348340430832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:00:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348340533661-20</Id><Topic><Title>Are you firing obama?</Title><Username>obomaisaclown</Username><Timestamp>1347925812596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 19:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By johnjoseph997 Excellent commentary!</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1348340533661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:02:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348340566703-21</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's New (Copy Cat) Flag</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1348180650601</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 18:37:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By johnjoseph997 Excellent commentary!</Msg><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348340566703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:02:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348340592967-22</Id><Topic><Title>9/11 attack designed by former Gitmo detainee</Title><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1348110435607</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:07:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By johnjoseph997 Excellent commentary!</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1348340592967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:03:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348340700007-23</Id><Topic><Title>Does Barry Believe in God?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347739167038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 15:59:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By johnjoseph997 Excellent commentary!</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1348340700007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348342070972-24</Id><Topic><Title>Obama appologizes to Mooslums but not Christians</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348333358469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By braincandy62. Thanks you for your clear insights</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1348342070972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348342081232-25</Id><Topic><Title>Obama reveals he doesn't know what national debt is and it is not his problem.</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348161017133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:10:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FYI--"deficits don't matter" was stated by tricky Dick Cheney. If you don't remember your history, you're doomed to repeat it.</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1348342081232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:28:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348349808554-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The one making a fool of himself was Obama lying to Americans about what occured while Romney's aim is right on target</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348349808554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 17:36:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348350543988-27</Id><Title>Univision does the job liberal media won't</Title><Msg>The big media has distinguished themselves with their lazy, biased coverage of President Obama. So it's nice to see a media outlet that asks tough questions and informs its viewers. Univision, take a bow. President Obama entered the Univision studio last Thursday for a televised candidate's appearance thinking it would be a cakewalk. After all, Latinos in the U.S. overwhelmingly voted for him in the last election, and he has no reason from the polls to believe he wouldn't still command their allegiance. And yet, the interviewers on Spanish-language Univision, Jorge Ramos and Maria Elena Salinas, did their job with admirable professionalism and aggressiveness. If only the rest of the media did such a good job. Interviewing the president on his record, the Univision journalists did what their English-language media fellows have steadfastly refused to do: Ask Obama tough questions about such things as immigration policy and the Operation Fast and Furious scandal, two things of high importance to Univision viewers. "I think up to 100 Mexicans might have died (in Operation Fast and Furious) and also American agent Brian Terry," Ramos said. "There's a report that 14 agents were responsible for the operation, but shouldn't the attorney general, Eric Holder, ... have known about that and if he didn't, should you fire him?" Obama's response was pure boilerplate, telling Ramos that Holder "has my complete confidence" Ramos' co-host Maria Elena Salinas wasn't happy, following up with the kind of question our Washington press corps can't be bothered to ask: "Why don't we have ... an independent investigation that is not done by the Justice Department?" Obama's evasive answer: The investigation was "honest" and this had all become a "political distraction." Ramos also hammered home Obama's broken promises on immigration reform. "You promised that (reform), and a promise is a promise," Ramos told Obama. "And with all due respect, you didn't keep that promise." Obama's response was incoherent, talking about "separation of powers" and other irrelevant issues. Univision asked tough questions and demanded answers. That's exactly the opposite of America's big media. Their left-wing bias has become all too apparent. Indeed, a new Gallup Poll shows Americans now distrust the mainstream media.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348350543988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 17:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348351838294-28</Id><Topic><Title>Univision does the job liberal media won't</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348350543988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 17:49:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, this was the closet thing to a real interview for Obama. So glad they didn't ask who is more talented Beyonce, or Jay Zee? I guess with 100 of their countrymen dead, they had to at least try to get Eric Holder fired. Heck, Eric could care less. Eric, only cares about Eric.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348351838294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:10:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348352960081-29</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're correct, this is an ongoing foreign policy crisis for this administration, and they haven't figured out how to handle it without lying to the American public. This investigation will end like the investigation into Fast and Furious, a complete white wash with little truth being told. You know it, I know it, but the media will either ignore it or slant the results. There is no accountability left in this administration. They have been caught not having a clue what really happened and why and now have been caught lying about the reasons they said it happened. Geez, Ricky are you really that stupid or that blind to what this administration is all about?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348352960081</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348353345158-30</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin knew embasy attack probable but did not protect staff</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1347598008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 00:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What we should not be ashamed about is the fact that this video was not produced by the American public in general and produced under a concept of freedom of speech. We have no reason to apologize or even explain our involvement or lack of involvement in the making or release of this video. Obama is not defending our right to produce or view this video. He is apologizing for our having a right to the freedom of speech. The radicals of this religion believe that we are the most liberal, decadent people in the world and are trying to export our liberalism into their world and they don't like it. Neither do I. You’re simply making excuses for his weak, liberal, compromising attitude. Seems strange to me that he is more than willing to compromise with the terrorist attitudes of the Middle East but not with his opposite member of Congress.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348353345158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:35:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348353396065-31</Id><Title>Democrat party Destroyed Black Community for Votes</Title><Msg>One Black mans perspective I came up in the sixties. I'm from Chicago. I came up in the sixties and we had black pride with the great songs in the sixties from Motown, and I went to all-black school in Chicago. I graduated from all-black school, and from that point we created a Afro-American group in high school to start learning the blacks about being prideful, taking care for the women, taking care of their bodies and stuff, and be proud of themselves. Listen to James Brown. And from that time, I went to Grambling a college in Louisiana. We supported Shirley Chisholm. Grambling was more like a so-so Uncle Tom school, but we helped Grambling get black courses to teach blacks to be proud of themselves. From there I came back and we had Harold Washington become the first black mayor of Chicago, and later -- after helping Harold -- I realized I was conservative. I came back from my mother and father, who worked hard, they took care of their families. I registered as a Republican. I realized the Democratic Party was the biggest culprit on destroy the black race. At that time I was kind of brainwashed. I just felt that black pride, Democratic Party was for the blacks, but it wasn't. I realized that long as they kept blacks on welfare, kept blacks on drugs -- the didn't care if black people stayed on drugs -- How did they keep blacks on welfare and on drugs? Well, it starts with no education. Black pride morphed into black victim hood. To create dependency this is how they do it. And it's again going on ever since the mid-sixties, and I seen it in the seventies and the eighties all the way to today. They felt that the black people was gonna be dependent on the Democratic Party. Democrats would come and campaign, get the blacks to vote Democratic. They started lying, and the blacks started selling drugs more in the seventies. And that's why the Democratic Party get about 90% of the black vote, because they keep the black kids on drugs and have abortions. They felt that as long as the blacks didn't get no education, they wouldn't worry about the blacks moving up and moving into good neighborhoods. Bad schools are kept open. Organizations like the Urban League, NAACP, the Black Hawkers, Jesse Jackson, they was there to make sure that the blacks kept voting Democratic. I first became aware of it during the fight over Clarence Thomas nomination Supreme Court. What going on is the civil rights coalition has its seat of power at the Democrat Party, and it's got to do a bunch of things in order to keep that seat. One is turn out the black population voting Democrat, and the biggest threat -- the biggest threat to that -- is to show an independent African-American rising to the top who's not a liberal Democrat. One who didn't use affirmative action, who didn't get propelled there by the Democrat Party." That was the biggest threat to the existing civil rights coalition: Clarence Thomas was gonna be the most powerful black man in the country if he just it to the Supreme Court he had to be destroyed. Because it -- it would upset way too much that had already been put in place to keep people like Jesse Jackson, Ralph Neas at People for the American Way and all these civil rights people at their positions of power and value in the Democrat Party. My family was born in the South. It was born in the South. And at the time it was a family, blacks had families who support each other. Then my family moved to Chicago when I was three years old. So I came from the old school where you had parents, mothers and fathers who stayed together, and they'd developed a family. We were together. We had a farm. We believed in Christ. We went to church every Sunday. We believed in morality. We believed in doing our fellow people right. I've been in the Tea Party in Ohio and I'm doing everything I can to help defeat Barack.I don't care what the president is. This president is so bad, I don't care what nationality he is. He's one of the worst presidents besides Jimmy Carter. It's hurting blacks all over.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348353396065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:36:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348353436920-32</Id><Topic><Title>Univision does the job liberal media won't</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348350543988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 17:49:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Holder won't resign, he needs to be fired. He is a lying creep and a racist.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348353436920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:37:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348353548331-33</Id><Topic><Title>Obama reveals he doesn't know what national debt is and it is not his problem.</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1348161017133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:10:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The National debt is not a concern? How long are the days on your planet?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348353548331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:39:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348353716941-34</Id><Topic><Title>Does Barry Believe in God?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347739167038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 15:59:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's God is power. He is in power and if you don't like what he does, he will simply go around Congress and do what he wants. He needs to be stopped.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348353716941</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:41:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348353867131-35</Id><Topic><Title>Are you firing obama?</Title><Username>obomaisaclown</Username><Timestamp>1347925812596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 19:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope, I was overseas and they didn't work as hard then as they do today to make sure the military got to vote on time.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1348353867131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:44:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348355475961-36</Id><Topic><Title>Does Barry Believe in God?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347739167038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 15:59:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Barry should completely call off that movie, about how he, and not the Navy Seals took out Osami. This bragging about personally controlling the kill list, isn't going away. These people have been hating Obama ever since he repeated that passage, he and his sister, grew up Muzlem. Then Barry changed to Christianity. What he really should have said, I became a Church goer to get votes. But he is saying, that he embraced the Prophet, then rejected him. That makes Obami a very hated man, one who looks very weak, apolgizing everytime something goes wrong.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348355475961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:11:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348358204968-37</Id><Title>They are not happy.</Title><Msg>Totally Brilliant, how come they don't see this? What can be done about it? I have never heard it put this way...so succinct and to the point...plain and simple!!! THE MUS LIMS ARE NOT HAPPY! They're not happy in Gaza .. They're not happy in Egypt .. They're not happy in Libya .. They're not happy in Morocco .. They're not happy in Iran .. They're not happy in Iraq .. They're not happy in Yemen .. They're not happy in Afghanistan .. They're not happy in Pakistan .. They're not happy in Syria .. They're not happy in Lebanon .. SO, WHERE ARE THEY HAPPY? ; They're happy in Australia . They're happy in Canada. They're happy in England .. They're happy in France .. They're happy in Italy .. They're happy in Germany .. They're happy in Sweden .. They're happy in the USA .. They're happy in Norway .. They're happy in Holland . They're happy in Denmark . Basically, they're happy in every country that is not Mu slim and unhappy in every country that is! AND WHO DO THEY BLAME? Not Islam. Not their leadership. Not themselves. THEY BLAME THE COUNTRIES THEY ARE HAPPY IN! AND THEN; They want to change those countries to be like.... THE COUNTRY THEY CAME FROM WHERE THEY WERE UNHAPPY! Excuse me, but I can't help wondering... How freaking stupid can these inbred clowns get?</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1348358204968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:56:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348360434203-38</Id><Topic><Title>Does Barry Believe in God?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347739167038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 15:59:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good for you lv66vette, you clearly got under the walrus's thick, thick layer of blubber. By the way, Jon2retarded, you are a mothbreathing idiot. Just ask your family and neighbors if you don't believe me.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1348360434203</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 20:33:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348360623077-39</Id><Title>losing customers</Title><Msg>is it maybe time to take some off the table as T appears to be losing market share?</Msg><Username>leemadison321</Username><Timestamp>1348360623077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 20:37:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348360668167-40</Id><Topic><Title>Does Barry Believe in God?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1347739167038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 15:59:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"mothbreathing". A typo that I like even more than "mouthbreathing". Kind of a Silence of the Lambs, jonnyretardy sitting in a damp, dark basement, compulsively masturbating all day kind of thing.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1348360668167</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 20:37:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348361581198-41</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat party Destroyed Black Community for Votes</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348353396065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:36:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Things would go so much better, if Barry were to loose. Gas costs for one. With all that printing of money (Billion of dollars), the Middle East knows it must raise energy prices, just to keep up the falling dollar's buying power. Black folks here in Bmore drives big cars. Gas is costing an arm &amp; a leg, and then some. Then to make driving even more expensive, folks are being saturated with speed cameras, and red light cams. Barry won't be happy till all our people are taking the bus. So then he can throw us underneath of it. Now Dem Governor O'Malley is looking at stop sign cameras. When will Black folks get off this plantation?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1348361581198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 20:53:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348369861695-42</Id><Topic><Title>Univision does the job liberal media won't</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348350543988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 17:49:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1348369861695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:11:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348371039113-43</Id><Title>After learning of Benghazi attack Obama goes to bed as events surrouding the attack continue</Title><Msg>Obama is one uncaring clown. This guy does not care about anything but his bank account and when the next hollywood party begins. He cares nothing about Americans. Barack Obama knew of the attack on the Libyan consulate within 90 minutes of it beginning. He knew that his ambassador was in grave danger and yet knowing all of this, and not knowing the status of Ambassador Stevens, Obama went quietly to bed</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1348371039113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:30:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348372190360-44</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he believes in redistribution</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348073752677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:55:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how else is he going to help his people? do you expect them to stay in school? handouts baby, more handouts or reparations, however you want to view it</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348372190360</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:49:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348372354481-45</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he believes in redistribution</Title><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1348073752677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:55:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oprah needs big $ to fuel her caboose.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348372354481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>