<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349590011294-1</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT DOWN, STOCK MARKET UP, AUTO INDUSTRY STRONG! SOUNDS GOOD TO ME! WHY CHANGE?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349574314302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:45:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Claim Your Copy of the ObamaCare Survival Guide This book peels back the rosy media cover-up on ObamaCare — and comes to you chock-full of easy-to-understand solutions and sensible consumer advice. So whether you're a senior or a small business owner, unemployed, or have a pre-existing condition, this authoritative guidebook will assist you to make better decisions about your healthcare — and the money you spend on your healthcare. In the ObamaCare Survival Guide, you'll discover: The ObamaCare 'scorecard': winners and losers under the new rules . . . The real reason why you can expect many of your benefits to shrink if you are on Medicare . . . Exactly how the new rules will benefit those with pre-existing medical conditions . . . Retired and under 65? Will ObamaCare help or hurt you? How ObamaCare presents a financial windfall for Big Pharma . . . How taxpayers will foot the bill for about half of ObamaCare's funding in the form of new taxes and fees (one 'surtax' in particular threatens American homeowners) . . . 2 reasons why insurance companies welcome ObamaCare, despite the new rules imposed on them . . . Finally, a bit of good news for seniors: the 'donut hole' in Medicare prescription drug coverage will finally be filled . . . How the new law deals with controversial issues such as coverage for abortions and contraceptives . . . Why those with high incomes may save money on their own healthcare plan, but will also pay more to help fund healthcare for the rest of the population . . . And much, much more . . .</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1349590011294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 02:06:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349610899329-2</Id><Title>Hallelujah...</Title><Msg>Athens, Georgia (AP) Georgia Republican Congressman Paul Broun said in videotaped remarks that evolution, embryology and the Big Bang theory are ‘lies straight from the pit of hell’ meant to convince people that they do not need a savior. Broun, a medical doctor, is running for re-election in November unopposed by Democrats. “I've come to understand that. All that stuff I was taught about evolution and embryology and Big Bang theory, all that is lies straight from the pit of hell,”said Broun. Broun also said that he believes the Earth is about 9,000 years old and that it was made in six days. He sits on the House Committee on Science, Space and Technology.” Uh, one would hope he won’t be sitting there for long. Hallelujah and pass me a rattlesnake.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1349610899329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 07:54:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349613905511-3</Id><Topic><Title>T Is Looking Good!</Title><Username>buchanan_f</Username><Timestamp>1349523846621</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 07:44:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great share. Many thanks</Msg><Username>colongill436</Username><Timestamp>1349613905511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 08:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349619644776-4</Id><Title>An interesting read</Title><Msg>I've owned this stock for 3 years thinking it has been undervalued, and it is finally starting to move up - I think based on a Zacks recommendation and this article. http://seekingalpha.com/article/876521-iec-electronics-a-misunderstood-company-at-a-fraction-of-private-market-value?source=yahoo Check it out and let me know if you agree. Upstate1</Msg><Username>upstate1</Username><Timestamp>1349619644776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:20:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349621738168-5</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT DOWN, STOCK MARKET UP, AUTO INDUSTRY STRONG! SOUNDS GOOD TO ME! WHY CHANGE?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349574314302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:45:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well jb when you are right you are right: o Unemployment down - Got to give you that, after 43 months of 8% and above unemployment, the President and his policies have finally brought us back to the point where he took over the job from President Bush - Mark one for the President o Stock market up - Again great job Mr. President your policies have brought the market back, because we all know, and you have made it very clear that the American people didn't build that - Mark one for the President o Auto industry strong - Not sure because the $19.4 Billion Federal relief with a $30 Billion package to follow came from the Bush administration and still required GM to file for bankruptcy in January of 2009 - For this one you may have to mark it for President Bush So jb two out of three still aint bad, but I'm not sure that this was the "hope and change" the American people voted for. The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349621738168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:55:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349625714160-6</Id><Topic><Title>What i discovered about whistle blowing at ATT</Title><Username>cencoastsurfer</Username><Timestamp>1349407895184</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 23:31:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have said for a long time, there isn't an employee or 1st level manager that works for AT&amp;T that isn't worthy of termination. The amount of paperwork that we are required to sign gives AT&amp;T the ability to get rid of anybody they want. The weak union allows it to happen. I have witnessed the most productive employees being forced out while the lazy friends and relatives stay employeed. My advice, be happy for the other 28 years of continuous employment, they could have terminated you way earlier. Good luck on your retirement.</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1349625714160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349629200067-7</Id><Topic><Title>And if you dare to question the Emperor's new clothes...</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349552117236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are so many lies being told about most everything that people become totally confused and give up. The Ponzi swindler recently sent to prison was interviewed there and told the reporter that "The whole government is one big Ponzi swindle". He should know as he swindled 50 billion from people. The whole thing will collapse as any Ponzi scheme does eventually.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1349629200067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:00:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349634309723-8</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT DOWN, STOCK MARKET UP, AUTO INDUSTRY STRONG! SOUNDS GOOD TO ME! WHY CHANGE?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349574314302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:45:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it really good news for the economy that the stock market is up? During the Great Depression, we had a powerful bull market from 1932 to 1937. In fact, in the depth of the Depression (1933), the DOW nearly doubled in a six-month period. Be careful when you try to use the stock market as a positive indicator of the economy. In fact the stock market loves it when the economy is slow and the Fed shovels bushels of money into the economy to goose it along. We should all be ready to sell when Ben turns off the spigot.</Msg><Username>punawai1</Username><Timestamp>1349634309723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 14:25:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349639079273-9</Id><Title>Way to go Mr. President, looks like your energy policies are really working</Title><Msg>I know you told us early in your term that rising gas prices are good for the economy and good for the environment, and going from an average of $1.83 per gallon (when you took office) to the current $4.00 per gallon is proof of how well your policies are working, but probably the best example is the state of California where there is a democrat administration and legislature running things. The people of California are now getting a full dose of how well things go when they are being ruled by democrats at both the Federal and state level. Way to go Mr. President $5 to $6 gas and long lines at the pump because of supply shortages is just what the doctor ordered. Maybe if we are lucky, and you get a second term, the rest of the country will get to enjoy the same things that our comrades in California are currently enjoying. The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349639079273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349639889690-10</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT DOWN, STOCK MARKET UP, AUTO INDUSTRY STRONG! SOUNDS GOOD TO ME! WHY CHANGE?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349574314302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:45:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Continued high unemployment, shrinking household income, big rise in healthcare costs with Obamacare. Believe your own eyes not what the liberal media is telling you that differs from reality. Have an exit strategy if we get 4 more years of BO there will be no reversing his socialist strategy it will be too late, things could get ugly in a hurry.</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349639889690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349640117955-11</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go Mr. President, looks like your energy policies are really working</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349639079273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gasoline prices and healthcare costs are on the same path thanks to</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349640117955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 16:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349640202283-12</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go Mr. President, looks like your energy policies are really working</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349639079273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BO</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349640202283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 16:03:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349648589244-13</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go Mr. President, looks like your energy policies are really working</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349639079273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$ 5.39 in LA</Msg><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1349648589244</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349654047008-14</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go Mr. President, looks like your energy policies are really working</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349639079273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*If any other of our presidents had criticized a state law that he admitted he never even read, would you think that he is just an ignorant hothead? * *If any other of our presidents joined the country of Mexico and sued a state in the United States to force that state to continue to allow illegal immigration, would you question his patriotism and wonder whose side he was on? * *If any other of our presidents had pronounced the Marine Corps like Marine Corpse, would you think him an idiot? * *If any other of our presidents had put 87,000 workers out of work by arbitrarily placing a moratorium on offshore oil drilling on companies that have one of the best safety records of any industry because one foreign company had an accident, would you have agreed? * *If any other of our presidents had used a forged document as the basis of the moratorium that would render 87000 American workers unemployed would you support him? * *If any other of our presidents had been the first President to need a Teleprompter installed to be able to get through a press conference, would you have laughed and said this is more proof of how inept he is on his own and is really controlled by smarter men behind the scenes? * *If any other of our presidents had spent hundreds of thousands of dollars to take his First Lady to a play in NYC, would you have approved? * *If any other of our presidents had reduced your retirement plan holdings of GM stock by 90% and given the unions a majority stake in GM, would you have approved? * *If any other of our presidents had made a joke at the expense of the Special Olympics, would you have approved? * *If any other of our presidents had given Gordon Brown a set of inexpensive and incorrectly formatted DVDs, when Gordon Brown had given him a thoughtful and historically significant gift, would you have approved? * *If any other of our presidents had given the Queen of England an iPod containing videos of his speeches, would you have thought it a proud moment for America ? * *If any other of our presidents had bowed to the King of Saudi Arabia would you have approved? * *If any other of our presidents had visited Austria and made reference to the nonexistent "Austrian language," would you have brushed it off as a minor slip? * *If any other of our presidents had filled his cabinet and circle of advisers with people who cannot seem to keep current in their income taxes, would you have approved? * *If any other of our presidents had stated that there were 57 states in the United States , wouldn't you have had second thoughts about his capabilities? * *If any other of our presidents would have flown all the way to Denmark to make a five minute speech about how the Olympics would benefit him walking out his front door in his home town, would you not have thought he was a self-important, conceited, egotistical jerk. * *If any other of our presidents had been so Spanish illiterate as to refer to "Cinco de Cuatro" in front of the Mexican ambassador when it was the 5th of May (Cinco de Mayo), and continued to flub it when he tried again, wouldn't you have winced in embarrassment? * *If any other of our presidents had burned 9,000 gallons of jet fuel to go plant a single tree on Earth Day, would you have concluded he's a hypocrite?* *If any other of our presidents' administrations had okayed Air Force One flying low over millions of people followed by a jet fighter in downtown Manhattan causing widespread panic, would you have wondered whether they actually get what happened on 9-11? * *If any other of our presidents had failed to send relief aid to flood victims throughout the Midwest with more people killed or made homeless than in New Orleans, would you want it made into a major ongoing political issue with claims of racism and incompetence? * *If any other of our presidents had created the position of 32 Czars who report directly to him, bypassing the House and Senate on much of what is happening in America , would you have ever approved? * *If any other of our presidents had ordered the firing of the CEO of a major corporation, even though he had no constitutional authority to do so, would you have approved? * *So, tell me again, what is it about Obama that makes him so brilliant and impressive? * *Can't think of anything? Don't worry. He's done all this in 34 months so you dont have that much time to come up with an answer.* *Every statement and action in this email is factual and directly attributable to Barrack Hussein Obama. Every bumble is a matter of record and completely verifiable. * AND NOW-- HE ACTUALLY WANTS US TO RE-ELECT HIM. WAKE UP AMERICA 2012 IS UPON US.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349654047008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:54:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349665783101-15</Id><Title>on the day obama was</Title><Msg>sworn into office , there was 1 million of his followers in attendence.....4 of them missed work ...</Msg><Username>oilup1234</Username><Timestamp>1349665783101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 23:09:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>