<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-23"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353675862869-1</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet: cap gain 30%, 50% tax on the rich</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353097971771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, we almost went the entire Thanksgiving day without sniping at each other over politics.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1353675862869</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 08:04:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353676001408-2</Id><Topic><Title>Motley Fool</Title><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1353621741635</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 17:02:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I stopped reading their junk long ago. For some reason it seems every T piece is negative and for the most part, they have been dead wrong.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1353676001408</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 08:06:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353682410925-3</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet: cap gain 30%, 50% tax on the rich</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353097971771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and most of your ilk never understand that the thieves in Congress will raise the rates that effect us all then write in loop holes that only the very rich can take advantage of. Just like they changed the tax rules on REIT's a few years back. The little guy couldn't take advantage of the flow through write offs but mega rich Democrats like the "Hero Of Chappaquiddick" Teddy Boy Kennedy could. I would trust Warren Buffet and his people as much as I woul;d trust Bernie Madaff.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1353682410925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 09:53:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353682825316-4</Id><Topic><Title>PTL "T", VZ &amp; Twinkies</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1353366337815</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 18:05:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great to see a post about AT&amp;T etal getting responses. Also great to be above 34 even if only a few pennies.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1353682825316</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 10:00:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353684600708-5</Id><Topic><Title>ring sales training for</Title><Username>carlenewertszzepbrk4322</Username><Timestamp>1304731549000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2011-05-06 21:25:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ur timing is simply best</Msg><Username>joshepjohn525</Username><Timestamp>1353684600708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 10:30:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353689145851-6</Id><Topic><Title>Why is ATT Rising?</Title><Username>houston110</Username><Timestamp>881014371000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 1997-12-01 17:12:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AT&amp;T isn't rising; the $$$ is falling. The FED is printing 40 billion dollars a month so the fall will continue.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1353689145851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 11:45:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353689582340-7</Id><Title>belt up we are head into the fifties,</Title><Msg>its the dividend folks are seeking.. yipee yoo cowboy!!!!!!. what a great ride in to the stratosphere. buy baby buy baby buy.</Msg><Username>capp013</Username><Timestamp>1353689582340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 11:53:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353690061821-8</Id><Topic><Title>belt up we are head into the fifties,</Title><Username>capp013</Username><Timestamp>1353689582340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 11:53:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Calm down cowboy; we will be lucky to hit 36 and 33 is more likely. The downtrend in October and November is likely to continue.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1353690061821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 12:01:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353694148079-9</Id><Title>Dividend???</Title><Msg>How will T sustain the current dividend rate?</Msg><Username>nuthead48</Username><Timestamp>1353694148079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 13:09:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353694234897-10</Id><Title>Dividends</Title><Msg>How can T sustain the current dividend payout?</Msg><Username>nuthead48</Username><Timestamp>1353694234897</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 13:10:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353695625768-11</Id><Topic><Title>Fantastic Advancement for T. Read Now!</Title><Username>robertwiltshire37</Username><Timestamp>1353689534970</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 11:52:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>got me a load more shares today</Msg><Username>johnnychristopher99</Username><Timestamp>1353695625768</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 13:33:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353703338764-12</Id><Topic><Title>Has aggressive 'Fix The Debt' campaign started yet?</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1353427660081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 11:07:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, he is too busy traveling around the Far East to get in his photo ops and Congress is too busy being on vacation again.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1353703338764</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 15:42:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353703421462-13</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news BO admin denies requests to defend Benghazi compoud during attack</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1351269709024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 12:41:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, and the latest from the 'intelligence' community is that they didn't alter the data and don't know who did. Who is on first?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1353703421462</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 15:43:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353703723742-14</Id><Topic><Title>California Nurses on Strike, cause of Barry</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1353462309458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 20:45:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A recent hearing sponsored by the Treasury and Labor Departments marked the beginning of the Obama Administration’s effort to nationalize the nation’s pension system and to eliminate private retirement accounts including IRA’s and 401k plans, NSC is warning. The hearing, held in the Labor Department’s main auditorium, was monitored by NSC staff and featured a line up of left-wing activists including one representative of the AFL-CIO who advocated for more government regulation over private retirement accounts and even the establishment of government-sponsored annuities that would take the place of 401k plans. "This hearing was set up to explore why Americans are not saving as much for their retirement as they could," explains National Seniors Council National Director Robert Crone, "However, it is clear that this is the first step towards a government takeover. It feels just like the beginning of the debate over health care and we all know how that ended up." A representative of the liberal Pension Rights Center, Rebecca Davis, testified that the government needs to get involved because 401k plans and IRAs are unfair to poor people. She demanded the Obama administration set up a "government-sponsored program administered by the PBGC (the governments’ Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation)." She proclaimed that even "private annuities are problematic." Such "reforms" would effectively end private retirement accounts in America, Crone warns. "These people want the government to require that ultimately all Americans buy these government annuities instead of saving or investing on their own. The Government could then take these trillions of dollars and redistribute it through this new national retirement system." Deputy Treasury Secretary J. Mark Iwry, who presided over the hearing, is a long-time critic of 401k plans because he believes they benefit the rich. He also appears to be one of the Administration’s point man on this issue. "This whole issue is moving forward very quickly," warns Crone. "Already there is a bill requiring all businesses to automatically enroll their employees in IRA plans in which part of every employee’s paycheck would be automatically deducted and deposited into this account. If this passes, the government will be just one step away from being able to confiscate all these retirement accounts." NSC has taken the lead in warning the nation about this new government onslaught and is plotting ways to stop it. "This effort ultimately is designed to grab the retirement nest eggs of America’s senior citizens. This new government annuity scheme, even if it is at first optional, will turn into a giant effort to redistribute the wealth of America’s older citizens," explains Crone. "This scheme mirrors what I expect the President will try to do with Social Security. He wants to turn that program into a welfare program, too." NSC will likely unveil a new grassroots campaign effort later this year or early in January to coincide with the seating of the new Congress.</Msg><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1353703723742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 15:48:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353708177674-15</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet: cap gain 30%, 50% tax on the rich</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353097971771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Bishop Romney.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1353708177674</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 17:02:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353708731496-16</Id><Title>noccentertimmy</Title><Msg>What has noccentertimmy been up to lately?</Msg><Username>chowciao</Username><Timestamp>1353708731496</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 17:12:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353718010663-17</Id><Title>Pensions</Title><Msg>I just opened a letter that was a few days old from Human Resources of AT&amp;T. They stated that they had refunded the pension account to the tune of 9-1/2 billion. This deficit was of course caused by the stock market decline. I'm glad to see management taking their obligations seriously. If the market recovers this money what will they do with this advance? Both the Baby Bell I worked for and AT&amp;T have always treated me and others fairly. I appreciate it.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1353718010663</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:46:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353725034359-18</Id><Title>After Hours Quotes...</Title><Msg>... “To give thanks in solitude is enough. Thanksgiving has wings and goes where it must go. Your prayer knows much more about it than you do.” - Victor Hugo “Thanksgiving provides a formal context in which to consider the instances of kindness that have enlightened our lives, for moments of grace that have gotten us through when all seemed lost. These are fine and sentimental subjects for contemplation.” – Jon Carroll “We give thanks for unknown blessings already on their way.” – Anonymous “I refuse to believe that trading recipes is silly. Turkey Tetrazzini is at least as real as corporate stock.” – B. Harrison “We can only be said to be alive in those moments when our hearts are conscious of our treasures.” - Thornton Wilder “Home is the place where, when you have to go there, they have to take you in.” - Robert Frost “I have strong doubts that the first Thanksgiving even remotely resembled the ‘history’ I was told in second grade. But considering that (when it comes to holidays) mainstream America's traditions tend to be over-eating, shopping, or getting drunk, I suppose it's a miracle that the concept of giving thanks even surfaces at all.” - Ellen Orleans “Express your appreciation, sincerely and without the expectation of anything in return. Truly appreciate those around you, and you'll soon find many others around you. Truly appreciate life, and you'll find that you have more of it.” – Ralph Marston “Thanksgiving comes to us out of the prehistoric dimness, universal to all ages and all faiths. At whatever straws we must grasp, there is always a time for gratitude and new beginnings.” - J. Robert Moskin “Part of the secret of success in life is to eat what you like and let the food fight it out inside.” - Mark Twain “None is more impoverished than the one who has no gratitude. Gratitude is a currency that we can mint for ourselves, and spend without fear of bankruptcy.” - Fred De Witt Van Amburgh "I don't like the turkey, but I like the bread he ate." – anonymous child “Home is not where you live but where they understand you.” - Christian Morgenstern</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1353725034359</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:43:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353725061322-19</Id><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Msg>... “Thanksgiving, man. Not a good day to be my pants.” - Kevin James “Thanksgiving is America's national chow-down feast, the one occasion each year when gluttony becomes a patriotic duty.” - Michael Dresser "We're having something a little different this year for Thanksgiving. Instead of a turkey, we're having a swan. You get more stuffing." - George Carlin “Forever on Thanksgiving Day, the heart will find the pathway home.” - Wilbur D. Nesbit “Sleep 'til you're hungry, eat 'til you're sleepy.” - Unknown “We should look for someone to eat and drink with before looking for something to eat and drink.” – Epicurus “I have seen the worst of the worst, and the least for which to be thankful…yet, even they have reason to celebrate life…Let us all give thanks…Eqalycurius "This Thanksgiving is gonna be a special one. For the first time ever, my mom says I don't have to sit at the card table." – jon retard “Great restaurants are, of course, nothing but mouth-brothels. There is no point in going to them if one intends to keep one's belt buckled.” - Frederic Raphael “Americans say they are planning to do a lot of their holiday shopping this year at warehouse stores like Costco. Beause, folks, nothing says Merry Christmas like 90 rolls of toilet paper.” - Conan O'Brien “Q: Why does nobody get laid on Thanksgiving? A: All the coats are on the bed.” – George Carlin "Both abundance and lack exist simultaneously in our lives, as parallel realities. It is always our conscious choice which secret garden we will tend... when we choose not to focus on what is missing from our lives but are grateful for the abundance that's present -- love, health, family, friends, work, the joys of nature and personal pursuits that bring us pleasure -- the wasteland of illusion falls away and we experience Heaven on earth." - Sarah Ban Breathnach ‘Have a good weekend, all.” – echo2165</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1353725061322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:44:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353725585259-20</Id><Title>AHQ in between but edited...</Title><Msg>... “Thanksgiving comes to us out of the prehistoric dimness, universal to all ages and all faiths. At whatever straws we must grasp, there is always a time for gratitude and new beginnings.” - J. Robert Moskin “Part of the secret of success in life is to eat what you like and let the food fight it out inside.” - Mark Twain “None is more impoverished than the one who has no gratitude. Gratitude is a currency that we can mint for ourselves, and spend without fear of bankruptcy.” - Fred De Witt Van Amburgh "Colorado and Washington just legalized marijuana. If Hostess can't figure out a way to make money off of that, then maybe they shouldn't be in the snack cake industry. I guess I'll just have to take my business to Little Debbie." --Jimmy Kimmel "I don't like the turkey, but I like the bread he ate." – anonymous child “Epicurean cooks Sharpen with cloyless sauce his appetite, That sleep and feeding may prorogue his honor Evan till a Lethe'd dullness” - Shakespeare “Home is not where you live but where they understand you.” - Christian Morgenstern “Thanksgiving, man. Not a good day to be my pants.” - Kevin James “Fools make feasts, and wise men eat them.” – Benjamin Franklin "Facebook and the Department of Labor have teamed up for a new app that displays job openings. It'll be weird when people find a job because of Facebook, then get fired from that job for using Facebook, then use Facebook to find another job. It's the circle of life." --Jimmy Fallon “Thanksgiving is America's national chow-down feast, the one occasion each year when gluttony becomes a patriotic duty.” - Michael Dresser “Gluttony kills more then the sword.” – George Herbert "We're having something a little different this year for Thanksgiving. Instead of a turkey, we're having a swan. You get more stuffing." - George Carlin</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1353725585259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:53:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353730650381-21</Id><Topic><Title>California Nurses on Strike, cause of Barry</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1353462309458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 20:45:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may have heard that Hostess Bakery plants shut down due to a workers' strike. But you may not have heard how It was split up. The State Department hired all the Twinkies, the Secret Service hired all the HoHos, the generals are sleeping with the Cupcakes and the voters sent all the Ding Dongs to Congress.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1353730650381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 23:17:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353730901314-22</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet: cap gain 30%, 50% tax on the rich</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353097971771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is Warren a Democrat favorite? He is a filthy, lying, cheating, didn't build that rich guy. Same goes for all the Hollywood types that give all their money to the Dem's...oh I think I just figured it out, they are rich guys that support the Democrats. I guess money does make a difference.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1353730901314</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 23:21:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353731351060-23</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ in between but edited...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1353725585259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:53:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Echo must have been hitting the Thanksgiving wine a bit harder today; there are several repeats in his three messages. I guess perhaps he isn't perfect, in spite of his protests otherwise.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1353731351060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 23:29:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>