<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-31"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356950040532-1</Id><Topic><Title>Could 2013 be the Last Year for Your Employer Paid Plan?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356202702130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:58:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hate the truth, don't you, robfisk aka jon2retard.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1356950040532</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 05:34:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356950123716-2</Id><Topic><Title>Could 2013 be the Last Year for Your Employer Paid Plan?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356202702130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:58:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And people who drive Prius's, like jon2retard.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1356950123716</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 05:35:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356951006292-3</Id><Topic><Title>Betcha Barry Will settle Dockworkers Strike.</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356653762613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 19:16:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey jon2retard, are those the same "handlers" Bishop Robme uses?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1356951006292</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 05:50:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356951194768-4</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be afraid, be very afraid!!!</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1356951194768</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 05:53:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356954616525-5</Id><Topic><Title>Might be time for a moment of prayer for the good people of Chicago</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356789009225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 08:50:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I feel better now. After reading about the crime problems in Chicago and the state's fiscal issues (i.e., $100 billion deficit). I read today that our "dear leader" is finally taking a stand and advising Illinois law makers to legalize gay marriage. I'm sure the good people of Chicago will be comforted by his support. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1356954616525</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 06:50:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356958309042-6</Id><Topic><Title>Dear Progressives</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1356903610859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 16:40:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jon Get the oatmeal out of your nose and take your pills. It's night night time.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1356958309042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 07:51:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356962404091-7</Id><Topic><Title>FCC Report: AT&amp;T, Verizon Control 80% of US Market</Title><Username>pearliehazellwmlk7157</Username><Timestamp>1309627074000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2011-07-02 13:17:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Major Information Happening</Msg><Username>jalexander808</Username><Timestamp>1356962404091</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 09:00:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356966487145-8</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And rightfully so!</Msg><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1356966487145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 10:08:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356966849695-9</Id><Topic><Title>pinhighshot...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356614875031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 08:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And just how many 'facts' do you really know about the case? Enough to be the prosecutor or the defense team? Not likely! You're just like your buddy Obama, shoot first and ask for the facts later and then just ignore the 'fact' that you didn't know what you were talking about. Good show, you're fun to watch at times.</Msg><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1356966849695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 10:14:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356975236956-10</Id><Topic><Title>pinhighshot...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356614875031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 08:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was raining and he was lingering between the homes. That is suspicious and Z was doing his job and following at a distance and notified the police. When he returned to his car after the dispatcher said we don't need you to follow, Martin was at his car and attack him.</Msg><Username>shasta1010</Username><Timestamp>1356975236956</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 12:33:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356975631975-11</Id><Topic><Title>FACT::House Speaker Ranks Higher than Senate Speaker</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1356786562504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 08:09:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ is worthless second only to bush. Both drunks.</Msg><Username>orri1934</Username><Timestamp>1356975631975</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 12:40:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356978531457-12</Id><Topic><Title>pinhighshot...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356614875031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 08:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There were two witnesses that support Zimmerman's story. They both were interviewed on local radio. Why did the lying media photo shop Zimmerman's picture and give him blue eyes? Why did they edit his 911 call to make him say something he didn't? A DELIBERATE attempt to encite trouble. If I have a gun and a punk assaults me he will go the same way Trevon did.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1356978531457</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 13:28:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356979199334-13</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Obama Giving 17 Fighter Jets to the brotherhood?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356619460727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 09:44:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kind of off the subject but, since you are curious, she had 3 and we are now 83,84,and 85 and all in good health. How is your family?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1356979199334</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 13:39:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356979710964-14</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Obama Giving 17 Fighter Jets to the brotherhood?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356619460727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 09:44:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are already delusional and will probably be a total nut case when you get old. Not to worry; you probably won't get old.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1356979710964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 13:48:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356981963920-15</Id><Topic><Title>pinhighshot...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356614875031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 08:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Under any circumstances, that kid did not deserve to die.</Msg><Username>ourgovisajoke</Username><Timestamp>1356981963920</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 14:26:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356982545791-16</Id><Topic><Title>pinhighshot...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356614875031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 08:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"that kid did not deserve to die" Deserve, perhaps not. But, if he was trying to beat my brains out he may have met the same fate. As it is, only Zimmerman knows the truth.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1356982545791</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 14:35:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356987353014-17</Id><Topic><Title>Rumors on Wall Street of a $20 Special Dividend Announced Today for Monday</Title><Username>xtgeminiman</Username><Timestamp>1356709049022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:37:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a joke! T has a 230% payout ratio. $20 special dividend would have to be an advance on dividends for the next ten years.</Msg><Username>aviacionado</Username><Timestamp>1356987353014</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 15:55:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356987732168-18</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Obama Giving 17 Fighter Jets to the brotherhood?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1356619460727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 09:44:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe we should give them to ___ #$%$ chaney and haliburton. .or his vice W.</Msg><Username>orri1934</Username><Timestamp>1356987732168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 16:02:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356988566694-19</Id><Topic><Title>Dear Mr. John Boehner -</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1356922980840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 22:03:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not going to comment on the pros and cons of this post other than to say I think it would be better to send to Mr. Boehner at his Congressional e-mail address than on a Yahoo Finance board.</Msg><Username>rdcn100</Username><Timestamp>1356988566694</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 16:16:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356989290717-20</Id><Title>After Hours Quotes...</Title><Msg>... "The inaudible and noiseless foot of Time.” – Shakespeare “New Year's eve is like every other night; there is no pause in the march of the universe, no breathless moment of silence among created things that the passage of another twelve months may be noted; and yet no man has quite the same thoughts this evening that come with the coming of darkness on other nights.” - Hamilton Wright Mabie "Time has no divisions to mark its passage. Even when a new century begins it is only we mortals who ring bells and fire off pistols." - Thomas Mann “You can destroy your now by worrying about tomorrow.” – Janis Joplin “No, life has not disappointed me. On the contrary, I find it truer, more desirable and mysterious every year ever since the day when the great liberator came to me: the idea that life could be an experiment of the seeker for knowledge and not a duty, not a calamity, not trickery.” – Friedrich Nietzsche “The object of a new year is not that we should have a new year. It is that we should have a new soul.” - G.K. Chesterton "These times of ours are serious and full of calamity, but all times are essentially alike. As soon as there is life there is danger. " - Ralph Waldo Emerson “Many people look forward to the new year for a new start on old habits.” - Unknown</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356989290717</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 16:28:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356989297050-21</Id><Title>AHQ (cont.)...</Title><Msg>... “Each moment is a place you've never been.” – Mark Strand “New Year's Eve, where auld acquaintance be forgot. Unless, of course, those tests come back positive.” - Jay Leno “I think the second you stop fighting it, time really is on your side.” – J.D. “We will open the book. Its pages are blank. We are going to put words on them ourselves. The book is called ‘Opportunity’ and its first chapter is New Year's Day.” – Edith Lovejoy Pierce “Every man regards his own life as the New Year's Eve of time.” - Jean Paul Richter “Your Merry Christmas may depend on what others do for you. But your Happy New Year depends on what you do for others.” – anonymous "There are some things which cannot be learned quickly, and time, which is all we have, must be paid heavily for their acquiring. They are the very simplest things, and because it takes a man's life to know them the little new that each man gets from life is very costly and the only heritage he has to leave." - Ernest Hemingway “New Year's Day is every man's birthday.” - Charles Lamb</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356989297050</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 16:28:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356989304653-22</Id><Title>AHQ (3)...</Title><Msg>... “Yesterday, everybody smoked his last cigar, took his last drink and swore his last oath. Today, we are a pious and exemplary community. Thirty days from now, we shall have cast our reformation to the winds and gone to cutting our ancient shortcomings considerably shorter than ever.” - Mark Twain "As if you could kill time without injuring eternity. " - Henry David Thoreau "I want to go ahead of Father Time with a scythe of my own.” - H.G. Wells “The proper behavior all through the holiday season is to be drunk. This drunkenness culminates on New Year's Eve, when you get so drunk you kiss the person you're married to.” - P.J. O'Rourke “Time, time, time, see what's become of me, While I looked around, For my possibilities; I was so hard to please. But look around, leaves are brown And the sky is a hazy shade of winter.” – Paul Simon “If your New Years Resolution includes dieting - I'm a big fan of the Mars Bar Diet. You don't eat the Mars bar, you stick it up you’re a#s and let a rottweiler chase you home.” - Billy Connally “The Old Year has gone. Let the dead past bury its own dead. The New Year has taken possession of the clock of time. All hail the duties and possibilities of the coming twelve months!” - Edward Payson Powell “It is better to spend money like there's no tomorrow than to spend tonight like there's no money.” – P.J. O’ Rourke</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356989304653</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 16:28:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356989310402-23</Id><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Msg>... “You can destroy your now by worrying about tomorrow.” – Janis Joplin "It Depends on Us... Another year lies before us like an unwritten page, an unspent coin, an unwalked road. the pages will read, what treasures will be gained in exchange for time, or what we find alone the way, will largely depend on us.” – Esther Baldwin York “Forever is composed of nows.” – Emily Dickinson “Be always at war with your vices, at peace with your neighbors, and let each New Year find you a better man.” – Benjamin Franklin “I will seek elegance rather than luxury, refinement rather than fashion. I will seek to be worthy more than respectable, wealthy and not rich. I will study hard, think quietly, talk gently, and act frankly. I will listen to stars and birds, babes and sages, with an open heart. I will bear all things cheerfully, do all things bravely await occasions and hurry never. In a word I will let the spiritual, unbidden and unconscious grow up through the common.” – William Ellery Channing “The Old Year has gone. Let the dead past bury its own dead. The New Year has taken possession of the clock of time. All hail the duties and possibilities of the coming twelve months.” – Edward Payson Powell “For last year's words belong to last year's language and next year's words await another voice. And to make an end is to make a beginning.” – T. S. Eliot “Time is an illusion.” – Albert Einstein “Have a Happy and Safe New Year, all.” - echo2165 “There is an appointed time for everything… a time for war, and a time for peace” – Ecclesiastes “Did the ball drop yet?"</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356989310402</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 16:28:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356990269070-24</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The Federal union employees" Just the union employees? Only about 28% of Federal employees are union members.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356990269070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 16:44:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356992396199-25</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great idea! The best way to lower spending is to not worry about paying for it! It's worked for the boomers since '82. At least the not worrying about paying for it part.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356992396199</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 17:19:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356993225576-26</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love it. Republicans cause the crisis, whether you're talking about the recession, refusing to raise the debt ceiling, or writing expiration dates into the temporary Bush tax cuts, and then accuse Obama of "crisis management type government". Get real. Spin it all you want, even you must have difficulty getting past the fact that Republicans couldn't even compromise with themselves with "Plan B". Oh well. Off the fiscal cliff we go. Tax hikes for everyone. Massive defense spending cuts. Get what you want from all this refusing to compromise yet? I have never, ever seen a group of incoherent incompetents like the Tea Brains. And I lived through Bush!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1356993225576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 17:33:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356993744943-27</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you recall the Democrats are the ones that insisted on an end date for the current tax rates. The Democrats have been presented with multiple options to avoid this mess and all have been refused by the President or Dirty Harry. Not having a budget for three years has also contributed to not getting any legislation done in the recent past as well. Most of the spending bills for at least three years have been passed with a Democratic majority and they paid zero attention to the cost of their spending. They will continue to ignore the costs of their spending unless something is given in return for the increased revenue. The increased revenue should not be for increased spending! Obama has been the major roadblock because he has basically taken the Democratic part of Congress out of the game. He won and he wants his way come he&amp;&amp; or high water. If we all have to pay to satisfy his ego, so be it, he doesn't care. When you fools wake up and realize that he has a much larger agenda for us all that he is sharing, you will be sorry it took you so long.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1356993744943</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 17:42:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356995121713-28</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Political grandstanding at its finest.</Msg><Username>jeff_hirsch</Username><Timestamp>1356995121713</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 18:05:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357000448207-29</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ricky, I paid for my own and probably part of yours, you ingrate. The low wage earners get a higher percentage of SS income for wealth redistribution purposes, and so you can continue too vote democratic. BTW, boomers just started collecting SS, not in '82. YSF.</Msg><Username>jamlsher99</Username><Timestamp>1357000448207</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 19:34:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357000780653-30</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for posting. Most of the cretins on this board will not understand what you wrote, but it precisely matches the tactics our 'leaders' are using.</Msg><Username>jamlsher99</Username><Timestamp>1357000780653</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 19:39:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357008440701-31</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a fool. Google the Council on Foreign Relations and see how the membership control BOTH parties. Bush and Kerry were both members of this self styled "elitist" organization. Read it's charter. It's purpose is to destroy the U.S. and merge us into their "New World Odor." There are two types that defend what is going on, fools and those shills that are part of this gang and expect a reward. Many will get the same reward Stalin gave to his supporters.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1357008440701</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 21:47:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357012019304-32</Id><Title>They Will Run Up T into the ex-Div Date</Title><Msg>I expect T to trade around 35 going into 1/8.</Msg><Username>xtgeminiman</Username><Timestamp>1357012019304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 22:46:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>