<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-09"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349757949249-1</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem very upset even though the Romny's have done nothing wrong. What do you think about Clinton dodging the draft? You like many especially those to obeyed their drat notice must be insensed at Clinton</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1349757949249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 00:45:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349758218474-2</Id><Topic><Title>Back in Black</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1349741938935</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:18:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's suppose to be a secret. A couple of Senator's sold us out in 1913 down on the little island off the Georgia coast. So many dummies believe it's run by the Federal Government. The same dummies who believe in Bishop Rmoney!</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349758218474</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 00:50:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349758341004-3</Id><Topic><Title>Snoop Dog's top ten reasons to vote for BO</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349711348914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:49:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lv666 is that you I saw the other day grabing yourself as you walked down the street smiling flashing that grill. Why to you feel the need to entertain yourself in public get a room. What is with those saging pants is that so your boyfriend has easier access</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349758341004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 00:52:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349758403226-4</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT DOWN, STOCK MARKET UP, AUTO INDUSTRY STRONG! SOUNDS GOOD TO ME! WHY CHANGE?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349574314302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:45:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another ignorant Bishop Rmoney supporter. He relies on the trailer trash vote.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349758403226</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 00:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349758739511-5</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT DOWN, STOCK MARKET UP, AUTO INDUSTRY STRONG! SOUNDS GOOD TO ME! WHY CHANGE?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349574314302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:45:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Even many Democrats are starting to question the unemployment numbers." Total #$%$ as usual. You can't really believe all the crap you post here, nobody can be that stupid, oh wait...</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349758739511</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 00:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349759149912-6</Id><Topic><Title>Snoop Dog's top ten reasons to vote for BO</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349711348914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:49:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lv666 yo yo, BO approves gay marriage so when is your big day?</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349759149912</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:05:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349760307281-7</Id><Title>Princeton professor says BO lied about Romney tax plan study</Title><Msg>Princeton professor said the Obama campaign is misrepresenting his work and that Mitt Romney’s tax plan does not require raising taxes on the lower and middle class as Obama claimed. “I can’t tell exactly how the Obama campaign reached that characterization of my work,” Rosen said Professor Rosen's objection follows a similar statement released by the AARP immediately after the Oct. 3rd debate. Senior Vice President John Hishta said, "America's voters deserve more than talking points" and “AARP has never consented to the use of its name by the Obama campaign."</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760307281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:25:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349760689738-8</Id><Title>Major Restaurant Chain Cuts Hours to Avoid Obamacare Costs</Title><Msg>A major restaurant group is cutting its employees hours in the hopes of cutting the costs of healthcare. Darden Restaurants, which owns the Red Lobster, Olive Garden, LongHorn Steakhouse, and Yard House chains has stopped offering full-time schedules to hourly workers, the Orlando Sentinel reports. The company plans to offer a maximum of 28 hours per week per employee. Under a section of President Barack Obama's Affordable Healthcare Act, large employers face fines of up to $3,000 per employee if they fail to provide insurance for employees who work an average of 30 or more hours per week. Darden said it offers health insurance to its 185,000 employees nationwide but many are on a limited-benefit plan which will be phased out under Obamacare.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760689738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:31:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349783193114-9</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sort of like Obama's military service.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1349783193114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 07:46:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349785515830-10</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Due to the popularity of the "Survivor" shows, Texas is planning to do one entitled: "Survivor, Texas-Style!" The lucky contestants will all start in Dallas, drive to Waco, Austin, San Antonio, Houston and down to Brownsville. They will then proceed up to Del Rio, El Paso, Odessa, Midland, Lubbock and Amarillo. From there they will go on to Abilene and Fort Worth. And finally back to Dallas. Each contestant will be driving a pink Prius with 13 bumper stickers which will read: 1 "I'm a Democrat" 2 "Amnesty for Illegals" 3 "I love the Dixie Chicks" 4 "Boycott Beef" 5 "I Voted for Obama" 6 "George Strait Sucks" 7 "Re-elect Obama in 2012" 8. "Vote Eric Holder Texas Governor" 9. "Rosie O’Donnell is Texas born" 10. "I love Obama care and Chuck Schumer" 11. "Barney Frank is my hero" 12. "I side with Jane Fonda" And the last sticker is… 13. "I'm here to confiscate your guns" The first contestant to make it back to Dallas alive wins.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349785515830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 08:25:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349785859523-11</Id><Topic><Title>Major Restaurant Chain Cuts Hours to Avoid Obamacare Costs</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760689738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's actually great for large companies like T, the fine is cheaper than the cost of medical insurance! Watch for many companies to drop their provided insurance and let the Kenyan provide it.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349785859523</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 08:30:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349789435886-12</Id><Title>winholders Creationist Hallelujah moment...</Title><Msg>...so excited, he choked the rattlesnake. To my post: “Broun also said that he believes the Earth is about 9,000 years old and that it was made in six days. He sits on the House Committee on Science, Space and Technology.” winholder replied: “You can post this kind of crap and try to paint all Republicans as being the same if you want…” Winjondandale, don’t you ever get tired of just making stuff up to suit your perverted views? Show me where I even mentioned other Republicans. You can’t, because I didn’t. I posted a few sentences verbatim about a Congressman from Georgia who disavows science in general, and brazenly states unequivocally that everything he “was taught about evolution and embryology and Big Bang theory, all that is lies straight from the pit of hell.” And, as stated, “he believes the Earth is about 9,000 years old and that it was made in six days.” This clown, who unbelievably is also a doctor, even more surprisingly sits on The House Committee on Science, Space and Technology…and, yes, he happens to be a Republican. I made no mention of any other Republicans, and, quite frankly, if he was a Democrat or an Independent I would still choose to have him removed from that Committee. The point wasn’t at all about politics…it was about ignorance and blind-faith stupidity. And it was about how the lack of education by the electorate permits fundamentalist crackpots to be put in positions of authority, not unlike in some third-world countries now promoting Sharia law. And it was about the importance of the Constitutional concept of the First Amendment, summarized by Justice Hugo Black in 1947, when he said, “In the words of Thomas Jefferson, the clause against establishment of religion by law was intended to erect a wall of separation between church and state.” However, now that you’ve chosen, as you usually do, to confuse the issue for your own version of truth, let’s examine your points. Yes, he’s a Republican. You wanted to drag the women politicians from California into this, for reasons unknown. But go ahead, if you will. Name me any other politicians from the Democratic side who would suggest that the earth is only 9000 years old. While you’re at it, how old do you think the earth is, winny? Do you agree with this guy, or not? If you don’t, why are you defending him? Oh, that’s right, global warming and evolution are simply liberal conspiracies designed to help an illegal alien President to take over America. Here, you’re the smart guy…please debate Dr. Williams, if you’d care to (which I seriously doubt – these are scientists – you’re some home schooled message board dipstick.) “The simple fact is, Creationists have NO evidence that points to a 6 - 10 thousand year age for the earth! This belief is an article of faith for creationists and they have never found any significant scientific data to back it up. Finally, I would like to raise the issue of motive in these questions of the age of the earth. Scientists have no reason to claim an age of the earth of 4.5 billion years except for the results of decades of research and thousands of tests by independent researchers indicating the effectiveness of radiometric dating and that 4.5 billion years is the correct age of the earth. They have no stake in this date - other than that the facts support it. As the geochronologist Dalrymple said, ‘I have no reason whatsoever to want the age of the earth to be any more or less than it happens to be. I would take great delight in proving that the earth is only 10,000 years old if it were possible to do so.’ Creationists, on the other hand, have an extreme interest in proving the age of the earth to be 6 - 10 thousand years - it is required by their fundamentalist (literal) Biblical theology. To them, the earth must have been created in six literal days six thousand years ago. Any other possibility is a violation of their deeply held religious beliefs. In fact, all of the creation ‘science’ organizations require members to adhere to clearly religious ‘creeds’ that require them to accept the authority of the Bible in all matters. While this may be good religion, it is very, very bad science! Can we really trust such people to make a fair and unbiased attempt to determine the true age of the earth? We certainly haven't seen any evidence of it so far.” – Dr. Robert Williams And one last point. Here’s what you’re promoting. On a recent broadcast of “The Newsroom” on HBO, head writer, Aaron Sorkin, compiled a terrifying list of the belief system of a group we are currently battling in Afghanistan: “tribal mentality, ideological purity, unmoved by facts, hostile fear of progress, pathological hatred of the U.S. government, control of women’s bodies and choices, severe xenophobia, compromise is weakness, intolerance of dissent, demonization of education, denial of science, undeterred by new information, fundamentalist interpretation of scripture literalism, disallowance of voting for some sects of the population.” Gee, that sounds almost identical to the ideology of another such group a bit closer to home – The Tea Party, or as some refer to them, America’s Tal#iban. Before you folks do away with The Department of Education, I highly recommend that you go back to school and stop promoting ignorance.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1349789435886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:30:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349791639967-13</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The first contestant to make it back to Dallas alive wins." As to the alive part, it ain't gonna happen!</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1349791639967</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349791794826-14</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama daughters are close to military age, I'm sure he will encourage them to pursue a military career.</Msg><Username>jim.morris41</Username><Timestamp>1349791794826</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:09:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349792655981-15</Id><Topic><Title>winholders Creationist Hallelujah moment...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1349789435886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow echo, you sure are long winded.</Msg><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1349792655981</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:24:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349793436902-16</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“The first contestant to make it back to Dallas alive wins” – fake ricky “As to the alive part, it ain't gonna happen!” – t.bfine So, anyone in Texas with a bumper sticker that says “I’m a Democrat” or supports the President of the United States, will get killed? You’ve stooped to promoting vigilantism???? What’s your modus operandi? Lynchings by primitive, drunken mobs in sheets? About 3 and a half million Texans (almost 44%) voted for the President in ‘08, so you’re suggesting genocide on about half your population. What on earth is the matter with you people? You should be ashamed of yourselves. (Oh, I know… just kidding, right? Like Mitt was with the 47%)</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1349793436902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:37:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349794155234-17</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope, too busy having vacations paid for by the taxpayers.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349794155234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349794499328-18</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clinton was not in Paris trying to convert the girls in the brothels to Mormonism. You forgot the 5 deferments Cheney got, then had to get his wife pregnant because he ran out of deferments.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349794499328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:54:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349794518814-19</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one in Romney's family ever served. His father was born in Mexico, why? Because the family moved there to avoid US laws about polygamy. Romney in 1966 went to France as a missionary,instead of going to Vietnam. Conveniently his missionary service ended when he go a high enough draft lottery number. No Romney son has served, 5 out of 5. See a pattern here? Let the average Joe work, while we play. Obama registered for the draft and if there was a draft he would have been right in the line. Obama's grandfather and uncle served in the military and generations before that. Obama's WWII vet grandpa was his role model and teacher. Even on Obama's African side, there was military service in the king's army. Patriotic family, dishonored by the right wing thug slander. Biden of course has sons serving. All Romney's boys are doing is waiting for the inheritance tax to be unlimited and papa kicks the bucket. Another deficit increasing republican plan for the richest among us. No sane person could ever vote for Romney. A deviant who could point to Obama's young daughters and say see see they aren't going to go in the military, (as if they know they won't), is a perfect example of insanity</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349794518814</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:55:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349794866266-20</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is Dubya? I know he sold the Crawford Ranch because he doesn't need the phony cowboy prop anymore. Could he be hiding out in a posh Dallas gated community? Maybe the Bishop can have a secret fund raiser at Dubya's mansion, but better have a sweep of all electronic devices. Ha Ha</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349794866266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:01:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349795420383-21</Id><Topic><Title>Major Restaurant Chain Cuts Hours to Avoid Obamacare Costs</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760689738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"And last year, the company also put workers on a "tip sharing" program, meaning waiters and waitresses share their tips with other employees such as busboys and bartenders. That allows Darden to pay more workers a far lower "tip credit wage" of $2.13, rather than the federal minimum wage of $7.25 an hour.' You conveniently left this part of the article out. Darden is going to screw their workers regardless of the ACA.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349795420383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:10:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349795887579-22</Id><Topic><Title>Princeton professor says BO lied about Romney tax plan study</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760307281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:25:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Rosen's paper did find that families making more than $100,000 per year would have to pay $81 billion more in taxes under Romney's tax plan, a 12 percent increase. But his paper did not explicitly say whether these families, whose incomes he assumes would be rising, would actually pay a higher tax rate. Rosen's conclusion that Romney's tax plan is mathematically possible rests on a questionable assumption: namely that Romney's tax cuts for the rich would lead to robust economic growth. In fact, economic growth sharply slowed during the Bush administration, when President George W. Bush cut taxes for the rich. Brad DeLong, economics professor at the University of California at Berkeley, also notes that President Ronald Reagan's tax cuts for the rich did not lead to much stronger economic growth either."</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349795887579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:18:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349796141686-23</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lv666 "Clinton was not in Paris trying to convert the girls in the brothels to Mormonism" Good point, this is a good contrast between democrats and republicans. The democrat Clinton was hiding from the draft behind the skirt of a prostitute in a Paris Brothel. The republican Romney would try to get these women to change their sinful ways and seek a better life.</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349796141686</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:22:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349796228887-24</Id><Topic><Title>robfisk aka jon2retard</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349527969552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We learned that Republicans really care about the national debt, but only when a Democrat is in the White House. As Dick Cheney put it, "Reagan proved deficits don't matter."</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349796228887</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349797099433-25</Id><Topic><Title>robfisk aka jon2retard</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349527969552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you got your member up robfisk's anal canal. I guess you did not see etc., #$%$. The douchebag poster conveniently leaves out Dubya's 4 trillion of debt. More distortions from the reich-wing parrots.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349797099433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349797420833-26</Id><Topic><Title>Princeton professor says BO lied about Romney tax plan study</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760307281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:25:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're citing Brad Delong you have got to be kidding me. Delong is an idiot and is in step even with orthodox Marxism on where the value of money comes from. The Bush tax cuts benefit everyone not just rich people like the Obama's</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349797420833</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:43:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349798501642-27</Id><Topic><Title>Major Restaurant Chain Cuts Hours to Avoid Obamacare Costs</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760689738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lv666 you know you never leave a tip. you and your posse run the wait staff ragged with your special requests and like Moochelle never leave a tip. Darden follows the same practice that all restaurants follow. Obama has effecitvely eliminated the health care these employees were receiving. As of 2011, the federal minimum wage for wait staff is $2.13 per hour plus tips, and the general federal minimum wage rate is $7.25. If the total of your tips plus your hourly base rate do not equal at least the federal minimum of $7.25 per hour your employer must make up the difference.</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349798501642</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:01:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349799579076-28</Id><Topic><Title>Princeton professor says BO lied about Romney tax plan study</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760307281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:25:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The main conclusion of the Rosen study is that under plausible assumptions, a proposal suggested by Governor Romney can be revenue neutral and keep the net tax burden on taxpayers about the same. That is, an increase in the tax burden on lower and middle income individuals is not required in order to make the overall plan revenue neutral.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349799579076</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:19:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349799663557-29</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They always bring up Clinton, but they made a big deal out of it when Clinton ran, and when what's his name, the one with palin ran, they made it such an issue. It's a riot the inconsistency. It's Obama/Robme and Biden/Ryin running this time. Obama/Biden have far more patriotic serve America families then the others.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349799663557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:21:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349800188456-30</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you go away permanently and help clean up the gene pool?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349800188456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:29:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349800208115-31</Id><Topic><Title>Princeton professor says BO lied about Romney tax plan study</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760307281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:25:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, he's a idiot because a loser like you say's so. Do you have a economics degree or a GED? I think it is the latter.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349800208115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:30:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349800340219-32</Id><Title>Looks like all those dopes...</Title><Msg>..and you know who you are....that just LOVE to see T drop like a rock so they can get more "free" shares in their DRIP are gonna get their wish - and then some. Dolts.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1349800340219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:32:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349800521583-33</Id><Topic><Title>Princeton professor says BO lied about Romney tax plan study</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760307281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:25:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe in a businessman rather than a community organizer.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349800521583</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:35:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349803398055-34</Id><Topic><Title>Princeton professor says BO lied about Romney tax plan study</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760307281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:25:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right. Rosen say's it's possible under "plausible" assumption IF the new tax code results in deficit spending that spurs growth. So it does cause a deficit, but if Oprah, Romney and Obama decide to use the borrowed money to invest in the US (something that these "job creators" haven't done so far) you may get to deficit neutrality some day. He also states quite clearly: "Because the Romney proposal does not specify in detail just what tax preferences might be eliminated or scaled back in order to broaden the tax base, much of the debate has focused on what provisions would be politically and administratively feasible." The fact that Romney won't reveal his tax plan, and that everyone is guessing at what he may do, should be worrisome to you. Why won't he reveal his plan? Because it will be painful for most of us. Great for him and everyone else with a massive offshore account, but painful for the rest of us.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349803398055</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:23:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349804743444-35</Id><Topic><Title>Princeton professor says BO lied about Romney tax plan study</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760307281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:25:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama isn't providing full disclosure of his future plans either. Have you seen any Presidential candidate do so in the past 40 years? You think that Obama will not increase the tax burden on the middle class? He will increase the tax burden on everyone but it won't be used to pay down debt, it will be to fund new Democratic Party spending plans. Most in Washington, Democrats in particular, still haven't gotten the message that we can't continue to spend as we have in the past. They still don't understand that you MUST budget and make extraordinary efforts to adhere to those budgets. They must review programs and plans put in place to see that they are performing as expected and within budget and if not make the necessary changes, up to and including stopping the programs. Neither is putting their full plans out for public review because Romney knows the MSM will tear anything he share apart and ignore the fallacies in Obama’s. Obama won't share his because if he did he knows he won't be reelected. As for all these competing economists’ opinions, if you ask 100 of them, you will 100 different answers, especially around election time. Many of them are just sharing opinions, they are being paid for them, and that surely has an impact on that published opinion.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1349804743444</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:45:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349804999418-36</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No sane person would vote for Romney because his son's haven't served in the military? Is that your voting logic? God help us because there are way too many like you out there waiting for their chance to vote.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1349804999418</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:49:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349805188959-37</Id><Topic><Title>Major Restaurant Chain Cuts Hours to Avoid Obamacare Costs</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760689738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tip sharing in nothing new, my youngest daughter worked for tips as a youngster and they did tip sharing then, back in the early 90's. Just more of this, if anyone makes any money and they're not a Democrat supporter, they must be cheating someone or stealing.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1349805188959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:53:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349805819826-38</Id><Topic><Title>winholders Creationist Hallelujah moment...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1349789435886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No I don't agree with anything he has said on this subject, or any other subject of which I am aware. I said 'you were trying' to make this about Republicans and you know you where. If not, why not just state that a member of a Congressional committee on science made these statements, versus a pointed reference to a Republican member of Congress. I wanted to bring the idiot ladies of California into your discussion because you were ‘trying’ to slam Republicans and ignore the same sort of lunacy exist in the Democratic Party as well. Neither side has a lock on stupid public statements, our President has proven that himself. As for the fake vette lover, I can no longer share anything with my mother as she passed over twenty years ago. At least I had one that taught be respect for parents!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1349805819826</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:03:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349805948361-39</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN, you choose...</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717882561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? Don't most devout Christians at least attend church services? Personally I don’t think he is either. He is most like an agnostic and believes he is the only true God.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1349805948361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:05:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349806100615-40</Id><Title>AT&amp;T stop Throttling my iPhone!</Title><Msg>Lifetime owners getting the shaft! I'll be going to Verison</Msg><Username>investorzzo</Username><Timestamp>1349806100615</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:08:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349806412685-41</Id><Topic><Title>And if you dare to question the Emperor's new clothes...</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349552117236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Quote of the Decade: "The fact that we are here today to debate raising America's debt limit is a sign of leadership failure. It is a sign that the US Government cannot pay its own bills. It is a sign that we now depend on ongoing financial assistance from foreign countries to finance our Government's reckless fiscal policies. Increasing America 's debt weakens us domestically and internationally. Leadership means that, "the buck stops here.' Instead, Washington is shifting the burden of bad choices today onto the backs of our children and grandchildren. America has a debt problem and a failure of leadership. Americans deserve better." ~ Senator Barack H. Obama, March 2006 Yet another quote that Obama likely has never read: "There are two ways to conquer &amp; enslave a nation. One is by the sword. The other is by debt." -John Adams 1826</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1349806412685</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349806591906-42</Id><Topic><Title>Snoop Dog's top ten reasons to vote for BO</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349711348914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:49:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh there are more than 10 good reasons not to vote for this clown again, and they have nothing to do with race, just stupidity and dishonesty.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1349806591906</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349808028425-43</Id><Topic><Title>Princeton professor says BO lied about Romney tax plan study</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760307281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:25:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>COSTELLO: I want to talk about the unemployment rate in America. ABBOTT: Good Subject. Terrible Times. It's 9%. COSTELLO: That many people are out of work? ABBOTT: No, that's 16%. COSTELLO: You just said 9%. ABBOTT: 9% Unemployed. COSTELLO: Right 9% out of work. ABBOTT: No, that's 16%. COSTELLO: Okay, so it's 16% unemployed. ABBOTT: No, that's 9%. COSTELLO: WAIT A MINUTE. Is it 9% or16%? ABBOTT: 9% are unemployed. 16% are out of work. COSTELLO: IF you are out of work you are unemployed. ABBOTT: No, Obama said you can't count the "Out of Work" as the unemployed. You have to look for work to be unemployed. COSTELLO: BUT THEY ARE OUT OF WORK!!! ABBOTT: No, you miss his point. COSTELLO: What point? ABBOTT: Someone who doesn't look for work can't be counted with those who look for work. It wouldn't be fair. COSTELLO: To whom? ABBOTT: The unemployed. COSTELLO: But they are ALL out of work. ABBOTT: No, the unemployed are actively looking for work. Those who are out of work gave up looking and if you give up, you are no longer in the ranks of the unemployed. COSTELLO: So if you're off the unemployment roles that would count as less unemployment? ABBOTT: Unemployment would go down. Absolutely! COSTELLO: The unemployment just goes down because you don't look for work? ABBOTT: Absolutely it goes down. That's how Obama gets it to 9%. Otherwise it would be 16%. He doesn't want you to read about 16% unemployment. COSTELLO: That would be tough on his reelection. ABBOTT: Absolutely. COSTELLO: Wait, I got a question for you. That means there are two ways to bring down the unemployment number? ABBOTT: Two ways is correct. COSTELLO: Unemployment can go down if someone gets a job? ABBOTT: Correct. COSTELLO: And unemployment can also go down if you stop looking for a job? ABBOTT: Bingo. COSTELLO: So there are two ways to bring unemployment down, and the easier of the two is to have obama's supporters stop looking for work. ABBOTT: Now you're thinking like the Obama Economy Czar. COSTELLO: I don't even know what the hell I just said! ABBOTT: Now you're thinking like Obama.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349808028425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349808125112-44</Id><Title>Romney if President will buy USA &amp; Sell USA, he's a nit wit</Title><Msg>This guy is a dope, four years ago I would like to have seen what he would have done, Obama kept us afloat after another dope, Bush, put us in this mess, never gave teeth to SEC All field mortgage brokers were killing their companies until poop hit the fan and top dogs at these companies saw, that these people were approved for loans that were beyond their means. I for the life of me do not get the sub prime mortgages, like why give people $$$ you know are at risk of not paying their debts. Obama kept this country going and anyone who knows basic micro economics Knows that when banks get hurt by underlings in those banks to monkey business it takes awhile to RECOVER from that type of depression/slow growth for years. MAY GOD BLESS AMERICA &amp; MAY GOD BLESS OBAMA</Msg><Username>lefronczak</Username><Timestamp>1349808125112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349808314732-45</Id><Topic><Title>And if you dare to question the Emperor's new clothes...</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349552117236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not if you dare. It is if you are nutty, cooky or paranoid enough to question the report. Don't give this tactic of hacks the respectablility of being daring and act like being insulted for it some sort of terrible punishment. It's idiocy and worthy of insult. Especially in your case. We all saw you quote BLS figures you though favored your party in one thread, and then call them lies in another. Not only are you nutty, cooky and paranoid. You are a partisan hack with no interest in this beyond how you can use it to trick honest Americans. You'll make a great party operative in China when you finally move there.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349808314732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:45:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349808415596-46</Id><Topic><Title>And if you dare to question the Emperor's new clothes...</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349552117236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great. You people have gone from Beck to Madonna to Madoff.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349808415596</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:46:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349808655113-47</Id><Topic><Title>Princeton professor says BO lied about Romney tax plan study</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760307281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:25:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You probably believe in the tooth fairy also.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349808655113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:50:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349808834807-48</Id><Topic><Title>Princeton professor says BO lied about Romney tax plan study</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760307281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:25:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obama isn't providing full disclosure of his future plans either." Yes, Obama has. You and your fellow birthers think Obama is plotting some secret tax conspiracy. That's nothing new. In reality, Obama's plans have been open and consistent since his 2008 campaign. I do love that you and Romney seem to think "Because it will make me look bad in the media" is a good reason for keeping things secret.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349808834807</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349808925647-49</Id><Topic><Title>Romney if President will buy USA &amp; Sell USA, he's a nit wit</Title><Username>lefronczak</Username><Timestamp>1349808125112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:42:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This guy is a dope, in four years Obama has sunk us , Obama put us in this mess. All field mortgage brokers were killing their companies until poop hit the fan and top dogs at these companies saw, that these people were approved for loans that were beyond their means. I for the life of me do not get the sub prime mortgages, like why give people $$$ you know are at risk of not paying their debts. Obama forced banks to make these loans and anyone who knows basic micro economics Knows that when banks get hurt by underlings in those banks to monkey business it takes awhile to RECOVER from that type of depression/slow growth for years. MAY GOD BLESS AMERICA</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349808925647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349809292815-50</Id><Topic><Title>winholders Creationist Hallelujah moment...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1349789435886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So is winholder. Speaking of science committees, I think a tea partier brain is alot like their beliefs regarding regarding reproduction. In the case of a legitimate thought, they just shut that thing down.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349809292815</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349809309518-51</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN, you choose...</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717882561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bishop Rmoney and the Mormon church is the one's to be afraid of. Check out "The White Horse Prophecy".</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349809309518</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:01:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349809782450-52</Id><Title>romney pulls a head in 11 swing states</Title><Msg>320 electorial votes in a landslide, put a successful businessman in office, not an ideolog that couldn't run a lemonade stand without a gov loan.</Msg><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1349809782450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:09:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349810074899-53</Id><Topic><Title>winholders Creationist Hallelujah moment...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1349789435886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can try a seance. Maybe that will work for you. I love your false equivalency, you Republicans are so good at it.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349810074899</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349810176449-54</Id><Topic><Title>romney pulls a head in 11 swing states</Title><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1349809782450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another complete idiot. This is the Republican Party's best hope.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349810176449</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:16:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349811270183-55</Id><Topic><Title>romney pulls a head in 11 swing states</Title><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1349809782450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>even snl is waking up to the real BO, and that's what Americans saw in the debate, an empty suit or chair.</Msg><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1349811270183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:34:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349811451694-56</Id><Title>SHould i sign a expensive SHARED/LIMITED data contract w T or go w Sprint UNLIMITED data?</Title><Msg>hahahaahahah..look out below..here comes the BOOM. CHURN and BURN BABY!</Msg><Username>rmbdata</Username><Timestamp>1349811451694</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:37:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349813411979-57</Id><Topic><Title>romney pulls a head in 11 swing states</Title><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1349809782450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. Romney is enjoying a post debate bounce but he is still behind in the polls, including polls in most of the swing states. Romney's bounce is beginning to fade. As I said in another thread, the debate put a spotlight on policy, and Obama wins that debate in the end. Seriously. Another tax break for the wealthy? C'mon man. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349813411979</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:10:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349814585256-58</Id><Topic><Title>Friday is ex-div day..</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1349375130559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:25:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was more correct than I wanted to be. Rough time for this stock. Taking a bit of a beating - probably more to come.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1349814585256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:29:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349814708258-59</Id><Topic><Title>romney pulls a head in 11 swing states</Title><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1349809782450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney is not behind in the polls and right now the race is well within the margin of error. Now, please provide details on Romney's proposed additional tax break for the wealthy.</Msg><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1349814708258</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:31:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349814761333-60</Id><Topic><Title>Major Restaurant Chain Cuts Hours to Avoid Obamacare Costs</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760689738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>T provides medical coverage without the threat of a fine. Why do you think they will suddenly drop it if they have to pay a fine when they do? Employer-provided health benefits include alot of benefits for both workers and employers. These will remain under the ACA. On a side note, Romney has stated he's open to taxing your health benefits to pay for his tax cuts for the wealthy: "Mitt Romney says he might be willing to reduce income tax deductions used by millions of families for home mortgage interest and health care costs. He suggested the changes could be part of a plan that includes a 20 percent cut in tax rates across the board, continuation of upper income tax cuts that Obama wants to end and a comprehensive tax overhaul plan that the Republican presidential contender has so far declined to flesh out in detail."</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349814761333</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349817085390-61</Id><Topic><Title>Romney if President will buy USA &amp; Sell USA, he's a nit wit</Title><Username>lefronczak</Username><Timestamp>1349808125112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:42:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Much easier to hit 'ignore' on this lunatic. Not worth it to respond.</Msg><Username>dave_martin_2244</Username><Timestamp>1349817085390</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349817319973-62</Id><Topic><Title>Romney if President will buy USA &amp; Sell USA, he's a nit wit</Title><Username>lefronczak</Username><Timestamp>1349808125112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:42:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This country was sold into bondage in 1913 when the "Federal" Reserve Act was signed. Wilson and the other crooks in Congress sold you to the usurors. They've been bleeding this country since with the Ponzi swindle known as compound interest. Most boobs are too stupid to learn how it operates even though there are a great many books on the subject. One is titled, "The Creature From Jekyll Island." Jekyll Island Georgia was where J.P. Morgan (front man for the Rothschilds) and his fellow shylocks got together and cooked the "Federal" Reserve up. Read it, you may learn something if your IQ is above room temperature.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1349817319973</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:15:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349820951818-63</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN, you choose...</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717882561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a Marxist and Romney's an American....you choose!!!!</Msg><Username>foxey_4ever</Username><Timestamp>1349820951818</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:15:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349824327731-64</Id><Topic><Title>Romney if President will buy USA &amp; Sell USA, he's a nit wit</Title><Username>lefronczak</Username><Timestamp>1349808125112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:42:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have retired from your brain, if you ever had one. Any kind of actual information and objectivity is alien to you. You continue to spam. This is pretty much a right wing, "macho" testosterone #$%$ MB. But, there are many hoping to get balls soon !</Msg><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1349824327731</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:12:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349825224401-65</Id><Topic><Title>Romney says he was completely wrong on his 47% comments.</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349709369096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:16:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like I thought no right winger says romney was completely wrong, because they were just saying the other day the remarks about the 47% were right. Well now what're you gonna do? etch-a sketch it? sorry to rain on your romney debate sugar high.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349825224401</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:27:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349826028162-66</Id><Topic><Title>winholders Creationist Hallelujah moment...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1349789435886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Win, on occasion you show some sense and the ability to understand other points of view, but then, often, you go off on a rant mainly anti-"liberal". I don't get you. Not that I want to.</Msg><Username>rcub5d</Username><Timestamp>1349826028162</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349826393231-67</Id><Topic><Title>romney pulls a head in 11 swing states</Title><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1349809782450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he can pull my head. But then he would say he didn't. Then he would say, maybe I will. Maybe Lyin Ryan says I should.</Msg><Username>rcub5d</Username><Timestamp>1349826393231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:46:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349826442779-68</Id><Topic><Title>Romney if President will buy USA &amp; Sell USA, he's a nit wit</Title><Username>lefronczak</Username><Timestamp>1349808125112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:42:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What the heck are you talking about, Obama forced banks to make loans, this problem started way before 2007, you and Dave- Martin can go split a beer I put you Martin on ignore These problems were going on way before Obama took office and he took us from the brink of death and kept us alive, you can't fix these issues overnight, ignore, Romney is worse than Bush the hillbilly down on his cow poop farm in Texas</Msg><Username>lefronczak</Username><Timestamp>1349826442779</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:47:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349826539090-69</Id><Topic><Title>Romney says he was completely wrong on his 47% comments.</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349709369096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:16:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why they call him "flipper"! LOL!!!</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1349826539090</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:48:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349827271508-70</Id><Topic><Title>Princeton professor says BO lied about Romney tax plan study</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760307281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:25:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cute</Msg><Username>rcub5d</Username><Timestamp>1349827271508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:01:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349828277658-71</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO mliitary service to their country from the romney clan, nothing, nada, zzzippp.. Not only in their old Mexico polygamy hiding place, but where they live now, America. I won't be voting for that.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349828277658</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:17:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349828482392-72</Id><Title>Polygamy and draft dodging is your thing?</Title><Msg>vote fer ronmey or whatever his name is.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349828482392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:21:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349828972946-73</Id><Topic><Title>Polygamy and draft dodging is your thing?</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349828482392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:21:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do You know any history of the Mormon Battalion and how vital is was to the Southwest? Quit watching theEdShow. It 's all lies</Msg><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1349828972946</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:29:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349830134012-74</Id><Title>Mitt is It</Title><Msg>Women are a lot smarter than Barry gave them credit for. The war on women campaign failed miserably, (the women polling is even). Barry's lead is evaporating. The only war Barry is waging is on the middle class. He has to destroy them, in order to push his Socialist agenda. A la the Food Stamp President. What they saw was the real Barry, and it was scary. That reminds me, Scary Kerry was his debate coach. We all saw Barry unplugged, with his mind on parade. He's a Parrot, only able to break down his mug, and deliver a teleprompter line. I really think Snoop Dog nailed it. Barry had some weed to calm his nerves before the debate. How else can you explain all that grinning, and laughing to himself. My man was high. I 've said before, the Dems would curse the day they heard his name. On Cavuto Tonight, they were predicting the triple play. The Presidency, The House, and maybe even the Senate. I can't wait till Plugs debates Ryan. Must see TV.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1349830134012</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:48:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349830373339-75</Id><Topic><Title>romney pulls a head in 11 swing states</Title><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1349809782450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another Green solar company in Denver is going bankrupt. Colorado is ready to launch a full scale investigation. This guy has the Chicago, gangster money laundering thing down. Can you imagine how much money he could steal in a 2nd term?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1349830373339</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:52:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349831360203-76</Id><Topic><Title>Back in Black</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1349741938935</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:18:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wall Street always backs both sides. Just in case. But, they know all these QE plans will eventually cause stagflation. Increasing prices on goods, while causing falling or stagnant wages. That is why Wall Street is Mitt's biggest donor. Barry's economy on crack will end badly. Also, they are tired of Barry always bashing them. But, Barry is hurting poor to middle class folks the most. The Hispanic vote will surprise many. These people are interested in jobs, Barry has failed anyone on the bottom rung of the economic ladder. Regime change is just weeks away!</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1349831360203</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 21:09:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349832874371-77</Id><Title>Peppeek</Title><Msg>A troll from the microsoft board</Msg><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1349832874371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 21:34:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349833179408-78</Id><Topic><Title>Major Restaurant Chain Cuts Hours to Avoid Obamacare Costs</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760689738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not true. It's Obama who wants to cut the mortgage deduction. He believes that minorities, because of his Fannie Mae meltdown, won't be deducting mortgage interest. Why, Barry had them approved, without ensuring they'd be able to pay the mortgage. Consequently, they defaulted. So, Barry sees this as a white, middle class subsidy. It will be gone in Barry's 2nd term. Also, it will cause a hit in real estate, causing more food stamp users. Destroying the middle class is job 1 for Obama.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1349833179408</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 21:39:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349835666498-79</Id><Topic><Title>Princeton professor says BO lied about Romney tax plan study</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349760307281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:25:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush tax Cuts gave a $ 1000.00 Tax credit for each child . ! to do away with the Bush Cuts , Would Make Every Household with Children , A TAX , Increase . !</Msg><Username>gandschisenhall</Username><Timestamp>1349835666498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349835740617-80</Id><Topic><Title>Peppeek</Title><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1349832874371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 21:34:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I go to any message board I like, when I like, how I like, not "from" any board, genius. Maybe you are in the wrong country.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349835740617</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:22:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349836179560-81</Id><Topic><Title>Peppeek</Title><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1349832874371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 21:34:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the way ya post at others, let me guess 1) ya drive a Prius 2) Liberal 3) Voted for Obama 4) Quick to call names on those that disagree with ya Rummy</Msg><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1349836179560</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:29:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>