<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345953635000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan is Trending #1 now on searches</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345748488000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 15:01:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey robfisk, went looking at the Prius today, how do you like yours?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1345953635000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 00:00:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345953825000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Hate Board</Title><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1345843662000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 17:27:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Bishop will be going back preaching to his congregation Nov.3.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1345953825000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 00:03:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345977426000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Hate Board</Title><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1345843662000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 17:27:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There goes the libtard alarm. You immediately accuse our speech as "racist" as you feel threatened by people who counter the mainstream media monopoly. People are tired of the biased mainstream media who do not cover what Obama has done destroy our industries, individual wealth and freedom, energy, and country in general. Educate yourself before assuming the role of a blind sheep to be used by your liberal communist superiors. -A good book about his communist influence is: The Communist: Frank Marshall Davis: The Untold Story of Barack Obama's Mentor. Mercury Ink, 2012. ISBN 978-1451698091 -A good movie that you should watch is "2016: Obama's America". When I was at the theatre, the audience applauded loudly after the movie was finished. This is just a small start for you, but I think it would at least help you pull your head out of the distal orifice of your alimentary canal. (aka - anus)</Msg><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345977426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 06:37:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345977746000-4</Id><Topic><Title>DOW at 13,000..President Obama Saved America!!!</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1345843666000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 17:27:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jbhdallas2000 either wants attention or his services are paid by the obama campaign or one of George Soros' groups.</Msg><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345977746000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 06:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345984743000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama denied access to UVA Campus</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1345937570000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 19:32:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “I worked that area 10 yrs .. all over the U.Va campus too.” – jon Wow, that must be one of your main landscaping gigs, I would assume. Hey, I saw some of your guys mowin’ over at the Darden Business School – do they all have green cards?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1345984743000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:39:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345987279000-6</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT: Watch Video Now!</Title><Username>crowthermju9460</Username><Timestamp>1345981974000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 07:52:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess I agree with that.</Msg><Username>rosebushlfx0337</Username><Timestamp>1345987279000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 09:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345990014000-7</Id><Topic><Title>DOW at 13,000..President Obama Saved America!!!</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1345843666000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 17:27:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good message from Bill Whittle: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3778luxnpI0&amp;feature=youtu.be</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1345990014000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:06:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345991330000-8</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT: Watch Video Now!</Title><Username>crowthermju9460</Username><Timestamp>1345981974000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 07:52:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>brilliant analysis</Msg><Username>brummerjon7251</Username><Timestamp>1345991330000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:28:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345992915000-9</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Midwest Terminations</Title><Username>fezofreese</Username><Timestamp>1345943740000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:15:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some of that should be done to craft in the PacBell region. Some of these Comm Techs, you could terminate today and not even notice tomorrow. Management seems like ostrich with heads in the sand.</Msg><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1345992915000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:55:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345993052000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Hate Board</Title><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1345843662000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 17:27:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right. He can not communicate with the average American Voter. Maybe if he put on Fruit of the Loom's he could associate with the common man.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1345993052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:57:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345993790000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan is Trending #1 now on searches</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345748488000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 15:01:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Obama campaign machine is having much smaller crowds at their events. They are actually trying to spin it that this is by design. If you believe that, then you'll likely believe that you can take $700 BILLION from medicare, and make it cover more seniors.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345993790000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:09:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345994356000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Hate Board</Title><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1345843662000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 17:27:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, New York. Get over your guilt. We voted Barry in, for his Hope &amp; Change. Now, we are in a bigger hole, financially. So now we can only hope for regime change. Investors really enjoy the truth about capital gains, and dividend tax increases, that are certain in Obama 2.0. So this is really relevant. Good try though. You are swimming upstream however. The electorate is starting to pay attention. If Mitt's taxes were an issue. Don't you think he would have been audited by now. This, and the fabricated war on women are just failed diversions, to this guys total ineptness in office. Regime change is just weeks away.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345994356000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345994733000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan is Trending #1 now on searches</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345748488000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 15:01:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was the GOP that put the big retirement tax on the Post Office.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1345994733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:25:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345995975000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Hate Board</Title><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1345843662000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 17:27:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read the book from which the movie is derived. A lot more detail and a lot more information about what is driving Obama Jr.'s ambition. He wants desperately to achieve his father’s dreams, of course daddy was a wanna be professional student and politician that died with a hardening liver and from driving while drunk. Must have been a he%% of a dream. He is a socialist, but not an ordinary socialist. Alinsky and other of his mentor have a philosophy that you can't defeat the oppression by the upper classes without the support of the middle class. If you destroy the middle class and create a joint hatred of the rich between the poor and the middle class, you will never win. Obama is in the process of destroying the middle class to gain support for his dismantling of the oppressive rich colonialists that run the businesses and control the money. He doesn't just want to redistribute the nation’s wealth, he wants to control it so only he or those like him can decide how, where and when to redistribute the wealth. In his mind he seeks and believes he can achieve changes that will allow him to continue this fight well after this coming election. This book starts to describe the agenda that Obama is not sharing with the general public. His past associations with questionable ‘mentors’ is indeed a bit frightening when you look at the attributes he ascribes to them and their influence on him.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345995975000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:46:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345996381000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Corn Prices up 23% world wide in July</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345252755000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:19:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Last night, I attended a Quenciada. I'm sure I spelled that wrong. That's a coming out party for young Hispanic Women. As I've said before, my wife works with both illegal, and legal immigrants. After a little sangria, I got some to admit to survive, some illegals they know, are involved in criminal activity. Remember, a couple weeks back, a report came out, back West, about a couple of guys lighting newspapers, and throwing them into the brush, off of the back of a pickup truck. They do this to get work. You'd think there would be a reward for info on this. However the story was completely dropped. Last I checked, wasn't arson still a crime in this Country.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345996381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:53:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345996417000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan is Trending #1 now on searches</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345748488000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 15:01:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reportedly, He has disowned another half brother because he chooses not to fight the good fight of their father. He is a physicist and told Obama he is living in China working as a business consultant because you can't find work as a physicist Africa. He dislikes his brother even more because he chooses to take the last name of his mother. The other brother says after the way Obama Sr. treated his mother, he wants nothing to do with the Obama name. Great family tree this guy is working to keep growing, huh?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345996417000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345996824000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the jobs?</Title><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1345646301000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-22 10:38:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama views racists as a hindrance to his goals, particularly racist’s opportunist like Jesse and Al. They draw attention to racial issues that take away from or bring too much attention to his anti-colonialist goals. His goal is not to improve things for the 'oppressed' races, but to bring down the colonialist attitudes of the white European ruling classes that are the source of all evil and power in the world. It is the time of the oppressed to rise, take control, and make the white European the same as the multi-colored masses.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345996824000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:00:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346005384000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Hate Board</Title><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1345843662000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 17:27:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When I was at the theatre, the audience applauded loudly after the movie was finished." Aka: The conservtard alarm.</Msg><Username>brainstemonly</Username><Timestamp>1346005384000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 14:23:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346006811000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I have read that he and Pastor Wright are still close friends." Yeah, taht Wright guy had some whacky religious services, didn't he? I wonder what kind of whacky stuff has been preached to Romney?</Msg><Username>brainstemonly</Username><Timestamp>1346006811000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 14:46:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346010845000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Hate Board</Title><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1345843662000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 17:27:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libs know what the truth is at least. Your side is sketchy. It would be difficult to have sex with one of you because of all the changes in position.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346010845000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 15:54:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346011419000-21</Id><Title>What needs to be done with the Romney capital gains relief</Title><Msg>1st. Hire people. Jobs gets votes. Someone needs to be the 1st and we have plenty of shovel ready needs. Privite sector hiring will snow ball better than government. 2nd Hike dividends. It puts money in peoples pocket. Grandma spends. Most of us will get them tax free (under Romney/Ryan). 3rd Pay off loans. Less debt less profit pressure. It also puts money in the lenders pockets. Lenders spend. Stephenson should make a pre-election conference call and promote privite sector stimulus. He needs to make the public some promises (after all he's not a Welsher). He needs to go out and earn us this tax cut! He's a chump if he don't hit back (at the feds) for shipping American jobs &amp; money overseas, with the in your face T-Mobile snuff out.</Msg><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1346011419000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:03:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346012498000-22</Id><Topic><Title>What needs to be done with the Romney capital gains relief</Title><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1346011419000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hire people. Just what Obama wanted, but the House, since they want him to be a one term President sit on their hands. As far as shipping jobs overseas, Romney is for it look at the stuff he imported to stock Staples, and Sports Authority. Then he took part of his profits,and hid the money in foreign banks. He has been playing both ends. If the American dollar went under due to his and other people shipping our best jobs out of the U.S. he still was a winner. Their may be great repurcusions if the GOP, Mitches boys approve everything they have been against when Obama proposed it.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346012498000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346014947000-23</Id><Topic><Title>What needs to be done with the Romney capital gains relief</Title><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1346011419000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's your problem (minn). 1st Stephensen isn't a politican. 2nd Obama's capitals gains tax is giong to ship more jobs overseas in one day than Romney's international enterprises did in his whole career. 3rd One thing we agree on is that Obama is no financial winner (and Ronmey is). 4th Mitch and the boys aren't trying to make 1% of the population shoulder a problem that needs a 100% effert.</Msg><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1346014947000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:02:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346015686000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Hate Board</Title><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1345843662000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 17:27:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is so straightforward. You're an idiot!</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1346015686000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:14:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346016177000-25</Id><Topic><Title>What needs to be done with the Romney capital gains relief</Title><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1346011419000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Minn, you idiot! What do you think the 800 Billion for "Shovel Ready" jobs money was for?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346016177000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:22:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346016471000-26</Id><Topic><Title>What needs to be done with the Romney capital gains relief</Title><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1346011419000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Back to the point. The democrats are going to try to depict the Romney capital gains tax cut as given to a few fat cats to put in foreign banks. Our boss (RS) needs to commit the extra money so the democrats can't. I wish this arguement was about how the money would be best spent.</Msg><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1346016471000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:27:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346016893000-27</Id><Topic><Title>What needs to be done with the Romney capital gains relief</Title><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1346011419000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you have an idiotic opinion about this too. Do you ever stop embarrassing yourself?</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1346016893000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:34:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346017355000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Ask the twit about his 2002 taxes</Title><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345215680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better ask the kenyan!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346017355000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:42:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346022647000-29</Id><Topic><Title>What needs to be done with the Romney capital gains relief</Title><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1346011419000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, Obama has had more obstacles to overcome in his life then RoHmney. I would make a comparision of President Hoover a self made millionaire, before getting into politics. He was President in what we call the great depression. We did not get out of this until another Millionare, but not self made one, FDR led America out of what many said was a ressession, that Hoover the self made million turned into the worst depression in history. Do you believe in the tooth fairy too?</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1346022647000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 19:10:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346026044000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan is Trending #1 now on searches</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345748488000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 15:01:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One would have to say that Obama is part of a disfunctional family. The problem is that of division. Now he is trying to divide us. Black against white, poor against rich. And the worst yet, young against old. If you are a senior, don't forget to talk to your kids, and grand children. Tell them, you can't take it with you. But Obama's redistribution, can steal what is your kids inheritance. Don't assume your kids understand. Barry loves to misinform the youth.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346026044000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:07:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346026687000-31</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY HIT A HOME RUN TODAY IN NEW MEXICO</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345774446000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 22:14:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will Mitt go to other areas where the economy is on life support? I believe this is a good strategy. Barry seems to only like going to college campuses. The kids don't know how successful America can be. They only know of bad times under the Dems. No summer jobs. Why? Unlimited illegal immigration to jobs these kids depend on. Restaurants, landscaping, and construction.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346026687000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:18:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346027474000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan is Trending #1 now on searches</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345748488000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 15:01:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow rob, your a jackoff of all trades, now your a psychologist. Maybe you can help out the Bishop, and his sidekick Ayn Rand Ryan. Those two have deep psychological problems.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1346027474000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346028162000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Hate Board</Title><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1345843662000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 17:27:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When I was at the theatre, the audience applauded loudly after the movie was finished." Most had missing front teeth and IQ's under 80. The republiCon base at its best.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1346028162000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:42:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346029011000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan is Trending #1 now on searches</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1345748488000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 15:01:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's just flush that big turd this November!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1346029011000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:56:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346029749000-35</Id><Title>Why did Barry's FCC &amp; Justice Pass the Vz Merger?</Title><Msg>Isn't Barry supposed to be pro Union? Why didn't he let this Vz-Cable, non-compete deal drag on until after the election? Instead, Barry decided to kick those without a contract below the belt. I thought he promised to walk the picket line if need be. OK, it might be bad to show a sitting President on the line, but this action will eventually cost several hundred thousand CWA-UNION jobs. And it does nothing to help the customer. Barry whacked Union members and customers like flies with a flyswatter.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1346029749000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346032426000-36</Id><Topic><Title>A little fun</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1345836514000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 15:28:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell us the funny joke about liberals putting the barrel of a loaded and cocked pistol in their mouth and then going break dancing !</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1346032426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:53:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>