<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350619346858-1</Id><Topic><Title>I'm voting for Romney</Title><Username>fatty_arbukkle</Username><Timestamp>1350528588928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 22:49:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I already voted for Obama/Biden and every democrat on the ballot and every democrat proposaL All done. I voted for Nixon, Reagan, and even GWB, never again will vote republican never ever.. You can't be like this towards a fine man and a fine President and not have backlash from thinking people who understand America.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1350619346858</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 00:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350642866381-2</Id><Topic><Title>Jobless claims hit an unexpected 4 month high</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1350572391490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 10:59:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>also the welfare rate has increased 32% to the highest level since obummer took office. I did not say to 32% either.</Msg><Username>spe754</Username><Timestamp>1350642866381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 06:34:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350643107560-3</Id><Topic><Title>Jobless claims hit an unexpected 4 month high</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1350572391490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 10:59:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ricky, you had better read the news. it went up last week. wonder how obummer was able to manipulate the numbers.</Msg><Username>spe754</Username><Timestamp>1350643107560</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 06:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350647535502-4</Id><Topic><Title>I'm voting for Romney</Title><Username>fatty_arbukkle</Username><Timestamp>1350528588928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 22:49:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I am a retired telecommunications person." "Personally I will contact someone for you." WOW!!!!</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1350647535502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 07:52:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350650807799-5</Id><Topic><Title>only the csco board is more insecure than t</Title><Username>tracker57888</Username><Timestamp>1350612791462</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 22:13:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all the boards are the same this time of election.</Msg><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1350650807799</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:46:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350654883004-6</Id><Title>Randall *</Title><Msg>Give the employees your take on a reverse stock split and cut in dividends because of the decisions made over the years running the dividends up to show wall street what a good job you are doing.......... until T can no longer pay them . We think it's the same jive obama is doing spending all that money running up the 16 Trillon dollar debt until oneday the government can no longer pay just the interest on it . Then when the S**** hits the fan after we blame the collapse on someone else who is president .</Msg><Username>onebellplaza</Username><Timestamp>1350654883004</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 09:54:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350655431265-7</Id><Topic><Title>I'm voting for Romney</Title><Username>fatty_arbukkle</Username><Timestamp>1350528588928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 22:49:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would ask obama about not raising my taxes 1 single dime as he is talking about socking the power companies with a carbon tax to raise hundreds of billions to reduce the debt by half in 10 years..........sounds good bro but I am sure the power companies have a plan in the works to deal with that tax you jiving idiot.</Msg><Username>onebellplaza</Username><Timestamp>1350655431265</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:03:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350655613396-8</Id><Topic><Title>I'm voting for Romney</Title><Username>fatty_arbukkle</Username><Timestamp>1350528588928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 22:49:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The CFR gets who they want everytime. They control BOTH parties and the lying press and unions. If you think you really have a choice you are a fool. The same types financed "Communism" in Russia. The head of Kuhn Loeb Nank in New York financed Trotsky from his own pocket to the tune of 20 million in 1917. Ask yourself why rich banksters would finance "Communists".</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1350655613396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:06:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350659313596-9</Id><Topic><Title>Latest poll show Obama pulling ahead</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1350609433001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 21:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was easy he is a writer for FOX so called NE.WS</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1350659313596</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 11:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350659726389-10</Id><Topic><Title>Latest poll show Obama pulling ahead</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1350609433001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 21:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is the rest of the list? It has got to be much longer than this</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1350659726389</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 11:15:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350659824400-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama will ban guns in his second term!!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1350575258049</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 11:47:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ name a piece of legislation he has introduced re: handguns.....I'm waiting</Msg><Username>hrod57</Username><Timestamp>1350659824400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 11:17:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350659907536-12</Id><Title>Sell Sell Sell</Title><Msg>Again sell sell sell check the 200 n 50 MDA's</Msg><Username>hrod57</Username><Timestamp>1350659907536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 11:18:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350659960174-13</Id><Topic><Title>WOW Awesome Romeny would not tax dividends</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1350492924834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:55:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just think that T dividend some will collect very soon would be all ours to do with what we want, no tax what a nice thought</Msg><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1350659960174</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 11:19:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350663225971-14</Id><Topic><Title>Spammers</Title><Username>soupbone15</Username><Timestamp>1350586852492</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 15:00:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not only are they working overtime,, they've started replying to there one post to bump them to the top all of the time. I think it's time to find a new message board source,, any ideas? I'll check bing to see if they are have a message board that isn't cluttered with crap.</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1350663225971</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:13:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350664282789-15</Id><Title>OK the "IGNORE USER" is working great now,,</Title><Msg>Getting rid of all spammers and political #$%$ and it left just 3 relevant posts to read about AT&amp;T stock,, finally making use of something YAHOO made better.</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1350664282789</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:31:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350665451212-16</Id><Title>Solid Gold Character Reference</Title><Msg>Solid Gold Character Reference Let see if I have this straight... Former President Bill Clinton... who lied to his own wife... was convicted of perjury... disbarred from practicing law in his home state... an admitted philanderer... who "Never had sexual relations with that woman, Miss Lewinsky" ...Impeached by the US House of Representatives... is giving testimonials for Barrack Obama's character and intentions!? Is this a great country or what?</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1350665451212</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:50:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350665507055-17</Id><Title>Only In America</Title><Msg>TOP-10 "Only In America" Observations ~ by a Canadian 1) Only in America, could politicians talk about the greed of the rich at a$35,000.00 a plate campaign fund-raising event. 2) Only in America, could people claim that the government still discriminates against black Americans when they have a black President, a black Attorney General, and roughly 18% of the federal workforce is black while only 12% of the population is black. 3) Only in America, could they have had the two people most responsible for our tax code, Timothy Geithner, the head of the Treasury Department and Charles Rangel who once ran the Ways and Means Committee, BOTH turn out to be tax cheats who are in favor of higher taxes. 4) Only in America, can they have terrorists kill people in the name ofAllah and have the media primarily react by fretting that Muslims might beharmed by the backlash. 5) Only in America, would they make people who want to legally become American citizens wait for years in their home countries and pay tens of thousands of dollars for the privilege while we discuss letting anyone who sneaks into the country illegally just 'magically' become American citizens. 6) Only in America, could the people who believe in balancing the budget and sticking by the country's Constitution be thought of as "extremists." 7) Only in America, could you need to present a driver's license to cash a check or buy alcohol, but not to vote. 8) Only in America, could people demand the government investigate whether oil companies are gouging the public because the price of gas went up when the return on equity invested in a major U.S. oil company (Marathon Oil) is less than half of a company making tennis shoes (Nike). 9) Only in America, could the government collect more tax dollars from the people than any nation in recorded history, still spend a Trillion dollars more than it has per year - for total spending of $7-Million PER MINUTE, and complain that it doesn't have nearly enough money. 10) Only in America, could the rich people - who pay 86% of all income taxes - be accused of not paying their "fair share" by people who don't pay any income taxes at all.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1350665507055</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:51:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350667468067-18</Id><Topic><Title>Right wing radical terds, Romney made a fool out of himself in front of America at the debate</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1350573485363</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 11:18:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is "Meet the Press" on "Faux" news? The US Ambassador to the UN was on "Meet the Press" telling all of us that the Libya attack was a response to a video and not a terrorist attack. Doesn't the State Department answer directly to the president or am I missing something?</Msg><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1350667468067</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:24:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350672588454-19</Id><Topic><Title>Right wing radical terds, Romney made a fool out of himself in front of America at the debate</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1350573485363</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 11:18:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your side will wish you had gotten your facts from FOX because the breaking news a few minutes ago says Fox now has obtained many documents showing the real facts of the Libya security request and panic setting in while the administration ignored their plight. If anything gets flushed down a toilet, it will be your side after this news is broadcast today.</Msg><Username>demsdontgetitever</Username><Timestamp>1350672588454</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:49:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350675825381-20</Id><Topic><Title>Right wing radical terds, Romney made a fool out of himself in front of America at the debate</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1350573485363</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 11:18:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is becoming increasingly clear to me that this Administration at some level tried to cover up and sweep under the rug what happened in Libya. Most media outlets took their word and were ready to move on. Fox Cable News, on the other hand, stayed after the issue and now the whole mess is unraveling. The President can say he said it was a terrorist attack (with his Rose Garden play on words) but it is nearly impossible for him to explain why UN Ambassador Susan Rice, who by the way, enjoys a Cabinet level position, subsequently appeared on 5 networks in one day telling America it was not a premeditated attack. Just one of many conflicting events that suggest that the President has a very serious problem on his hands. Everyday more facts come to light including earlier but recent probing attacks on the very same embassy and repeated pleas from the embassy for more protection which were either ignored or dismissed by the President's Administration. The President seems to realize he has a big and festering problem on his hands. Clinton even tried to defuse the mess by taking the hit, but it simply isn't working. A growing number of Americans aren't buying it. What is obvious is that their feeble attempts to make it go away aren't working and the story gets worse every day and it doesn't look like they will be able to push the mess past the election.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1350675825381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:43:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350676056846-21</Id><Title>BO Libya coverup</Title><Msg>BO's concoction of the video story to explain the attack in Benghazi was a cover created by Obama to cover up the disaster that our operation involving the removing of Moammar Khadafy proved to be. Getting rid of Khadafy basically turned the Benghazi area into an Al-Qaeda stronghold. BO concocted the story that the video was responsible for the death of the ambassador and the three other Americans in the attack in Benghazi, because BO had tried to tell this great story, "Look what we did. We cleaned up Libya. We got rid of an evil guy, and we've made Libya part of the Arab Spring, a great outbreak of democracy. Look, aren't we wonderful." When instead what happened was we kicked him out of there and then left ourselves nobody to control what was happening in the aftermath, and Al-Qaeda has established a beachhead in Benghazi. Obama's running around saying that there is no more Al-Qaeda, until yesterday when he pulled it out of his speeches. He was saying there was no more Al-Qaeda. The CIA knew within 24 hours that it was a militant attack, that there was no video, there was no spontaneous demonstration. The State Department knew immediately. The White House knew. Obama started the ball rolling on the video to cover up an absolute disaster. Obama's raising the flag, "Look at me, look at me. The ringleader of the Benghazi attack is now doing media appearances in the Middle East. He' going on The Oprah shows of that region bragging about what he did. He's not hiding behind a mask or anything. The ringleader of the attack is doing media appearances, is doing television shows. The president's ideology has put a screen over his consciousness. And when the real world tries to intrude on it, it can't get through. Because after all: The War on Terror is over, Al-Qaeda's been defeated, the Arab Spring has brought democracy to Libya. And a terrorist attack that brutally kills four Americans is wildly inconsistent with that ideology and worldview. The president can't process reality, and his aides can't get through to him.</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350676056846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350676229314-22</Id><Topic><Title>T Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>haroldinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1350655753839</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:09:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, I just downloaded it and I might end up using this every day now...</Msg><Username>frozencustardking</Username><Timestamp>1350676229314</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:50:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350676566390-23</Id><Topic><Title>T taking beatings like a red-headed rung child.</Title><Username>drake.marsh17</Username><Timestamp>1350657653674</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:40:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Something is up and we will know soon!</Msg><Username>romanroman79</Username><Timestamp>1350676566390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:56:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350677664411-24</Id><Topic><Title>BO Libya coverup</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350676056846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Had this happened on Bush's watch he probably already would have some heads on poles. They may not have been the right ones, but the message would be perfectly clear to the killers.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1350677664411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350678110585-25</Id><Topic><Title>BO's war on women</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1350521702406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:55:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Despite all the rhetoric, federal records show that women who work in the Obama White House earn less than men -- about 18 percent less.</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1350678110585</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:21:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350679747199-26</Id><Topic><Title>BO's war on women</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1350521702406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:55:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone thinking the GOP isn't at war with women is suffering from Romnesia. New term just coined by the dems, I luv it, so appropriate.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1350679747199</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:49:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350680938895-27</Id><Topic><Title>BO's war on women</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1350521702406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:55:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Anyone thinking the GOP isn't at war with women is suffering from Romnesia” Need more proof. Just last night… “Republican Rep. Joe Walsh of Illinois told reporters Thursday night that there should be no abortion exception for the ‘life of the mother’ because ‘with modern technology and science, you can't find one instance’ in which a woman would actually die, according to a radio station. "There is no such exception as life of the mother, and as far as health of the mother, same thing, with advances in science and technology," Walsh said. Walsh's remarks echo Rep. Todd Akin (R-Mo.), who similarly relied on an ignorance of science and medicine to proclaim a belief that women's bodies are able to prevent pregnancy in cases of ‘legitimate rape.’ Walsh wouldn't have to go far to find a counter-example that undermines his medical theory. Rep. Jackie Speier (D-Calif.) has spoken movingly on the House floor about needing an emergency procedure to terminate a pregnancy that threatened her life. Ectopic pregnancies, or pregnancies that occur outside the uterus, are a life-threatening condition that occur in one in every 40 to one in every 100 pregnancies, according to the National Institutes of Health.” – Huff. Post UPDATE: 10:30 a.m. -- Planned Parenthood Action Fund released the following statement Friday from Executive Vice President Dawn Laguens in response to Walsh's statements: “Joe Walsh’s ignorance about women’s health is alarming. It is deeply troubling that he and some politicians have such a fundamental disregard for women and women’s health. As the advocate for Planned Parenthood health centers, we know that ending a pregnancy can often be a very complex, personal decision and that there are absolutely times that a woman’s life depends on it," the statement reads. “If Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan are elected, these ignorant statements will be more than words -- they would become law. Joe Walsh and the Tea Party Congress are ready to completely ban abortion, and Mitt Romney has said that he ‘would be delighted’ to sign an abortion ban into law. The Romney/Ryan ticket has promised that they would put women’s personal medical decisions in the hands of politicians like Joe Walsh and Todd Akin.” Hey, boys. Guess what? The women of this country don’t really give a sh#! what your good ol’ boys’ club wants to call it. Vietnam and Korea weren’t called wars either. Ladies, if you husband would willingly let you die were you in such a position, I believe voting accordingly would be in order (perhaps on your way to the divorce lawyer.)</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1350680938895</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:08:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350681879855-28</Id><Topic><Title>BO's war on women</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1350521702406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:55:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100% #$%$.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1350681879855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:24:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350682034383-29</Id><Topic><Title>BO's war on women</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1350521702406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:55:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most men had a single black book. Romney being a Morman had binders of women.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1350682034383</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:27:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350682034919-30</Id><Topic><Title>BO's war on women</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1350521702406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:55:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most men had a single black book. Romney being a Morman had binder of women.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1350682034919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:27:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350682360638-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obama will ban guns in his second term!!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1350575258049</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 11:47:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup you haters said the same thing BEFORE his FIRST term .</Msg><Username>tjm611</Username><Timestamp>1350682360638</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:32:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350683976927-32</Id><Topic><Title>BO's war on women</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1350521702406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:55:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Much ado about nothing. If this is what we have to worry about for the future of this country, we are indeed a nation of simple-minded imbeciles, including those of you that try to make a big deal out of this phrase and yet ignore Obama's failure with respect to immigration reform, the Benghazi incident, and his past relationships with known radicals and terrorists. You ignore the current economic mess and want to take issue with a simply phrase that did not mean what you all say it does. Guys like echo and the MSM have small minds with a large inability to recognize important issues that might have an impact on all of us.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1350683976927</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:59:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350684082170-33</Id><Topic><Title>BO's war on women</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1350521702406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:55:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The number of unemployed in this country has increased dramatically in the past three years, not just women...everyone.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1350684082170</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 18:01:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350685340164-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obama will ban guns in his second term!!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1350575258049</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 11:47:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you call us haters? Why do you hate babies? What do you want to kill them for? What have they done? More babies are killed every year through abortion than people are killed through gun violence, car accidents and wars combined. 42 million per year.</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1350685340164</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 18:22:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350685932728-35</Id><Topic><Title>Spammers</Title><Username>soupbone15</Username><Timestamp>1350586852492</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 15:00:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Use the Ignore User option on a post you object to. I've heard it deletes that person from showing up for you on the board.</Msg><Username>crazyhorse1786</Username><Timestamp>1350685932728</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 18:32:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350686772659-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obama will ban guns in his second term!!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1350575258049</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 11:47:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I hunt, I target shoot and I own 7 different kinds of guns, none of which are the automatic, assault weapon type." Very few individuals legally own automatic, assault type weapons. The back round check required for the federal registration is extensive.</Msg><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1350686772659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 18:46:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350688956224-37</Id><Topic><Title>Right wing radical terds, Romney made a fool out of himself in front of America at the debate</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1350573485363</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 11:18:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only feeble attempt is by faux news to try and cover up their boys huge red faced mistake at the debate. It is so pathetic a candidate for President gets his wrong facts right off faux news, never listens to the original statement, and then accuses someone without checking into it. That's no President.. The President's words were exactly what he said they were to the letter, that's all there is. I hope Romney gets another tongue lashing from Obama about offending American patriots in service to their country. Someone whose family fought for their country, Obama's, and someone whose family, Romney's, who sought all benefits but never served.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1350688956224</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 19:22:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350692347975-38</Id><Topic><Title>Obama will ban guns in his second term!!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1350575258049</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 11:47:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, he won't ban guns. The gun owners know how to stop these corrupt usurping commies.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1350692347975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 20:19:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350693849680-39</Id><Topic><Title>T taking beatings like a red-headed rung child.</Title><Username>drake.marsh17</Username><Timestamp>1350657653674</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:40:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is true, on other blogs, major news…</Msg><Username>v.roman61</Username><Timestamp>1350693849680</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350696303627-40</Id><Title>After Hours Quotes...</Title><Msg>... Fiery colors begin their yearly conquest of the hills, propelled by the autumn winds. Fall is the artist.” - Takayuki Ikkaku “The cosmos is all that is or ever was or ever will be.” – Carl Sagan, Cosmos, opening line “The business of America is not business. Neither is it war. The business of America is justice and securing the blessings of liberty.” – George Will "The vice presidential debate between Joe Biden and Paul Ryan went on tonight. It seemed like someone spiked Biden's ensure with a five-hour energy drink or something.” – Jimmy Kimmel “To doubt everything or to believe everything are two equally convenient solutions; both dispense with the necessity of reflection.” – Henri Poincaré “The whole aim of practical politics is to keep the populace alarmed (and hence clamorous to be led to safety) by menacing it with an endless series of hobgoblins, all of them imaginary.” – H. L. Mencken “Hatred is self-punishment” – Josea Ballou “Paul Ryan’s handling committee says he just has to do one thing. All he has to do is not look like a beady-eyed little weasel…Before the debate, Ryan said he'll stick to the facts. So, see, he's already lying…Paul Ryan looks like the guy who guards the keg at a frat party.” – Letterman/Kimmel “If you are part of a society that votes, then do so. There may be no candidates and no measures you want to vote for, but there are certain to be ones you want to vote against. In case of doubt, vote against. By this rule you will rarely go wrong. If this is too blind for your taste, consult some well-meaning fool (there is always one around) and ask his advice. Then vote the other way. This enables you to be a good citizen (if such is your wish) without spending the enormous amount of time on it that truly intelligent exercise of franchise requires.” – Robert A. Heinlein “Something in your voice tells me we approach the question of remuneration.” – Iain Banks “A new poll found that only 47 percent of voters find Mitt Romney to be trustworthy. Then Romney was like, 'Well, I hope it's not the same 47 percent I don't care about’!” – Jimmy Fallon “The world is round; it has no point.” – Adrienne E. Gusoff “Through hoarding, I have captured the market and own all of the erasers from golf course, scorecard pencils.” – anonymous “Doubt is not a pleasant condition, but certainty is absurd.” – Voltaire "Liberals were freaking out after Obama’s first debate and they were borderline suicidal, which is tough on them because when you lock yourself in the garage with the Prius running, nothing happens…Also, yesterday was National Coming Out Day, a day set aside for people to embrace and announce who they really are. Your move, Mitt Romney.” - Bill Maher “The boundaries which divide Life from Death are at best shadowy and vague. Who shall say where the one ends, and where the other begins?” – Edgar Allen Poe “Scrabble was invented by Nazis to #$%$ off kids with dyslexia. This is true, they proved this one.” – Eddie Izzard</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1350696303627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:25:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350696310822-41</Id><Title>AHQ (cont.)...</Title><Msg>... “Nothing is more admirable than the fortitude with which millionaires tolerate the disadvantages of their wealth.” – Rex Stout “Having placed in my mouth sufficient bread for three minutes' chewing, I withdrew my powers of sensual perception and retired into the privacy of my mind, my eyes and face assuming a vacant and preoccupied expression.” – Flan O’Brien “Brain; an apparatus with which we think we think.” – Ambrose Bierce "Chris Christie was in Ohio stumping for Mitt Romney. It was felt as far north as Canada." –David Letterman “If God had wanted to put everything into the universe from the beginning, He would have created a universe without change, without organisms and evolution, and without man and man's experience of change. But he seems to have thought that a live universe with events unexpected even by Himself would be more interesting than a dead one.” – Karl Popper “For my sister’s 40th birthday, I sent her a singing mammogram.” – Robert Schmidt “Opinions founded on prejudice are always sustained with the greatest of violence.” – Francis Jeffrey "One of President Obama's goals tonight is to win back female voters. Which explains why Obama is going to answer every question with a passage from 'Fifty Shades of Grey’.” - Conan O'Brien “When you're an addict, you can go without feeling anything except drunk or stoned or hungry. Still, when you compare this to other feelings, to sadness, anger, fear, worry, despair, and depression, well, an addiction no longer looks so bad. It looks like a very viable option.” – Chuck Palahniuk “Humankind cannot stand very much reality.” - T. S. Eliot “To be conscious that you are ignorant is a great step to knowledge.” – Disraeli "Ross Perot has endorsed Mitt Romney. This could help Romney get the vote of people you forgot were still alive." - Conan O'Brien “I was walking down the street the other day when this guy asked if I wanted a frozen banana...I said 'no' but then thought I might want a regular banana later, so...yeah.” – Mitch Hedberg “The World is divided into armed camps ready to commit genocide just because we can't agree on whose fairy tales to believe. In the end, Religion will kill us all.” – Ed Krebs “The question of whether Machines Can Think... is about as relevant as the question of whether Submarines Can Swim.” – Edsger Dijkstra "A CNN poll today said that 46 percent of viewers who watched thought Obama won and 39 percent thought Mitt Romney won. So, it looks like Obama’s strategy of staying awake through this one paid off.” – Jimmy Kimmel “Too many people want to have written,” – Terry Pratchett</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1350696310822</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:25:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350696317921-42</Id><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Msg>... “The price of freedom of religion or of speech or of the press is that we must put up with, and even pay for, a good deal of rubbish.” – Robert H. Jackson “The Venus de Milo is a good example of what happens to somebody who won't stop biting her fingernails.” – Will Rogers “When the fox preaches, look to the geese.” – German Proverb “Mitt Romney once again tried to distance himself from his infamous 47 percent comments, saying, 'the words that came out were not what I meant.' And if that sounds like a good excuse to you, try it on your girlfriend." - Seth Meyers “I have been commissioned to write an autobiography and I would be grateful to any of your readers who could tell me what I was doing between 1960 and 1974.” – Jeffrey Bernard “The aim of argument, or of discussion, should not be victory, but progress.” – Joseph Joubert “Character consists of what you do on the third and fourth tries.” – James A. Michener “On the subject of equal pay for women, Romney said that when he was filing cabinet positions as governor of Massachusetts, he went out of his way to make sure he hired women. He said he had 'binders full of women, which is a little creepy. Binders full of women is something they'd find in a serial killer's basement at the end of Law &amp; Order…Maybe for Mitt Romney that's the closets he's ever gotten to looking at a dirty magazine." - Jimmy Kimmel “Posterity is just around the corner.” – George S. Kaufman “When you say 'Bedtime, bedtime, bedtime!' that's not what the child hears. What the child hears is 'Lie down in the dark... for hours... and don't move... I'm locking the door now’.” – Dylan Moran “As many colors of the rainbow are an outcome of one pure light, the many religions of the world are an expression of one divine source.” – Jaggi Vasudev "The time for fact checking is after the event when voters have stopped watching. We should not be sullying their emotional reactions with accuracy." – Stephen Colbert, on Candy Crowley fact-checking Mitt Romney during the presidential debate. “To appreciate nonsense requires a serious interest in life,” – Gelett Burgess “Drink no longer water, but use a little wine for thy stomach's sake.” – The Bible, 1 Timothy 5:23 “Two in every one people in this country are schizophrenic.” – anonymous "Couple of things: One, the women’s group was called MassGAP and they approached Governor Romney, not the other way around. And two, my guess is they did not refer to what they presented as a binder full of women, but perhaps as an organized collection of qualified resumes. But hey, Binder of Women, Book of Broads, whatever.” – Jon Stewart “We want the finest wines available to humanity, we want them here, and we want them now!" – Withnail “Have a good weekend, all.” – echo2165 “One of the questions whose answers we seek is why we seek.” – Gene Wolfe</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1350696317921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:25:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350701658092-43</Id><Topic><Title>Weapons Ban in the US .. By U.N. (thru Obama's back door deal)</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1350699340119</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 22:15:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what you say is true.I have been following this for sometime.The UN also wants to charge a tax for inernet use.</Msg><Username>ls3487</Username><Timestamp>1350701658092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 22:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>