<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-31"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351660870646-1</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for "O"</Title><Username>bullbear308</Username><Timestamp>1351628963340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey LARDQUAKE, I'll make you a deal. When the President is re-elected, and he will be, I'll buy you two seats to SF on the airline of your choice so you have room for your ponderous pimpled #$%$ and, as long as you have gotten energetically to your "nooks and crannies" in the shower that morning and don't open your mouth to speak, won't cause anyone near you excessive discomfort. I'll meet you at the airport and spit once hard right smack in your dimwitted, bulging piggy eyes. I'll let you have my car and driver for the rest of the weekend and pay for the hotel of your choice. Deal?</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351660870646</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351685707788-2</Id><Topic><Title>The Canned Food Is On It's Way, New Jersey</Title><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1351631670260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:14:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What a laugh. Romney is collecting canned food" Perhaps you missed Romney this weekend ask well wishers to make cash contributions to the Red Cross consistent with its first choice for helping. This was before the storm had even slammed into the East Coast. If indeed you missed it, I've now shared the whole story with you.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1351685707788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 08:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351685817303-3</Id><Topic><Title>Big Bird, Binders, &amp;Bu!!</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351641072966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:51:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama will save Big Bird while Romney saves the Eagle.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1351685817303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 08:16:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351688593105-4</Id><Title>NYSE Traders Will Experience Spotty Cell Phone, Wireless Internet Service</Title><Msg>But the real problem is right now there is no Verizon service or wifi in the exchange. http://finance.yahoo.com/news/traders-nyse-no-internet-bloomberg-121910728.html</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1351688593105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:03:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351690808666-5</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok, list the points then. You are being just as Vague as Willard. It is becoming easier to remember his real name due to his lack of truth telling. Was Willard the truth telling Disney Character?</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351690808666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:40:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351691620606-6</Id><Topic><Title>The Canned Food Is On It's Way, New Jersey</Title><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1351631670260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:14:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See u are the same embarssment to they party u were b4</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351691620606</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:53:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351691750577-7</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for "O"</Title><Username>bullbear308</Username><Timestamp>1351628963340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All #$%$. who is paying u to spred these lies, and misreps? your boy willard is on the ropes, and his lies r getting more and more evident. the informed voter knows.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351691750577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:55:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351691891426-8</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for "O"</Title><Username>bullbear308</Username><Timestamp>1351628963340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on, but why would you even want to met the character? he and willard are out looking for carrots to send soup the the jersey shore. the rats that they are.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351691891426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:58:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351692012596-9</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for "O"</Title><Username>bullbear308</Username><Timestamp>1351628963340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on brother. none of the romneys served their country, except for a political photo opt.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351692012596</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:00:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351692227715-10</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for "O"</Title><Username>bullbear308</Username><Timestamp>1351628963340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More good one's not to vote for willard mitt, draft doggin, liar, rat romney.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351692227715</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:03:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351694833486-11</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for "O"</Title><Username>bullbear308</Username><Timestamp>1351628963340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I already voted for Obama/Biden and every Democrat and Democrat supported issue, done.. To reiterate: I must give credit to Christie for PRAISING OBAMA'S GOOD WORK, it was great. Live on TV, there's no denying it, no denying, it's great. Worse he chastised romeny for wanting to make a photo op out of new jersey and Christie let romney's camp have it on that side to. It's so great.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351694833486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:47:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351694968884-12</Id><Title>TIME TO PUT BACK-UP POWER &amp;</Title><Msg>Communications equipment in a better location. i am a retired communications worker, and we were usually given a hot lower level location for our equipment. it happen in japan, and it happened on our east coast. water and electricity does not mix.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351694968884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:49:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351695102692-13</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “…due to all of the ‘thumps (sic) down from liberal's responses” – jon I think your boiler room cubicle manager is about to give you a rating of a thump upside the head for being such an incompetent boob.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351695102692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:51:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351695231246-14</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for "O"</Title><Username>bullbear308</Username><Timestamp>1351628963340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Derivative. Boring.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351695231246</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351695288733-15</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for "O"</Title><Username>bullbear308</Username><Timestamp>1351628963340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only to spit in its eye. Why else would anybody want to meet it?</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351695288733</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:54:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351695292745-16</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Doomberg should Step Down</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351639429508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i BELIEVE YOU R THE PAID POSTER R U NOT? Some posted you were a paid word person. IF YOU R HAVE U MADE ENOUGH TO MOVE OUT OF YOUR PARENTS BASEMENT YET?</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351695292745</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:54:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351695730051-17</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's put it this way. Where is Romney'.s moral compass. It is spinning, as he is speeding up his lies. I voted Obama the other day, and my ballot had a write in position. Dog Catcher. I wrote the Willard in, then I later remembered is hatred towards dogs, and felt very bad. Hope he is not elected to either position.</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351695730051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:02:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351696475912-18</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, there it is in a nutshell. LARDQUAKE thinks he is funny or so blindingly clever people believe him. This is what comes from being isolated, uneducated, illiterate and full of yourself. You are not funny or even mildly amusing, nor does anybody believe what you have to say. Intellectually, you are a festering dungheap and symptomatic of the dumbing down rot that eats at the heart of the country. Take some classes and learn how to write and think. You are an idiot!</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351696475912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:14:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351696489804-19</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What Romney believes! 1 Reducing taxes and regulations will create jobs. This was the policy under Bush that took our country from a budget surplus to a budget deficit and failed to sustain a vital growing economy. Not true. The economy was good until 2007 when the house and senate was controlled by the Democrats. Bill Clinton stated in 1999 that everyone should be able to buy a house and deregulated financing for the housing market. 2. Only those individuals currently covered by medical insurance should be covered for pre-existing conditions. Obama care is a disaster waiting to happen. The Country is broke!! There are 17 new taxes that the middle class will have to pay. Pre-existing conditions will be taken care of by the Romney administration. 3. Competition between the insurance companies will reduce medical costs. Isn’t this what we have today for everyone under the age of 65? Have you premiums gone up and health care improved? The doctors will not accept Medicare because Obama took 716 billion out of medicare to pay for Obama care, so payments to doctors will be less. 65% of doctors are against Obama care. 10 million people will be added and not 1 new doctor will be added to take care of these people. Be prepared for long waiting at the doctors office. 4. The current Social Security system should be changed to allow individuals to invest their retirement funds in the stock market in hopes of getting a higher return. How much money would you have lost if you had sold the stocks in your retirement fund at the bottom of the recession? Not true. The current Social Security system is going broke and needs to be fixed. Romney will fix that 5.You believe that higher income earners (those in the top 10%) should pay taxes at lower rate than Warren Buffet’s secretary or the average wage earner. Warren Buffet’s secretary pays income tax. Warren Buffet pays capital gains tax which is the lower tax bracket 6. Taxes and regulations, not the lack of demand, were the major cause of the recession. The collapse of the housing market caused the recession. That recession was over in June of 2009, 6 months after Obama took office. 7. That the banking and financial industry does not need to be regulated. What do you think caused the housing industry to collapse and the banks to need financial aid from the government to survive? Barney Frank and Chris Dodd were in charge of Banking and Financing industries both Democrats they allowed things to get out of control Bush gets the blame because he was President. 8. Women should be paid less than men for the same job. There is no way of figuring that out. Romney is for equal pay. 9. That the United States should increase its military spending even though the U.S. already spends more on defense than the next 13 countries with the highest defense budgets. We need a strong defense. Obama is weakening our military that is not acceptable 10 That companies are people and should be allowed to make unlimited political contributions without disclosure. They are both doing that. Obama goes one step further, he is getting illegal contributions from over seas. Socialism does not work. I want a free society. My vote goes to Romney</Msg><Username>ls3487</Username><Timestamp>1351696489804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:14:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351697926361-20</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>after fake food drive did rommie give the can goods to his staff.?</Msg><Username>orri1934</Username><Timestamp>1351697926361</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:38:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351697955099-21</Id><Title>T Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Msg>See all T charts - all on one screen - for free. I use this free standalone lightweight tool (does not install anything on your web browser or computer - this is not an annoying browser toolbar nor an add-in). It is called Yahoo Finance 7 Ways and lets me see all charts (e.g. 1 day, 5 days, 1 month, 3 months, etc.) on the same page for any given security. Do a web search for the website RSTNL and download it from the Downloads section of that website. You can also go to the website CNET, do a search for Yahoo Finance 7 Ways in the downloads section, and download it from there.</Msg><Username>royinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1351697955099</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:39:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351698224346-22</Id><Topic><Title>The Canned Food Is On It's Way, New Jersey</Title><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1351631670260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:14:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't the president once 'miscalculate' the total number of STATES in our Union??? You sound as bright as your ignorant user name.</Msg><Username>dave_martin_2244</Username><Timestamp>1351698224346</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:43:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351699296725-23</Id><Topic><Title>The Canned Food Is On It's Way, New Jersey</Title><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1351631670260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:14:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, he said he had been in 57 states. Furthermore, he said he had one left to go. Perhaps his teleprompter hicccupped. Mainstream media covering his tail said he must have been tired.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1351699296725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:01:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351699539390-24</Id><Topic><Title>The Canned Food Is On It's Way, New Jersey</Title><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1351631670260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:14:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't the president once 'miscalculate' the total number of STATES in our Union" no, he didn't miscalculate, there is nothing to calculate. Unless people like your group need calculators to count to 50. since he is from state # 50 I bet he knows by now there aren't 51. pretty sure they taught him that at the Senate. It is insulting your intelligence, what little there is of it, not his..</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351699539390</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:05:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351699867516-25</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO PUT BACK-UP POWER &amp;</Title><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351694968884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:49:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I worked for PT&amp;T in the San Diego area. None of our offices were located so as to be damaged by flooding. All were susceptible to earthquake though. They went through the older buildings in the 60's and added reinforcing steel. After the big fire in a C.O. in New york they also went through and made sure all conduits were sealed and added other fire protection measures. The primary cause of natural outages was from fires in the back country. Contractors that didn't call the cable locater would often dig up an underground conduit run.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351699867516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:11:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351699947472-26</Id><Topic><Title>The Canned Food Is On It's Way, New Jersey</Title><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1351631670260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:14:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Overlooked your final sentence. Needs to be rewritten to read: Romney NEEDS to be president...not a community organizer pretending to be a leader. With that, you are officially terminated to the spammers and other jerks via ignore.</Msg><Username>dave_martin_2244</Username><Timestamp>1351699947472</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:12:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351700241547-27</Id><Topic><Title>"A coward dies a thousand times before his death, but the valiant taste of death but once."</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1351531591967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama served when????. Never met a Veteran that fought for socialism. Never saw a President that used the word I more then Obama. Never saw a President that blamed other people for his mistakes. If Romney win's will he get to blame Obama for the economy or Bush.</Msg><Username>waynesue</Username><Timestamp>1351700241547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351702923005-28</Id><Topic><Title>The Canned Food Is On It's Way, New Jersey</Title><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1351631670260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:14:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mittens gave $2 to red cross.</Msg><Username>orri1934</Username><Timestamp>1351702923005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:02:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351703247055-29</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So if you have become democrat then you should be stating: I am too stupid to choose what size fountain drink I should buy. Therefore, I will let Mayor Bloomberg choose for me. I am on welfare and it is my right to get tattoos with welfare money I receive... Gov. of MA I will choose not to give permits to a business that I disagree with instead of letting the market dictate if that business survives or fails. BTW - I am not a Republican and most definitely not a Democrat, but if you cannot see the fear mongering, lying, and hypocrite nature of the Democratic party then I doubt you were ever a Republican.</Msg><Username>jk8369</Username><Timestamp>1351703247055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:07:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351705353656-30</Id><Topic><Title>The Canned Food Is On It's Way, New Jersey</Title><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1351631670260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:14:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now you know why his grades are sealed.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1351705353656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:42:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351708493992-31</Id><Title>Ready to die and the market has nothen to do with it.</Title><Msg>Happy Halloween</Msg><Username>stodsall</Username><Timestamp>1351708493992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:34:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351709624100-32</Id><Title>Sorry Shorty</Title><Msg>It has been confirmed today that you have lost the battle. You better start covering, or don't; I just LOVE to see you clowns get your heads beat in, LOL!</Msg><Username>shipleyinsuranceservices</Username><Timestamp>1351709624100</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:53:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351710688621-33</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “Last Census .. they made 2 personal visits .. a field worker, then a supervisor .. (looking for illegals - chuckles)” – jon, he of tall tales The US Census Bureau has nothing whatsoever to do with U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE), which is the investigative arm of The Dept. of Homeland Security (DHS). Are you certain they weren’t from The SPCA investigating your relationship with your dog? “My "mailed in" census form = 1 home &amp; 1 person .. their drive by (seeing the Garage &amp; 4 vehicles) threw ‘red flags’ - so funny.” Yeah, a real knee-slapper, jon. You mailed in your census form, then they drove by and viewed your four vehicles – a 50 c.c. moped with training wheels, your “parts” vehicle, the 1970 Gremlin on cinderblocks next to the outhouse, your rusted out, but only working vehicle – your main ride – a 1985 Yugo GV, with 319,000 miles, complete with dashboard hula girl and an 8-track sound system, aptly named because sometimes Yugo and sometimes you don’t, and last but not least, the Zamboni machine you bought off E-Bay, thinking you could resurface the ice on your pond in July. Wow, jon, four vehicles for just you…we are all duly impressed. You forgot about your motorized skate board and The Scooter you won in a poker game from your 93 year old deaf and blind, invalid neighbor. “me &amp; puppy are really excited ...(chuckles)” My, you ARE excited…we see you humping the dog’s leg. Now that’s a touching tale of a profound bond between a lad and his dog – man’s best friend…and in jon’s case, his ONLY friend. You know, jon, in Old Yeller, they shot the dog in the end. (of the movie, not the dog…they shot him in the head, because tail wounds are seldom mortal.) “I should have hi-lited (SIC) it” – The word is highlight, jon. “…your (SIC) a smart guy…” You’re obviously not!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1351710688621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:11:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351712380061-34</Id><Topic><Title>T Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>royinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1351697955099</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well this is not a mind blowing app, but it is useful and I like it - thanks for the tip.</Msg><Username>itsacalabreeze</Username><Timestamp>1351712380061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:39:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351714264193-35</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Warren Buffet’s secretary pays income tax. Warren Buffet pays capital gains tax which is the lower tax bracket" It's all income tax, and all the other responses you had were equally wrong. If this is an example of right wing thinking, no wonder they fall for con man romney.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351714264193</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:11:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351716964970-36</Id><Title>penson fund needs money?</Title><Msg>att sending letter out about penson fund under funded ? any body get this letter.?</Msg><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1351716964970</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:56:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351717501422-37</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fake yes, now it comes out thousands of dollars were spent to make the Event look larger than it was. Not for Political reasons however, Willard had called off all Political Events right?</Msg><Username>minnflier</Username><Timestamp>1351717501422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:05:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351720267031-38</Id><Topic><Title>Why I can't vote for Romney</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351626646266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just vote Communist and get it over with. You'll feel better.</Msg><Username>crazyhorse1786</Username><Timestamp>1351720267031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:51:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351725232607-39</Id><Topic><Title>The Canned Food Is On It's Way, New Jersey</Title><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1351631670260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:14:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You stupid #$%$ Israel has been pushing to name Jerusalem as its capitol for over 50 years and Romney supports it and the canned goods are going to wherever they're most needed.</Msg><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1351725232607</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:13:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351725853531-40</Id><Topic><Title>Va. Election VOTES Will Not Be Released Till Fri.</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1351724256139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:57:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH my. WHAT will "we" ever "do" (!!) WITHOUT imediatte "knews" (??) from Vaginny...peePEE...POOpoo (!!) and "your" there magic "UNDERPANTS (teehee)...whoopee grins cushion...FRIED "food"...and "Bowl" MOVEMENT (!!) You are a pathetic, illiterate idiot.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351725853531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:24:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351727081972-41</Id><Topic><Title>Va. Election VOTES Will Not Be Released Till Fri.</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1351724256139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:57:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Your" figuring out how to change your aliases faster LARDCAKES (!!) Did you get the "FAT FIGNERS" keyboard at WALMART "today" ...?? (grins)</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351727081972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351727484505-42</Id><Topic><Title>Va. Election VOTES Will Not Be Released Till Fri.</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1351724256139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:57:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can "YOU" tell (??) (grins)</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351727484505</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:51:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351727616265-43</Id><Topic><Title>Va. Election VOTES Will Not Be Released Till Fri.</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1351724256139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:57:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PORE "puppy". "Please" send me your address in ADVANCE...of my "Trip" (!!) and SEW "I" can call your local SPCA (teehee). YOu are an IDito.</Msg><Username>yourenohelp</Username><Timestamp>1351727616265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:53:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351732107030-44</Id><Title>Obama goes to Church?</Title><Msg>This guy claims to be a Christian, but hardly ever attends Church. Unless, of course he's close to an election. If he believes in God, way does he wear a ring that say Allah is the the only true God.? Could he be thanking Allah for the hurricane, that wiped out the One Percenter's property. Anything to get Bengazi out of the headlines. His latest reason to duck the Ambassador's rape and murder involves the FBI. He doesn't want to say, or do anything that would interfere with their investigation. When will they release the autopsy reports on the four Americans? This global warming issue may yet get him over the line. Problem is, no one with half a brain is buying it. New Jersey had a hurricane like this back in the 1800's. Way before coal fired plants burned their first lump of coal.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351732107030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351733423065-45</Id><Topic><Title>Philadelphia Freedom</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351638957297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today, my family (wife &amp; kids), and I participated in early voting, here in the People's Republic. The lines were out the door, and snaked around the building. The previous, 1st day of early voting, the lines were even longer. I asked several people what made them turn out. One guy's son was a Custom's Agent. He was feed up with illegal immigration. A couple other had Police in their families, and were tired of all the crime. None appeared to be Barry's supporters. I think that toe sucking guy, former Clinton brain, Dick Morris is right. I'm sensing A Mitt landslide. In the Hood however (where I work), early voting is way down, No lines seen. Some estimates show down 70%. We still could loose though. I understand that a Company in Spain, (headed by George Soros), makes most of the voting machines. We should get a receipt to show how we voted. Just in case there is a recount. Someone remarked yes, like those hanging chads in Florida. I joked, I saw a guy in line with a shirt supporting gay marriage. I believe he was nicknamed Hanging Chad.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351733423065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:30:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351733644254-46</Id><Topic><Title>Teachers Should Go For Mitt</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351644405039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most Teachers my wife work with, say they probably won't vote. Most are disillusioned with all that Hopey Change that Barrack promised.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351733644254</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:34:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351734460081-47</Id><Topic><Title>The Canned Food Is On It's Way, New Jersey</Title><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1351631670260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:14:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interestingly, Obummer was denied, asked not to come to New York by Doomberg. Also, Cumo does want to be seen next to Obami. So, I guess the Big Guy Christie won by default. Next to Christie, you see how weak, and skinny this President is. He looks like that guy that used to get sand kicked in his face by the bigger guys. Barry's glad to be anywhere, but at the WhiteHouse. There, someone might ask him a serious question, on Bengazi, or something.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351734460081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:47:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351734779687-48</Id><Topic><Title>penson fund needs money?</Title><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1351716964970</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:56:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This isn't good. Sounds like lump sums are gone. Obama, and the Unions, are supposed to be looking out for the working man. Verizon East (the Union side) got to keep their pensions, though Management has had theirs frozen for years. Please fill us in, if anyone has more info.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351734779687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:52:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351735287509-49</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Doomberg should Step Down</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351639429508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have a Mayor here in Baltimore. Her name is Rawlings Blake. She is as dumb as a box of rocks. She is an O'Malley clone. She doesn't lie anywhere as well as O'Malley though. I hope she get's caught soon. A six-grader could unravel her coverups. She recently got caught in a phone contract scandal. Millions for phones that can't make any calls.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351735287509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 22:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351735494634-50</Id><Topic><Title>Obama goes to Church?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351732107030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Answer me this. If there was anything to global warming, climate change, or hocus pocus. Why did Owl Gore just build a fab place on the beach? Wouldn't he be worried about rising tides?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351735494634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 22:04:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351737050352-51</Id><Title>Gawdawful!</Title><Msg>Just gawdawful. Zilch about AT&amp;T, just spammers and political hucksters on the board now. Everybody's left the house except these spoiler guys talking to themselves. Yahoo is sunk!</Msg><Username>timetraveler2u</Username><Timestamp>1351737050352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 22:30:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351737409355-52</Id><Topic><Title>Obama goes to Church?</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351732107030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are just too hard to believe. I hope you sleep well.</Msg><Username>rcub5d</Username><Timestamp>1351737409355</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 22:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351737743165-53</Id><Topic><Title>Philadelphia Freedom</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1351638957297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This fool shows his true drunk self just in time for all to consider all he has said. As they say, Just sayin'.</Msg><Username>rcub5d</Username><Timestamp>1351737743165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 22:42:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>