<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355914471019-1</Id><Title>Should Chicago be the model for federal gun control laws?</Title><Msg>Currently Illinois does not issue concealed carry licenses, nor does it recognize CCL's from other states. Open carry is also illegal, except when hunting. A firearm can only be transported if it is unloaded and locked in a case. The city of Chicago requires that all firearms be registered with the local police department. Based upon these laws and others, the state of Illinois and the city of Chicago should be one of the safest locations in the country as far as firearms and the problems that they present are concerned. I have listened to our president and members of his party talk about the evils of guns and those who choose to own guns are, and have come to agree with them. Guns are evil and the people that own them are also evil. Further if we could only confiscate all of the guns from those evil law abiding citizens, then there would be no murders in our country ever again, because our entire country would become a firearm free zone, and everyone knows how safe firearm free zones like schools, churches, post offices, and movie theaters have become. Again the president is correct take all of the guns away from those evil law abiding citizens, because then and only then will the people of this country be safe. In the case of Chicago only 400 homicides had been recorded for the first nine months of 2012, and I am sure that since Chicago is a virtual gun free zone none of those homicides were caused by guns. In your heart you know he is right, The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1355914471019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 05:54:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355915149311-2</Id><Topic><Title>Should Chicago be the model for federal gun control laws?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1355914471019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 05:54:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The sad thing is that your sarcasm will be go undetected by many of this board!</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1355915149311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 06:05:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355923569650-3</Id><Topic><Title>Conn Shooter's Mom, tried to commit him</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1355881449505</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:44:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's hard to believe his Mom had all those guns in the house" How many people have you known who were bright but had almost zero common sense? Perhaps we should legislate common sense.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1355923569650</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 08:26:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355925623261-4</Id><Topic><Title>Wack job, jon...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355782175162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 17:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “When called out, and asked to take his views to Newton to see how the grieving parents and families would react to his malignant and insidious suggestion, he (jon) reacts in his typical fashion – “dance til your balls fall off” and tales of “man-bras” - all very mature responses to a legitimate question of his boorish insensitivity.” That was yesterday – In his intellectual debate style of ignoring the issue at hand, he counters with another round of school yard taunts equivalent to “so’s your mother!”, although nowhere near that sophisticated. His responses, all seemingly steeped in bathroom bodily function obsession, indicated that he suffers from various paraphilia, likely brought on by childhood abuse. Hence, rather than either denying or acknowledging that he said the authorities in Newton were manipulating evidence for political purpose, his retort was as follows: “Your Flatulency” - “Chit For Brains” - “change your depends" - "hershey squirts" – “EAT MY SHORTS” - “grand orifice” I rest my case. “I'm not hiding .. just let me know when you get near Richmond and I'll work out the arrangements to accomimodate (SIC????) you .... ya disgusting LITTLE pigmy pus-bag - SMILES !! Oh, MY, jon! You are one disturbed individual. Okay, jon, give me your address. Wear your digital cammies you got in the 60’s (again, no response) and bring your entire macho gun show collection (in all likelihood, a pellet gun and a Whamo slingshot) I’ll bring an unabridged dictionary. BTW, how is it you’re here everyday? I thought you mowed yards or had a paper route or somethin’. Plus, I thought you lived in Charlottesville. What happened? I guess with all these websites out there now identifying predators, you have to move around a lot. Try Connecticut. There are people up there waiting for you to come tell them how their losses were just a conspiracy for an attack on the 2nd Amendment.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355925623261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 09:00:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355926795036-5</Id><Title>Downgrade</Title><Msg>AT&amp;T Inc Cut to Sector Underperform From Sector Perform by Scotia T Last update: 12/19/2012 9:05:15 AM (END) Dow Jones Newswires (212-416-2800) December 19, 2012 09:05 ET (14:05 GMT)</Msg><Username>razzledazzle5050</Username><Timestamp>1355926795036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 09:19:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355926883668-6</Id><Topic><Title>Wack job, jon...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355782175162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 17:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"thinking "modern weaponry" is even known by the States is wishful, at best." You don't think Bush flying planes around Texas gave him any military chops? Our ability to rebel against an overreaching Federal government lies in the states, which have at least nominal control over their National Guard units, and in local law enforcement--just ask the Lubbuck,Texas sheriffs who are preparing for Obama's UN invasion. Leaving this power with Rick Perry et. al. is worrisome enough. Giving it to Win, Lav &amp; Jon? Nuts!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355926883668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 09:21:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355927958806-7</Id><Topic><Title>Should Chicago be the model for federal gun control laws?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1355914471019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 05:54:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just another version of "we need to arm the elementary school teachers." I went to college in a state that outlawed a type of alcohol called Everclear, but I sure did drink alot of it in those days. Everclear was legal the next state over, and thus was easy to get. It should tell you something that Mexican drug cartels come to the US to legally purchase weapons and then smuggle them over the border. Froggie is simply making the case for a Federal ban, since local or state bans don't work. But I imagine that will go undetected by many on this board.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355927958806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 09:39:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355928262108-8</Id><Topic><Title>Wack job, jon...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355782175162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 17:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... I don’t disagree with you in the slightest. I was merely pointing out, that, IMO, the truly “modern weaponry” is not something that you or I or the public even knows about. And that isn’t at the state level. I believe we have weapons that can assure that we will never lose an “all-out” war (beyond nukes), although that doesn’t bode well for mankind. On the other hand, Rick Perry or jon or any like-minded individual, cannot, at this point at least, take out Washington with a space-based laser, was my point. On the other hand, if jon was leading a secessionist effort from Richmond, I would think the Jefferson Davis Monument could be vaporized at a moment’s notice as a warning, if so desired. (Kinda’ like “The Day the Earth Stood Still” - "Klaatu barada nikto") Seriously, I don’t think our capabilities are really known by many, least of all, the local National Guard.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355928262108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 09:44:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355928920355-9</Id><Title>upgrade!!</Title><Msg>At t upgraded by tdw investments gooo t hit 35 again hahahahewhheh</Msg><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1355928920355</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 09:55:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355929109187-10</Id><Topic><Title>T is one of top picks like crimson on apex</Title><Username>ethelvillarreal43</Username><Timestamp>1353943269318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:21:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice report</Msg><Username>rayboston342</Username><Timestamp>1355929109187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 09:58:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355929397932-11</Id><Topic><Title>Should Chicago be the model for federal gun control laws?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1355914471019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 05:54:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “I went to college in a state that outlawed a type of alcohol called Everclear” I went to college in a state that didn’t! Ah, yes, Everclear, he said with fond memories. The brand name of Grain Alcohol available at two different potencies – 151 proof (for rookies) or (the only one used) 190 Proof – 95% pure alcohol. The main ingredient in “Creepers”, a college recipe handed down through the ages and mixed in metal Garbage Cans for college parties. Ten quarts per garbage can, Two parts -Grapefruit juice, two parts – oh, wait I’m sworn to secrecy about the recipe. “Creepers”, So named, because with little taste or aroma, the coeds loved them, but halfway through your first one, they crept up on you. If you couldn’t get lucky with Creepers, you had to be jon.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355929397932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 10:03:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355929666280-12</Id><Topic><Title>Wack job, jon...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355782175162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 17:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the truly “modern weaponry” is not something that you or I or the public even knows about" Ahh. . . You mean post-modern weaponry. Weaponry that deconstructs the cultural metanarrative by revealing the temporary and shifting nature of our relationship to its symbols. As in your example of vaporizing the Jefferson Davis Memorial. I'll give you that. There are few postmodernists in the National Guard. :) Yet small arms and IEDs seem to do a good enough job in a pinch.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355929666280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 10:07:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355930017982-13</Id><Topic><Title>Should Chicago be the model for federal gun control laws?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1355914471019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 05:54:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bet you haven't heard that most of the guns used by the drug cartels come from Mexican cops and military. I've read that one whole squad of army men deserted with their weapons and joined one of the cartels. As closely watched as our weapons were in basic we had 2 M-1 rifles go missing. If I want a weapon I can always get one. The worst school killing on record happened back in the 20's I believe. It was with an explosive. Yeah, they had loony bins back then too.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1355930017982</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 10:13:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355930401855-14</Id><Topic><Title>Wack job, jon...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355782175162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 17:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There were many inaccuracies in the early reports. One was that the .223 cal. weapon was found in the car. Believe it was you that took me to task for repeating what the "Ministry Of Truth " said. Knowing how capable many of the pols and appointed law officials are of lying it is still possible that all he used were the pistols. Horrible enough even so. I've seen the press tell too many lies to facilitate an agenda or castigate someone trying to expose corruption to trust very much of what they say</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1355930401855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 10:20:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355930743304-15</Id><Topic><Title>Should Chicago be the model for federal gun control laws?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1355914471019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 05:54:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"that most of the guns used by the drug cartels come from Mexican cops and military" Yes, I am aware. Yet they still find it useful to purchase guns in the US in rather large quantities.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355930743304</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 10:25:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355932218517-16</Id><Topic><Title>Should Chicago be the model for federal gun control laws?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1355914471019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 05:54:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ricky, Chicago is breaking their record for homicides this year! That is where his sarcasm originated! BTW, the homicides were not from bad language.</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1355932218517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 10:50:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355932368711-17</Id><Topic><Title>Should Chicago be the model for federal gun control laws?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1355914471019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 05:54:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Add a little grape juice for color and you had 'Purple Jesus'! Used in the USAF and also made in garbage cans!</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1355932368711</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 10:52:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355933638545-18</Id><Topic><Title>Should Chicago be the model for federal gun control laws?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1355914471019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 05:54:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"BTW, the homicides were not from bad language." Now don't you wish that was the only weapon they had available?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355933638545</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 11:13:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355936000893-19</Id><Title>Where is the best place to buy Ammo?</Title><Msg>Finding it online at a pretty good price, Wal-mart has competitive prices. Social Security bought many thousands of hollow points in August maybe they could sell off some of their surplus at a discount. Bought some new guns for Christmas but ammo is expensive any suggestions?</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1355936000893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 11:53:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355936050021-20</Id><Topic><Title>Should Chicago be the model for federal gun control laws?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1355914471019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 05:54:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I still have a scar from an ill-advised flaming shot of Everclear. It's the only time I've ever been on fire.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355936050021</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 11:54:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355936607482-21</Id><Title>Buy (ALU) today! Everyone on Wall Street is!</Title><Msg>Alcatel-Lucent, S.A. (ALU) -NYSE Massive blocks of stock are being bought today on this company! Here are the reasons why! Stock breaking new daily highs! Upgraded to Buy and Outperform! Lands 2.1 Billion Dollar Deal! Alcatel-Lucent Wins Contract With Telefonica Alcatel-Lucent, S.A. (ALU) -NYSE</Msg><Username>immglobal2012</Username><Timestamp>1355936607482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 12:03:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355936690467-22</Id><Topic><Title>Buy (ALU) today! Everyone on Wall Street is!</Title><Username>immglobal2012</Username><Timestamp>1355936607482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 12:03:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice call ALU! I sold CLWR and bought ALU, stock is super strong today! Check out ALU.</Msg><Username>albertiandoli</Username><Timestamp>1355936690467</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 12:04:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355938050740-23</Id><Topic><Title>Wack job, jon...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355782175162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 17:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Marjorie and Robert. Look at what they have to live with. How are they liking Arizona?</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355938050740</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 12:27:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355940610073-24</Id><Topic><Title>Should Chicago be the model for federal gun control laws?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1355914471019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 05:54:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your crime numbers is pure #$%$ in Ill. Crime rate is soaring there and only criminals have guns. If someone is busting your door open you won't even have time to call 911. In Ks. bang! criminal with weapon is gone! read the facts stupid!</Msg><Username>romannorga</Username><Timestamp>1355940610073</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 13:10:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355940689917-25</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the best place to buy Ammo?</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1355936000893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 11:53:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SGA Ammo in Ok.</Msg><Username>romannorga</Username><Timestamp>1355940689917</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 13:11:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355940749188-26</Id><Topic><Title>Conn Shooter's Mom, tried to commit him</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1355881449505</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:44:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just the other day, in China a 36 year old man, (who had a psycological illness), sliced, and diced 22 children with a knife, who were entering their school. No one was killed, but it wasn't for his lack of trying. So, as usual gun grabbers are going against the weapon, but not the criminal.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1355940749188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 13:12:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355941970804-27</Id><Topic><Title>Conn Shooter's Mom, tried to commit him</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1355881449505</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:44:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. That man injured 22 children. It took him over half an hour to do so. (Slow response times in China). Lanza killed 26 people in a little over two minutes before police arrived. Most of those had multiple rounds (up to 11). If he had been less thorough, he probably could have gotten more. See the difference? Do you understand that while the criminal is responsible for launching the attack, it is the gun that allows him to kill 26 people? How many people do you think Lanza could have injured with a two-minute response time? Do you think those teachers may have been able to stop him from injuring anyone if he were only armed with a knife? No one expects crime to disappear without assault rifles. We expect the carnage to diminish. If there is one thing we do know, the existence of large numbers of guns in our society has not reduced crime or carnage. Evidence is it has increased it.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355941970804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 13:32:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355942473132-28</Id><Topic><Title>Should Chicago be the model for federal gun control laws?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1355914471019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 05:54:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... From jon’s dog: “A smart dog does not continue to stop in the middle of a busy highway… (not surprisingly, being jon’s dog, followed by more genitalia fixation – must run in the family. Let me guess based on your obsession – he’s a Shih Tzu?) A clue for jon and his dog: A smart dog does not find himself in the middle of a busy highway.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355942473132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 13:41:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355942848456-29</Id><Topic><Title>Should Chicago be the model for federal gun control laws?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1355914471019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 05:54:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at that Cisco. You were right!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355942848456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 13:47:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355943125557-30</Id><Topic><Title>Conn Shooter's Mom, tried to commit him</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1355881449505</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:44:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another point that many are missing is this President's failure to lead. You can't lie, cheat, and contstantly move the goal posts like Barry is doing with the financial cliff talks. He got 51% of the vote, (via widespread voter fraud), yet he's trying to roll the Republicans. It's like the dems like to say, don't let any disaster go to waste. So, constantly dividing the country, among rich &amp; poor, black &amp; white, will do nothing to solve any problems, in these Obama self imposed, hard economic times. The Conn. shooter's house was said to be worth $40 Million. Maybe all that class warfare spiel got this kid upset. There is some evidence that the family believed that they, as are all of us, are all under too much government control.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1355943125557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 13:52:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355943757224-31</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the best place to buy Ammo?</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1355936000893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 11:53:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great info. Got my hands on a AR 15 and a magnum Judge also bought a gun safe, also need to load up and ammo now</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1355943757224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 14:02:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355944040531-32</Id><Topic><Title>Conn Shooter's Mom, tried to commit him</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1355881449505</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:44:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. The list of people I don't want having access to an AR-15 just keeps getting longer and longer. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355944040531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 14:07:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355946081474-33</Id><Title>Cars versus guns...</Title><Msg>... “And then, compare your list to the number of automobile related deaths in the U.S. Every year for the last 62 years those deaths have exceeded 32,367 each and every year. There have been well over 2 MILLION of them since 1950! Do you also advocate "automobile control" too? After all, if there were no cars = no car deaths. Same illogical argument as your gun control fantasy!” – gms47cb (that would be jon) Hey, what great logic. I’ll go one step further. Eliminate all the automobiles and they’ll be no more drive-by shootings! Advocate automobile control? No, I just renewed my license, tags and insurance simply because I enjoy spending time at the BMV – Why? Are there laws that say I have to do that stuff? Oh, right, the “automobile control” of which you are apparently oblivious, has already favorably impacted the statistics. Thanks for, quite accidentally on your part, debunking your “Illogical argument”. And how timely – check this out, goofy. Gun deaths set to outstrip car fatalities for first time in 2015 Liz Goodwin – The Lookout – earlier today “The CDC estimates that auto-related deaths--long on the decline as more motorists wear seat-belts and face harsher penalties for drunk driving--will fall to 32,000 in 2015. Deaths from firearms, which include suicides and accidents, are estimated to rise to 33,000 over the same period.” You really don’t have to argue with these people. Just give them enough rope… Oh, wait, rope legislation pending. Oh, wait again…they already did that with the hemp laws. Change that…give them enough rope and they’ll embarrass themselves to death.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355946081474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 14:41:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355946117812-34</Id><Topic><Title>Wack job, jon...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355782175162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 17:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I don't think we should repeal the 2nd amend, just reword it. " Yea, whatever. Now take your bright idea and ram it through 2/3 of the Senate, 2/3 of the House, and 3/4 of the states. That's how you "reword" the constitution. Good luck with that. Now tell us all about your expertise in constitutional law. You and echo are really quite the pair, Ricky.</Msg><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1355946117812</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 14:41:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355947180217-35</Id><Topic><Title>Ascending Triangle</Title><Username>xtgeminiman</Username><Timestamp>1355771700749</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 14:15:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are correct sir. I sold my weekly short puts earlier this week and wrote calls at the 34.5 strike. Options are the only thing keeping me alive in this POS stock. I am hoping for a strong push into the dividend and then I am out of this POS.</Msg><Username>xtgeminiman</Username><Timestamp>1355947180217</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 14:59:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355947296055-36</Id><Topic><Title>Wack job, jon...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355782175162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 17:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the insight, ramsdude. I see you graduated from elementary school. Lucky you. Some students get shot before they get to learn about the amendment process, much less partake in it. In reality, we don't even need to reword it. The legal authority of the government to regulate arms is well established. The only reason to reword it is so boneheads don't decide its their Constitutional duty to shoot law enforcement officers every time their is a slight change in the law. There is some value in clarity. Now tell us all about your expertise in Constitutional law. You can start with an explanation of how Constitutional law is different from constitutional law.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1355947296055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 15:01:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355947323121-37</Id><Topic><Title>Buy (ALU) today! Everyone on Wall Street is!</Title><Username>immglobal2012</Username><Timestamp>1355936607482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 12:03:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just looked at ALU! $1.48 new high and many institutions are buying right now!!!</Msg><Username>wagnerr37</Username><Timestamp>1355947323121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 15:02:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355947806872-38</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the best place to buy Ammo?</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1355936000893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 11:53:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks Bud</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1355947806872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 15:10:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355951361079-39</Id><Title>wow</Title><Msg>usually runs up to ex-div - this could be much worse than usual post ex-div, most likely new 52 week low</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1355951361079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 16:09:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355951825856-40</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the best place to buy Ammo?</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1355936000893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 11:53:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know where I have been getting it for dirt cheap lately is Estate Sales. They got to get rid of it and can't take it back to their warehouse if it's an Estate Liquidation company. Check the papers and Craigs list for the sales. Just stay out of my territory please. :-)</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1355951825856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 16:17:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355955341179-41</Id><Title>Hey Terrel Eddy!</Title><Msg>What's up with your friends at "Jew watch" these days. I bet they're glad to have someone like you helping to keep track of those scamps. I think folks on the board might enjoy hearing some of your stories about Jews. They are, eh, fascinating to say the least. By the way, I forwarded your contact information to SPLC so they could follow and enjoy your contributions to the "Jew Watch" site. For well thought out postings like those you write, it's a shame you should have to remain anonymous!</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1355955341179</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 17:15:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355966863985-42</Id><Topic><Title>Conn Shooter's Mom, tried to commit him</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1355881449505</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:44:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You kidding, right? Then you should blame Palin and her bull's eye target ad, etc.... The mother of the shooter didn't lock up her guns, though she knew her son had problems!</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1355966863985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 20:27:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355967789586-43</Id><Topic><Title>Conn Shooter's Mom, tried to commit him</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1355881449505</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:44:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>really, you need to talk about this on a stock message board? What in the h#$@ does this have to do with T stock?</Msg><Username>bill_meister</Username><Timestamp>1355967789586</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 20:43:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355975700853-44</Id><Topic><Title>Cars versus guns...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1355946081474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 14:41:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>also one of the differences between a car and a gun is, very few people intentionally try to run over someone to kill them; that cannot be said about people pointing guns at others and pulling the trigger</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1355975700853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 22:55:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355979551915-45</Id><Title>Sandy Hook</Title><Msg>To understand what happened I think we will never know . To talk of gun control is an issue that we should address . I feel that automatic weapons should be banned...large ammo clips also..yet weapons legally purchased should not be banned . If we lived in a perfect world then there would be no crime...yet there is..and a lot of it .Think for one moment what runs through the mind of a common criminal that robs a bank or a simple store. I hate to say it but the gun owners do have a valid point .Criminals do not care about the laws concerning guns ,their only concern is to rob . You who would take weapons from everyone are wrong..for then only the bums would have weapons . Criminals DO NOT care about laws only about getting away with a crime .Your zealous actions will be counter productive .</Msg><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1355979551915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 23:59:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>