<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349669411703-1</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go Mr. President, looks like your energy policies are really working</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349639079273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The oil companies want "Controlled Scarcity" as it's good for profits. The Kenyan supports it fully. They tried to close a refinery in Bakersfield, CA. a few years back even though the oil field there was still productive. The state legislature made them put it up for sale. It's still operating. But, there has not been a new refinery in Calif. in a good many years and you see what happens with any breakdown of the existing ones. The eco-freaks have blocked any new refineries and most well drilling. They should all move to the Matto Grosso and live off carrion and insects so they don't offend Mother Gaia.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1349669411703</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 00:10:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349694679518-2</Id><Title>‘Worst US Quarterly Earnings Since 2009’</Title><Msg>The slowdown in the global economy and anaemic US recovery is expected to result in one of the worst US quarterly earnings seasons since late 2009. Analysts expect earnings for the period ended September to decline, the first negative result after 11 consecutive quarters of gains. Energy and materials companies are tipped to lead the downturn with the financial sector set to be one of the few bright spots. Wall Street analysts expect third-quarter earnings per share for S&amp;P 500 [.SPX 1460.93 --- UNCH (0) ] companies will fall 2.7 percent versus the same quarter a year ago, according to FactSet. Just three months ago analysts had forecast growth of 1.9 percent. In the past three months, warnings from large companies about reduced full-year profits due to global economic weakness fuelled this pessimistic view. FedEx [FDX 86.47 -0.06 (-0.07%) ] and UPS [UPS 73.10 0.13 (+0.18%) ], often seen as barometers for world economic health, cut their full-year guidance during their last earnings releases, citing the slowdown in global trade. In August, talking to the Financial Times, the chief executive of Caterpillar, bellwether of the industrial economy, warned of the greater uncertainty about global growth, predicting it could take another five years before Europe’s economy begins to grow. Jeff Kleintop, chief market strategist at LPL Financial, said: “We expect corporate profits will be negative and revenues soft, as the global slowdown and below average economic growth in the US has affected companies.” The earnings season starts with Alcoa [AA 9.09 0.02 (+0.22%) ] reporting on Tuesday, followed by JPMorgan [JPM 41.71 -0.11 (-0.26%) ] and Wells Fargo [WFC 35.84 -0.13 (-0.36%) ] on Friday. However, downbeat earnings expectations are yet to weigh on the broad market with the S&amp;P 500 up more than 16 percent so far this year. Stock prices are being supported by the Federal Reserve buying large amounts of bonds, which lowers interest rates and boosts the attractiveness of riskier assets such as equities. “If we see that the markets do not correct even after earnings disappoint and guidance gets worse, then it will be clear that fundamentals have given way to the Fed,” said Quincy Krosby, market strategist at Prudential Financial. Equity investors are also looking beyond the most recent quarter toward the final quarter of the year given the expectation that profits will rebound. S&amp;P 500 companies are on course for record cash profits for 2012. That outlook may suffer from downward revisions should companies express caution about their future earnings in their results in the coming weeks. “Even with lowered expectations, earnings could disappoint and place stocks under pressure,” said Michael Kastner, principal at Halyard Asset Management. “It’s worrying to see the warnings from Fed Ex and other weakness from the transport sector that suggests this will not be a good quarter.” Financials are expected to be one of the few bright spots with analysts expecting earnings growth for the quarter of 10 percent according to FactSet. Ahead of earnings season, companies tend to downplay expectations and look to surprise the market with better results. “We expect more upside surprises in the third quarter, primarily because consumer health is in a good shape and with 80 percent of companies tied to consumers their earnings will be better than the consensus estimate,” said Phil Orlando, chief equities strategist at Federated.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1349694679518</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 07:11:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349695873513-3</Id><Topic><Title>What i discovered about whistle blowing at ATT</Title><Username>cencoastsurfer</Username><Timestamp>1349407895184</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 23:31:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AT&amp;T has an Asset Protection hotline number, 1-800-807-4205. Please give the AP hotline a call and report your observations and concerns.</Msg><Username>lkakin</Username><Timestamp>1349695873513</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 07:31:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349696430040-4</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go Mr. President, looks like your energy policies are really working</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349639079273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought you guys wanted a hands off approach by government. You know, let the market place set prices. Get the government off our backs. Capitalism will save the day. Now it sounds like you want price controls. Which way is it?</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1349696430040</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 07:40:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349700722997-5</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go Mr. President, looks like your energy policies are really working</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349639079273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>California has a problem with gasoline supplies due to long-term government regulation in that state. Don't try to blame the free market, dork. California doesn't use the free market.</Msg><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1349700722997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 08:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349701736092-6</Id><Title>T Shareholders! Get The Facts!</Title><Msg>I have heard that T is going to the moon and I have heard that it is going to tank! Which one is it? I tend no to believe too much of the hype and rumors on here…I did find this report while doing some DD, opinions welcome! Copy &amp; Paste this to your browser -- goo.gl/KvhaH</Msg><Username>dominguezoneal340</Username><Timestamp>1349701736092</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:08:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349704489787-7</Id><Topic><Title>Friday is ex-div day..</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1349375130559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:25:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>post dividend dumping continues</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1349704489787</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:54:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349704584385-8</Id><Topic><Title>on the day obama was</Title><Username>oilup1234</Username><Timestamp>1349665783101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 23:09:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>youtube /watch?v=tpAOwJvTOio</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349704584385</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:56:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349706774065-9</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT DOWN, STOCK MARKET UP, AUTO INDUSTRY STRONG! SOUNDS GOOD TO ME! WHY CHANGE?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349574314302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:45:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unemployment down, stock market up, auto industry strong! Sounds good to me! Why change. I'm not, and I don't fall for faux news lies so easy like the others on here. When you say a man does eveything wrong, even when he doesn't, you're dishonest. Correct and complete information on ObamaCare: http://www.healthcare.gov/law/timeline/index.html</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349706774065</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 10:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349707823829-10</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT DOWN, STOCK MARKET UP, AUTO INDUSTRY STRONG! SOUNDS GOOD TO ME! WHY CHANGE?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349574314302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:45:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unemployment down With the GDP at 1.3% and 114,000 jobs created I don't believe unemployment is down. The other poll that showed 670,000 jobs is misleading in my opinion they are part time jobs just for the Holiday season. Those jobs will disapear at the end of the holiday season. Stock market up QE3 is printing 40 billion dollars and pumping that money into the econmy. The dollar is being devalued and the market will drop very soon.I am investing in the metals at this time.After the election if Obama wins I will sell off most os my positions except the metals. Auto industry strong Romney said to let the auto industry go through the bankrupcy process. Obama spent $20 billion and then the auto industry went through the bankrupcy process anyway. If the President is re-elected he probably will be impeached over the Lybia coverup not mention fast &amp; furious. If you want Socialism then vote for Obama.If you want Capitalism vote for Romney.I would suggest watching Fox news and CNN news and see the differance in reporting.A few weeks after the election the seniors on medicare advantage will have a big suprise thanks to Obamacare. This are just my opinion.</Msg><Username>ls3487</Username><Timestamp>1349707823829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 10:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349707890484-11</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go Mr. President, looks like your energy policies are really working</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349639079273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“If any other of our presidents had…blah, blah, blah …Every statement and action in this email is factual and directly attributable to Barrack Hussein Obama. Every bumble is a matter of record and completely verifiable.” – fake ricky And if you read another Tea Party email of lies and lame nonsense, posted from a fool who spends all day with copycat aliases, would you feel sorry for him knowing that he is a pitiful character, or just ridicule him as his own family does? Some life! How pathetic. “Q: Did Obama double the debt and commit every "bumble" he's accused of in a critical chain e-mail? A: No. The debt hasn't doubled, and of the 24 claims only six are true. We found another seven to be partly true, and the rest to be false, misleading or exaggerated. This harshly critical e-mail has been circulating since at least the summer of 2009 and we've been asked about it more than 50 times. The version readers have sent to us contains 24 claims that it says are all true: "Every bumble is a matter of record and completely verifiable." Not quite. We found that four of the claims are simply false. Others had some basis in fact but were twisted to the point of giving the reader a false impression, hence we judged them to be misleading or exaggerated. Only six of the claims were true. Another seven were partly true, having some accuracy to the claim but lacking context or containing other errors. We'll take each of the claims in order:” Available at FactCheckOrg</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1349707890484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 10:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349708189975-12</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go Mr. President, looks like your energy policies are really working</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349639079273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No bumbles except those flying around in your brain from faux hoax news and those left on romney's campaign trail.. I'm voting for Obama, he's done a great job. Never seen any President so on top of issues and logical in problem solving. He's amazing as President. And I thank him for being the Commander who was in charge of taking down OBL and many many other key terrorists.Thank you Mr. President.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349708189975</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 10:56:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349708444963-13</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go Mr. President, looks like your energy policies are really working</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349639079273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So now you blame gas prices in LA on the President, why not Romney, he is just as at fault. At least be honest in personal attacks.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349708444963</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:00:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349709228973-14</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go Mr. President, looks like your energy policies are really working</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349639079273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All these statements are absolutely true and it is just the tip of the iceberg. Everyone knows the liberal press lies that is why newspaper subscriptions and viewership of the nightly news has fallen off tremendously. Repeating their lies makes you a liar.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1349709228973</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349709369096-15</Id><Title>Romney says he was completely wrong on his 47% comments.</Title><Msg>All caught on camera violators say this and say they didn't mean it. Yeah, he meant it. When are Ryan, Sununu going to say it too, that they were completely wrong? They said Romney was completely right. Caught with foot in mouth again,sometimes I feel sorry for ronmy and his blunders.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349709369096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:16:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349710704011-16</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go Mr. President, looks like your energy policies are really working</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349639079273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please explain how are the almost tripling of gas prices under the Obama admin has anything to do with Romney.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1349710704011</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:38:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349711002024-17</Id><Topic><Title>Romney says he was completely wrong on his 47% comments.</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349709369096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:16:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you see the SNL skit of the debate. They sure nailed BO, that was funny funny. Anyone who missed it needs to see it.</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349711002024</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349711348914-18</Id><Title>Snoop Dog's top ten reasons to vote for BO</Title><Msg>Snoop's 10 reasons why he is voting for Obama: “1.He a black n*gga. 2.He mad cool yo. 3.That n*gga look like he can fight. 4.He wears a durag like me. 5.Michelle got a #$%$ 6.He's BFFs with Jay-Z. 7.He's hugged Beyonce before, and sniffed her neck. 8.We use the same hair clippers. 9.He smokes Newports. 10.I seen that n*gga hoop before and he got a jumper.</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349711348914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:49:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349711577181-19</Id><Topic><Title>Special Report</Title><Username>breecefr170200</Username><Timestamp>1349709385068</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like these guys, they're really good.</Msg><Username>andrebgout66588</Username><Timestamp>1349711577181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349711621143-20</Id><Topic><Title>Snoop Dog's top ten reasons to vote for BO</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349711348914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:49:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of BO's supporters will vote for him for these reasons. What does that tell you?</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349711621143</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:53:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349711688930-21</Id><Topic><Title>Snoop Dog's top ten reasons to vote for BO</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349711348914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:49:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't say it a strong BO supporter did look it up.</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349711688930</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:54:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349711827952-22</Id><Topic><Title>Romney says he was completely wrong on his 47% comments.</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349709369096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:16:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish a politician (every politician) would say something without having to say" I was taken out of context" or " I clearly meant..." (in this case, who put that camera there). If you say something, back it up! Yes I said it, and here's why! Have some backbone! Geez! Politicians have the spine of a Licorich whip.</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1349711827952</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:57:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349712261465-23</Id><Topic><Title>Romney says he was completely wrong on his 47% comments.</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349709369096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:16:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“If you’ve got a business — you didn’t build that. Somebody else made that happen,” BO</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349712261465</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349712552860-24</Id><Topic><Title>Romney says he was completely wrong on his 47% comments.</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349709369096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:16:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BO race baiting in his 2007 speech “The people down in New Orleans they don’t care about as much!” Obama, then a presidential candidate, said in a speech at Hampton University in Virginia. “When Hurricane Andrew struck in Florida, people said, ‘Look at this devastation. We don’t expect you to come up with your own money here. Here’s the money to rebuild. We’re not going to wait for you to scratch it together, because you’re part of the American family,’” Obama said. “We need additional federal public transportation dollars flowing to the highest need communities. We don’t need to build more highways out in the suburbs,” where, the implication is, the rich white people live. Instead, Obama says, federal money should flow to “our neighborhoods”: “We should be investing in minority-owned businesses, in our neighborhoods, so people don’t have to travel from miles away.”</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349712552860</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349713276644-25</Id><Topic><Title>robfisk aka jon2retard</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349527969552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The man has us 16 TRILLION in debt". Most of the debt came from your hero Dubya, but you knew that. I guess you like most reich-wingers, think the polls are fixed also. The polls say the Bishop will go back to preaching is lies on Nov.7. I don't even think his Boston congregation wants the liar back.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349713276644</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:21:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349713799965-26</Id><Topic><Title>Snoop Dog's top ten reasons to vote for BO</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349711348914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:49:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get back under your rock, your mother is calling you.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349713799965</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:29:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349714079006-27</Id><Topic><Title>Hallelujah...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1349610899329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 07:54:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lot of dumb rednecks in Georgia, and most vote republican. They go to church on Sunday with the wife and family, and on Monday they are screwing their 2nd cousins.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349714079006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:34:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349715161769-28</Id><Topic><Title>T Shareholders! Get The Facts!</Title><Username>dominguezoneal340</Username><Timestamp>1349701736092</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got it. Good job mate.</Msg><Username>v.roman61</Username><Timestamp>1349715161769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:52:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349717118273-29</Id><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Msg>Nope! Mitt will send those 47% folks... not his kids... but send your kids to die... The 5 Romney Boys Will never Joined Military to Serve our Country. They r doing more important stuff like helping daddy become president.. The Romney's act like the Military is for poor people...</Msg><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349717882561-30</Id><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN, you choose...</Title><Msg>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN, you choose...</Msg><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717882561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:38:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349718299005-31</Id><Topic><Title>robfisk aka jon2retard</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349527969552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You liberal democrats are the most INSULTING people on the planet. When you are in a position to debate logic with logic and can't, you just sling insults.How can anyone take you people seriously. Reich-wingers, the new frothing at the mouth insult.</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1349718299005</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349718414694-32</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are working on the inheritance tax, to eliminate it. That's all these guys think about. They have their gold and silver nothing will ever touch them war recession depression, they are covered.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1349718414694</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:46:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349719370745-33</Id><Topic><Title>Special Report</Title><Username>breecefr170200</Username><Timestamp>1349709385068</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure thing. Been receiving good alerts from them</Msg><Username>jeridwlv199116</Username><Timestamp>1349719370745</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:02:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349720174279-34</Id><Topic><Title>robfisk aka jon2retard</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349527969552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Obama administration passed another fiscal milestone this week, according to new data released by the Treasury Department. As of the close of business on Oct. 3, In the less-than-three-years Obama has been in office, the federal debt has increased by $4.212 trillion--more than the total national debt of about $4.1672 trillion accumulated by all 41 U.S. presidents from George Washington through George H.W. Bush combined.</Msg><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349720174279</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349720611410-35</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN, you choose...</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717882561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt Romney is a Mormon, Obama is a Mus.lim, I have chosen</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349720611410</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:23:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349720777247-36</Id><Topic><Title>Snoop Dog's top ten reasons to vote for BO</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349711348914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:49:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget the free Obama phones! youtube /watch?v=tpAOwJvTOio</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1349720777247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:26:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349722622094-37</Id><Topic><Title>robfisk aka jon2retard</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349527969552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You reich-wing republicans got the corner on insults my friend. Not much logic on this board, with you mouth breathers. Your friends have been insulting our President and his family before he even took office. You douchebags can dish it out, but you can't take it.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349722622094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349722713201-38</Id><Topic><Title>Snoop Dog's top ten reasons to vote for BO</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349711348914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:49:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you just imagine the outrage if someone white had said this.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1349722713201</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:58:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349722887099-39</Id><Topic><Title>T Shareholders! Get The Facts!</Title><Username>dominguezoneal340</Username><Timestamp>1349701736092</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Continue sharing this to us please. Thanks in advance.</Msg><Username>espinoza.flynn43</Username><Timestamp>1349722887099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349723773589-40</Id><Topic><Title>robfisk aka jon2retard</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349527969552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, comparing George Washington's, Lincoln, and Teddy Roosevelt etc. debt to Obama is a fair comparison. I didn't know Washington's economy was on the same level as Obama's. Just more republican disinformation to sway the uninformed voter. That's what you reich-wingers count on, the dummies.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349723773589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:16:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349724408779-41</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Five generations of Romney's since they first came to this country and not one has served in the military. Mitt was in Paris in the 60's while the serfs were dying in Vietnam. Now this coward is beating the drums of war with Iran. Just another chicken hawk born with a silver spoon up his anal orifice.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349724408779</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:26:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349724689119-42</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN, you choose...</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717882561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are showing your ignorance, but when that's all you got...</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349724689119</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:31:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349729783499-43</Id><Topic><Title>robfisk aka jon2retard</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349527969552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, don't forget to take your blood pressure meds tonight. I don't want you to stroke out!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1349729783499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:56:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349730956186-44</Id><Topic><Title>robfisk aka jon2retard</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349527969552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess with your head stuck up Ricky's rear end, you missed the part that said 'accumulated by all 41 U.S. presidents from George Washington through George H.W. Bush combined'. You didn't comprehend the word, accumulated and combined? Oh sorry, it wasn’t presented as a Democratic Party talking point and must have been confusing.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1349730956186</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349731100371-45</Id><Topic><Title>robfisk aka jon2retard</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349527969552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But, but, but The Anointed One said he would fix all that. He failed. He failed at keeping out the lobbyists from his administration. He failed at creating the most open administration ever. He failed so many things; the debt to him is a minor issue.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1349731100371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:18:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349731425651-46</Id><Topic><Title>5 Romney Boys Will Join Military to Serve our Country?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717118273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you're not paying attention either. The government sends the boys and girls overseas; Obama sent at least 30K more to Afghanistan. It is a volunteer military these days. Did your kids volunteer? If so, good for them and my thanks to them; if not, you need to shut your pie hole, assuming that is the hole this nonsense is coming from.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1349731425651</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:23:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349731737505-47</Id><Topic><Title>Hallelujah...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1349610899329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 07:54:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can post this kind of crap and try to paint all Republicans as being the same if you want, but then we have to start a list of #$%$ Democrats as well. I am sure you don't want to do that. We could start with just the female contingent from California and make even this jackass look sane.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1349731737505</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:28:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349732044898-48</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go Mr. President, looks like your energy policies are really working</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349639079273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*If any other of our presidents had been the first President to need a Teleprompter installed to be able to get through a press conference, would you have laughed and said this is more proof of how inept he is on his own and is really controlled by smarter men behind the scenes? * The bigger question is how did he know what the questions from the media were going to be so he could have his answers appear on the teleprompter? Oh, never mind, I just answered my own question; of course he knew because he hands out the questions to the MSM before hand. Silly me.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1349732044898</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:34:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349732222159-49</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT DOWN, STOCK MARKET UP, AUTO INDUSTRY STRONG! SOUNDS GOOD TO ME! WHY CHANGE?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349574314302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:45:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you looked at the market today? One day, not one week or not even a month constitutes a market rally. Besides, he claims he has not control or ability to impact the market or gas prices. Even many Democrats are starting to question the unemployment numbers.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1349732222159</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:37:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349739283293-50</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT DOWN, STOCK MARKET UP, AUTO INDUSTRY STRONG! SOUNDS GOOD TO ME! WHY CHANGE?</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349574314302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:45:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here you are again dallas, you are in need of some home counciling....obama is leading us into bankruptcy, and no, obama is not a christian, he has admitted that he is a muslim....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1349739283293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349740721930-51</Id><Topic><Title>Snoop Dog's top ten reasons to vote for BO</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349711348914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:49:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Snoop actually said that Barry should skip the weed the next time he debates. Man, he's right. That's why Barry was doing all that smirking, while Mitt was hitting grand slams. It looked like a Denny's 7am breakfast hour, the way Mitt was smacking them. Good call Snoop Daddy, Fifty. This guy's heart really isn't in the problems of a 2nd term. Mouchelle is putting all that pressure on him, cause she wants da plane, and all those perks.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1349740721930</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:58:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349741261580-52</Id><Topic><Title>T Shareholders! Get The Facts!</Title><Username>dominguezoneal340</Username><Timestamp>1349701736092</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice link, thank you</Msg><Username>atkinsw85</Username><Timestamp>1349741261580</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:07:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349741266168-53</Id><Title>BPT pays big $1.82 Dividend - Ex-Div Date 10/11/12 - 10%+ Annualized Yield</Title><Msg>Snag it. Run-up rally just starting.</Msg><Username>borderlaw</Username><Timestamp>1349741266168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349741524094-54</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go Mr. President, looks like your energy policies are really working</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1349639079273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's supply and demand. The media refuses to draw the connection between 40 million people (illegals), getting driving permits, causing fuel prices to soar. Governor Moonbeam almost overnight, allowed all these low mpg, energy sucking lowriders on the street. Economics isn't rocket science. If you want to get California back in black, vote for Mitt. He's the NEW Reagan. Drill for Oil, and send illegals packing, and watch the jobs come back.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1349741524094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:12:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349741938935-55</Id><Title>Back in Black</Title><Msg>Mitt's people got to get to the AC/DC folks. That sounds a little bit weird, Mitt being a Mormon, and all. But Mitt will balance the budget, get us back in black. No more red ink. They could play that song at all of Mitt's rallies.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1349741938935</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349742725487-56</Id><Topic><Title>robfisk aka jon2retard</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1349527969552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I only post under my name, which really is robfisk. Yvette should know this. I am so glad I got that Prius, since Barry's anti-American Oil policies, have sent gas prices to the Moon. Definitely, out of this world. I love the look, other Brothers give me in the hood, when they spy my ride. I one day plan to open a chain of pizza joints in the hood. Pizza is very healthy, and because of all the Chinese restaurants, here in inner city Baltimore, I miss my cat.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1349742725487</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:32:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349747206313-57</Id><Topic><Title>Back in Black</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1349741938935</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:18:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Red ink" is what creates our currency under the swindle known as the "Fed". Your credit and currency are all "monetized debt". It's an old racket that originated in Babylon thousands of years ago. No debt, no money. They then charge vigorish or rent on this fairy tale creation of theirs called "Federal Reserve Notes". It's not "Federal" but a private corporation and it has no "reserves."</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1349747206313</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 21:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349751925469-58</Id><Topic><Title>Snoop Dog's top ten reasons to vote for BO</Title><Username>lkglhklkh</Username><Timestamp>1349711348914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:49:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get rid of O'vomit and the Democrap Congress</Msg><Username>jotrout</Username><Timestamp>1349751925469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:05:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349752177617-59</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN, you choose...</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717882561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt Romney has created jobs...vs ..Obama has no clue how to create jobs, you choose</Msg><Username>ls3487</Username><Timestamp>1349752177617</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349752638932-60</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN, you choose...</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717882561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol.....yes he has outsourced every job possible to China... old lyin Mitt and lyin Ryan</Msg><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349752638932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:17:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349752639902-61</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON... vs. OBAMA IS CHRISTIAN, you choose...</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349717882561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol.....yes he has outsourced every job possible to China... old lyin Mitt and lyin Ryan</Msg><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349752639902</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>