<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-02"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357131221303-1</Id><Title>Hastings’s “blunt assessment”…</Title><Msg>... “They’re crazy, but they’re not that bat sh#t crazy,” - Democratic Representative Alcee Hastings, in a reference to the extreme obstructionist elements of the GOP. That would include many on this board, who unsuccessfully continue to try to push Tea Party mentality while experiencing another beat down from the general public. Wake up, boys and girls. Obviously, Middle America likes the decision…so, if the market likes it this morning, as well, just who is it then that you are pretending to represent? Somebody tell me when the ball drops.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357131221303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 07:53:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357133199820-2</Id><Topic><Title>Turn T Into Your Personal ATM!</Title><Username>joneselwood243</Username><Timestamp>1355850999239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:16:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$$#$%$</Msg><Username>jackwhite565</Username><Timestamp>1357133199820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:26:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357136631262-3</Id><Topic><Title>Ensquared Challenges AT&amp;T on Revised iPhone Insurance Prices</Title><Username>lakishawolaklofxtq1775</Username><Timestamp>1310314651000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2011-07-10 12:17:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are amazing.</Msg><Username>charles.meadow</Username><Timestamp>1357136631262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:23:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357137324725-4</Id><Title>Could finish Lower Today</Title><Msg>It wouldn't surprise me if this market slid back down to even today.</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1357137324725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:35:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357137499630-5</Id><Topic><Title>Turn T Into Your Personal ATM!</Title><Username>joneselwood243</Username><Timestamp>1355850999239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:16:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you folks that use yahoo message boards for free advertising are thieves. I know they charge quite a bit for a small start up offering free service; however INO must be a fairly well established company and should buy a spot ad. If your service is worth using there will be people willing to pay you at least a small annual fee that would allow you to be fair with Yahoo.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357137499630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:38:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357138166074-6</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Chart looks ominous</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1356630861968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 12:54:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It looks like the breakout is here. We are on our way to $40. Get in early and be aware that there will be pull backs along the way. The upper Bollinger Band is $34.50. Conservative investors may want to just buy call options at this time and wait for the real breakout.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357138166074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:49:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357139488279-7</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1356577227990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 22:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't see how six people disagree with the one rational post I have seen from you. I think they just see your name and disagree without even reading what you posted. The best way to achieve your goal is by cutting the spending for schools, defense, retirement for federal employees including Congress and the president, wages for government employees, agricultural payouts for not growing crops, etc. For a complete list go to Ron Paul's web site if it is still up.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357139488279</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:11:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357139579341-8</Id><Topic><Title>Could finish Lower Today</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1357137324725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:35:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, hard to understand what there is to be so giddy about. I received a lovely e-mail from my liberal congressman telling me what a great job he did for me over the last several days. I sent him a scathing response. Fat lot of good it will do, but I feel a little better.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1357139579341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:12:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357139717166-9</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky - The UNARMED LADY ??</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1357103628695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 00:13:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tRicky also believes that when a drunk gets behind the wheel of a car and kills someone in an accident, you should blame the car!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357139717166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:15:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357141600019-10</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1356577227990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 22:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ever think those nice shylocks that own the "Fed" might be behind all the borrowing of their fairy tale money on which they collect vigorish? Such a deal!</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1357141600019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:46:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357141828755-11</Id><Title>Bernacke's favorite song</Title><Msg>"...up, up and away in my beautiful balloon."</Msg><Username>crazyhorse1786</Username><Timestamp>1357141828755</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:50:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357142154452-12</Id><Topic><Title>Could finish Lower Today</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1357137324725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:35:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe not AT&amp;T. DowJones announced this morning "AT&amp;T Inc. (T) will webcast a keynote address by John Donovan, Senior Executive Vice President -- AT&amp;T Technology and Network Operations, at the Citi Global Internet, Media &amp; Telecommunications Conference in Las Vegas on Wednesday, January 9at 8:15 a.m. PT. The webcast will be available live and for replay at AT&amp;T Investor Relations." Of course January 9 is over a week away but AT&amp;T is due for a major run up and is up 2% today after trading low all last week and Monday.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357142154452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:55:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357142764447-13</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1356577227990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 22:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is the only thing that makes sense of the low interest rates that persist in spite of the risky economy.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357142764447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:06:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357144718887-14</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1356577227990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 22:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With the exception of defense, that's peanuts. About 2/3 of Federal spending is Medicare/Soc. Sec. &amp; Defense--and these three sections are growing faster than Federal spending as a whole. Interest on the public debt is also quite large, and growing faster than Federal spending as a whole. You cannot address spending while ignoring Soc. Sec. &amp; Medicare &amp; Defense. Yet Republicans increased spending on defense and instituted Medicare Part D--the prescription drug benefit, accelerating the growth in Medicare spending. Obama has been lowering defense spending and found savings in Medicare. So despite the ARRA and Health Reform, spending under Obama has been on the decline. It has been my opinion that all the focus on schools, public employee pay, agricultural payouts, etc., is a distraction from the real issues. Unless you cut Medicare, Soc. Sec and interest on the public debt, the automatic increases from these programs will quickly outstrip any savings you manage to squeeze from other sources. And squeezing ENOUGH savings from ALL of these sources is nary impossible to do from a political perspective. But small changes in Medicare, Soc. Sec and the deficit result in large savings when compounded over time. This is why I support the Grand Bargain and am beyond fed up with the minority Tea Brains and Grover Norquist blocking a grand bargain.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357144718887</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:38:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357144963488-15</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T lays off 12 union workers</Title><Username>jamisteinhauerrvoha975</Username><Timestamp>1311441363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2011-07-23 13:16:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool picks. I love it.</Msg><Username>winstenaubrey</Username><Timestamp>1357144963488</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:42:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357147270212-16</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky - The UNARMED LADY ??</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1357103628695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 00:13:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jon, when she pushes 26 children in front of a train at once, we'll talk about maybe putting up some safety barriers. Coral, drunk driving is illegal. You can be driving perfectly fine before you hit a checkpoint, but if you blow a 0.08% BAC, you're going to jail. Contrary to what your simple mind perceives, this is a perfect example of government making something illegal because when allowed to exist in the society it has the potential to cause death, even if some of the individuals restricted or arrested have done nothing that would otherwise suggest people are at risk. Of course we blame the driver when he kills someone. But as a society, we also recognize, blame and make illegal the act of drunk driving itself. The success of drunk driving laws at reducing automobile deaths is an argument *for* similar restrictions on high-capacity magazines and assault rifles. We also do not ban alcohol and we do not ban cars because these are not the specific things that cause the large numbers of deaths. We specifically ban driving with a BAC of 0.08% or higher. Similarly, we are seeking background checks and specific bans on specific types of weapons and magazines believed to be responsible for large numbers of deaths. We are not seeking to ban all guns.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357147270212</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:21:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357147681936-17</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1356577227990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 22:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same feeble old argument 'its just peanuts! Pretty soon all those 'peanuts' add up to several trillion dollars. We have all just been screwed by Congress again. This current 'crisis' has been known to exist for at least the last two years, in reality more like the past 10 years, and Congress just kept pushing a solution or actions that might at least mitigate the problems out to future date where as individuals or a Party they wouldn't be blamed. This was a self-created crisis for political power reasons. They have done it again. The spending reductions are meager in this deal and won't be coming in any future ‘negotiations’. Obama just got the largest ego boast of his life and he won't deal with anyone any longer; my way or the highway just became the new Washington D.C. BAU. They accomplished renewing the Bush tax cuts, period! Nothing else was accomplished to reduce spending, reform tax laws, reform entitlement programs; they just wasted the past three years doing nothing. The next four years are going to really tough economic years, likely worse than the last four.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1357147681936</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:28:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357147954427-18</Id><Topic><Title>Hastings’s “blunt assessment”…</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357131221303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 07:53:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ball dropped when Congress showed their collective stupidity, selfishness, and ignorance over this past weekend.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1357147954427</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:32:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357148560535-19</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There will be no serious discussions around spending reductions as long as Obama is President.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1357148560535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:42:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357149115118-20</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T lays off 12 union workers</Title><Username>jamisteinhauerrvoha975</Username><Timestamp>1311441363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2011-07-23 13:16:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>im in connecticut ive heard of no such layoffs...we have guaranteed job offers .......</Msg><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1357149115118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:51:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357149178713-21</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Boomers began running up the debt in the early 1980s. They certainly did not plan for the strain their retirements will put on Soc. Sec. and Medicare/Medicaid. Medicare is broke, Soc. Sec will be by the time I retire, and we are running record deficits--not saving. Our debt is approaching 100% of GDP, spending will rise automatically due to boomers collecting Soc. Sec. &amp; Medicare. When you were young and poor you had the greatest safety net this country has ever seen. When you were old and enjoying the highest incomes of your lives you lowered taxes on yourselves." You really hate anyone you think is Boomer don't you? You do realize that the Boomers that spent 30-40 years working and paying taxes are not the reason for the Medicare and/or Social Security laws and spending rules don't you? How about laying the blame where it belongs...at the feet of Congress and for most of those years you complain Boomers weren't saving and planning for their retirements, Democrats controlled Congress. How about all those receiving the benefits that you seem to think are sacrosanct that have paid little or no taxes to support the benefits they receive from those that did and still are working. In reality Congress isn't providing those benefits, the Boomers that paid taxes for decades and many still are paying, and those still working that are bestowing these benefits, Congress is choosing the people to whom these resources are granted. By the way, I am not a Boomer.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1357149178713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:52:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357154488256-22</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1356577227990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 22:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The spending reductions are meager in this deal" There are no spending cuts in the fiscal cliff deal. In fact, the final bill contained a fair amount of pork. As I said, you tea brains idioted yourselves out of the discussion. We've now lost two opportunities for a grand bargain and have another round of crisis politics to look forward to in a few weeks. Congratulations.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357154488256</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:21:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357154846427-23</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How about laying the blame where it belongs...at the feet of Congress" I blame you for making me question my confidence in democracy. You can ignore the responsibility you have as an American citizen, winholder, but unfortunately you can't give it up. You are responsible for Congress. Whatever happens in this country I lay squarely at the feet of the American people because I believe in the power of American democracy.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357154846427</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:27:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357156032875-24</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am partially responsible for 4 people being in Congress. If you simply review the activities and actions or lack thereof in Congress for the past eight year at a minimum, you should be losing confidence in them. Have you heard the MSM's review of the most recent debacle? The money being given away in a bill that 'had to be passed' is outrageous at best. A bill that was given to member to consider and read about 10 minutes before a vote was called for. Did Nancy have anything to do with another, let's vote for it so we can find out what is in it? They haven't passed a budget in three years, but then again they never paid past budgets any attention other than to use the arguments for and against for political theater and power games in the media. The current 'crisis' has been staring them in the face for decades yet they couldn't and still haven't done anything truly constructive to resolve any of the important issues. Congress has spend it nearly into oblivion, they have ignored a real 'crisis' in immigration and in our banking and real estate markets until they both slapped them in the face. If you have any measure of confidence in Congress lately, you're a bigger fool than even your posts reflect. These aren’t professional politicians, they are professional criminals, and fools and we keep returning the same crooks and fools to their positions of power and near royalty for very suspect reasons. Have confidence in them at your own peril.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1357156032875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:47:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357156187139-25</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And your point is? I mentioned Federal union employee's, I never said how many were or weren't just simply that they may be some getting a raise. Are you so bored that you have to look this deep for something to post about</Msg><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1357156187139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:49:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357157056493-26</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I am partially responsible for 4 people being in Congress." Good 1st step. Now you need to realize that the Tea Brains you support are doing exactly what you put them there to do. You may remember being very upset that Congress took a break over Thanksgiving. Do you remember what I said I was worried about? That the Tea Brains would go back to their gerrymandered districts and find out that their base was just as looney after the election as it was before the election, and the spirit of compromise that followed the election would dissipate. I was right, and you all idioted yourselves out of the discussion. Congratulations.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357157056493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:04:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357159173048-27</Id><Topic><Title>Could finish Lower Today</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1357137324725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:35:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Want to revise your call with about 20 minutes left? Would take a hell of a drop to close even. Who's your advisor, or is this your own thinking?</Msg><Username>dm74575</Username><Timestamp>1357159173048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:39:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357160229737-28</Id><Topic><Title>Hastings’s “blunt assessment”…</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357131221303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 07:53:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harry Reid deserves so much more than an f-bomb. The man should be run out of Washington and Nevada.</Msg><Username>texlec</Username><Timestamp>1357160229737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:57:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357160758689-29</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans did cause a crisis; Congress collectively did this on their own. This 'crisis' isn't really a crisis just the fruits of a do nothing Congress that doesn't have the courage to do what is right for the American people. They passed a bill they barely read and while complaining and warning that the American taxpayers were going to suffer if the Democrats didn't get their way, they gave tax breaks to Hollywood, NASCAR, rum producers, algae growers, and electric motor scooter makers. How infantile and imprudent. They didn't have time to figure out the tax laws they wanted to keep or get rid of but they had time to define tax roll back for some of the most undeserving on the list. Good job guys and gals, now go back home before you can do any more damage. If this mountain of trash is the best our Congress can devise, we truly are in a world of trouble.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1357160758689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:05:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357160865787-30</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The end date was the compromise that the Democrats insisted upon before they would vote for it. I guess at some point in time they did understand the meaning of the word.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1357160865787</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:07:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357160931542-31</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you would have preferred that we didn't go after Al Queada?</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1357160931542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:08:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357161876803-32</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Winholder, look at it this way. 99% of the Bush fiscal policy remains in place, including his high spending and most of the Bush tax cuts. Even Obama's payroll tax cut for the middle class got wiped out, but the GOP doesn't care about extending that tax cut, does it? Another chance for a grand bargain blown by you Tea Brains.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357161876803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:24:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357163695358-33</Id><Title>AT&amp;T and January Effect</Title><Msg>In the past five years AT&amp;T has always gone down in January. Today the price jumped all the way from the lower Bollinger Band to break through the upper band. Up 3.5% today on volume 28% above average.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357163695358</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:54:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357163964664-34</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is just plain stupid. You could have said this about the republicans and it would have been more to the point.</Msg><Username>ourgovisajoke</Username><Timestamp>1357163964664</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:59:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357164340846-35</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T and January Effect</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357163695358</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:54:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, it it good that it broke through the upper Bollinger Band? Just trying to learn.</Msg><Username>dynnyd</Username><Timestamp>1357164340846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:05:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357164348608-36</Id><Topic><Title>Could finish Lower Today</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1357137324725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:35:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The whole market was up today big time. It must be the thrill of going over a cliff. The fall feels great; but the landing takes all the fun out of it. I know because I was a paratrooper in WWII.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357164348608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:05:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357165030426-37</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T and January Effect</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357163695358</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:54:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A breakthrough of this magnitude usually continues for a week or two; even longer. This is especially true when it comes from below the lower band.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357165030426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:17:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357169619119-38</Id><Topic><Title>Grover's cliff...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1356880373444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “By the way, I am not a Boomer.” – winholder Perhaps not, Winnie, but you ARE a bummer. You are a sanctimonious blowhard who hasn’t been correct on anything you’ve said here for years. Your predictions have been predictably wrong and your rants have been the epitome of the losing side you have backed, and are absolutely comical in retrospect. I picked only a couple, but your history here speaks for itself. And yet you continue…after the election, after today, and after tomorrow…how come you guys never learned humility? Oh, right, because you represent the privileged class of the imaginary oligarchy you’d like America to become…Sorry, pal, you’re wrong again… Famous quotes from the sage of the Tea Party – “Tee Partie Untie” “Nobody will need Trumps October Surprise. Obama is providing enough material to end his term as President at one…His own words will cost him this election.” Winholder,10/23 “Bull. Even the MSM questions which religion he (Obama) claims” – Winholder, queen of the Birther’s. “This is from this Sunday's Parade Magazine, the Ask Marilyn column.” – All media, domestic, foreign, public and private are, according to winholder, part of the MSM conspiracy…but Ask Marilyn is a solid, reputable journalist and, besides, Rush, Ann &amp; Sean, his “Go-To” source for factual information. (you got a problem with Miss Manners?) “Whats Nov7 gonna do to T? Depends on who wins. If Obama wins, sell everything you have, quickly.” – winholder, crack financial analyst…no, wait, financial analyst on crack. “Polls don't elect anyone and if you are using the polls as a decision tool for any election, you're a fool.” – said like a true GOP strategist who thought demographics were pictures from the devil. “I don't know for sure if Obama is a Muslim or even if he sympathizes with them…His track record of failure will cost him this election” – Right, Winnie, he’s a Muslim until you want to criticize Rev. Wright…then he’s a radical, #$%$ Christian…kinda’ like Jesus was. “Romney simply stated a well know truth…” Winholder, on the “47% comment”. Good call there, Winnie. When you defended the most famous mis-speak of the entire campaign, the writing was on the wall. “If this (swiftboating tactics) is what it takes to get rid of Obama, I am all for it.” – More shameless strategy along with gerrymandering, voter suppression and other repugnant GOP tactics. "Most people think we need an election before a budget can get passed--to let the American people weigh in." Yep, we need to get rid of a lot of the uncompromising Democrats in order for anything to happen.” – Uh, excuse me, Winnie, but did you happen to notice we had an election and the people have spoken. These were your own words. Why can’t you accept them? Oh, yeah, and about my comment this morning…”Obviously, Middle America likes the decision…so, if the market likes it this morning, as well, just who is it then that you are pretending to represent?”</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357169619119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:33:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357170728094-39</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T and January Effect</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357163695358</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:54:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks!</Msg><Username>dynnyd</Username><Timestamp>1357170728094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:52:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357170789387-40</Id><Title>Today for the Shorts</Title><Msg>Heard that the increased dividend taxes from the fiscal cliff was causing some cynics to short T in the last several months. Hopefully those shorts got spanked today. Sometimes the money just flows from the weak hands to the strong, as it did today. Thank you. I wish for there to be more heavy spankings in the months ahead.</Msg><Username>bunchnut</Username><Timestamp>1357170789387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:53:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357171191408-41</Id><Topic><Title>Could finish Lower Today</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1357137324725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:35:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As I thought, no response. He should change his name to "fuzzy".</Msg><Username>bunchnut</Username><Timestamp>1357171191408</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:59:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357177406236-42</Id><Topic><Title>Could finish Lower Today</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1357137324725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:35:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah @bunchnut, any jackoff can come on board with stupid comments like this #$%$. Looking at his track record in permalink, he's all over the place with equally stupid comments to many different message boards. On the sports threads, they are called trolls...don't know what term you have for this species here. Would like to hear what would make this idiot post such an incredibly stupid call.</Msg><Username>dm74575</Username><Timestamp>1357177406236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 20:43:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357178898284-43</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T and January Effect</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357163695358</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:54:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next time, drop the other shoe Wilkes. All that technical jumbo jumbo is just dandy, but it would be nice to draw some sort of conclusion without having to ask. Is this Bollinger Band a creation by a guy I used to see many years ago on the old FNN that had a stuttering problem when he spoke? If so, he's come a long way to have a Band named after himself. He was just another semi-regular guest personality at the time. Bill Griffeth and Sue Hererra were anchors on the same show broadcast out of Fontana, Ca. Sue's last name was different and Bill had a dandy 70's mustache. Man, time flies. Now, I lock in on Fox Business when I need a financial fix. Thanx for for asking the question I had in mind @dynnyd!</Msg><Username>dm74575</Username><Timestamp>1357178898284</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:08:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>