<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372765197410-1</Id><Topic><Title>Situation worsens for White South Africans</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372661795393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 02:56:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“Iv'e (sic) posed a challenge to atheists to prove my God wrong.” - preacher lew Seriously, lew? You’re asking people to prove something wrong that you have absolutely no “proof” of to begin with, other than a blind “faith” in a belief that you just happened to be born into? You’re spouting nonsense from an ancient text, the authorship of which you have no clue about. What’s more, you’re referencing The Old Testament, particularly the Hebrew Scriptures of Isaiah and Jeremiah, which were written well before your own religion was even conceptualized. “Flee out of the midst of Babylon, and deliver every man his soul: be not cut off in her iniquity; for this [is] the time of the LORD'S vengeance; he will render unto her a recompence.” – Jeremiah 51:6 Ah, praise the Lord and pass the ammunition, huh, lew? You clowns seem to be really big on vengeance…that’s not something that coordinates even remotely with my views on spirituality. And what’s up with Tyre?... “…after the end of seventy years shall Tyre sing as an harlot…And it shall come to pass after the end of seventy years, that the LORD will visit Tyre, and she shall turn to her hire, and shall commit fornication with all the kingdoms of the world upon the face of the earth…” – Isaiah 23:15 and 17 There’s your theme for next Sunday’s sermon at the KIan meeting, lew…”Finding Redemption and Salvation With a Seventy-Year Old #$%$.”</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1372765197410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 07:39:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372773988471-2</Id><Title>Wow, heard there is a massive promo coming to FEEL</Title><Msg>Why Warren Buffet has got nothing on FEEL</Msg><Username>jaydenhess835</Username><Timestamp>1372773988471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 10:06:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372774037567-3</Id><Title>hail the duckheads</Title><Msg>who sold in advance of a new divy declaration</Msg><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1372774037567</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 10:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372774357343-4</Id><Topic><Title>Situation worsens for White South Africans</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372661795393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 02:56:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't be ridiculous. Do you think that everyone who disagrees with your wacked-out interpretation of the Bible is an atheist trying to "prove the Bible wrong"? You're just picking for some sort of fight to validate to yourself just how super-faithful you are. Try some humility. There are many interpretations of God's Word. Why do you think that YOU are so special to have the single right one? And what an idiotic statement anyway. If something can't be "proven wrong" does that make it true? Your belief in God and the Bible is an article of faith, is it not? If, for instance, Saddam Hussein rebuilt parts of Babylon (which he did) and the US military built a base on the ruins of Babylon (which it did) does that destroy your faith in God? Now you stated that the Bible states that Babylon will NEVER be built on again, not even an itty bitty part. Yet it has been built on. Does that mean the Bible is wrong or your dogmatic interpretation of the Bible is wrong? I'll let you pick.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1372774357343</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 10:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372774518202-5</Id><Topic><Title>Situation worsens for White South Africans</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372661795393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 02:56:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are what you are. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1372774518202</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 10:15:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372776475140-6</Id><Topic><Title>Will Egypt Lead The WAY !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372726911171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"To help settle things in the middle east ?? So maybe "T" Stock will do what it's supposed to ??" Wow. It's good to have a reminder of just how dumb most investors are. The reason T stock is not rising with the rest of the market is that it is a dividend producing public utility, commonly considered a "defensive stock". During the recession and the period of low interest rates, people turned to these stocks to protect their money and to get some income, so there was a slight "bubble" in these stocks. Now that the economy is improving and the Fed is hinting at raising interest rates, people are moving their money away from these defensive stocks. T is doing just fine and exactly what it is supposed to do. It is a great income stock at these prices. It's performance has absolutely nothing to do with Egypt, Obama or whatever else you heard Rush blame everything on today. And I hope that you are not managing your own money.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1372776475140</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 10:47:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372782113478-7</Id><Title>You need to start your research on FEEL right away!</Title><Msg>This one is super-hot, FEEL creates cutting-edge golf club</Msg><Username>ccopeland427</Username><Timestamp>1372782113478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 12:21:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372782383865-8</Id><Topic><Title>Will Egypt Lead The WAY !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372726911171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well icky .. some how it just wouldn't seen right not to imbed "T" in this post !! You are correct in that "T" is in a bubble. I don't complain about T, nor do I complain about any of my stocks .. . That (gas ?) "bubble" that you have ?? .. perhaps you should either try burping or ferting to clear it, then you may understand that many worldly, 'and' more local events can have positive &amp; negative effects on on any decisions about investing. We in the U.S. have a "so so" ecomomy but we're losing on the ability of "decent personal income", thus, lack of extra income in which to save or "INVEST" - all due to Obama's policies of "FREE MONEY" for unskilled dependent's .. (without earning it). . Egypt had a fair economy till Morsi lied his way in, to become president .. much like Obama !! Try reading up on the Egyptian ecomomy since Morsi &amp; his mooslum brotha-hood have taken over and scrapped their "Constitution" .. better still, watch what the citizens do in the next 24 hours. But you 'liberals' don't understand "true" economics .. as long as you have "barely enough" to survive on .. then your gov't will fill 'your void'. Now .. pay for your OWN damn stuff, ya "stay at home" flunky .. smiles</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372782383865</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 12:26:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372785889249-9</Id><Topic><Title>Will Egypt Lead The WAY !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372726911171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, on that note, I'll just thank you and all those like you for participating in these American financial markets. Really, we couldn't do it without you.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1372785889249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 13:24:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372787349499-10</Id><Title>Daily give back of all gains starting earlier than usual today...</Title><Msg>Only the run to ex-div is keeping this from total collapse. Hate to see what happens after the 10th! My advice- GET OUT NOW WHILE YOU STILL HAVE YOUR PANTS!! PS- PLEASE DO YOUR OWN DD AND DON'T BLINDLY FOLLOW MY ADVICE!! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372787349499</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 13:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372787507753-11</Id><Title>Check out FEEL right now! It is about to go on a massive run</Title><Msg>Anti-aging sector gets facelift with FEEL’s revolutionary software</Msg><Username>marksdominic283</Username><Timestamp>1372787507753</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 13:51:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372788394502-12</Id><Title>Have you checked out FEEL</Title><Msg>Tiger Woods is Silent on FEEL’s newest design of golf club</Msg><Username>nielsentyler880</Username><Timestamp>1372788394502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 14:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372788822042-13</Id><Topic><Title>Will Egypt Lead The WAY !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372726911171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh you're sooo welcome 'icky' .. so you finally realize that any "GOOD thriving ecomomy" creates larger "investor pools"... and foreign investors may like "T" also. Well good !! See, I told you (for your bubble) that sometimes a good burp, or a good fert can sometimes clear the ole brain ....</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372788822042</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 14:13:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372789402627-14</Id><Topic><Title>Will Egypt Lead The WAY !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372726911171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! Just keep watching CNBC and I think we'll do alright.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1372789402627</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 14:23:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372789666261-15</Id><Title>To all Posters</Title><Msg>I will be removing all post that have nothing to do with this stock.</Msg><Username>workhard1966</Username><Timestamp>1372789666261</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 14:27:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372790593889-16</Id><Title>Wow! Negative for the day again</Title><Msg>everything gone</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372790593889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 14:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372799274004-17</Id><Topic><Title>Will Egypt Lead The WAY !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372726911171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...Jon – seriously, what are you…like 12? You write like an analphabetic psychoneurotic buying punctuation marks from Vanna White.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1372799274004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 17:07:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372801622583-18</Id><Topic><Title>I hate that racist #$%$ Paula Dean, you Phony</Title><Username>lefronczak</Username><Timestamp>1372542804859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 17:53:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Paula is going to be so disgraced and chastised for her use of the "N" word, and if it is so reprehensive, it should be banned completely. If that is the attitude, I want to see every rapper that has recorded this word or honky, whitey, cracker, or ofay lose their recording contracts no later than tomorrow morning. It is unacceptable or it is not! Pick one.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1372801622583</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 17:47:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372801768992-19</Id><Topic><Title>14 REPUBLICANS voted to reward illegal alien lawbreakers</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372652864809</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 00:27:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any bill that puts the ability of illegal entrants to this country ahead of those seeking citizenship legally and through the proper channels is just simply wrong for a whole host of reasons. To do this breaks the American spirit of honesty, fair play and hard work to achieve something worthwhile.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1372801768992</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 17:49:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372801954195-20</Id><Topic><Title>What have we learned today from our MSM?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372450034388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:07:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ricky, Ricky, you know as well as anyone that the trial is still in progress and that no verdict has been reached. I thought you believed in our justice system and our Department of Justice? Why not wait until all the facts are known and fairly evaluated before you rush to judgment? Are you just following the example of your fearless leader and jumping to conclusions? You don't know squat about what happened that night unless you were there as a witness. Where you? If not, you just need to shut up.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1372801954195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 17:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372802074912-21</Id><Topic><Title>Will Egypt Lead The WAY !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372726911171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of the people in Egypt don't seem to be able to make a clear decision about what they want. Maybe they should ask Obama again. He is real good at choosing new leaders.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1372802074912</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 17:54:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372802310019-22</Id><Topic><Title>Situation worsens for White South Africans</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372661795393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 02:56:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama should stay home and figure out how to lead us out of the mess he has put us in. There are still 14M more people out of work that there were in 2001, at least according to Time Magazine and his health care plan is hitting the skids on a daily basis. Housing prices and food process are going up again, even though the government insists there is not inflation but few are making enough to take advantage of these situations because they are working for less or not working at all. But it is very important that we develop trade with countries that don't have a pot to #$%$ in or a window to throw it out of....kind of like many Americans.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1372802310019</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 17:58:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372803971507-23</Id><Topic><Title>Wow! Negative for the day again</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372790593889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 14:43:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW!! TODAY SHOWS U KNOW NOTHING !!</Msg><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1372803971507</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 18:26:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372806579789-24</Id><Topic><Title>Will Egypt Lead The WAY !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372726911171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, Obama only knows to repeat what his teleprompter tells him ...</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372806579789</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 19:09:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372809076705-25</Id><Topic><Title>Will Egypt Lead The WAY !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372726911171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... oh eggo - seriously, they were free - ya nosey ole fert ! Here, "" " " "" ' " ' ' ", and I have plenty more !! They were extras on the set and Vanna dropped them off here on her way home, asking me to post them .. just to 'irritate' you .. ya got it !! Speaking of "analphabetic psychoneurotic" problems .. it sounds like you forgot to take your meds today. Now tuck your head between your legs and park your nose in it's regular parking spot !!</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372809076705</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 19:51:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372810076081-26</Id><Title>You got to hand it to old Mr. Slick</Title><Msg>Just when you think old Mr. Slick and his party are going to be held accountable for their actions you read the following as reported in the Washington Post: "The Obama administration will not penalize businesses that do not provide health insurance in 2014, the Treasury Department announced Tuesday. Instead, it will delay enforcement of a major Affordable Care Act requirement that all employers with more than 50 employees provide coverage to their workers until 2015." While the Republicans whale and moan with great gnashing of teeth, old Mr. Slick just winks and laughs at their feeble attempts to play in big boy politics. Let's face it folks the current leaders of the Republican party are nothing more than feckless wonderers in the political landscape and deserve to be primaryed and replaced. Again you sure got to hand it to old Mr. Slick. He sure knows how to play in the big boy game. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372810076081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 20:07:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372815968980-27</Id><Topic><Title>14 REPUBLICANS voted to reward illegal alien lawbreakers</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372652864809</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 00:27:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many illegals are concerned about this bill. The last thing they want is to have to pay taxes, and learn English. I say if these Republicans want to reward their backers with an endless suppy of cheap labor, let's open the borders to the Irish. Their economy sucks, and they already speak the lingo. Besides, they won't rob us blind, and flood our communities with drugs.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1372815968980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 21:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372816964856-28</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare to hit low income earners the hardest</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1371226801124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Canada here I come.</Msg><Username>gigabyte426</Username><Timestamp>1372816964856</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 22:02:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372821779330-29</Id><Topic><Title>You got to hand it to old Mr. Slick</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372810076081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 20:07:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I stayed registered as a Republican for a long time as I felt I might be able to sway the primary vote. I gave up and now am an Independent. Unless something drastic happens I shall never vote for another Republican. I gag when I see "Dem." beside someones name too. These people are all bought and paid for by the NWO crowd of BOTH parties. It may be cash or blackmail or some of both. Who cares, they are all corrupt.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1372821779330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 23:22:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372821870555-30</Id><Topic><Title>Wow! Negative for the day again</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372790593889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 14:43:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please Beau$39 - honor your word and do not attempt to communicate with me. I've had enough of your BS. I'm through with you. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372821870555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 23:24:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>