<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373097647859-1</Id><Topic><Title>“one of the prettiest sounds on Earth at sunset.”</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372938978571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 07:56:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well! Well! Well! If nothing else our "dear leader" is consistent in his support of the Muslim Brotherhood and its continued rule of countries within the middle east. Even after the people in Egypt had the unmitigated gall to overthrow the tyrants of the Muslim Brotherhood, our "dear leader" took the opportunity (as reported on Bloomberg on July 5, 2013) to say a few words of support for his friends in Cairo: "The Obama administration’s call for an “inclusive” political process in Egypt with a role for the Muslim Brotherhood has been overshadowed by deadly clashes between security forces and supporters of the Islamist group." "While President Barack Obama’s administration has stopped short of condemning the July 3 military takeover, it has called on Egyptian leaders to pursue “a transparent political process that is inclusive of all parties and groups,” including “avoiding any arbitrary arrests of Mursi and his supporters,” Bernadette Meehan, a spokeswoman for the National Security Council, said July 4 in a statement. " Well! Well! Well! It should be infinitely clear now to anyone who has ears to hear, our "dear leader" is only happy with a tyrannical dictator when the tyrannical dictator is one of his choosing. Yes our "dear leader" was right, the Muslim call to prayer is “one of the prettiest sounds on Earth at sunset.” "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1373097647859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 04:00:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373119171401-2</Id><Title>Re: “one of the pithetic sounds on Earth at sunset.”</Title><Msg>.(__Q___). ... .... . ..____xxxxXXXXxxx... x ...~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ IfUB. o. .</Msg><Username>pkornie</Username><Timestamp>1373119171401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 09:59:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373119389529-3</Id><Topic><Title>Re: “one of the pithetic sounds on Earth at sunset.”</Title><Username>pkornie</Username><Timestamp>1373119171401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 09:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: “one of the pethetic sounds on Earth at sunset.” .(__Q___). ... .... . ..____xxxxXXXXxxx... x ...~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ IfUB. ... More .(__O__). o. . Sentiment: Strong Buy . .</Msg><Username>pkornie</Username><Timestamp>1373119389529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 10:03:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373120612049-4</Id><Topic><Title>how do i stop my union from taking dues out of my paycheck</Title><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1373062693186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 18:18:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quit or go to management. It's that simple. I am no fan of the leadership of local1298 but without a union, you would be ONE of those contractors (maybe).</Msg><Username>thunder2niner</Username><Timestamp>1373120612049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 10:23:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373121681713-5</Id><Topic><Title>What have we learned today from our MSM?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372450034388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:07:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just start with a Google search of "beat whitey night" and see where it leads to all of the black on white violence that is NOT deemed racial. We've done a 180, whites work; blacks live off of our labor, whites are suffering under lynch mobs; authorities look the other way, blacks are elected because they're black; whites are called the source of all evil, etc, etc</Msg><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1373121681713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 10:41:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373121971557-6</Id><Topic><Title>Never Bully ... like in You're Chicago !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372972090062</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:08:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's just the black culture's way of doing things. To suggest otherwise proves you are racist.</Msg><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1373121971557</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 10:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373125215806-7</Id><Topic><Title>As a reminder, Ex-date is Monday, July 8th</Title><Username>fly4u7777</Username><Timestamp>1372931132738</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 05:45:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the reminder. I like to buy puts to take advantage of the drop that often occurs ex-dividend.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1373125215806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 11:40:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373126356148-8</Id><Topic><Title>What have we learned today from our MSM?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372450034388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:07:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Martin was too anxious to demonstrate his MMA training" According to Zimmerman, Martin walked up to his truck and tried to talk to him but he rolled up the windows. Then Martin ran away. That doesn't sound too anxious to get into a fight to me. But I agree, failure to communicate was a large problem but from what I can tell it seems to have been all Zimmerman's.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1373126356148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 11:59:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373126525026-9</Id><Topic><Title>What have we learned today from our MSM?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372450034388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:07:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How what a ridiculous thing to say. If Martin was alive he'd probably be treated in the media exactly like the girl on the witness stand was. But Martin is dead. You really need to think about what you are repeating before you repeat it.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1373126525026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 12:02:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373127035289-10</Id><Topic><Title>What have we learned today from our MSM?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372450034388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:07:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you kidding me? Those kids were prosecuted. You racists are the source of all evil, that's for sure.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1373127035289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 12:10:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373160199371-11</Id><Topic><Title>What have we learned today from our MSM?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372450034388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:07:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So far Z has acted like he was an angel from heaven standing there calmly getting hit. Oddly it is adult Zimmerman who had MMA training and was carrying a loaded gun ready to fire. Not the terriible hooded juvenile "suspect" with candy in his hand, trying to get back home in the rain. Gee, why didn't he fight back, just a little? It would have been more believable if he told what really happened. I wonder what the real story of events was, probably not in Z's favor I would bet.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1373160199371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-06 21:23:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>