<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359005464899-1</Id><Topic><Title>Premises Technicians MUST VOTE TWICE!</Title><Username>cwa_renegade</Username><Timestamp>1358830853490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:00:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Retired Technician, , talk like that you will soon finded 50% less Tech's.</Msg><Username>waynesue</Username><Timestamp>1359005464899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 00:31:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359006779806-2</Id><Topic><Title>The REAL Killer, List Of School Shootings Known To Be Linked To SSRI's</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1358886099113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:21:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You like logic so lets use some. 1. Mental problems have always existed and modern guns have been around for over a hundred years without any school shootings. The worst school murder in 1927 used dynamite. No drugs or guns. 2. School shootings and drug use seem to have developed at the same time. 3. Then it seems very likely that the use of drugs has something to do with the genesis of school shootings.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359006779806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 00:52:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359017961734-3</Id><Topic><Title>The REAL Killer, List Of School Shootings Known To Be Linked To SSRI's</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1358886099113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:21:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many of the psychiatric drugs are destroying people permanently, both mentally and physical for lifetimes(usually shortened lifetimes). I think that is the intention, and I think they have been intended to primarily destroy Whites, under the guise of pretending to help them. IMO, the mental health field is a truly evil institution. That`s why Massa Bongo Bongo and his sidekick clown Biden want to use it in their effort to take away guns(of Whites primarily). Will a veteran with PTSD who seeks psychiatric assistance risk losing the right to own a gun for the rest of their life? Is that the plan?</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359017961734</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 03:59:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359020479933-4</Id><Topic><Title>For "icky" .. Ca.Town Sch. Board Purchase !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1358990752478</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 20:25:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think war has been declared on White America and many do not have a clue it is being waged. It is a one sided war with children as one of the main targets. Schools must have guns because obviously the criminals have targeted schools as the 'enemy' for destruction, much like drone attacks target and destroy the enemy. School boards may believe they need guns to protect themselves against lone gunmen. In reality, they need the guns to enable themselves to fight an enemy using them as a primary target, an enemy engaged in a war to destroy this country. Just my opinion.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359020479933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 04:41:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359035945537-5</Id><Topic><Title>what a news!</Title><Username>ronbadger80</Username><Timestamp>1359033714046</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 08:21:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for the reply, now I subscribed and my new report just came into my mailbox! thanks one more time</Msg><Username>jonesherman118</Username><Timestamp>1359035945537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 08:59:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359036156843-6</Id><Topic><Title>Premises Technicians MUST VOTE TWICE!</Title><Username>cwa_renegade</Username><Timestamp>1358830853490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:00:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you don't complain once about the CEO's pay, perks, etc... plus wasting $4 Billion on the T-Mobile fiasco. Cry me a river.</Msg><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1359036156843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:02:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359037640226-7</Id><Topic><Title>For "icky" .. Ca.Town Sch. Board Purchase !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1358990752478</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 20:25:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “I think this country has been seized by a criminal element, possibly from a foreign nation…” – lavender Ah, yes, we’ve long lived in fear of being taken over by that powerhouse, Kenya. Or did you have someone else in mind? “…staging these shootings and killing scores of people, many of them White children, in order to take away our right to own guns…” Suggesting that the recent tragedies are a cover for another of your mindless conspiracies, reveals that you are, obviously, a very troubled individual, simply ranting in the middle of the night. Either that, or, more likely, just another racist demagogue pandering your prejudices to like minded, uneducated and frightened people looking for an easy scapegoat. Either way, you are a prime example of why a certain segment of society should not be permitted to own firearms. BTW, your anti-white conspiracy has no basis in fact: “African-American children and teens are almost five times as likely as their white peers to be killed by firearms (11.30 per 100,000 African-American youth vs. 2.31 per 100,000 white youth.” - National Center for Injury Prevention and Control, 2009 “…the Colorado movie shooting appeared more like a professional hit job, done by more than one person…Same with Sandy Hook…Schools need guns to protect themselves from what appears to me to be very well thought out attacks by professional killers under the hire of a criminal element staging a violent coup, in plain sight. With a front man who is most likely an illegal alien who hates this country`s White majority and is doing everything he possibly can to assist in its elimination.” – lavender, again Gee, lav, we can’t possibly imagine to whom you might be alluding. Oh, maybe this other quote from you will clarify it: “That`s why Massa Bongo Bongo and his sidekick clown Biden want to use it in their effort to take away guns(of Whites primarily).” While I’m sure you will deny you mean The President, I have, nevertheless, just reported you to Yahoo and higher authorities. We’ll let them figure it out. Perhaps with enough self-incrimination from you, those black helicopters you constantly are hearing will be showing up sooner than you expected.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1359037640226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:27:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359037780061-8</Id><Topic><Title>Happy MLK Day!</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358814519155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:28:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, smart #$%$, you explain why what Obama does is so often the opposite of what he says.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359037780061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:29:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359038588020-9</Id><Topic><Title>For "icky" .. Ca.Town Sch. Board Purchase !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1358990752478</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 20:25:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Jon, Have you seen any Colt LE 6940s for sale in your area? Looks like a sweet little piece. The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1359038588020</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:43:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359039941689-10</Id><Topic><Title>For "icky" .. Ca.Town Sch. Board Purchase !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1358990752478</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 20:25:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Oh you tricky tricky white boy"; when will you stop injecting race into every post you make. I agree that we are not getting the full story on many things that are going on. Benghazi is a prime example. We have not even been told why that facility existed. The US Consulate is not even in that city. If the truth were known, I suspect Obama would have to be put in jail.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359039941689</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 10:05:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359040756180-11</Id><Topic><Title>The REAL Killer, List Of School Shootings Known To Be Linked To SSRI's</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1358886099113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:21:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I presume you meant "attacked". Where did you hear that he had been warned? You must be aware that his opponent was Al Gore who never save anyone from anything. In fact "he invented the internet" and now we are all wasting our time on silly debates.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359040756180</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 10:19:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359041055708-12</Id><Topic><Title>Top 5 causes of accidental death in the US</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358687253589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Use of knives, bats, personal body weapons and blunt objects (as highlighted in red) are the tools," That's true, but what of it? That's the excuse? What if Lanza only had "Use of knives, bats, personal body weapons?" How many dead children? None probably. There is no argument for the continued availability to the public for assault weapons. Why are you guys so liberal about gun rights? Even with children mowed down, you can't acccept the fact assault weapons have no place in the public's hands. Taking them away now will save many more children, why are you against that? An no you don't know how many shootings were averted when previous gun restrictions were passed, because they never happened. There probably would have been more columbines. Because there was a columbine, doesn't mean the restrictions weren't working. Another faulty excuse. There is something wrong with people sho support no restrictions on guns.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1359041055708</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 10:24:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359041100942-13</Id><Topic><Title>Back to the mid $34's by Friday.......finally.</Title><Username>twoforfunjustask</Username><Timestamp>1358893027166</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like we are well on our way. Congratulations!!</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359041100942</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 10:25:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359046022875-14</Id><Topic><Title>Top 5 causes of accidental death in the US</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358687253589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When are you going to settle on the fact that the guns are not the reason these schoolchildren are dead, it was the guy that shot them? It was the mentally deranged shooter and his ignorant mother that allowed him access to those same weapons. A gun is just that, a gun and it can't do anything without someone to load, point and operate the gun. The people responsible for those actions are the people responsible for whatever happens next, not the gun. Taking guns away from lawful citizens will not prevent the next shooting. The criminals with their illegal guns will still be out there and will still have their guns. The big difference is that 'we' won't. When you start passing laws based on emotion versus facts and common sense, you’re heading down the wrong path.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1359046022875</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 11:47:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359046408378-15</Id><Topic><Title>Top 5 causes of accidental death in the US</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358687253589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Keep in mind no one is talking about getting rid of "guns", just particular kinds of guns." Keeping in mind of course that our government seldom stops with the first step. They, in their faulty logic assume that if they could take away one kind of gun, then what is to keep them from logically taking away ALL of them? Nothing is there to stop them from going further because they hold themselves accountable to no one. Once a law is passed that the voters don't like, it is too late to do anything about it at the next election...Obama's health care bill is a prime example, not only did the majority of the people not want it, most of those voting for it didn't understand it even if they had read it. Gun laws, changes to immigration, etc. are just the next steps. Meanwhile, the tax code is still so convoluted no one can really understand it, the unemployment rate is still higher than ever and our economy is still in the tank, but let’s not worry about that, we have more important things to fight and argue about. Yeah, good government is getting harder and harder to find. Slippery slope anyone?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359046408378</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 11:53:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359046986782-16</Id><Topic><Title>Top 5 causes of accidental death in the US</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358687253589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And there are many differing opinions regarding who is at fault in a gun death, the gun, or the shooter. So what is your point? Dead is dead regardless of what you call the cause. There was no ‘switch’, you kill a kid in school with a gun or you kill one in a doctor’s office the cause is really irrelevant.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1359046986782</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 12:03:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359050571228-17</Id><Title>If you believe in charts</Title><Msg>it is time to buy. The Stochastic has turned up and the price is at the lower half of the Bollinger Bands. The only signal not yet saying buy is the Relative Strength. http://finance.yahoo.com/echarts?s=T#symbol=t;range=1y;compare=;indicator=bollinger+sma%28200,50%29+volume+stochasticslow+rsi;charttype=candlestick;crosshair=on;ohlcvalues=1;logscale=off;source=undefined</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359050571228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 13:02:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359051527373-18</Id><Topic><Title>Top 5 causes of accidental death in the US</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358687253589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “Keeping in mind of course that our government seldom stops with the first step.” Oh, for goodness sakes, when will you ever stop with such nonsense.? That’s right, any regulation is bad regulation. What a crock. “…if they could take away one kind of gun, then what is to keep them from logically taking away ALL of them?” Well, let’s see…how about that the new regulation would specifically set what’s allowed and not allowed, and very specifically confirm it has no intention of overturning your 2nd amendment rights. That probably isn’t good enough for you, because you obviously are of the mindset of a government conspiracy against everything you represent. Unfortunately, just because you cry, “but what’s to prevent them from doing this…or doing that”…doesn’t mean a thing to logical people. Murder is often a capital offense…Cancel that…’what’s to prevent them from making shop lifting punishable by execution?” Great logic, Winnie. Have you ever really debated beyond your cubicle? “Nothing is there to stop them from going further because they hold themselves accountable to no one.” Another bizarre statement. Law abiding citizens hold government accountable to the citizenry. Government, IS, in fact, citizens just like you and me. It gets really old having you wacko Tea Party types constantly suggesting that our duly elected government officials are in your opinion, comparable to foreign enemies upon whom you want to wage your fundamentalist war. Grow up and accept that you lost the election. “Gun laws, changes to immigration, etc. are just the next steps…” The next steps to what?…oh, right a Marxist takeover. Trotsky’s outside your home right now stealing your hubcaps. Grab your guns. “Meanwhile, the tax code is still so convoluted no one can really understand it…” Excuse me??? The tax codes presently favor the wealthy and corporations. Yes, people are trying to do something about that which was a prime issue in the last election. Who do you think continues to fight that tooth and nail? (Hint: look in the mirror.) “…the unemployment rate is still higher than ever…” total Bull. ‘…and our economy is still in the tank…” – but slowly recovering from your trickle down scheme, despite your desire to obstruct anything to benefit anyone other than the one-percenters. “Yeah, good government is getting harder and harder to find.” Oh, right, you look for good government. Sure you do. If you Wall Street pimps had your way, ANY government would be hard to find. Your laissez-faire attitude fits your opening statement: “Keeping in mind of course that our government seldom stops with the first step…if we allow any regulation to Wall Street, the next thing you’ll know they’ll want us to tell the truth about insider trading, merger arbitrage, derivatives, and the asymmetrical information which permits us to exploit the situation… then where will we be.?” “Slippery slope, anyone?” It appears to me that you guys have created your own slippery slope, and your downward spiral will continue until you change your tune. Fighting reasonable gun control legislation is a prime example of you being totally out of touch with a majority of Americans.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1359051527373</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 13:18:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359052846534-19</Id><Topic><Title>Premises Technicians MUST VOTE TWICE!</Title><Username>cwa_renegade</Username><Timestamp>1358830853490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:00:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure the Union member head count is a big concern for both sides of negotiations. Which is another reason for the CWA to get their heads out of their butts and focus on the local concerns of each unit. The Tulsa unit is lacking, as I hear most others are. This, in my opinion, is due to the pressure from the regional head quarters. Like I have been saying for years, the Union is as much a business as AT&amp;T. But the CWA needs to start worrying about where their members are going. If they are not careful, someone may be smart enough to contact the IBEW or Teamsters for representation. Do me a favor av8lover, and pass that on up to your president.</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1359052846534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 13:40:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359052875125-20</Id><Topic><Title>For "icky" .. Ca.Town Sch. Board Purchase !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1358990752478</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 20:25:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How you see the need for schools to purchase AR-15s to defend themselves as some sort of victory is beyond me. I would prefer the school not need them, and I would prefer those children not live in communities where they may get shot. This is a failure, Jon. A reversion to the state of nature, a failure of our government and our civilization. People who need AR-15s to go to school or leave the house are not free. They live in fear. Those guns from the Fast and Furious operation were purchased legally by straw buyers, Jon (Agents did not purchase them, they tracked the purchasers). It was illegal to smuggle them into Mexico, but it was not illegal for those gangs and druglords to purchase them in the United States. They did not need to smuggle them back into California from Mexico. If gangs and druglords in the United States want AR-15s, they merely need to go to Walmart and purchase them. According to the BATF, 70% of the guns seized in Mexico from 2007 to 2011 were purchased legally in the US. We are creating and feeding the drug gang violence that make it necessary for schools in southern California to be armed with AR-15s. A situation which you seem very proud of.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359052875125</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 13:41:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359053097680-21</Id><Title>When everyone is positive, it is time to SELL!!!!</Title><Msg>TRUTH/FALSEEE???</Msg><Username>mlg4044</Username><Timestamp>1359053097680</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 13:44:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359053155579-22</Id><Title>looks weak today</Title><Msg>not much conviction into earnings</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1359053155579</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 13:45:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359056819543-23</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Insiders SELLING?! (SHOCKING REPORT)</Title><Username>ashley.haggerty</Username><Timestamp>1359055272223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks !</Msg><Username>william.wise72</Username><Timestamp>1359056819543</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:46:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359057084353-24</Id><Topic><Title>For "icky" .. Ca.Town Sch. Board Purchase !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1358990752478</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 20:25:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jon, you're speaking to Ricky: King of the Idiots! I'm done arguing with that nonsensical Jerk!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1359057084353</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:51:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359058088568-25</Id><Topic><Title>For "icky" .. Ca.Town Sch. Board Purchase !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1358990752478</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 20:25:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... And, par for the course, we have another brilliant response from jon, representing those advocating the elimination of public education. “(para-phrasing)” = paraphrasing “spontainous” = spontaneous out-burst = outburst OH contrare' = au contraire Madam “Sec. of State” = Madam Secretary fore-sight = foresight “You and the Administration LIED to America…” Is that a fact, jon? So you were actually there to know what happened better than anyone in the government? Would you care to give us one credible source beyond you hearing it from Glen Beck or Ann Coulter? “ya snot-nosed jerk” Clueless, classless and clammering for attention. I’ll bet your dog spells better than you do. What’s his name, btw.? “Phi-dough”? “ “Snu-pee”? “Roe-v.-Ver”?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1359058088568</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:08:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359059516036-26</Id><Topic><Title>When everyone is positive, it is time to SELL!!!!</Title><Username>mlg4044</Username><Timestamp>1359053097680</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 13:44:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>both</Msg><Username>cangelosi_g</Username><Timestamp>1359059516036</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:31:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359060173479-27</Id><Topic><Title>For "icky" .. Ca.Town Sch. Board Purchase !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1358990752478</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 20:25:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ANOTHER "FACT" Finally, Jon figures out the proper use of quotation marks. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359060173479</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:42:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359060350316-28</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Insiders SELLING?! (SHOCKING REPORT)</Title><Username>ashley.haggerty</Username><Timestamp>1359055272223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blessed is he that siteth upon 480 volt for he shall rise again.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359060350316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:45:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359060470809-29</Id><Topic><Title>Top 5 causes of accidental death in the US</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358687253589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"his ignorant mother that allowed him access to those same weapons." Which begs the question, why did his ignorant mother have access to military-style combat rifles? "Taking guns away from lawful citizens will not prevent the next shooting." Are you sure? Taking military style assault rifles away from one ignorant mother would have prevented the last one. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359060470809</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:47:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359060543574-30</Id><Topic><Title>Top 5 causes of accidental death in the US</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358687253589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you just type "Congress sux!" It would be about as useful and save everyone alot of time.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359060543574</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:49:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359060832053-31</Id><Topic><Title>The REAL Killer, List Of School Shootings Known To Be Linked To SSRI's</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1358886099113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:21:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Will a "few" fall through the cracks" Of course they will Jon. So why give them access to AR-15s?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359060832053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:53:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359060860376-32</Id><Topic><Title>looks weak today</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1359053155579</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 13:45:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Closing in the green for the third day in a row is a lot better than it had been doing. Volume has been dropping each of those days indicating a lack of demand as the price goes up. Is the earnings report after the close?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359060860376</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:54:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359060974038-33</Id><Title>Added to my watch list</Title><Msg>T has found support at $33.35. On the upside, the resistance is located at $35.05. 76% chance up at foxchart website.</Msg><Username>msilcpom</Username><Timestamp>1359060974038</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:56:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359061469585-34</Id><Title>miss</Title><Msg>hmmmmmm</Msg><Username>govinsider</Username><Timestamp>1359061469585</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 16:04:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359061641402-35</Id><Topic><Title>looks weak today</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1359053155579</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 13:45:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>flat today</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1359061641402</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 16:07:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359061944512-36</Id><Topic><Title>The REAL Killer, List Of School Shootings Known To Be Linked To SSRI's</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1358886099113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:21:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's not logic. It's not even factual. What on earth makes you think there were no drugs in 1927? They put cocaine in Coca-Cola back then for christs' sake. Lithium, Opium, you name it, were widely available and used and abused. But even if your "FACTS" (as jon would put it) are true, and school shootings and drug use increase at the same time, that is no indication that drugs cause school shootings, or that school shootings cause drugs. The famous example of this fallacy is the actual fact that both ice cream sales and crime increase in the summer months. Does that mean that ice cream causes crime? Or crime causes ice cream sales? Nope. It means it's hot out. Whatever drives people to commit mass shootings, banning assault rifles means they will not be able to kill as many people in as short amount of time as they have been able to do since the assault rifle ban was lifted. Now there's a relationship you should look into. But the idea here that we can prevent random violence by properly prescribing anti-depressants is just ludicrous. It is just a lame attempt to obfuscate by the NRA.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359061944512</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 16:12:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359061961063-37</Id><Topic><Title>miss</Title><Username>govinsider</Username><Timestamp>1359061469585</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 16:04:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"earnings" are old economy. Growing 2% with high single-digits forecast? Who cares? Dudley, Yellen and The Bernack are printing.</Msg><Username>jjjinglehimersmith</Username><Timestamp>1359061961063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 16:12:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359062063413-38</Id><Topic><Title>The REAL Killer, List Of School Shootings Known To Be Linked To SSRI's</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1358886099113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:21:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Many of the psychiatric drugs are destroying people permanently," Is that what happened to you? Maybe you've been white genocided and you don't even know it! You should ask the people at Captain D's.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359062063413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 16:14:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359062084177-39</Id><Title>DOW stalwart + Extreme Printing - who cares about 'earnings'?</Title><Msg>Another Bernack on Crack aftermarket rally</Msg><Username>jjjinglehimersmith</Username><Timestamp>1359062084177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 16:14:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359062099747-40</Id><Topic><Title>miss</Title><Username>govinsider</Username><Timestamp>1359061469585</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 16:04:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two cents is not much of a miss and T seems to be taking off in the after market. In this case I think the after market trading is significant.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359062099747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 16:14:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359062445598-41</Id><Topic><Title>miss</Title><Username>govinsider</Username><Timestamp>1359061469585</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 16:04:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>REVENUE.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1359062445598</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 16:20:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359063001104-42</Id><Title>T's Report Looks Good</Title><Msg>Besides overall revenue growth, the wireline performance looks encouraging and the 6% share buyback is a nice kicker. That's more than the 5% IBM usually does. T has the added incentive of its relatively big dividend payout for buybacks. I hope they keep it up. It's timely for T to start reducing share count before revenue growth in the US flattens out. If T grows revenue next year close to 2% they should be able to buy back a lot more stock -- compared to IBM's flat revenue growth.</Msg><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1359063001104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 16:30:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359063310724-43</Id><Topic><Title>looks weak today</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1359053155579</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 13:45:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>..make that down a bit today.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1359063310724</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 16:35:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359064823494-44</Id><Topic><Title>T's Report Looks Good</Title><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1359063001104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 16:30:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The T keeps trying to entice me with junk mail to sign up for cable and phone service. What a huge waste of money those mailings have been. Especially because they don't serve my area. They are dummies, killing trees to reach customers like me who will probably never be customers because their area isn't served. Every two weeks, or so...like clockwork...junk mail. DUH, AT&amp;T.</Msg><Username>rimmdiva</Username><Timestamp>1359064823494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:00:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359064960189-45</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Insiders SELLING?! (SHOCKING REPORT)</Title><Username>ashley.haggerty</Username><Timestamp>1359055272223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DANGEROUS SCAM VIRUS REPORTED !</Msg><Username>alphonite</Username><Timestamp>1359064960189</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:02:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359066875184-46</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Insiders SELLING?! (SHOCKING REPORT)</Title><Username>ashley.haggerty</Username><Timestamp>1359055272223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow! surprisingly good one, thanks</Msg><Username>johnbussell595</Username><Timestamp>1359066875184</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:34:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359067083825-47</Id><Topic><Title>what a news!</Title><Username>ronbadger80</Username><Timestamp>1359033714046</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 08:21:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow! surprisingly good one, thanks</Msg><Username>johnbussell595</Username><Timestamp>1359067083825</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:38:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359067164052-48</Id><Topic><Title>Back to the mid $34's by Friday.......finally.</Title><Username>twoforfunjustask</Username><Timestamp>1358893027166</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks wilkes71.</Msg><Username>twoforfunjustask</Username><Timestamp>1359067164052</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:39:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359067506501-49</Id><Topic><Title>Back to the mid $34's by Friday.......finally.</Title><Username>twoforfunjustask</Username><Timestamp>1358893027166</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks again wilkes71. I've been following the charts along with my other DD efforts and I have to agree with your previous post today. There appears to be a "buy" signal forming although waiting for relative strength. Good luck and thanks again for your kindness.</Msg><Username>twoforfunjustask</Username><Timestamp>1359067506501</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:45:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359068952096-50</Id><Topic><Title>The REAL Killer, List Of School Shootings Known To Be Linked To SSRI's</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1358886099113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:21:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will you liberals ever give up on blaming Bush for everything? Obama has been President for four years and has succeeded in only making things worse but you wn't hear any of that.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1359068952096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 18:09:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359070033571-51</Id><Title>Strong Growth in Wireless and U-verse Drives Revenue and Adjusted Earnings Per Share Growth in AT&amp;T's Fourth-Quarter Results</Title><Msg>Strong Growth in Wireless and U-verse Drives Revenue and Adjusted Earnings Per Share Growth in AT&amp;T's Fourth-Quarter Results Full-Year 2012: Strong Earnings, Record Cash Flows, $23 Billion Returned to Shareowners 2013 Outlook: Solid Revenue Gains, EPS Growth in Upper-Single Digits with Continuing Free Cash Flow Strength Dallas, Texas, January 24, 2013 ShareThis $(0.68) diluted EPS in the fourth quarter compared to $(1.12) diluted EPS in the year-ago period. Excluding significant items and adjusting for the sale of Advertising Solutions, EPS was $0.44 versus $0.40, up 10 percent year over year For full-year 2012, excluding significant items and adjusting for the sale of Advertising Solutions, EPS was up 8.5 percent year over year Consolidated revenues of $32.6 billion, up 0.2 percent versus reported results for the year-earlier period, and up 2.8 percent excluding Advertising Solutions and Superstorm Sandy impact Record cash from operations of $39.2 billion and record free cash flow for full-year 2012 $4.4 billion in stock buybacks in the fourth quarter with 126.6 million shares repurchased; for the full year, the company repurchased 371 million shares, or about 6 percent of shares outstanding, for $12.8 billion $23 billion returned to shareowners in 2012 through dividends and share repurchases Record Smartphone Sales and Strong Wireless Postpaid Net Adds Wireless revenues up 5.7 percent versus the year-ago quarter; wireless service revenues up 4.2 percent 780,000 wireless postpaid net adds, largest increase in three years; 1.1 million increase in total net wireless subscribers Record smartphone sales of 10.2 million, the most ever sold by any U.S. carrier; postpaid smartphone customer base now 47.1 million, up 2.5 million from third-quarter 2012 Smartphones 89 percent of postpaid phone sales Postpaid wireless subscriber ARPU (average monthly revenues per subscriber) up 1.9 percent to $64.98 Wireline Consumer Revenue Growth Accelerates Wireline consumer revenue growth continues to accelerate, with revenues up 3.0 percent versus the year-earlier period, their strongest growth in more than four years 36.3 percent growth in U-verse® revenues 8.0 million total U-verse subscribers (TV and high speed Internet) in service; a net gain of 192,000 U-verse TV subscribers and 609,000 high speed Internet subscribers Total wireline broadband data ARPU up more than 10 percent year over year Note: AT&amp;T's fourth-quarter earnings conference call will be broadcast live via the Internet at 4:30 p.m. ET on Thursday, January 24, 2013, attDOTcom/gen/press-room?pid=23672&amp;cdvn=news&amp;newsarticleid=35937&amp;mapcode=corporate|</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359070033571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 18:27:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359070610986-52</Id><Topic><Title>The REAL Killer, List Of School Shootings Known To Be Linked To SSRI's</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1358886099113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:21:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>many people should not be on these medications. they are because they are an economic pipeline to all the various social agencies and dr.s involved. it's a money racket plain and simple</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1359070610986</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 18:36:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359073464465-53</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Insiders SELLING?! (SHOCKING REPORT)</Title><Username>ashley.haggerty</Username><Timestamp>1359055272223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Insiders" are ALWAYS selling shares. They are also ALWAYS buying shares. I use DCA with my dividends and over the years ( about 55 years) it has given me a much better return than any other method I've tried. In 11929 T sold for $300. In 1937 it sold for $70. But, it paid the same $9 per share dividend. It eventually went back up to about $150. Had you hung on for 20 years and reinvested those dividends you would have more than covered losses and made an over all decent return.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1359073464465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 19:24:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359075036992-54</Id><Title>Women in combat</Title><Msg>I wonder if the fellas in position of power are really doing women a favor by allowing them to serve in combat? It could eventually mean that if women are deemed capable and competent, they will not only be allowed to serve in combat, they will be required to. That will change the game for many women in the military I would think. I`ve read that most of the casualties in the decades long illegal unnecessary evil middle eastern wars have been White men. Is there also a ban on non White men serving in combat? If there is, maybe they should first lift that ban instead of filling a possible shortage of combat soldiers with women. It will be interesting to see what the demographics of women serving in combat will be. Hopefully it will not be yet further genocide of the White race. We are after all disappearing as planned and eventually will not exist as a race. We don`t need any further means to eliminate us, especially not in unnecessary wars for a foreign nation. Regardless, is this really what most men want? Women defending them?</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359075036992</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 19:50:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359076520080-55</Id><Topic><Title>Are some of the gun control instigators sending a message?</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359074249688</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 19:37:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As a mater of fact, most victims of drive by shootings are people of color, many not the intended target BTW. Retail , wholesale what dam m difference does it make MFer?</Msg><Username>anncisback</Username><Timestamp>1359076520080</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 20:15:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359077100994-56</Id><Topic><Title>Women in combat</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359075036992</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 19:50:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Israeli women soldiers are home defense. When it comes time to send out combat forces to meet any enemy they stay home. They have their backs against the sea -- they know better. The men worry about them instead of focusing on opposing forces.</Msg><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1359077100994</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 20:25:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359077576790-57</Id><Topic><Title>Women in combat</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359075036992</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 19:50:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does this have to do with "T"? This is a stock board.</Msg><Username>asalwaysurconfused</Username><Timestamp>1359077576790</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 20:32:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359077610409-58</Id><Topic><Title>Premises Technicians MUST VOTE TWICE!</Title><Username>cwa_renegade</Username><Timestamp>1358830853490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:00:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For all the griping you do, have you attended any meetings, got involved on committees, run for a union office; or just sit around whining?</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1359077610409</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 20:33:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359081792933-59</Id><Topic><Title>Premises Technicians MUST VOTE TWICE!</Title><Username>cwa_renegade</Username><Timestamp>1358830853490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:00:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>av8lover, to answer your question below, yes, yes, yes,and yes</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1359081792933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 21:43:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359082914639-60</Id><Topic><Title>NETFLIX!</Title><Username>roach_sons</Username><Timestamp>1359080930673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 21:28:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What???</Msg><Username>asalwaysurconfused</Username><Timestamp>1359082914639</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 22:01:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359085349650-61</Id><Topic><Title>Women in combat</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359075036992</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 19:50:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Is there also a ban on non White men serving in combat?" No Lavendar, there is no such ban. The US military will take women, homosexuals, africans, asians, hispanics, white people and even illegal immigrants and all of them defend their country in combat and many of them have lost their lives in combat. But do you know what the US military won't take? Racist sacks of sh** like you.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359085349650</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 22:42:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359086967776-62</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Insiders SELLING?! (SHOCKING REPORT)</Title><Username>ashley.haggerty</Username><Timestamp>1359055272223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sellling now.</Msg><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1359086967776</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 23:09:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359087724047-63</Id><Topic><Title>Women in combat</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359075036992</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 19:50:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Israeli women soldiers are home defense. " No. Women have served in combat roles in the IDF since 2000.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359087724047</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 23:22:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359089261192-64</Id><Topic><Title>Women in combat</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359075036992</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 19:50:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're posting on the wrong board.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1359089261192</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 23:47:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359089617711-65</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Insiders SELLING?! (SHOCKING REPORT)</Title><Username>ashley.haggerty</Username><Timestamp>1359055272223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll think I'll be retired in the year 11929.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1359089617711</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 23:53:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>