<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-25"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366889852901-1</Id><Title>T way overpriced here and heading lower. PE way too high and too much debt</Title><Msg>see you all @ 34 again soon</Msg><Username>tracker57888</Username><Timestamp>1366889852901</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:37:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366889856523-2</Id><Topic><Title>No need to jump off bridges...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366813869908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 10:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? I need to comment on a 25 cent kick off the bottom on a day when the PPS is down about $2? And yes, I did notice as I bought some 2015 leap call options. GL</Msg><Username>wcsg122</Username><Timestamp>1366889856523</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:37:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366892720457-3</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“Oh dear! Oh no! Say it isn't so!...Obama administration had advance warning on Fisker" – Frog boy Oh, dear! Oh no! Say it isn’t so! While your right wing blog sources have already retracted the last bunch of nonsense you posted here about the Saudi terrorist being deported, apparently you chose, instead, to just keep throwing out more of your fictionalized versions of events as you see them. Why not post the other viewpoint of the article, which also included this…people are smart enough to decipher their own versions of the truth without your blatant and pathetic birther/swiftboat versions of events. (From the story)… “Aoife McCarthy, a spokeswoman for the Energy Department, said the June 2010 email was taken out of context. "The document shows that one person at a meeting discussed the possibility that Fisker might not meet a financial commitment" required by the Energy Department, McCarthy said in an email. The department received the needed certification five days later and subsequently made the loan payment, she said. The documents were released Wednesday by the House Oversight and Government Reform committee, which is looking into the federal loan to the troubled car maker. Continuing financial and production problems has led to the lay-off of three-fourths of its workers. White House spokesman Jay Carney accused congressional Republicans of leaking the documents in an effort to embarrass the Obama administration. "The committee's efforts to stoke false controversy by selectively leaking a few out-of-context documents just do not stand up to scrutiny," Carney said Wednesday. A top Energy Department official said the department acted "decisively" to protect taxpayers' interests since Fisker's financial woes became clear nearly two years ago. Nicholas Whitcombe, former acting director of the car loan program, said the department stopped payments to Fisker in June 2011 after the company failed to meet milestones required in the loan agreement. Since then, "the department has continued to communicate with Fisker as it has sought to revise its business plan and achieve profitability," Whitcombe told the committee. The Energy Department is "committed to ensuring that the taxpayers' interests are protected to the maximum extent possible," he added. But Rep. Jim Jordan*, chairman of the Oversight subcommittee on economic growth and regulation, said it is hard to understand why the Energy Department ever thought Fisker was a viable company that should receive taxpayer money. "The Obama administration owes the American taxpayer an explanation as to why this bad loan was made in the first place, and what they are going to do to minimize the loss that taxpayers face," said Jordan, R-Ohio. Rep. Elijah Cummings, D-Md., said the loan program, which has benefited car companies such as Ford, Nissan and Tesla, was exceeding expectations. The Fisker loan represents less than 2 percent of the car-loan program, Cummings and other Democrats said. "There is no evidence that the (Energy) department did anything wrong with this loan," Cummings said. "No evidence that politics played any part in the award to Fisker." – end * Note: Rep. Jim Jordan is a former state wrestling champion elected to the House from the most Republican District in Ohio. He’s also a darling of the far right. He seems to have concerns about taxpayers’ money, (in this case 171 million). Not surprisingly, however, he has no problems with arguing against the Pentagon’s recommendations to save 3 BILLION dollars on tank production, because the tank plant is in his own District. Frog, we’ll be awaiting your next editorial of concern for all of us….something like this…“Oh, dear, Rep. Jordan wants to blow 3 billion dollars when the Pentagon, who should know a bit more about tanks than a grappler turned politician, wants to waste 3 Billion dollars!! In your heart, you know I’m a hypocrite. (Let’s see here…$3,000,000,000 minus $171,000,000 equals 2 Billion, Eight Hundred and Twenty-Nine million worth of hypocrisy.) Ribbit!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366892720457</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366895531154-4</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are really running out of straws to grasp. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366895531154</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:12:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366896658800-5</Id><Topic><Title>T way overpriced here and heading lower. PE way too high and too much debt</Title><Username>tracker57888</Username><Timestamp>1366889852901</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:37:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The market looks ahead while you look in the rear view mirror. The forward P/E is 13.67. As for debt, AT&amp;T has an A- bond rating so you are by yourself in that also.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1366896658800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366897062030-6</Id><Topic><Title>T way overpriced here and heading lower. PE way too high and too much debt</Title><Username>tracker57888</Username><Timestamp>1366889852901</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:37:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wilkie, where do these fools come from? What can possibly be their motive for posting stupid krap like that every day? These Trollers put out a comment that makes no sense like Googles going to 100. Or aapl will be 50. The only thing I can think of is the responses they get fills a serious void in their social lives. This idiot goes straight to ignore.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366897062030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366897248066-7</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, this administration will always leave plenty of 'straw' to grasp. They continue to get caught in lies and the MSM helps them out. The latest is the refusal to honor a house subpoena for the rest of the fast and furious documents. The problem is that when the judge rules they must comply, most of those documents will be gone! This administration is nowhere near the ‘transparent’ administration that was promised. This AG needs to be in jail or at least fired. The Justice Departments track record since he took over is more controversy than justice.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1366897248066</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:40:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366897901041-8</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wilkie, in my time on the job, I was at every major company you can name. Both public and government. In the course of my work, I heard #$%$&amp;moaning as I went about my business. Bitterness is pervasive in any segment of business, whether it's the janitor or a mid-level or above level. I couldn't help overhearing all the griping about everything from "he/she's so incompetent...how did they EVER get promoted" to "I can't wait to get out of this place for________(fill in the blank for various reasons) My conclusion. Very few employes at most levels are dissatisfied with their jobs whether unionized or not. I must have been an exception. Never did I once not want to get up and make the commute to put in my time. That's not to say every fellow employee or manager were people I'd have a beer with after hours, but there weren't many I truly did not care for.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366897901041</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:51:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366897947337-9</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. You're trying to play pin the scandal on Obama but there's nothing there. A few days ago House Republicans disgraced themselves by releasing a highly partisan report basically claiming that the robo-signature attached to State Department letterhead is the same as a real signature. I don't know about you but where I'm from when your sent to do a job you do it. You don't spend your time #$%$ around trying to bring down the boss. I'm sick of it. The American people are sick of it. It is a disgrace and you should be ashamed.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366897947337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366898352533-10</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many stories can you tell in a day? Nothing better to do?</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1366898352533</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:59:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366898936614-11</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without union dues, it is very doubtful we would be compensated as well as we are. The politics however, bothers me. Especially the overwhelming financial contributions that finds its way to a certain political party. Other than that, I have sat at grievances that saved jobs, recouped back pay or other monetary disputes, settled sexual harassment situations, unfair overtime procedures and so many union/management contractual violations that I can't even remember the specifics. We have to part ways on the topic of union or union-free work environs. So while there are drawbacks to a union shop, this can be said. No union member can be let go on the whim of a boss. Just that simple protection validates unions. Now public unions. That's a whole different matter...</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366898936614</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:08:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366899201385-12</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dave what is O.R.T.T.</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1366899201385</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366899446197-13</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining VZ</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366853726268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 21:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I already gave you my take on this Wilkie in response to your direct question to me. Maybe your Y.L. Garage didn't need a union, but there are bigger companies out there that do.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366899446197</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:17:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366899482753-14</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes I agree with u i retired from at t worked hard was not a slacker ....have a nice retire ment compared to many i know had 30 years job went to other side of state so i retired they buy out a lot of employees...they have many rules to work by it was not easy .....thankful for all ...saved on my own as well not many boomers have ...they want 2 houses a new trk and new harley no end to what they are in depth for ...glad t is rebounding a bit own 1200 shrs hope we hit over 38 near furutre hated the drop</Msg><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1366899482753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:18:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366899570564-15</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, sounds like he couldn't pass the test to get hired.</Msg><Username>cliffsoudil</Username><Timestamp>1366899570564</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:19:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366900087184-16</Id><Topic><Title>No need to jump off bridges...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366813869908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 10:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great hedge against inflation. At the rate they are printing $$ it will probably take $100 to buy a share of AT&amp;T in 2015. Forgive me for getting so excited about that 25 cent move but it made me $500.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1366900087184</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:28:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366902244450-17</Id><Topic><Title>T on sale great buy</Title><Username>catspaw33129</Username><Timestamp>1366828658359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 14:37:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you bought on margin, you have already made a pretty nice bundle. This is one of the most predictable moves that I have seen in a long time. Buying yesterday was a no brainer.</Msg><Username>gman310</Username><Timestamp>1366902244450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366903244173-18</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“The Justice Departments track record since he took over is more controversy than justice. “ - Golf boy You’re aware, of course, that Holder was bi-partisanly and overwhelmingly approved by the Senate Judiciary Committee, 17 to 2, and then confirmed by a vote of 75 to 21. However, I assume you’d prefer someone whose credentials are beyond reproach, like say maybe, Ed Meese, John Ashcroft or Alberto Gonzales.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366903244173</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:20:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366903932374-19</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think we all have a pretty clear picture of the drill. froggy spends his morning consuming large amounts of media. It's likely he is unable to concentrate on anything substantive for very long so he bounces from CNN to Fox to thumbing through copious amounts of largely redundant "print" media. When he has finished consuming, it is time to regurgitate. He chooses a couple of items to cut and paste, puts nice little bullets on them so that they look like they could be products of original thought and posts them on Yahoo message boards. Cutting and pasting takes much of froggy's afternoon. I suppose that there is also a lot of distracted upping and downing for important tasks like seeing if the mailman has come yet, whether anything has mysteriously appeared in the refrigerator since last time he looked, etc., and whether that lump on his face is growing or if it is the same size it was 25 minutes ago. And for his significant contribution to society, we pay for his medical care and keep a SS check coming to him every month. Waste upon waste.</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1366903932374</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:32:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366906273874-20</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you give him waaaaaaay to much credit. He goes to WND, picks a random story, and reposts it as described.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366906273874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:11:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366907258132-21</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You obviously like to be screwed over by crooked pols and the ones they hand YOUR money to. OR, you're a paid shill for the thieves.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1366907258132</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:27:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366907363870-22</Id><Topic><Title>T on sale great buy</Title><Username>catspaw33129</Username><Timestamp>1366828658359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 14:37:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is it so hard to believe someone bought over 9000 shares??? Many, many, many individuals own more than 9000 shares of T (including me - my largest holding by far). What's the big deal? There's 5.4 BILLION shares of T out there - somebody has to own them - lol.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1366907363870</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366907538218-23</Id><Topic><Title>T way overpriced here and heading lower. PE way too high and too much debt</Title><Username>tracker57888</Username><Timestamp>1366889852901</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:37:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My guess is he shorted yesterday and is really hurting now. He may even believe his post will have an affect on the stock price.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1366907538218</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:32:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366907618322-24</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you're right. Froggie is a shill. But I think he does it for free.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366907618322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:33:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366907975276-25</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know the new hurricane season is approaching us in June ,lets select a few names for the storms shall we...arnold...bert...christopher...danny...echo...francis...gert...henny...ivan...jenny...katharina (like katrina)etc. etc. if we do have an echo hurricane I guess the Saffir-Simpson scale would have to be raised to a category 6 rating because of all the WIND that storm would BLOW !!!!</Msg><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1366907975276</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:39:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366908348821-26</Id><Topic><Title>$37.25</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1364849217249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 16:46:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well she's back at $37.25 - right where it was on April 1st (and everyone was happy at the time). So 3 weeks later and ready to move up again from here.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1366908348821</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366909687714-27</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I" think you have best(s) sense of "humor" on this Board..(!!) "I" is very glad to see you "making" (teehee) funny funny post again..(!!)..grins..</Msg><Username>jon3retiree</Username><Timestamp>1366909687714</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366910388638-28</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How many stories can you tell in a day? Nothing better to do?" How many times can you deny reality in a day, such as clain Obama is not a serial liar, or that he's competent?</Msg><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1366910388638</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:19:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366912312393-29</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems that those who can no longer get union benefits are very envious of those who did. All of your union bashing will not change the fact that unions are why this country is where it is today. Thank God for unions!!</Msg><Username>gman310</Username><Timestamp>1366912312393</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:51:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366916326436-30</Id><Title>8 to 1 bid to ask....why is it stuck at 27.23 should</Title><Msg>be at 27.31 R1 ?????????????????</Msg><Username>scooterbenz</Username><Timestamp>1366916326436</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:58:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366916569548-31</Id><Topic><Title>8 to 1 bid to ask....why is it stuck at 27.23 should</Title><Username>scooterbenz</Username><Timestamp>1366916326436</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:58:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>37.23..............................mistake</Msg><Username>scooterbenz</Username><Timestamp>1366916569548</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:02:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366917080404-32</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You’re aware, of course, that Holder was bi-partisanly and overwhelmingly approved by the Senate Judiciary Committee? Yes, and they all make mistakes. He will turn out to be one of the worst. I would take almost anyone in place of this arrogant, lying, racist fool.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1366917080404</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:11:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366918149600-33</Id><Title>Has congress finally gone too far?</Title><Msg>I don't know about you, but I love my Obama phone. I love my high tech smart phone. I love the free text messaging, the camera and the 100 free minutes. I loved the fact that the government made it so easy for me and my 6 million friends to get this wonderful service regardless of our eligibility. And now I find out that there are 50 members in congress who are trying to take away my free phone. Where is their compassion? Where is their sense of fairness? How many poor children are going to go to bed sad when they can't get their text messages or pictures of their "besties"? Please call your congress person now, and tell them not to vote to cut off my free phone service. Thanks this is real important. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366918149600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:29:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366918373794-34</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well Whop, here is what the acronym stands for: Order of Repeatermen and Tollboard Testmen. The ORTT personnel were very specialized at one time. Their genesis goes back to when Ma Bell used smoke signals and tin cans attached to rope to communicate. Just kidding Whop. It was a very small unionized part of the Bell System that probably has gone the way of ancient analog technology. I'm not sure if they are still representing members, as they probably merged with the CWA. The contracts were negotiated separately from the much bigger CWA and had basically the same benefits. The main difference was dues. ORTT paid about 75% less than our CWA brothers. I was proud to serve as a steward and will never forget the occasional battles we had with management.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366918373794</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366918876744-35</Id><Topic><Title>Has congress finally gone too far?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366918149600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:29:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next thing you know they will want to take away our 99 weeks of Loafing, I mean unemployment!!!</Msg><Username>traderal23</Username><Timestamp>1366918876744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366919267444-36</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said Gman! Union strong.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366919267444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:47:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366919626859-37</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dave I hate to guess at your age, but I was with AT&amp;T/SWBT for 30 years and don't remember having that in the Oklahoma area. It's an interesting part of history. Before I retired from Installation/Repair 6 months ago, management had done away with so many jobs that we were doing more and more duties. In smaller towns they were about to start having us do our own Central Office wiring, that was when I said enough is enough. We had already lost our supplies attendants who made sure we were stocked and inventory was maintained. They were expecting productivity to increase but didn't give us credit for the work. Not to be offensive to anyone, but I blamed the union for letting it happen. Nobody would put their foot down and say NO_WAY! The word SAFETY got lost in the books somewhere, and we were expected to do 14 hours of work in 8 hours. All of that pressure to be more productive is why I believe in the stock today. T is weeding out the old slow farts and highering younger high producing ones. You and worked when Safety was first, Quality was second and Productivity was third. The AT&amp;T of today has swapped Safety for Productivity. And it appears to be in all of the phone companies. I've talked to Verizon and Sprint technicians that are going thru the same thing.</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1366919626859</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:53:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366919979540-38</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beau, times have changed and T is not what it used to be. Regardless, it still offers a lot to middle class workers that has pretty good job security. Maybe not new-hires, but once you rack up some years, your in to stay unless you don't follow the rules. You know what I mean. Tardiness, absences, stretching coffee breaks, etc. You are so right about how making a good wage leads to excess spending. I did as you did. Maxed the 401 plus supplemental and still contributed to a self-directed IRA every year. It's really comes down to this. It isn't necessarily how much you make...it's what you do with what you earn that matters. Maybe someone else said that before, but I lay claim to it. As for T stock price? I'm not overly concerned about it. The dividends allow me to pay for the things that are important to my family. The stock price will be what it is.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366919979540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366921062028-39</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't argue that. The company is not what it used to be my friend. I can only comment on what I experienced. I am fortunate to have a FCC license, so I had the opportunity to do just about everything you can think of. Ship to Shore radio, every form of local and long distance carrier (except "N" which was being phased out). I climbed poles, worked manholes spliced, provisioned, trouble shot just about any type of circuit you can name, worked the frames, b-boxes, fiber huts, T1to T3, you name it, I had my hands on it. Inside and in the field. I even had access to all the digital switches (through a back door program) to check translations, etc., even though i wasn't a switchman. I loved what I did. The only thing I didn't do was tech support. I still stay in touch with my former PCO and I've heard all about the new T from the folks that are still there. Needless to say, they don't have the same opinion that I have. But you know how it goes. It's a paycheck. And it's a damn good paycheck, thanks to all the bargaining that got the members to this point from many years ago. P.S. I once sat as an observer/negotiator at a contract renewal. Now THAT was an interesting experience!</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366921062028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:17:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366921318574-40</Id><Topic><Title>Has congress finally gone too far?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366918149600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:29:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...Hey, Frog boy…back so soon? This time with the “Obama Phone”???? Wow, talk about desperation…must be slim pickens for your side, huh? Man, you’ve got multiple lies goin’ on, they all get rejected, but you keep on crankin’ them out. Please fill us in on why everybody’s laughin’ at Glen Beck’s latest conspiracy theory about Boston, yet you brought it here as though it was the gospel truth? And then you disappear like a cheap dinner guest in a restaurant when the check arrives. If you are ever to be taken seriously, when you’re way-out-there-wrong, you need to admit it and apologize…oh, that’s right, you speak for the folks with the monopoly on taking personal responsibility for your actions…(hmmm, the word hypocrisy has already been bandied about today)…like intentionally lying as your only strategy. In the immortal words of Ricky Ricardo, “Froggie, I’m home…and you’ve got some splainin’ to do!!!!” “It’s been commonly called the Obama Phone, but that’s an urban legend as free cell phones originated under President Bush. The original Lifeline phone program started back in the 80’s under Ronald Reagan. And it’s not paid for by the taxpayers, but through a fee assessed to the telecoms.” So, frog boy, they aren't coming after your guns, and they're not coming after your phone...but the folks in white with the butterfly nets may be coming after you. You are a pathetic liar. You’re not a frog at all…just that green algae, more appropriately known as pond #$%$. Ribbit!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366921318574</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:21:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366922212191-41</Id><Topic><Title>LOADING UP THE TRUCK TODAY! JUST BOUGHT 7000 shares......not done yet!</Title><Username>superhigh_penthouse_naplesfl</Username><Timestamp>1366812590987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 10:09:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If what you say is true, I commend you. Somehow, the Trolling lowlife's didn't attack you.The dividend will make you happy and expect slow but steady price appreciation. Good move!</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366922212191</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366922364859-42</Id><Topic><Title>LOADING UP THE TRUCK TODAY! JUST BOUGHT 7000 shares......not done yet!</Title><Username>superhigh_penthouse_naplesfl</Username><Timestamp>1366812590987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 10:09:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Jimbo, how do you know what anyone has in their portfolio? I'd like to see your 86K appear on a statement. You are so funny making a lame joke. Nice knowing you. IGNORED.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366922364859</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:39:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366923153077-43</Id><Topic><Title>Has congress finally gone too far?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366918149600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:29:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you, Thank you, For making an old man feel better. Just knowing that those 50 congress people (according to you) are not going to be able to take away my Obama phone or the Obama phones of the 6 million other citizens is a true comfort. Or that congress or the administration will be unable to take away or restrict my second amendment rights, also makes me feel much better. Thank you again for all that you do. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366923153077</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:52:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366925923931-44</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are killing T</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842470940</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:27:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure they can. And watch the jobs bleed away to right to work states like mine. Happening in aerospace now. I think that is what happened in Detroit? There are enough laws to protect workers. Unions are unyielding anchors run by fat cat leaders on the backs of workers. You would have been fine with out paying someone to protect you....... Its an outdated joke. You are uninformed.... Just the way they like it. Go get your bowling ball. Peace... The Capper.</Msg><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366925923931</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:38:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366926355400-45</Id><Topic><Title>Has congress finally gone too far?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366918149600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:29:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know you are making a funny; but seriously, why doesn't Congress investigate more thoroughly the actions of our President? He supplied the Mexican drug cartel with assault rifles; He supplied the Muslim Brotherhood with arms to overthrow the governments of Egypt, Libya, and Syria; He ordered the DHS to buy enough military hardware to establish his own army; and Congress does nothing to stop him.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1366926355400</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:45:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366926713833-46</Id><Topic><Title>8 to 1 bid to ask....why is it stuck at 27.23 should</Title><Username>scooterbenz</Username><Timestamp>1366916326436</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:58:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know why you think there is a "should be" price, but I am happy with $.25 up every day. That would get us to $40 in less than three weeks.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1366926713833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:51:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366927427648-47</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No vendetta.. Just facts. Great for those that got nice packages.. As you can see those are gone. Happening all over multiple industries. Its just over because union entities cant compete with nonunion ones due to the inefficiencies unions are able to employ. I saw it running a semiconductor fab in ohio years ago. You need 3 or 4 people to do a job a cross trained individual could do easily. Not lean 6 sigma by a long shot. Sorry I didnt take the test to work for T. I took those while getting my EE and Industrial Mgt degrees. Passed a couple of them but thanks for your concern. Anyway T is nothing but a divi stock now. Fees too high and I wonder why that might be? Peace The Capper.</Msg><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366927427648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:03:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366927747840-48</Id><Topic><Title>Has congress finally gone too far?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366918149600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:29:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“Thank you, Thank you…for making an old man feel better.” Well, that’s not exactly an apology for lying, but it’s a start. Stay well, frog boy…don’t croak…oh, wait…your mating season is approaching…forget my last…</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366927747840</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366928241372-49</Id><Topic><Title>Has congress finally gone too far?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366918149600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:29:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now that is funny.... I dont care who you are. Lol!</Msg><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366928241372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366935379196-50</Id><Topic><Title>Has congress finally gone too far?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366918149600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:29:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, but I worked for a living and paid taxes (still do). Where are my freebis? No one gives me nuttin'.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1366935379196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366935636197-51</Id><Title>I like that it was never...</Title><Msg>..for 1 second in negative territory today. Nowhere to go but up from here.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1366935636197</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:20:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366935807205-52</Id><Topic><Title>Has congress finally gone too far?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366918149600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:29:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That sad..!! If you and me dates..I would give you some nuttin'..grins (!!)</Msg><Username>jon3retiree</Username><Timestamp>1366935807205</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:23:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366935863511-53</Id><Title>Loonie Tadpole Tunes...</Title><Msg>...Frog-like postings (except this one is true…finally, some credibility for the GOP) John Boehner's Future Son-in-law Once Busted for Pot (cue “cry me a river” from the tanning bed, Joe Cocker version) by Kristen Butler, UPI “Speaker of the House John Boehner may have something new to cry about -- his daughter's impending marriage. Lindsay Boehner, who lives in Hollywood, Florida, is engaged to Jamaica-born Dominic Lakhan, and records show they're set to tie the knot May 5, reports N. Y. Daily News. Lakhan was pulled over in 2006 for a traffic violation, and a Pembroke Pines, FL. police officer found *four grams of marijuana in his ashtray and "observed in plain view a 16 oz. Natural Light beer can opened in the driver door," according to a police report. "Officer also detected the odor of burnt #$%$ emitting from the interior of the vehicle." Lakhan, 38, admitted to possessing the marijuana “for personal use” and was charged with misdemeanor possession. Records also show Lakhan was charged with possession of an open container of alcohol while driving back in 2003. Republican House Speaker John Boehner is a social conservative, widely known to be a religious Catholic and firmly against marijuana legalization. “ – end of UPI story *that’s a seventh of an ounce…no sweat in a de-crim state, but if you’ve got four grams in the ashtray of your car…well, I’d just ask what the traffic violation he originally got pulled over for was…levitating himself out of John Boehner’s driveway? Oh, but in your heart, you know the hypocrisy crescendos…</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366935863511</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:24:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366937221336-54</Id><Topic><Title>T way overpriced here and heading lower. PE way too high and too much debt</Title><Username>tracker57888</Username><Timestamp>1366889852901</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:37:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And, you only posted that because YOU DO believe your comments affect the stock price ! HAhaha !</Msg><Username>cadmium_nitrate</Username><Timestamp>1366937221336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366937254565-55</Id><Topic><Title>T way overpriced here and heading lower. PE way too high and too much debt</Title><Username>tracker57888</Username><Timestamp>1366889852901</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:37:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Disagree. Stock is NOT going to 34. It is going to about 32.</Msg><Username>cadmium_nitrate</Username><Timestamp>1366937254565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:47:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366937264523-56</Id><Topic><Title>Has congress finally gone too far?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366918149600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:29:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HeeHee..you said "croak"..(!!)..chuckles..</Msg><Username>jon3retiree</Username><Timestamp>1366937264523</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:47:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366940466459-57</Id><Title>Things are solid,great div and earnings,</Title><Msg>The board of directors of AT&amp;T Inc. (NYSE:T) today declared a quarterly dividend of $0.45 a share on the company’s common shares. The dividend is payable on May 1, 2013, to stockholders of record at the close of business on April 10, 2013. At the same time, the board authorized the repurchase of up to 300 million shares, representing approximately 5.5 percent of AT&amp;T common shares outstanding, with no expiration date. This authorization is in addition to two other 300 million share repurchase authorizations approved by the board of directors in December 2010 and July 2012. The company completed repurchases under the December 2010 share authorization last year.</Msg><Username>efmutton39</Username><Timestamp>1366940466459</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 21:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366945764450-58</Id><Topic><Title>Has congress finally gone too far?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366918149600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:29:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor thing. You originally posed the question about monitoring the number of thumbs down a post gets. I posed a very simple follow up - why would anyone spend their time doing that? Not surprisingly, you are unable to answer and resort to bluster. If you don't want to make it my business, then don't post. Easy. It's a public board, jon, not your private tea party. Have you been seen by a doctor about your memory and loss of cognitive function issues?</Msg><Username>wledigmacsen</Username><Timestamp>1366945764450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 23:09:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366948044385-59</Id><Topic><Title>Has congress finally gone too far?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366918149600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:29:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>same here never got anything free 60 yrs old retired had 37 yrs of work in never unemployed my neighbor a young guys work low jobs for 5 months than gets unemployment and stamps runs out work for like 5 moinths again soooo some folks really need the help iam for that some are users and abuers ,,,</Msg><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1366948044385</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 23:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>