<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-12"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373625735061-1</Id><Title>Tax trap ll</Title><Msg>The feds made so much money on the last sell off they decided to run the price back up again. Its an honest yield killer, easy come easy go, shell game. I'm not going to buy (or sell) till they taper.</Msg><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1373625735061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 06:42:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373626386408-2</Id><Topic><Title>Tax trap ll</Title><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1373625735061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 06:42:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sammy gets the same amount if a person breaks even or loses money so its best that some people make a quick buck (rather than dealing with long term investors. A quick buck is a quick 20% tax.</Msg><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1373626386408</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 06:53:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373627359334-3</Id><Topic><Title>Tax trap ll</Title><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1373625735061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 06:42:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We might get a few more head fakes but they aren't going to allow an honest price till they dump their own shares.</Msg><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1373627359334</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 07:09:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373627899655-4</Id><Topic><Title>Tax trap ll</Title><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1373625735061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 06:42:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its al about Bernanke but Bernanke is a lame duck. I smell a rat.</Msg><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1373627899655</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 07:18:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373639454858-5</Id><Topic><Title>Tax trap ll</Title><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1373625735061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 06:42:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The tribal wisdom of the Dakota Indians, passed on from generation to generation, says that, "When you discover that you are riding a dead horse, the best strategy is to dismount." However, in government and in corporate America, more advanced strategies are often employed. By their own standards, proven examples are as follows: 1. Buying a stronger whip. 2. Changing riders. 3. Appointing a committee to study the horse. 4. Arranging to visit other countries to see how other cultures ride horses. 5. Lowering the standards so that dead horses can be included. 6. Reclassifying the dead horse as living impaired. 7. Hiring outside contractors to ride the dead horse. 8. Harnessing several dead horses together to increase speed. 9. Providing additional funding and/or training to increase dead horse's performance. 10. Doing a productivity study to see if lighter riders would improve the dead horse's performance. 11. Declaring that as the dead horse does not have to be fed, it is less costly, carries lower overhead and therefore contributes substantially more to the bottom line of the economy than live horses. 12. Rewriting the expected performance requirements for all horses. And of course my personal favorite........... 13. Promoting the dead horse to a supervisory position.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1373639454858</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 10:30:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373646583682-6</Id><Topic><Title>Tax trap ll</Title><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1373625735061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 06:42:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some of these sure sound familiar. You might add: Hiring a consultant to examine the horse and make a recommendation.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1373646583682</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 12:29:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373646746695-7</Id><Title>Yikes!!! Another nasty day for T!!</Title><Msg>$39 seems like a lifetime ago - glad I didn't pay $39 like one dope did. Save those dividends and you'll be even in 20 years. Better yet sell now and cut your losses. Buy something that goes up once in a while. Or short right before it goes down and go long right before it goes up like wilkes always does (don't know how he does it - and still loses $400,000!).LOL Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1373646746695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 12:32:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373647885899-8</Id><Topic><Title>Tax trap ll</Title><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1373625735061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 06:42:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The rider (Napolotano) couldn't deal with the stench &amp; maggots from the Obama 'horse' any longer .. and decided she could get to California quicker by walking till she could hitch-hike a ride with the first LGBT vehicle to come along !!</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1373647885899</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 12:51:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373656410150-9</Id><Topic><Title>PCYC filed for a new cancer drug approval</Title><Username>deal.smart</Username><Timestamp>1373569358528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PCYC breaks out to new highs again today. PCYC is on an amazing break out run again today.</Msg><Username>deal.smart</Username><Timestamp>1373656410150</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 15:13:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373667207113-10</Id><Topic><Title>Who is the fella occupying the WH? no one seems to know for sure</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1373528518138</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 03:41:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The colored fella probably isn`t even an American citizen, that`s how bad it is. Most likely an illegal alien occupies the White House. Go ahead and laugh about it, the criminal elite responsible for him and his colored gang`s installation will destroy you too at some point. Probably quicker than a lot of the people you try to ridicule.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1373667207113</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 18:13:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373668333871-11</Id><Topic><Title>DOJ(HOLDER?) organized protests in Sanford</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1373563450415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 13:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>per emil, Maybe we need a back to Europe movement for the whites. I don`t think many European countries would let us in. Their politicians are flooding their countries with colored immigrants too. I`ve read that White South Africans have applied to immigrate to England and been denied entrance. Geez, many of them have English ancestry. Emma West, a native Brit, was caught on youtube ranting against the immigrants. She was put in jail for months and had her young child taken from her. I wouldn`t be at all surprised if a colored immigrant judge decided her fate. We Whites live in countries that were created and developed by Whites that have been taken over by coloreds. We are now dictated to and told what to do, think, and learn by other races. Have you noticed the pictures of Bradley Manning, the extremely pale White hero/soldier? They always have some big Black soldier as his captor/guard leading him around like a slave. Sickening.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1373668333871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 18:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373670270979-12</Id><Topic><Title>DOJ(HOLDER?) organized protests in Sanford</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1373563450415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 13:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The likes of Soros appear to really hate White people. Which is weird because those types have excelled as a result of living in White European cultures. I`ll bet the likes of Soros make sure the puppets they install hate Whites as much as they appear to. I have always sensed that mr and mrs obongo don`t much like Whites, other than a very elite few(and their fondness for those few may be a pretense). Nor do many of their pals. I am more curious than ever, I wonder who the colored fella occupying the White House really is. We don`t know who he is! He could be a convicted criminal, even a murderer, for all we know, maybe from another country, the possibilities are endless. Simply amazing and sickening.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1373670270979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 19:04:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373672969220-13</Id><Topic><Title>Yikes!!! Another nasty day for T!!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1373646746695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 12:32:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your logic is so lame and boring. Your telling me in light that telecom technology still has a long ways to go with plenty of extra business venues that spin off from home detection, gps and just plain oh cell phone usage. At&amp;t, Verizon and Sprint are well positioned to truly grow over next ten years I have already put my money where my mouth is AT&amp;T will keep growing along with the telecom sector.</Msg><Username>nobrainerduh</Username><Timestamp>1373672969220</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 19:49:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373674461659-14</Id><Topic><Title>DOJ(HOLDER?) organized protests in Sanford</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1373563450415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 13:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No Lav the front men are like Obama but the ones behind them are the relatives of the ones that led the slave trade. Look up Aaron Lopez. of Newport, Rhode Island. Same ilk as Soros and the financiers behind many of the race agitating groups. They are mentioned in the second and third chapters of Revelations.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1373674461659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 20:14:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373675946295-15</Id><Topic><Title>DOJ(HOLDER?) organized protests in Sanford</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1373563450415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 13:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.. The D.O.J and H.L.S are both involved deeply with staging of manpower in Sanford , awaiting a jury verdict ... which 'suddenly' may raise questions about Napolotano's motive for her resignation ?? Does she NOT want to comply with her marching orders 'to Sanford' ..by Obama -- because of the nature of "her mission" ..as it pertains to our U.S. Law .. under our Constitution ?? We know that "Eurckle Holder" (like Obama) doesn't shivaget about our Constitution .. he (like Obama) has a certain brotherhood of loyalty going with each other. On the other hand .. could it be that Napolotano has a 'wee-bit' of loyalty &amp; character towards her country - or does she THINK this is going to 'blow-up' in their Administrative Faces .. and suspects a potential period of enternal unrest, in our Govt. .. in our country ?? Her sudden announcement (Sanford) .. her timing (Sanford) .. her mission (Sanford) ?? - coluld be that's what's making the hair on my dog's back stand straight up ?? Is she bailing out - then locking &amp; loading ?? ... just wondering .....</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1373675946295</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 20:39:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373679027671-16</Id><Title>After Hours Quotes...</Title><Msg>...“We could never imagine what a strange disproportion a few or a great many pieces of money make between men, if we did not see it every day with our own eyes.” – Jean de la Bruyere “It is a law of nature we overlook, that intellectual versatility is the compensation for change, danger, and trouble." – H.G. Wells "Texas Gov. Rick Perry says he will not run for governor for a fourth term, though he hasn't ruled out running for president again. The voters have, he just hasn't." - Jay Leno “Patience and shuffle the cards.” – Cervantes “He took the brandy flask and poured out a glass of neat spirit, stiff enough to help anybody over anything.” – Algernon Blackwood "Despite his prostitution scandal several years ago, Eliot Spitzer is running for comptroller of New York. He's paying someone $800 a day to collect signatures to put him on the ballot. He said it's the second best $800 he's ever spent." - Conan O'Brien “Words make you think a thought. Music makes you feel a feeling. A song makes you feel a thought.” – Y. Harburg “Mrs. Snow had lived forty years, and for fifteen of those years she had been too busy wishing things were different to find much time to enjoy things as they were.” – Eleanor H. Porter “While there may be power in forgiveness, there is even more power in lobbing a Molotov cocktail through someone's dining room window.” – Jim Norton “The glory of creation is in its infinite diversity.” – Gene Roddenberry</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1373679027671</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:30:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373679060098-17</Id><Title>AHQ (cont.)...</Title><Msg>...“To the intelligent man with an interest in human nature it must often appear strange that so much of the energy of the scientific world has been spent on the study of the body and so little on the study of the mind." – Edward Thorndike “Playing ‘Bop’ is like playing Scrabble with all the vowels missing.” – Duke Ellington "Pakistan now says Osama bin Laden was able to be avoided by wearing a cowboy hat. A Pakistani authority said, 'I guess he just got lost in a sea of other Muslims wearing a cowboy hat’.” - Conan O'Brien “I’m not a mathematician, but I've been hanging around with some of them long enough to know how the game is played.” – Brian Hayes “Conformity is the jailer of freedom and the enemy of growth.” – John Fitzgerald Kennedy “It really seems to me that in the midst of great tragedy, there is always the horrible possibility that something terribly funny will happen.” – Phillip K. Richard “The Second Amendment was meant to give citizens the right to bear arms against the government, back when Uncle Sam's toys were as lame as yours… Handguns are sheer lunacy.” – Rachel Marsden “There is an obesity epidemic. One out of every three Americans... weighs as much as the other two.” – Richard Jeni "Great news for NSA leaker Edward Snowden. He's just been named Cinnabon Customer of the Month in the Moscow Airport." - David Letterman “It’s a round trip. Getting to the summit is optional, getting down is mandatory.” – Ed Viesturs</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1373679060098</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373679112088-18</Id><Title>AHQ (3)...</Title><Msg>...“To die will be an awfully big adventure.” – James M. Barrie “The game [of poker] exemplifies the worst aspects of capitalism that have made our country so great.” – Charles Lamb “I do not know what it was about that boy but just looking at him, even I wanted to clout him on the head. It was a head that invited violence.” – Patrick DeWitt “I am trying to do two things: dare to be a radical and not be a fool, which, if I may judge by the exhibitions around me, is a matter of no small difficulty.” – James A. Garfield “It is a curious thing that every creed promises a paradise which will be absolutely uninhabitable for anyone of civilised taste.” – Evelyn Waugh “Mexico has replaced the U.S. as the world's fattest nation. The U.S. is now number two. The Mexican government has done a lot of research. It turns out their people eat way too much Mexican food." - Conan O'Brien “Don’t you love it when people in school are like, "I'm a bad test taker"? You mean, you're stupid. Oh, you struggle with that part where we find out what you know?” – Daniel Tosh “Overwork: n., a dangerous disorder affecting high public functionaries who want to go fishing.” – Ambrose Bierce “She had a voice so husky it could have pulled a dogsled, and the gun she was holding gave me a bad case of barrel envy.” – Patrick Major Dallas “The drop of rain maketh a hole in the stone, not by violence, but by oft falling.” – Hugh Latimer</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1373679112088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:31:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373679159914-19</Id><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Msg>...“I don't understand people who say life is a mystery, because what is it they want to know?” – Jack Handey “Music has always been a matter of energy to me, a question of fuel. Sentimental people call it inspiration, but what they really mean is fuel. I have always needed fuel. I am a serious consumer. On some nights I still believe that a car with the gas needle on empty can run about fifty more miles if you have the right music very loud on the radio.” – Hunter S. Thompson "Republicans are already trying to paint Hillary Clinton as too old to be president. In fact, a new ad claims she's so old that she could be a Republican." –Conan O'Brien “I know nothing grander, better exercise, better digestion, more positive proof of the past, the triumphant result of faith in human kind, than a well-contested American national election.” – Walt Whitman “But hearing oftentimes The still, sad music of humanity.” – William Wordsworth “I'm not a hypochondriac, but my gynecologist firmly believes I am.” – Rodney Dangerfield "Indeed, when I am in really great trouble, as any one who knows me intimately will tell you, I refuse everything except food and drink." – Oscar Wilde “Behold, I show you a mystery; we shall not all sleep, but we shall all be changed, in a moment, in the twinkling of an eye.” – Corinthians “Recent studies have shown that approximately 40% of authors are manic depressive. The rest of us just drink.” – Melodyie Campbell “Mr. Tulkinghorn, sitting in the twilight by the open window, enjoys his wine. As if it whispered to him of its fifty years of silence and seclusion, it shuts him up the closer. More impenetrable than ever, he sits, and drinks, and mellows as it were in secrecy, pondering at that twilight hour on all the mysteries he knows.” – Charles Dickens “Have a good weekend, all.” – echo2165 “The world, dear Agnes, is a strange affair.” - Moliére</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1373679159914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:32:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373686596871-20</Id><Topic><Title>Yikes!!! Another nasty day for T!!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1373646746695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 12:32:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THXS thinks everyone is selling in 30 days ..... boring is right just an attention getter misery loves company socialpath with severe character behavior disorders along with masassictic tendences probably brought on by bad parenting or thrown to babysisters who were busy with there bf...later</Msg><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1373686596871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 23:36:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373686719261-21</Id><Topic><Title>Yikes!!! Another nasty day for T!!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1373646746695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 12:32:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pleasee read my reply to nobrainerdub it may help you!!! Iam busy gave u enough of my value time</Msg><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1373686719261</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 23:38:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>