<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-31"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359610554562-1</Id><Topic><Title>How sad what Florida has become</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359423608733</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 20:40:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Everyone is carrying in Florida, hence bad guys don't try anything here The Police keep a low profile, and just respond after all the gunsmoke clears." In Jacksonville not too long ago there was a drive by shooting in which 5 people were shot, no one killed though. It hardly made the news.. Shootings are a regular occurence there. A couple of summers ago a 'youth' shot up a mall in Jacksonville, luckily only one person was shot but not killed. It hardly made a blip on the local news either, and not at all on the national news. I don`t think they ever found the Black 'youth' who did the shooting. But they sure determined who the White guy was that shot a Black 'youth' recently in Jacksonville - within hours. Jacksonville is a dangerous city and I think it had a past reputation in Florida as being the poor relative of cities in Florida. . Now though I believe all large cities in Florida are just as dangerous, and some people actually feel safer in Jacksonville than other cities. I`ve heard a lot of people say they would never live in the metropolitan Miami area, for example. Florida does have a large White conservative base which supports gun rights. But the millions of immigrants who have flooded the state are overwhelming that base. If the rats and snakes in our government are ever allowed to legalize the millions of illegal immigrants in Florida that conservative base will have no clout. The migrants have more babies than Whites, and after they are legalized then there will again be another flood of illegals. Just like what happened after Reagan legalized millions of illegals. It will only be a matter of time then until no one will be carrying, legally that is. The future non White majority will not want White folks owning guns and they will decide what is law. You can bet on it.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359610554562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 00:35:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359612346447-2</Id><Title>TV is BAD BAD BAD to Whites imo</Title><Msg>I`ve watched some cable tv lately(not my tv), and it is really bad, much worse than I thought. I flip through channels trying to find something to watch, with no luck, once in awhile stopping to watch a show for a few minutes, out of curiousity. Just a while ago for example, I watched Bill Mahr talking to Nancy Pelosi for a couple of minutes. It was truly sickening. They were gloating over the fact that Whites are a minority in California. Pelosi laughed viciously after very cleary and hatefully specifying that White MEN are now THE minority in California. IMO, there was a real sense of hatred and vengence in her behavior. For the first time, I now understand why so many White conservatives can`t stand her. She deserves it. A nasty nasty women. Mahr pretended to be an example of that White male, letting it be known that it was ok with him that he was now a minority . What a fraud. He is not the White European male that has been targeted for elimination. Not at all. I believe actually he is a member of the tribe that targeted the White European male for elimination and has played a major role in their ongoing genocide. When I finally find the place I want to settle, I may throw the tv away once and for all. It is a tool being used mainly to genocide White Americans with almost no entertainment, educational or news value at all.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359612346447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 01:05:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359626799608-3</Id><Topic><Title>Awesome report for AT&amp;T , but is it true ?</Title><Username>pattersonsofia289</Username><Timestamp>1359562568045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 11:16:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good report !</Msg><Username>mara.meisel</Username><Timestamp>1359626799608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 05:06:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359634570951-4</Id><Topic><Title>How sad what Florida has become</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359423608733</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 20:40:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can pay a ton of taxes and not work. Trust me.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1359634570951</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 07:16:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359639056139-5</Id><Topic><Title>How sad what Florida has become</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359423608733</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 20:40:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... "Everyone is carrying in Florida…” Oh, great, just what we need. Of Florida’s population, nearly 3 million are between the ages of 65 and 84, and another half million, or so, are OVER 85 years old. Let’s just give ‘em all AR-15’s and let them self-regulate and ease the tax burdens of real Americans by culling the socialist herds off Medicaid and Medicare. Over 65? Sign up today for your free assault rifle by joining The Golden Years Posse (affectionately referred to as Grannie Zimmerman’s Vigilantes.) Incidentally, I have numerous relatives in Florida of all ages, and none, to my knowledge, carry because they are not frightened, incompetent, racist wackjobs (like many on this board) who are so incapable of taking care of themselves that they feel a need to turn their communities into The O.K. Corral.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1359639056139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 08:30:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359643654325-6</Id><Topic><Title>Winholder - not unexpectantly stalled</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1359578716503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 15:45:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The economy is stagnant at best and I for one don't believe that is the real story. Immigration and gun control deflections aren't going to save him when UE numbers come in higher this week than 'expected'. I would like to find out who the person is that has all these high 'expectations' that continually get smashed on a continuing basis. You can only redistribute for so long before you run out of the other guy’s money or they hide it or take it offshore. Obama is pushing the envelope already. If a business is growing their profits, unless it is via increased spending on their government related contract awards, government has little to do with it. Government’s most common influence on profits, other than defense spending or disallowing the Medicare folks for bidding drug prices, is to weaken profits. More government is not the answer; it is the key to the problems. That however sad and true does not fit the liberal mantra, but government itself is the worst example of business acumen in the world.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359643654325</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 09:47:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359644490477-7</Id><Topic><Title>Failing yet again</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359574479522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:34:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Where were you last quarter, winholder?" One quarter does not constitute a streak of any kind or the ‘rebirth’ of our economy. Just ask any basketball player that suffers through a great first quarter only to lose the game. The problem is Ricky that this is not 'one' downtick in an advance estimate, it is a constant revision of the economic statistics after they are originally released or released with excuses already included. The unemployment rate is still too high, regardless of the FED's claim of controlling inflation, prices are going up, and wages aren't. Taxes for the middle class that according to the government wouldn't be allowed to happen because the middle class drives our economy is a reality surprise that they can no longer hide. This administration, with help from several past administrations, is driving the middle class off a 'fiscal cliff'. The stock market jumping up for a few days or weeks is not necessarily a sign of a recovering economy, just a sign that the money movers in the market charted a new way to drive stock levels up a few points so they could manipulate their moves into profits. The stock market is such a game of chance that often its moves have little or no relevance to actual business conditions. You're fooling yourself, and not many others, with your 'we are on our way to the utopia he promised' fun and games. It is falling on deaf ears and the audience is growing.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359644490477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 10:01:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359644602343-8</Id><Title>Press release coming on CERP</Title><Msg>trend bullish</Msg><Username>ride.thewave</Username><Timestamp>1359644602343</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 10:03:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359644829311-9</Id><Topic><Title>Another sad story from Chicago</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1359563646065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 11:34:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Send more AR-15s to Chicago and the death by gun rate will go down. Is that what you think?" That depends a lot of who owns those new shipments. If it is the public, the criminals won't be so ready to attack for fear of being shot.</Msg><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1359644829311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 10:07:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359644845436-10</Id><Topic><Title>Failing yet again</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359574479522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:34:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Spinmeister, tell it to the 7.8% who are unemployed and the cast of thousands not included in that stat who have given it up as hopeless.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1359644845436</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 10:07:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359645036480-11</Id><Topic><Title>Another sad story from Chicago</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1359563646065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 11:34:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They tried but Holder won't release the data he is hiding from Congress. People were too busy listening to Harry Reid and his 'information' about Romney's taxes and that poor woman he killed witlh cancer. The noise was just too loud to hear the truth.</Msg><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1359645036480</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 10:10:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359645599551-12</Id><Topic><Title>Another sad story from Chicago</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1359563646065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 11:34:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have few issues with requiring background checks when someone wants to purchase a weapon. I have some reservations with the government controlling what type of weapons beyond a reasonable point. I think the current push is reactive overreach, which is typical of the crisis management style of this administration. I have a problem with the government knowing which weapons I have in my closet. I have a problem with the lack of effort that has been put into the background checks and the prosecution of criminals that use or even posses a gun in the commission of a crime. In many cases, local, state and even Federal agencies charged with this challenge are not doing their jobs properly and now the law abiding gun owners are being set up to pay the price. There are no easy answers, but the answers need to be discussed, researched, and debated until there is agreement, not dictated by fiat by some government blockhead. We need responsible decisions to fix these problems, not a rush to judgment to keep the voters happy.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359645599551</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 10:19:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359646334943-13</Id><Topic><Title>TV is BAD BAD BAD to Whites imo</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359612346447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 01:05:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mahr pretended to be an example of that White male, letting it be known that it was ok with him that he was now a minority. Mahr pretends a lot. He pretends he is a comedian. He is a rich liberal. He assumes there is nothing about which he should be concerned. He doesn't think Obama will come after his money until he has exhausted everyone else's or Mahr quits contributing to liberal causes. He runs out of money, or stops his contributions, he is toast! He just isn’t smart enough to know it and his friend Nancy won’t tell him the truth.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359646334943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 10:32:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359646611531-14</Id><Topic><Title>2010 FBI data murders in U.S.</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1359587208243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:06:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shhhh! Don't let Echo see this post, he is under the impression that all murders, all holdups and all car jacking's are done with the assistance of an AR-15 or similar type weapon. If he is shaken out of his delusion, he might crack. If that happens he will surely never pass a background check for the mentally deranged.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359646611531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 10:36:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359646725858-15</Id><Topic><Title>Failing yet again</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359574479522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:34:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"One quarter does not constitute a streak of any kind or the ‘rebirth’ of our economy. " But it represents that "it is deteriorating because of past actions of the same group in this circular firing squad blah blah blah"? Eureka! You've figured it out. It's only true and it's only a streak if it's bad news. Otherwise, it's a lie or a one time event, eh? We've had 8 quarters of growth since 2009. Does that constitute a streak? A major factor in lowering GDP in Q4 was reduced Federal spending--an ongoing trend since the stimulus was passed. Does that constitute a streak? Nope, just the single advance report on a single quarter of GDP, that's a streak. How about the latest report from the BEA, published this morning: "Personal income increased $352.4 billion, or 2.6 percent, and disposable personal income (DPI) increased $331.3 billion, or 2.7 percent, in December, according to the Bureau of Economic Analysis. Personal consumption expenditures (PCE) increased $22.6 billion, or 0.2 percent. In November, personal income increased $135.8 billion, or 1.0 percent, DPI increased $125.5 billion, or 1.0 percent, and PCE increased $41.6 billion, or 0.4 percent, based on revised estimates." Hey, that's good news! Must mean the BEA is lying today, right?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359646725858</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 10:38:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359647012815-16</Id><Topic><Title>ricky is not the brightest bulb</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1359589333438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ricky believes the Party line...’if it is not fixed yet, it will be soon, just hang in there.’ Well, we have all been hanging in there for four years and the march to the sea seems to have stalled. Ricky can't see that the march has stalled; he is too busy keeping time with the marching music played by all the network news outlets and liberal writers. The noise is all consuming and distracting to the point of insanity, from which most believers are suffering. It’s not entirely his fault; he was raised and semi-educated by liberals. It is all still GWB’s fault and he made such a mess of things that the brilliance of Lord Barry is not sufficient to fix all the problems that quickly. We must be patient and understand that they have to continue to manipulate the data so as to not frighten the masses to revolution.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359647012815</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 10:43:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359647022376-17</Id><Topic><Title>Failing yet again</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359574479522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:34:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell them what? The Tea Brains want to end your UI benefits? That decrease public spending and public employment are the main drag on the economy and employment at the moment? Gladly. What I won't do is tell them the figure is a lie when I don't like it and that it's true when I do like it. Which is what winholder and the entire cult of the Tea Brain does. I have no patience for it and neither should you.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359647022376</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 10:43:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359647568619-18</Id><Topic><Title>ricky is not the brightest bulb</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1359589333438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The data speaks for itself. In this post you cite it as proof that "the march has stalled" and claim that "they" will "continue to manipulate the data." You're a two-faced SOB, and you've proven it over and over again. Americans are not as dumb as you need them to be.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359647568619</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 10:52:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359648913723-19</Id><Topic><Title>ricky is not the brightest bulb</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1359589333438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most Americans are dumber than anyone needs them to be. I learned that years ago when going door to door trying to stop the scam of a taxpayer financed football stadium. Most prefer lies to truth.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1359648913723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 11:15:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359649234009-20</Id><Topic><Title>Failing yet again</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359574479522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:34:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Tell them what?" Tell the thousands upon thousands of still unemployed and hopelessly unemployed what you told us: "But beyond that, this is one slight downtick in an advance estimate of one indicator in what has been a good year."</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1359649234009</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 11:20:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359649370827-21</Id><Topic><Title>Union Vote</Title><Username>dynnyd</Username><Timestamp>1359593067464</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 19:44:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today suggests it had nothing to do with the voting results.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1359649370827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 11:22:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359650733398-22</Id><Topic><Title>2010 FBI data murders in U.S.</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1359587208243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:06:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, almost as bad if Governor Cuomo, who said: "No one hunts with an assault rifle," "No one needs 10 bullets to kill a deer. End the madness." Ever found out that most Americans are not worried about the deers shooting back. LOL "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1359650733398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 11:45:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359652699424-23</Id><Topic><Title>Failing yet again</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359574479522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:34:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It has been a good year, tb. It's been a good year for markets. It's been a good year for private sector growth. It's been a good year for private sector employment. The drag, as I've noted, has been public sector employment. Dec. to Dec, the unemployment rate has declined from 8.5% to 7.8%. And it's been declining steadily since hitting 9.8% in Nov. 2010. I expect further declines as the number of payroll jobs continues to rise and the retirement becomes a viable option as the markets recover. And the fact is "hopelessly unemployed" doesn't really compute anymore. It's not 2008 or 2009. We've left the tunnel. There is light. People can find jobs. If you've let your skills atrophy or failed to adapt or simply don't think its worth it to take a job you're qualified for, you may have difficulty. But the economy is creating jobs and it is growing. What happened to that personal responsibility you've been talking so much about? What I will also tell people is that, if we can stomp the Tea Brains, they will have a safety net. They will have access to education, training and employment services. We may be able to stop the bleeding in public sector employment. We can end the politics and economics of repeated fiscal crisis. What will you tell the 7.8% unemployed? Obama sux? Shoulda let Detroit fail? No UI, just increase my Medicare spending? I'd really like to know.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359652699424</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 12:18:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359652879898-24</Id><Topic><Title>How sad what Florida has become</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359423608733</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 20:40:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a total moron......</Msg><Username>ugabulldog4u</Username><Timestamp>1359652879898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 12:21:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359654651362-25</Id><Topic><Title>T ranked numb. 6 in a top ten most Overvalued stocks list at the site Extreme Value Stocks Interesting website.</Title><Username>calebcaleb692</Username><Timestamp>1359653080491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 12:24:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stop Lying!! T is not even mentioned.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359654651362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 12:50:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359657772586-26</Id><Topic><Title>T ranked numb. 6 in a top ten most Overvalued stocks list at the site Extreme Value Stocks Interesting website.</Title><Username>calebcaleb692</Username><Timestamp>1359653080491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 12:24:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just another sneaky way to promote a web site.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1359657772586</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 13:42:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359658607960-27</Id><Topic><Title>2010 FBI data murders in U.S.</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1359587208243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:06:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's our wonderful Janet Napolitano for you! A dumber B you will never meet! We are so glad she's there and not here anymore. She's as worthless there as she was here.</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1359658607960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 13:56:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359658614218-28</Id><Topic><Title>2010 FBI data murders in U.S.</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1359587208243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:06:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“WASHINGTON - President Obama is riding a wave of personal popularity into his second term, with his highest favorability ratings since his first year in office, according to a new Washington Post-ABC News poll. Fully 60 percent of Americans have a favorable impression of Obama in the new poll…” And this has what to do or to prove that the economy is improving? Zero is the correct answer. I would be extremely popular as well if I continued to give away the Federal treasury to all those that I have put out of work and those that choose to never work. Then I want to install all the illegal’s in this country as instant citizens that can keep voting for me. This paragraph is just more MSM liberal support for their boy! As for the rest of your rant, you proved nothing except that you are the same sort of brainwashed, no, brain stagnated liberal as Ricky and too many others for this country to be successful. You are not the middle road liberal you claim, you're part of the radical left that is very dangerous. We appreciate your comments and for sticking up for Ricky, they make the day a bit more entertaining and humorous. You're tiring, but funny.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359658614218</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 13:56:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359659194305-29</Id><Topic><Title>ricky is not the brightest bulb</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1359589333438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which data? One week it is all peaches and cream, we are headed for the most promising economy in decades, and the wisdom of Obama has saved us all, then suddenly and 'unexpectedly' we are going the other direction. As the old saying goes, there are lies, damned lies, and statistics. We all know that like polls, most statistics can be used to get whatever answer you need. Of course when someone calls you on the manipulation, you can always claim that the 'facts' just hadn't caught up with the statistics used, or some other political mumbo jumbo. It happens far too often for you to continue this blatant and foolish denial.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359659194305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 14:06:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359659456286-30</Id><Topic><Title>Failing yet again</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1359574479522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:34:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Personal income increased $352.4 billion, or 2.6 percent, and disposable personal income (DPI) increased $331.3 billion, or 2.7 percent, in December, according to the Bureau of Economic Analysis. That can't be allowed to continue, that means that someone is using government facilities and infrastructure to steal and cheat their way to success. That is against liberal policies, unless you're a rich Democratic political donor.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1359659456286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 14:10:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359659652060-31</Id><Topic><Title>2010 FBI data murders in U.S.</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1359587208243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:06:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Mahr is worse than a liberal; he is a rich, self-centered idiot. He says more stupid things than Harry, Nancy, Barney, Teddy and Obama combined and all in their defense, for which there is none.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1359659652060</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 14:14:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359659880995-32</Id><Topic><Title>Another sad story from Chicago</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1359563646065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 11:34:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"eggohead" .. your quote .. "have a self-inflicted accidental discharge" ?? This is what happened to him when his momma caught him in the closet with a Playboy!</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1359659880995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 14:18:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359662200971-33</Id><Topic><Title>2010 FBI data murders in U.S.</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1359587208243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:06:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rexas is the hillbilly captial of the world. w is the leader.</Msg><Username>orri1934</Username><Timestamp>1359662200971</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 14:56:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359663167643-34</Id><Title>Is the AT&amp;T stock a good utility stock to own?</Title><Msg>How does AT&amp;T measure up when strictly considered as a utility company? To be able to answer the question, one needs to compare the company with one of the largest utility companies in the U.S. The first that comes to mind is DUK. This analysis uses data based on 1/27/2013 pricing therefore there may be a slight change to the numbers. Okay then, here we go: AT&amp;T, Credit Rating, A-; DUK BBB+ AT&amp;T, Dividend Yield, 5.29%; DUK 4.51% AT&amp;T, Debt-to-Equity 75.35%; DUK 96.61% AT&amp;T, P/S 1.5; DUK 2.81 AT&amp;T, Enterprise Value/EBITDA, 5.67; DUK 13.18 AT&amp;T, Payout Ratio 70%; DUK 75% AT&amp;T, Earnings growth rate 7%; DUK 3% The conclusion from the data shown above is rather obvious. The AT&amp;T stock offers a tremendous value at the going share prices when considered strictly a utility company. It is understandable why and how the company is in a big hurry to buy back shares given that they can barrow funds at cheaper rates than the dividends they pay out. Disclosure- I am long the AT&amp;T stock.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1359663167643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 15:12:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359665111676-35</Id><Topic><Title>ricky is not the brightest bulb</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1359589333438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"One week it is all peaches and cream, we are headed for the most promising economy in decades" No. One week is statistical noise. The overall data is consistent with a moderate recovery. Either way, winholder, either it's lies or its not. You can't pick and choose the good weeks as lies and the bad weeks as truth. At least you can't and consider yourself honest. "We all know that like polls, most statistics can be used to get whatever answer you need." Which is what you do. If you look at economic indicators or polls in their entirety over time they create a very good picture of the economy or public opinion. If you pick one instance of one indicator you won't get a good picture. If you decide all positive indicators are lies and all negative indicators are the truth you'll be someone who uses statistics to lie to people. That is what you do. That is what the conservative media does.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359665111676</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 15:45:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359666618158-36</Id><Title>jon...</Title><Msg>... Protecting it by passing the final wording the way it is today .. leaving it in the hands of "commom sense" folks, .when the Goverment fails in it's abilities, it's "Oath &amp; Duty" of this same "common sense" by protecting this "document" for the good of the people with the right to protect themselves when the Goverment CAN'T, then trying overturn our 2nd Amendment Right, to defend ourselves from ALL ENEMY's "Foreign and DOMESTIC" - Thats a FACT - jon A FACT? No, jon, that’s not even a coherent paragraph. It’s a mish-mash, run-on-sentence of discombobulated gibberish, separated by random punctuation scattered liberally around like you were broadcasting seeds. The only cogent message received is that you are exactly the guy to whom Bobby Jindall is referring.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1359666618158</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 16:10:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359670171467-37</Id><Title>Why Does AT&amp;T Suck So Bad?</Title><Msg>hahahahaha... other than the POS gimps that run the company...?</Msg><Username>antilib_eats_azzz</Username><Timestamp>1359670171467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 17:09:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359671363192-38</Id><Topic><Title>Why Does AT&amp;T Suck So Bad?</Title><Username>antilib_eats_azzz</Username><Timestamp>1359670171467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 17:09:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What no answers? Too hard of a question to the AT&amp;T gimps?</Msg><Username>antilib_eats_azzz</Username><Timestamp>1359671363192</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 17:29:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359673161639-39</Id><Topic><Title>2010 FBI data murders in U.S.</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1359587208243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:06:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh and do you like her Deer in the headlights look when she's at the podium? Like she's scared of her own shadow! And she's the director of Homeland Security?? What a joke she is! Man made distaster, wft??? She's a God made disaster. Oops, I used the word God echo and ricky. I know your not a believer, so go ahead, try to have it removed!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1359673161639</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 17:59:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359675084457-40</Id><Topic><Title>jon...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1359666618158</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 16:10:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Echo, way too good. This jon guy is just tedious and jejune.</Msg><Username>rcub5d</Username><Timestamp>1359675084457</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 18:31:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359681118606-41</Id><Topic><Title>How sad what Florida has become</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359423608733</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 20:40:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...Dude, you're on Staten Island. Clue in to Global Warming. The Homeless aren't anywhere - they're everywhere. If they were actually somewhere, they wouldn't be homeless.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1359681118606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 20:11:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359687442795-42</Id><Topic><Title>2010 FBI data murders in U.S.</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1359587208243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:06:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When seconds count, a cop is only minutes away!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359687442795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 21:57:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359691201403-43</Id><Topic><Title>How sad what Florida has become</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359423608733</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 20:40:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We had spaghetti for dinner.</Msg><Username>wledigmacsen</Username><Timestamp>1359691201403</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 23:00:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359692559932-44</Id><Topic><Title>jon...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1359666618158</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 16:10:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...random punctuation scattered liberally around like you were broadcasting seeds." Well now, there's a turn of phrase for you!</Msg><Username>wledigmacsen</Username><Timestamp>1359692559932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 23:22:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359693859039-45</Id><Topic><Title>How sad what Florida has become</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359423608733</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 20:40:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are being sprayed like a bug, it is because you are a bug. Live with it!</Msg><Username>wledigmacsen</Username><Timestamp>1359693859039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 23:44:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359693990710-46</Id><Topic><Title>Note to Jon</Title><Username>cloudview92</Username><Timestamp>1359693124238</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 23:32:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Jon. You too!</Msg><Username>wledigmacsen</Username><Timestamp>1359693990710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 23:46:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>