<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370327156354-1</Id><Topic><Title>the reason you loose and i win!</Title><Username>irnebarnk</Username><Timestamp>1370317314926</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 23:41:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thats a great site</Msg><Username>alejandropefro</Username><Timestamp>1370327156354</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 02:25:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370354417472-2</Id><Topic><Title>the reason you loose and i win!</Title><Username>irnebarnk</Username><Timestamp>1370317314926</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 23:41:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But it puts a virus on your computer.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370354417472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:00:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370355064531-3</Id><Title>5 million shares traded at the open today</Title><Msg>Volume since then has been below normal.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370355064531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:11:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370355331308-4</Id><Topic><Title>the reason you loose and i win!</Title><Username>irnebarnk</Username><Timestamp>1370317314926</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 23:41:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah i signed up for there email alerts to</Msg><Username>robbin291</Username><Timestamp>1370355331308</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:15:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370355602369-5</Id><Topic><Title>dont give up theres hope!</Title><Username>princeghara</Username><Timestamp>1369866771349</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-29 18:32:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very good! i SUBSCRIBED</Msg><Username>robbin291</Username><Timestamp>1370355602369</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370355619321-6</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shulman was asked about his 157 visits while under oath at the Congressional hearing. He never denied the 157 visits. When asked about the purpose of the visits he said "one of them was for the Easter Egg hunt with my children". Did you make up that line about "White House records show former IRS Commissioner Douglas Shulman signed in for 11 visits" or is that more propaganda direct from the President?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370355619321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:20:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370356089987-7</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for your suggestion about how to solve the deficit. Unfortunately, I doubt that it will work. Calling those who advocate following the Constitution "fascist" won't reduce the spending at all.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370356089987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:28:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370357796308-8</Id><Topic><Title>Back to a 5% dividend !!!!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369770746424</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:52:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>smithers, get out of the market, you can't handle small swings. Today you're happy? you're watching way too close.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1370357796308</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:56:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370357810217-9</Id><Topic><Title>Land of the free</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369948675101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes and overpaid</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1370357810217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:56:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370358540074-10</Id><Topic><Title>5 million shares traded at the open today</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370355064531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:11:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the second day in a row that someone has quoted a big transaction that TDAmeritrade doesn't show. Wilkes when you say 5 million shares are traded at the open today, are you referring to the 1st hour? Because that's how long it took to get to 5 million according to TDAmeritrade,, I wonder if my data is not including pre-market sales and your data is, because there is a 5 million share discrepancy in my hourly data compared to my daily data. Either way I guess I should get off the subject and focus on the more important subject of IS THERE A LIMIT as to how many spammers I can put on ignore,, they are getting out of hand and I notice that you (wilkes71) seem to be having a fit with them also.</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1370358540074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:09:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370359502509-11</Id><Topic><Title>5 million shares traded at the open today</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370355064531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:11:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When I open my TDAmeritrade account it automatically opens "Trade Architect". On the "TRADE" page of that program it shows the volume. I also use Yahoo's Stock chart in the one day mode. It shows the volume every minute and institutional buying is easy to spot. There has not been any since the open today. As for the spammers, they really annoy me. It is like they are too cheap to buy an ad. I checked one out yesterday and my E-set virus program warned me that it wanted to put a cookie on my computer.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370359502509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370360127573-12</Id><Topic><Title>Land of the free</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369948675101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you don't think home schooling is under attack, please explain why they are threatening to deport this German family unless they enroll their children in the public school.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370360127573</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:35:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370360638201-13</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“Did you make up that line about "White House records show former IRS Commissioner Douglas Shulman signed in for 11 visits" or is that more propaganda direct from the President?” – wilkes Do yourself a favor, wilkes. Copy and paste the below statement into your search engine: “The Fake Story About the IRS Commissioner and the White House.” Then do yourself an even bigger favor and read some truth for a change. Take your pick – The Atlantic, Politico, dailycaller, huffingtonpost, politicususa, freakoutnation, outsidethebeltway, etc. “Indeed, of the 157 events Shulman was cleared to attend, White House records confirm that he actually went to 11 events over the 2009-2012 period” Those White House log-in records are available to you and the rest of your pathetic pack of dis-information lunatics. Then do us all a favor and either apologize for unintentionally passing along bogus lies from Fox, or simply admit that you are just another paid shill for the far right willing to say anything to harm this administration.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1370360638201</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:43:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370360657539-14</Id><Title>Fake echo...</Title><Msg>Do my eyes deceive me, or has Jon lost another alias? Jon3retired. Bam! Gone! Zonbac98. Bam! Gone! Echo.2l65. Bam! Gone! Jon, are you starting to get the message, or are you too dense to understand?</Msg><Username>hotdoggitwiggie</Username><Timestamp>1370360657539</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:44:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370363894004-15</Id><Topic><Title>2 Million Shares Bought at 12:45</Title><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1370278809964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 13:00:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My apologies bshipley, wilkes71 has shown me on a different post where on other monitoring services the volumn differs from what I see on TDAmeritrades 'StrategyDesk' ,,</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1370363894004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:38:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370364819894-16</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I chose the Daily Caller from your suggested list but the more that I read the confuseder I got. Here are a couple of direct quotes: "When challenged last week by congressional investigators about just 118 of the 157 apparent White House visits, Shulman did not dispute the number, only identifying several reasons why he visited so often." "The liberal Atlantic website published a piece Friday morning speculating that the number of Shulman’s actual White House visits could be as low as 11, despite widespread coverage of those revelations on Thursday." I now see where your "factual" 11 came from but all I can conclude from the rest of the article is that nobody wants to reveal what is really going on behind the curtain. The only apology that I can see that is needed is one from the President for claiming a transparent administration.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370364819894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:53:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370366318820-17</Id><Topic><Title>5 million shares traded at the open today</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370355064531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:11:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4 million more shares traded at 12:41. I was loading up on puts thinking this was just a short term move but I don't think I will buy any more. Somebody must know something.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370366318820</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:18:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370366585632-18</Id><Topic><Title>Fake echo...</Title><Username>hotdoggitwiggie</Username><Timestamp>1370360657539</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:44:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH 'echo/icky' .. you little weiner in a poodle skirt with your other 4 or 5 aliases !! Yes, since he was booted of the board he's been spending a few days in Rodanthe &amp; Avon, in the surf and the 'blue water' 20 miles or so off of Hatteras Inlet. I heard a rumor his arms were a little sore from the 4 Yellowfin he reeled in. At his age his arms aren't quite what they were 2 years ago .. but he'll get over it. In the event he does get a new alias, how can he find a way to squash these petulant little pusilanimous pipsqueek aliases that you keep posting under ?? ..... never mind, getting rid of you flea-bag types will require something larger that Orkin .. maybe you can try huffing something from the middle east .. (Syria ??) ..... I'll pass your message on ....</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1370366585632</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:23:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370368189005-19</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He went to the actual White House 11 times. He went to the Executive Offices adjacent to the White House 157 times. He usually met with people who were charged with implementing the health law. Or, to put it more clearly, he was doing exactly what anyone with any iota of sense would expect him to do. But you and your Tea Brain friends don't have a single iota of sense, do you? All you have is whatever the conservative media told you to think that day.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370368189005</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:49:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370368914714-20</Id><Topic><Title>2 Million Shares Bought at 12:45</Title><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1370278809964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 13:00:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for saying that, good trading to you!</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1370368914714</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370369296384-21</Id><Topic><Title>5 million shares traded at the open today</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370355064531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:11:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you buy Puts today? I don't understand why you did that, but I do hope that it works out for you. As I see it, I see a slim chance that "T's" price might briefly fall to a range of $34.25-34.75 (a testing of the recent bottom), but you better be very agile on covering your option, because the price will most likely bounce right back to today's range, possible on the same day, good Luck to you.</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1370369296384</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:08:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370369297282-22</Id><Topic><Title>Land of the free</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369948675101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are not "threatening to deport this German family unless they enroll their children in public school". That is nonsense--it is simply not what is happening. You clearly have no idea of the facts of the story. Yet you're willing to accuse the US government of attacking homeschooling. It is irresponsible. It is lying. You should be ashamed. This is why people think you are idiots. It is because you are. I certainly can't have a conversation with someone who simply has no clue. So I'll just ask a few simple questions that you should try to answer before you attempt to engage in this discussion: Do you know what asylum is? Do you know what it is usually reserved for? Do you know the process of applying for asylum? Do you think Germany is a despotic government? Do you know where Germany is? Do you know what the European Union is? Do you know if other countries in the European Union allow homeschooling? Do you know in what other countries homeschooling is illegal? Do you think that every person in these countries who decides they want to homeschool should be granted asylum? Once you research those questions you may be able to comment on the subject. Until then, don't comment. You have no idea what you are talking about.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370369297282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:08:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370374306524-23</Id><Topic><Title>5 million shares traded at the open today</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370355064531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:11:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WILKES71, take a look at KO, it might be a nice Divi play at $38.90. I don't own it right now, but I will if I can get it at that price, let me know what you think, thanks.</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1370374306524</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:31:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370374548854-24</Id><Title>This board is proof</Title><Msg>that fascists have free speech.</Msg><Username>freakedout35</Username><Timestamp>1370374548854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:35:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370375858897-25</Id><Topic><Title>5 million shares traded at the open today</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370355064531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:11:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>37 Million, and the price is up, not bad!</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1370375858897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:57:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370375885227-26</Id><Topic><Title>Land of the free</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369948675101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ricky, you don't know this case or you would know that your statement that "multiple judges rejected their application" is absolutely false. A US immigration judge ruled in 2010 that the family did face persecution from the German government and granted the Romeike family political asylum. The family moved and settled in Tennessee. The DOJ and DHS are trying to reverse that judge's decision. I fail to see any good reason to reverse the decision. There is ample proof that they were being persecuted for their Christian Faith. How will the USA benefit by deporting this Concert pianist and his outstanding family? What has it got to do with Homeland Security? What has it got to do with Justice? If you can see nothing sinister about this, your brain has ceased to function.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370375885227</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:58:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370376319191-27</Id><Topic><Title>5 million shares traded at the open today</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370355064531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:11:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Puts are cheap when the stock price is high and calls are cheap when the stock price is low. The calls that I bought for 16 cents yesterday sold for 25 cents today. I'm hoping to sell the 30 puts that I bought cheap today to sell tomorrow at a profit.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370376319191</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:05:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370376835224-28</Id><Topic><Title>This board is proof</Title><Username>freakedout35</Username><Timestamp>1370374548854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:35:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like everyone else as long as you stay politically correct.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370376835224</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:13:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370377846185-29</Id><Title>Finally "daylight come and me" find out what a liberal really thinks</Title><Msg>Harry Belafonte (appearing on MSNBC) recently gave some insight into the thinking and beliefs of some liberal thinkers. When asked how our "dear leader" should take control of the political debate? Mr. Belafonte responded: “That there should be this lingering infestation of really corrupt people who sit trying to dismantle the wishes of the people, the mandate that has been given to Barack Obama, and I don’t know what more they want,” “The only thing left for Barack Obama to do is to work like a third world dictator and just put all these guys in jail.” Belafonte added that Republicans were “violating the American desire,” and described Republicans as an “infestation.” I must say that I admire the candor of the "banana boat man", and now it becomes clear why certain people have become the heroes of the liberal elite (e.g., Fidel Castro, Hugo Chavez, Mao Ce-tung, Che Guevara, etc.). Makes me wonder if the left will be truly satisfied when all of these guys are put in jail? "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1370377846185</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:30:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370378400928-30</Id><Topic><Title>Fake echo...</Title><Username>hotdoggitwiggie</Username><Timestamp>1370360657539</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:44:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahhh...too bad. Well it's only a matter of time and your "personality" will do the rest. Glad you got a little vacation, though I don 't think bobbing for goldfish in a truck stop #$%$ toilet bowl qualifies as reeling in four yellow tail. But even you can dream little man. Even you.</Msg><Username>hotdoggitwiggie</Username><Timestamp>1370378400928</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:40:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370378523133-31</Id><Topic><Title>Finally "daylight come and me" find out what a liberal really thinks</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1370377846185</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:30:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stupid post.</Msg><Username>hotdoggitwiggie</Username><Timestamp>1370378523133</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:42:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370378667887-32</Id><Topic><Title>Land of the free</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369948675101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes he is, as are most of the socialist staff he has appointed or hired. Soon he will be forced to lose his AG and the IRS will never be the same again with all the oversight they will soon be getting. He is not sorry about what the IRS or the Justice Department did, only that they were stupid enough to get caught.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1370378667887</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:44:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370378677619-33</Id><Topic><Title>Land of the free</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369948675101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There is ample proof that they were being persecuted for their Christian Faith." No, wilkes, there is not. The German government requires ALL children to attend school, not just Christian children. The German law has been reviewed by the European High Court of Human Rights. The Romeike's have several options other than applying for asylum--1. send their kids to public school in Germany. 2. Send their kids to private school in Germany. 3. Relocate to another EU country that does not outlaw homeschooling. Asylum usually has a much, much higher bar. "How will the USA benefit by deporting this Concert pianist and his outstanding family?" It does not, but that can be said for 13 million other illegal immigrants. Nor does it matter what jobs they hold when they apply for asylum. I am all for opening up the immigration pool, wilkes, and I'd be happy to let them and many other immigrants stay. But singling out a white, European family by you people--who opposed the DREAM Act of all things--is all too telling. You are what you are and you demonstrate it repeatedly. "What has it got to do with Homeland Security?" "Justice". Nothing. That is not the basis for our immigration laws. "If you can see nothing sinister about this, your brain has ceased to function." Oh grow up. The original ruling is ridiculous. At least 28 countries- in Europe, Latin America, Asia and the Middle East-have banned homeschooling. Kazakstan, Turkey, El Salvador, Moldova, Guatamala, to name a few. Would you like it if we grant asylum to everyone in these countries who decides to homeschool their children? Or just the white, European, Christian ones? You are so transparent. A sinister plot against homeschooling from this? What a joke you Tea Brains are. But if you want to, let them stay. Let EVERYONE who can't legally homeschool in their native countries in through the asylum process. I'm all for it.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370378677619</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:44:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370378763817-34</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, but they had a lot of Easter egg hunts and his isn't very good at finding eggs, only conservative organizations.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1370378763817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:46:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370378908091-35</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you saying that even the MSM is lying about what the WH log shows? Why would they do that? Where did you get your information about what the log shows? The MSM media? The same ones that reported it along with Fox and others. How can you tell who is telling the lies?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1370378908091</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:48:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370379147750-36</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" He usually met with people who were charged with implementing the health law. " Oh, so now your privy to government meeting minutes and the subject matter of those meetings? Since when? Or did you just 'consult' with another liberal web site? It appears you know more about what is going on in the White House than does the President and many of direct reports. Strange don't you think?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1370379147750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370379252135-37</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All they have to do is tell the truth and not a different version of it every time the sock puppet mouth piece gets in front of a TV camera. They haven't been able to do that for several years now.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1370379252135</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:54:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370379520897-38</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go FOX News</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1369912936115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 07:22:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now that is a BIG lie!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1370379520897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:58:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370379799511-39</Id><Topic><Title>Way to go FOX News</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1369912936115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 07:22:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, you and all the other stupid liberals that watch the channels that are among the lowest watched are all right and everyone else is wrong. Because Fox reports something, it has to be wrong or a lie, right? Even when they are reporting the same things as the liberals based MSM outlets. That shows just how brain washed you liberals are. Of course the administration says that everything they don't like is a conservative conspiracy just like the one Hillary found against her lying, cheating, corrupt, immoral husband. The world is wrong, we are right, regardless of the facts or the simple smell of the lies being told. Amazing, simply amazing.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1370379799511</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:03:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370379895074-40</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Rictardo</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1370056426720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 23:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just what sort of 'consulting' do you do?</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1370379895074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:04:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370380781568-41</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How can you tell who is telling the lies?" It's pretty simple, winholder. The ones who report the head of the IRS visited the White House Executive Offices as normal behavior are the honest one, because it's normal behavior. You only have to have a tiny, tiny, little itty bitty bit of sense to know that's normal behavior. Dude heads a large Exec. Branch agency, dude might visit people in the White House where the leadership of the Executive Branch is housed. See how that works? The people who are lying to you are the ones who report it as not normal, at least without further elaboration. So let's try an exercise: Someone says Shulman visited the White House 157 times in four years. How do you react to that? Do you instantly decide it means there's a sinister conspiracy and if you can't read between the lines to see the truth that Obama is going to eat your white babies, you're stupid? Then you're Glen Beck. Or do you think, so what? He's the head of an agency, the White House houses the entire administration, sounds like normal to me. Before I jump to extremely irresponsible and unsupported conclusions I will seek out more information. Then you're Gwen Ifill. That's how you tell the difference between a liar/idiot/shill and a real journalist.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370380781568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:19:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370381161031-42</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would be nice. A simple solution though is to stop watching Fox News.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370381161031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370381384348-43</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“I chose the Daily Caller from your suggested list but the more that I read the confuseder I got.” – wilkes Well, wilkes, you folks repeatedly demonstrate that the more you read, the confuseder you get. You just get wackier and wackier and confuseder and confuseder. Fortunately, you don’t read MUCH, so you may not attain maximum confuserationality. As you well know, I erroneously included the daily caller in the list, as the daily caller was the originator of the lie you want so desperately to snowball into another swift boat effort. That was my error, which afforded you the opportunity to ignore all the other sources and continue throwing out lies of no consequence. If you, or your cronies winbagfrogjon want to debate the actual validity, then start showing some sources who have actually checked the white house logs to back up your ridiculous 157 claim. They’re available to any and all legitimate news sources, if you’re a journalist not a witch hunter. Winholder crying “what’s your source” is pathetic…the source is the white house logs, which serve multiple purposes. It’s hard to believe that you guys see a government official doing his job and complain…if he never went to the WH, you’d complain just as much. “The liberal Atlantic website published a piece Friday morning speculating…” There was no speculation…and how revealing that you find fault with a well respected publication founded by some of the greatest minds of the mid-nineteenth century. Those smart people are scary, alright, and must make you confuseder and confuseder.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1370381384348</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:29:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370382061316-44</Id><Title>OH NOooo!!!</Title><Msg>T can no longers ell old products, LOL!!! http://blogs.barrons.com/techtraderdaily/2013/06/04/apple-may-face-ban-on-some-product-following-samsung-win-say-bloomberg-dj/?mod=yahoobarrons</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1370382061316</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370382714818-45</Id><Topic><Title>Land of the free</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369948675101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THEY HAVE ALREADY BEEN GRANTED ASYLUM!!! They are not illegal aliens. The sinister part is that DOJ and DHS are now spending a great deal of effort to reverse that decision. Don't you wonder WHY?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370382714818</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:51:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370401907896-46</Id><Topic><Title>man my diamonds got diamonds! over 300% in gains!</Title><Username>goodshahs</Username><Timestamp>1370225127725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 22:05:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>enjoy free money! ha im signing up</Msg><Username>rickyross342</Username><Timestamp>1370401907896</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:11:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370401961099-47</Id><Topic><Title>ROSG only the beginning ?? Perhaps the..</Title><Username>ribyklooner</Username><Timestamp>1369955325297</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 19:08:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>im signing up! free gains why not!</Msg><Username>rickyross342</Username><Timestamp>1370401961099</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370402709906-48</Id><Topic><Title>Fake echo...</Title><Username>hotdoggitwiggie</Username><Timestamp>1370360657539</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:44:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YELLOW TAIL TUNA ?? - (ha ha ha, u thtuped idiot) .. uisdumer din dogidu warze yohaed sta parcked .. ukeepzit shubbed upyo office ?? tanks 4 da seben tumz dounz .. ya caweir widdle richerd-haed. nare 'danse' foyo sell maets yo petulant widdle kwaer dekbrane migit .....</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1370402709906</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:25:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370403236112-49</Id><Topic><Title>Fake echo...</Title><Username>hotdoggitwiggie</Username><Timestamp>1370360657539</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:44:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hee..Hee..you drunkier than "ME" is..(!!) YOu As "THTUPED" as is always..(!!)</Msg><Username>jon3retiree</Username><Timestamp>1370403236112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>