<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363412000919-1</Id><Topic><Title>It looks like Obama wants to bankrupt America</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1362778576708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:36:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean boyfriends.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1363412000919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 01:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363412057635-2</Id><Topic><Title>It looks like Obama wants to bankrupt America</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1362778576708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:36:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zombie69, is this really you?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1363412057635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 01:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363431374715-3</Id><Title>Lower target price: $34.00</Title><Msg>Rationale: 1. Company internals continue to deteriorate. Various press releases cite the company's intent to sell none core assets to fund buy backs and more importantly yet the dividend. I would consider the buy backs of secondary nature but the dividend is of paramount importance given that it was raised not long ago. 2. The company is actively engaged in international expansion, i.e. to enter the markets in India, of which they lack the financials to support such market expansion. 3. The overall market is destined to undergo a correction of some kind. In conclusion, it appears that the corporate strategy of basing the revenue and profitability outlook on wireless growth assumptions is becoming optimistic and something has to give. As a result of all these negative factors, we are likely to see the stock price weakening during the days ahead.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1363431374715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 06:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363432396183-4</Id><Topic><Title>Lower target price: $34.00</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1363431374715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 06:56:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Continued.... It seems to me that AT&amp;T is doing things backward. You first sell the the none core assets and then do the buying of whatever looks atrractive in price. For example, a couple of weeks back, they purchased spectrum from VZ for $3 to 4B. It appears that they lacked the financials to support such a transaction. In the meantime, the competition continues to intensify from all angles. DISH, DIRECT-TV and others are likely to create pricing pressures of which in turn will lower the revenue/profitability of the company.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1363432396183</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 07:13:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363436488849-5</Id><Topic><Title>Detailed AT&amp;T Research Report !!!</Title><Username>ashleyjones221</Username><Timestamp>1362156250127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:44:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks !</Msg><Username>philip.durham</Username><Timestamp>1363436488849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 08:21:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363438124276-6</Id><Topic><Title>Organizing for Action</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363135052065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 20:37:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you fall asleep in spelling class?</Msg><Username>mdeare2001</Username><Timestamp>1363438124276</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 08:48:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363439353283-7</Id><Title>AHQ (3)...</Title><Msg>...“May your uncontrolled reveling on St. Patrick’s Day have no permanent consequences.” - Anonymous "Contrariwise, if it was so, it might be; and if it were so, it would be; but as it isn't, it ain't. That's logic." - Lewis Carroll, Alice's Adventures in Wonderland "...They discovered only a small asteroid inhabited by a solitary old man who claimed repeatedly that nothing was true, though he was later discovered to be lying." - Douglas Adams “If seeing this nice lady (Michelle Obama) on TV saying she likes the movies, or nutrition, or exercise fills you with rage, get help.” – Bill Maher “Underneath this flabby exterior is an enormous lack of character.” - Oscar Levant “The only winner in the War of 1812 was Tchaikovsky.” - Soloman Short "I must have missed the moment when racism ended. I wonder when it was? The time Ross dated Aisha Tyler on 'Friends?' Or when Keebler added a black elf? Oh, I know. It must have been when they made slavery illegal in Mississippi all the way back in ... four weeks ago." – Stephen Colbert “All who have meditated on the art of governing mankind have been convinced that the fate of empires depends on the education of youth.” – Aristotle (All but the Tea Party) “One of the most dangerous phases of self-interest in industry has been the part it has played in bringing about wars between nations.” – Kirby Page, The Commercial Motive “The big news is the new Pope. His name is Jorge Mario Bergoglio. If you're saying to yourself, 'Boy, that name sounds familiar,' you're right. For seven years he was the ace reliever for the Yankees.” – David Letterman “Wisdom becomes nonsense in the mouth of a fanatic.” – Otto Schuwdrmr</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1363439353283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:09:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363439370083-8</Id><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Msg>...“St. Patrick’s Day is the one holiday where your full-blown alcoholism could possibly go undetected.” - anonymous “I'll bet your father spent the first year of your life throwing rocks at the stork.” - Irving Brechert “I am the spirit of the morning sea, I am the awakening and the glad surprise.” – Richard Watson Gilder "All tours of the White House have been canceled due to budget concerns. Don't worry, there's another way get into the White House if you don't belong. Fake your birth certificate." - Craig Ferguson "In despair there are the most intense enjoyments, especially when one is very acutely conscious of the hopelessness of one's position." - Fedor Dostoevsky “I've been on so many blind dates, I should get a free dog.” - Wendy Liebman “Republicans in Arkansas passed the strictest abortion law ever…they say in the bill that life begins when your sister gets drunk.” –Bill Maher "A passionately lived life is not always comfortable. Going for it involves being open to all of life - the joys, the sorrows, the mundane as well and the magic, the splendid victories, the most abject defeats. You might even stop closing your eyes during the scary parts of the movie. It takes committed, high energy, full-tilt boogie participation to have the kind of life you want." – Nicholas Lore “Being an optimist after you've got everything you want doesn't count.” – Kin Hubbard "In accordance with Vatican tradition, the cardinals in the papal conclave will release white smoke when a Pope is chosen. The practice was started by those two ancient leaders, Cardinal Cheech and Cardinal Chong.” –Jimmy Fallon “Moping melancholy, And moon-struck madness.” – John Milton, Paradise Lost "Life is just part of the big picture." - Alyson Goff “Have a good weekend, all.” – echo2165 "Strange is our situation here upon Earth." - Albert Einstein</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1363439370083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:09:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363439494636-9</Id><Topic><Title>Detailed AT&amp;T Research Report !!!</Title><Username>ashleyjones221</Username><Timestamp>1362156250127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:44:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good one !</Msg><Username>markchester919</Username><Timestamp>1363439494636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363439528244-10</Id><Title>What if AT&amp;T bought Vodaphone's non-US Assets and sells the 45% of VZ Wireless to VZ</Title><Msg>Someone thinks its a possibility...are their networks compatible? Comments please. AT&amp;T (NYSE:T) is still attracting attention in late afternoon hours. Bank of America analyst David Barden thinks the company might buy Vodafone’s (NASDAQ:VOD) non-U.S. assets for about $70 billion. The deal could help AT&amp;T gain “global scale” and help Verizon Communications (NYSE:VZ) get full control of Verizon Wireless, according to StreetInsider.</Msg><Username>infosecman1</Username><Timestamp>1363439528244</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 09:12:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363444945715-11</Id><Topic><Title>Organizing for Action</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363135052065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 20:37:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bouch was correct, you're an idiot.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1363444945715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 10:42:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363445649786-12</Id><Topic><Title>Guess Who</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1363296073605</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must have failed in your basic reading tests. I NEVER said Bush wasn't responsible for the things he did while in office, I just said that Obama is blaming EVERYTHING for which he has failed to keep his campaign promises on Bush. He preaches to move forward, never look back, don't play the blame game and then blames past events on someone else, constantly talks about the past and blames everyone but himself and his administration. Obama has yet to claim responsibility for anything that has failed under his watch. He won't even claim responsibility for some of his stupid speech...calling the cops dumb before he even knew that full story, having his people claim that Romney caused the cancer death of a woman, calling for more gentle speech and doing just the opposite in his within days, denying he knew anything about the situation in Libya; I could go on, but you know the story, you just won't pay attention.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1363445649786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 10:54:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363455848541-13</Id><Topic><Title>Detailed AT&amp;T Research Report !!!</Title><Username>ashleyjones221</Username><Timestamp>1362156250127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:44:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report !</Msg><Username>oyolam</Username><Timestamp>1363455848541</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 13:44:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363463190626-14</Id><Topic><Title>Detailed AT&amp;T Research Report !!!</Title><Username>ashleyjones221</Username><Timestamp>1362156250127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:44:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks</Msg><Username>roger.morris</Username><Timestamp>1363463190626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 15:46:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363474330873-15</Id><Topic><Title>Detailed AT&amp;T Research Report !!!</Title><Username>ashleyjones221</Username><Timestamp>1362156250127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:44:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for sharing .</Msg><Username>brian.rossi</Username><Timestamp>1363474330873</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 18:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>