<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-21"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363872851452-1</Id><Topic><Title>BCCI --COFFEE UPGRADE ON FIRE!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>sioigtry</Username><Timestamp>1363623709870</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 12:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah it is all the way up to 9 cents.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363872851452</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:34:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363873162094-2</Id><Topic><Title>BCCI Baristas Coffee Company Inc @ 0.09 will be listed in Nasdaq under the symbol BAPI. Now franchising</Title><Username>johnjohn5200</Username><Timestamp>1363797513224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know about undervalued but it is a rare penny stock that makes 25% net profit on a million dollars in total sales for the year. With 8 locations they should do better this year.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363873162094</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:39:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363874378394-3</Id><Title>Balanced budget in five years.</Title><Msg>Ron Paul is presenting a realistic plan to balance the budget in five years. I'm afraid he will get the same results that his dad did. He admits that "President Obama and his big-spending pals in Washington actually believe our expanding budget deficit is sustainable." It is humorous that Obama is so focused on sustainable energy and yet so blind to a sustainable economy.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363874378394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:59:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363874606629-4</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan with his BA and minor in Econ</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1363621508131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 11:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Four revealing statements in one post by ssDepends: “…he was granted access to scholarships because of his color” “…his grades didn't pass muster until the 'black' leverage was applied.” “…not the only black to have been given preferential treatment” “…won’t be the last to enjoy special benefits because of his color.” …followed, incredulously, with this absurdity: “This (sic) not necessarily a racist statement just a fact of life in America.” Uh, sorry, Gomer, but yes it is. You saying otherwise does not make it so. And you folks who don’t get that will continue to make a mockery of your party while being ridiculed by the majority of Americans…so, please, keep it up. Keep saying really stupid things like this, from the same post: “He was elected because most black voters voted for him because of his color…” No he wasn’t and no they didn’t. They voted for him because of the following statistics, showing that what your party represents alienates nearly all people of color (not to mention women and other minorities), and continues to cause your antiquated philosophy to be rejected by the pragmatic and moderate American people of all classes. “In the United States, roughly 85 percent of African-Americans identify as Democrats or left-leaning, according to the American National Election Studies. Only 6 percent said they were Republicans or included to the right. The Washington Post recently estimated that the Republican Party is 92 percent white and that among the remaining 8 percent, blacks were an almost imperceptible sliver.” –Tampa Bay Times, today, 3/21/13 Black voters voted for him because almost NO black voters are Republicans. Did all the white voters vote for Romney because he was white? (uh, besides you bigots, I mean.)</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1363874606629</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363875023348-5</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan with his BA and minor in Econ</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1363621508131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 11:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahhhh, looking for another excuse to apply the old "racist" tag on someone who offers an opinion and didn't mention "race". I contended was he was from Kenya, not because he was Black/ White. University's not just Harvard like a mix of students on campus. Colleges will often accept someone from another part the Country that apply as well. Never used "evil" progressives, you did, apparently you must think progressives are evil. The" shadow cabinet' that Obama has of approximately 20 or more progressives who are influencing his decisions on important issues, including circumventing the Constitution. By your racist rant contending I am an ignorant "hillbilly" (my apology to hillbillies) indicates to me, you cannot like many other Obama supporters accept any criticism of this President</Msg><Username>jim.morris41</Username><Timestamp>1363875023348</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:10:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363875151297-6</Id><Topic><Title>Balanced budget in five years.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363874378394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OOPS. I meant RAND Paul</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363875151297</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363875877794-7</Id><Title>5% is so near</Title><Msg>buy under $36 get 5% div</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1363875877794</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:24:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363875934532-8</Id><Topic><Title>Balanced budget in five years.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363874378394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But would he be getting advice from his lunatic father?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1363875934532</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:25:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363876721813-9</Id><Topic><Title>Balanced budget in five years.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363874378394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His father is a medical doctor and far from a lunatic. In fact he may be the only sane Congressman that we have had in recent history. If they had taken his advice we would not be involved in Afghanistan and would not have invaded Iraq. We would have had a balanced budget for the last 20 years and be one of the very few countries not in debt. If that is lunacy, we need more lunatics in government.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363876721813</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:38:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363877043128-10</Id><Topic><Title>5% is so near</Title><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1363875877794</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:24:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today and tomorrow may be the last chance to buy below $36. T seems to always run up just before dividend and at least mini-crash after dividend.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363877043128</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:44:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363879363004-11</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan with his BA and minor in Econ</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1363621508131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 11:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one is looking for excuses except rwnj's like yourself. The Pres was born in the USA not Kenya, he was kind enough to show records others don't have to. He doesn't need to show school records, until starting with Romney, palin and going back 50 years, every politician shows there school records. You have no idea what Harvard does or doesn't do in admissions. Obama was admitted on his obvious intelligence, a remarkable ability to remember and focus, as well as having the required high grades. Once at Harvard he passed the muster and became president of the Law Review. Later he was a Professor himself. Not enough credentials for you? And you say you aren't a racist, do you? Oh yes, you are a racist.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1363879363004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:22:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363879416852-12</Id><Topic><Title>Balanced budget in five years.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363874378394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to see him speak more, he's a kook.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1363879416852</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:23:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363880130023-13</Id><Topic><Title>Balanced budget in five years.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363874378394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is a kook in the same sense that George Washington was a kook. Both advocate avoiding foreign entanglements.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363880130023</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:35:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363880225662-14</Id><Topic><Title>Balanced budget in five years.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363874378394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has already publicly stated that unless their plans include his additional taxes and other issues the talks won't succeed. He is saying 'compromise means doing what I want'. That is his standard position and it really handcuffs any Democrat in Congress that had thoughts of actually doing their jobs and negotiating something that might help this country.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1363880225662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:37:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363881391247-15</Id><Topic><Title>It looks like Obama wants to bankrupt America</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1362778576708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:36:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bothers you to hear truth doesn't it? Or, perhaps you too are one of the political shills thati inhabit many boards spreading the leftist lies.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1363881391247</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:56:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363884562643-16</Id><Topic><Title>Balanced budget in five years.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363874378394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With Medicare, he wants to basically roll it into Obamacare, so seniors could buy health insurance on a Federal Exchange, with a subsidized high risk pool, and subsidies for low income seniors. He somehow thinks this will be cheaper for seniors (he expects premiums to rise by 90% over Medicare on average, but much of it to be covered by subsidies for lower income seniors) so any savings will come from raising the retirement age to 70 (soemtime in the future) and removing subsidies for higher income seniors. He expects a Medicare budget of $0 in 2014, but then moves the spending to another line "Congressional Health Insurance for Seniors" --which continues to grow at an accelerated rate. So I'm not really sure what he thinks he accomplishes. An Obamacare/Romneycare like exchange for Medicare is not a bad idea, but I'd like to see how they work first. With Social Security, he advocates cutting benefits for well-to-do seniors, and, of course raising the retirement age sometime in the future. Nevertheless his budget includes Social Security spending doubling in the next ten years. Defense spending also continues to rise. So where do the spending cuts come from? You guessed it. Discretionary and safety net spending. Infrastructure, education, unemployment insurance, cut by 50% to 75% this year. In the middle of a slow recovery. All to pay for future increases in old age benefits, which will be severely reduced by the time I retire. He eeks out zero deficit through 2016 but after that unreduced growth in old age spending pushes the deficit back up to half a trillion. So yes, wilkes, I think I know exactly what the Tea Party wants.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1363884562643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363884699699-17</Id><Topic><Title>Balanced budget in five years.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363874378394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If they had taken his advice we would not be involved in Afghanistan and would not have invaded Iraq. We would have had a balanced budget for the last 20 years and be one of the very few countries not in debt." You could say the same for Gore. Probably Obama. Two wars, a few massive tax cuts for the wealthy, a massive recession and here we are!.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1363884699699</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:51:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363884866350-18</Id><Topic><Title>Balanced budget in five years.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363874378394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. He is saying compromise is compromise. Unless Republicans are willing to compromise a teensie tiny bit, there's no point in negotiating. Oh well. . . Obama's too nice. He should just stomp the tea brains. The best place for a tea brain is between asphalt and rubber.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1363884866350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:54:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363884900832-19</Id><Topic><Title>Balanced budget in five years.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363874378394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. He's a kook in an entirely different way.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1363884900832</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:55:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363885164463-20</Id><Topic><Title>It looks like Obama wants to bankrupt America</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1362778576708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:36:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or in your case the right wing corporate lies.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1363885164463</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:59:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363885179565-21</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan with his BA and minor in Econ</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1363621508131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 11:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“…so, please, keep it up. Keep saying really stupid things” – my response to diaper boy, earlier. And right on cue… Ask (for people to say more stupid things) and ye shall receive “…didn't mention ‘race’. I contended was he was from Kenya…The ‘shadow cabinet' that Obama has of approximately 20 or more progressives who are influencing his decisions on important issues, including circumventing the Constitution” – Depends response As long as you choose to continue making a fool out of yourself, rather than simply passing along mindless and meaningless Birther nonsense, kindly do the following so we can discuss it: Give us all sourced information (with references) you have proving that the President is from Kenya. Please explain what you ditto heads mean when you use the term “progressives” in an arbitrarily derisive fashion. What specifically frightens you about the standard accepted definition, meaning “moving forward, advancing, promoting or favoring progress”? Are you really afraid of progress, or is that simply double-speak for wanting to protect the status quo of the 2% special interests you represent? Please also list the 20 or more “progressives” who are influencing the President’s decisions. Are Presidents no longer permitted to have advisors? Would you like to call them “Czars” for more scare tactic propaganda as you’ve previously done? Would you like to have seen a complete novice and intellectual light-weight like George W. Bush govern entirely on his own without the benefit of advisors? Last, please explain exactly how these behind the scenes bogey-men are conspiring to circumvent the Constitution. Please be specific there, if you will…you know, something like Mr. Reagan did…trading arms for hostages and circumventing both The Constitution AND Congress by clandestinely fighting an undeclared war in Central America from the basement of The White House, while claiming ignorance. Or, just have Lavender blather about The New World “Odor”. Please…more stupid stuff from the Legions of The Stupid. And this just in: GOP Bolsters Ranks Routers: Possum Holler, Alabama 3/21/13 As a reaction to a belief that President Obama won this past election based solely on black voter turnout, which they feel was entirely racially motivated, rather than the intolerance of their own party’s platform, GOP Chairman, Reince Priebus, today announced a new voter registration drive targeting a very large segment of the Tea Party movement and like minded supporters. They’re looking to capture the votes of a huge segment of their base, particularly in rural, red states, by going after potential voters with IQ’s in the single digit to low-teen numbers. They are introducing this new program with a national PR effort, including the campaign slogan, “You’re Never Too Stupid for the Republican Party” “We feel we already have most of them,” said Priebus, “but few of them are registered, most don’t read or have a TV, and the others either couldn’t find their way to the polls, or were still too drunk from the weekend to realize it was Tuesday on election day. We’re countering that next time with free rides to the polls in NASCAR style pick-up trucks and free kegs, horseshoes and a gun show at every polling place. While not officially sanctioned, specific locations will also include rattlesnake handling, Ted Nugent music, and possibly, a lynching or two.” Disclaimer: this information is satirical only, and should be taken with the same credibility as the yellow cake uranium reason offered up to justify invading another country.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1363885179565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363885991188-22</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan with his BA and minor in Econ</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1363621508131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 11:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you think Kenya is "another part of the country"? Another part of the same country Harvard is in? It is not the fact of your criticism but its nature that displays your ignorance. You need to start from that premise and try to criticize intelligently. So please, try again, without references to Kenya or shadow cabinets or the idea that a multiracial poor kid had an unfair advantage in life compared to the likes of Bush, Romney, or John Kerry. Otherwise people will continue to think you are ignorant because you provide ample evidence that you are.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1363885991188</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:13:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363890070339-23</Id><Title>The Washington Post</Title><Msg>The Washington Post The Arctic Ocean is warming up, icebergs are growing scarcer and in some places the seals are finding the water too hot, according to a report to the Commerce Department yesterday from Consulafft, at Bergen , Norway Reports from fishermen, seal hunters, and explorers all point to a radical change in climate conditions and hitherto unheard-of temperatures in the Arctic zone. Exploration expeditions report that scarcely any ice has been met as far north as 81 degrees 29 minutes. Soundings to a depth of 3,100 meters showed the gulf stream still very warm. Great masses of ice have been replaced by moraines of earth and stones, the report continued, while at many points well known glaciers have entirely disappeared. Very few seals and no white fish are found in the eastern Arctic, while vast shoals of herring and smelts which have never before ventured so far north, are being encountered in the old seal fishing grounds. Within a few years it is predicted that due to the ice melt the sea will rise and make most coastal cities uninhabitable. * * * * * * * * * I apologize, I neglected to mention that this report was from November 2, 1922, as reported by the AP and published in The Washington Post - 90 years ago. *****************</Msg><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1363890070339</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363890849972-24</Id><Title>It looks like Obama gets the medal of distinction</Title><Msg>from Israel. Too bad for the rwnj's, they're so so wrong, about everything A-Z.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1363890849972</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:34:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363890993225-25</Id><Topic><Title>The Washington Post</Title><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1363890070339</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd suggest you be wary of "reports from fishermen, seal hunters and explorers" from 1922. What you should be looking at is the global concensus among modern scientists who have far better tools and methods at their disposal. But hey, I know you guys are stuck in the past. If a message from seal hunters in 1922 gets you to see the light, well I think that's just swell!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1363890993225</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363894921436-26</Id><Topic><Title>The Washington Post</Title><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1363890070339</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you have any more similar articles? There has to be a lot more global warming krap to read and laugh about. It's an huge improvement over the spam and other BS that gets posted. Excellent post! Well deserved Thumb Up mate.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1363894921436</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:42:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363896198485-27</Id><Topic><Title>It looks like Obama gets the medal of distinction</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1363890849972</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:34:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, he dis stink allright!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1363896198485</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363896311750-28</Id><Title>A ho hum week</Title><Msg>So far this week the closing price has been within pennies each day right around $36.16. Today it looks like it will again close within pennies. All week the price has not varied more than 35 cents. Except for Monday when volume hit 51M, volume has been about average. This must be the lull before the run up for dividend.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363896311750</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:05:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363896803324-29</Id><Topic><Title>It looks like Obama gets the medal of distinction</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1363890849972</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:34:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That crowd that "greeted" Obama did not look very friendly, burning the American flag and waiving all those derogatory signs. When they get his limousine back from the shop they better check it real close for explosives.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363896803324</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:13:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363897467729-30</Id><Topic><Title>The Washington Post</Title><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1363890070339</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And here is your up to date report from all those modern scientists. "Averaged over all land and ocean surfaces, temperatures have warmed roughly 1.33°F (0.74ºC) over the last century,"</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363897467729</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:24:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363898384348-31</Id><Topic><Title>The Washington Post</Title><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1363890070339</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Averaged over all land and ocean surfaces, temperatures have warmed roughly 1.33°F (0.74ºC) over the last century," That is correct, but you left out the next sentence: "Average temperatures have risen more quickly since the late 1970s (0.31 to 0.45°F per decade)." So just about all of the temperature increase has been in the past forty years. previous decade averages were in the 0.14 degree range. Just search for the EPA's climate change page. But I'm not hear to argue climatology with you. I'm smart enough to defer to the experts on things I don't know much about. Are you? Or will you decide it was cold last week so entire scientific community studying the issue must be wrong and Rush must be right?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1363898384348</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:39:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363898510893-32</Id><Topic><Title>Balanced budget in five years.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363874378394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The world has changed in huge ways since George was in power. Now information is passed along in seconds not days or even weeks as it did back then. Very little way to make any comparisons on international affairs. We do need to stop spending what we do not have and we do need to stop overpaying gov't employees(including pensions). The gov't is creating the haves and have nots as fast as anyone.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1363898510893</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:41:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363900193651-33</Id><Topic><Title>Balanced budget in five years.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363874378394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very excellent points. My father-in-law went to work for the Post Office in 1926 at 25 cents per hour because he liked the pension they offered. He died in 1953 and the pension supported his widow until 1998. Now the same job pays $47 per hour and the pension is even better. In WWII I was paid $21 per month plus $50 jump pay plus my wife got $40. My grandson is in the Army now and gets over $3,000 per month including housing allowance. It is no wonder we have a national deficit and the post office has to keep raising postage rates.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363900193651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:09:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363901140094-34</Id><Topic><Title>The Washington Post</Title><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1363890070339</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rush has a pretty good batting average and he says the temperature has been dropping for the last 8 years so that proves the EPA has been doing a great job; because before the EPA the temperature has never dropped. I think he was just being his usual comical self.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363901140094</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363902082055-35</Id><Title>Will the Keystone pipeline ever be approved?</Title><Msg>The current administration has held up approval of the Keystone pipeline for the stated reason of environmental concerns. For the American people this would seem to be a laudatory reason that shows great judgement and concern for the environment. So then Johnny asks that great Wizard of Washington "Oh great wizard is their an alternative for getting oil from Canada?" And the Wizard says "Well Johnny yes there is; we can put that oil in railroad tanker cars, and move the oil that way." Johnny then exclaims "Wow! Mr. Wizard you sure are smart. Do you know anyone that has a railroad that could do that job?" The wizard responds: "Well Johnny that's why I am the Wizard. I have a friend who owns a big railroad company that says he is more than willing to step up and do the job, because he knows how concerned I am about the environment." Then Johnny says: "Wow Mr. Wizard! It must be wonderful to have so many rich and powerful friends." The Wizard responds: "Yes it is Johnny, yes it is." "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1363902082055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:41:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363902783196-36</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Keystone pipeline ever be approved?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1363902082055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't they build a refinery in Canada? I guess then they would need a whole bunch of pipelines to ship the different products from the refinery to market. Obviously I don't know what I am talking about but I never let that stop me from asking questions. I recall there were environmental concerns about the pipelines in Alaska and they turned out to be helpful to the environment.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363902783196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:53:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>