<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-18"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361166112064-1</Id><Topic><Title>Zonbac on ricky</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1361021210353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 08:26:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dan2003hr and zonbac98 = twins!</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361166112064</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 00:41:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361192325003-2</Id><Topic><Title>Presidential Awards</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1360978916900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 20:41:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems you are mixing apples and oranges. Unlike you, I will avoid being tacky about it.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1361192325003</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 07:58:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361197076521-3</Id><Title>Speaking of awards...</Title><Msg>... “More proof of MSM's selection process in reporting…” - ssdepends “…you can't understand what you read but also indicates that you believe all the hog wash in the MSM…” - wilkes “That is just an excuse the Democrats use to help the MSM…” – pinhighshot “…your president and the MSM has "singled" out military look alike style rifles !!” – zonbacjon “I know that the MSM and the dems believe that our "Dear Leader" beat the heck out of that pesky little man made of tar, but I guess time will tell whose lunch ultimately gets consumed.” – The Frogg Less “Guys like echo and the MSM have small minds with a large inability to recognize important issues that might have an impact on all of us.” - windandale Ah, yes, the source of all the problems in the world according to the usual suspects above, who are united in knowing that only they know the truth, and suggesting everyone else is united in a conspiracy against them…everyone else being, “The Main Stream Media”…those dastardly villains who, in a conspiracy of leftist, radical, socialistic rage to overthrow our government and destroy our way of life, will stop at nothing to capture and dominate every aspect of what we see, read and hear, and twist facts to fuel their vision of world domination at the expense of Mom, apple pie, guns and fundamentalist values. Or, as most sane people call them…The Free Press, which last time I checked, was also included in The First Amendment for all you Constitution thumpers. And look here, will you? The annual Polk Award winners for 2012, just announced. Somehow, it would appear that Fox was overlooked. Paging Mr. Murdoch…paging Mr. Limbaugh… That’s right, windandalejonwilkesfrog…apparently professional journalists and the rest of the world, think you folks are relying on a very small segment and a very biased source for your journalistic input. It’s remarkable how you want to tell everybody else that they’re wrong, while you vilify legitimate news sources, criticize the “Intelligentsia”, ridicule public education and fawn over dimwits like Bachman, Palin, Cain, etc.…not to mention having illiterates like jon and rob representing you here. “The George Polk Awards are conferred annually to honor special achievement in journalism. They were established by Long Island University in 1949…Some of the most respected names in journalism have won Polk Awards, including Edward R. Murrow, Christiane Amanpour, Carl Bernstein, David Halberstam, Gay Talese, Fred Friendly, I.F. Stone, Morley Safer, Joseph Lelyveld, Anthony Lukas and Walter Cronkite.” List of 2012 Winners: Political Reporting Mother Jones Foreign Reporting The New York Times Television News Reporting CBS News War Reporting McClatchy Newspapers Video Reporting GlobalPost National Reporting Bloomberg News Local Reporting Milwaukee Journal Sentinel Magazine Reporting The New Yorker Justice Reporting The New York Times State Reporting California Watch Medical Reporting The Washington Post Business Reporting The New York Times Education Reporting Maine Sunday Telegram Documentary TV Reporting Frontline</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361197076521</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 09:17:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361199144925-4</Id><Topic><Title>Busted</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1361016149006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 07:02:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If you need to try to make a political point that all murderers are motivated by political affiliation, so be it." Murders occur at a much greater rate per 100k population in black areas. The fact that blacks in the country are in the high 90 percentile democrats is a separate but related issue. I see it as the gov't saying take it from us instead of robing and killing to get enough to get by.</Msg><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1361199144925</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 09:52:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361208197390-5</Id><Title>70B debt, 70B goodwill and 144% payout ratio</Title><Msg>who am i ? AT&amp;T</Msg><Username>invstr_msg</Username><Timestamp>1361208197390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 12:23:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361215466045-6</Id><Topic><Title>Speaking of awards...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361197076521</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 09:17:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Echo thinks that all these awards they have won are something special, but he forgot that most of the awards are being given by their coworkers in the same industry. This is just another coke or ego fueled rant when he couldn't find anything useful to accomplish with his time. As they say in Texas, all hat and no cattle...but a lot of cattle waste. They are all competent at writing stories, it is just the spin, or outright lies that often get added to their work. How many times has NBC or CBS had to retract stories because they were being sued for…setting up car crashes to create fires, having a national reporter fired for using what he knows was invented information for a big story. They should stick to reporting the news, not creating it. If you want to call something an editorial, that is one thing, but you shouldn’t editoralize in a ‘news’ story.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1361215466045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 14:24:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361215699477-7</Id><Topic><Title>Busted</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1361016149006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 07:02:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't good old Dan lose his job over this story?</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1361215699477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 14:28:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361215948394-8</Id><Topic><Title>Presidential Awards</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1360978916900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 20:41:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But, like most of the politicians, you didn't include any statistics about how many of those murders were committed with legally purchased weapons versus those stolen or purchased from the thief's. None of the gun banishment team includes how few murders are committed with the so-called assault weapons either. Wonder why? Guns laws will not stop, won't even slow down the criminals access to guns, it will only make them more brave knowing that more and more law abiding citizens are less likely to be armed.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1361215948394</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 14:32:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361229733682-9</Id><Title>Ban Democrats from guns</Title><Msg>67% of firearm murders took place in the country’s 50 largest metro areas. The 62 cities in those metro areas have a firearm murder rate of 9.7, more than twice the national average. Among teenagers the firearm murder rate is 14.6 or almost three times the national average. Those are the crowded cities of Obama's America. Those are the places with the most restrictive gun control laws and the highest crime rates. And many of them have been run by Democrats and their political machines for almost as long as they have been broken. Obama won every major city in the election, except for Jacksonville and Salt Lake City. And the higher the death rate, the bigger his victory. He won New Orleans by 80 to 17 where the murder rate is ten times higher than the national average. He won Detroit, where the murder rate of 53 per 100,000 people is the second highest in the country and twice as high as any country in the world, including the Congo and South Africa. He won it 73 to 26. And then he celebrated his victory in Chicago where the murder rate is three times the statewide average. In 2006, the 54% of the population living in those 50 metro areas was responsible for 67% of armed killings nationwide. Those are disproportionate numbers especially when you consider that for the people living in most of those cities walking into a store and legally buying a gun is all but impossible. Mayors of Obama's American cities blame guns because it’s easier than blaming people and now the President of America has turned to the same shameless tactic. The NRA counters that people kill people, but that’s exactly why Obama's American leaders would rather talk about the guns. Chicago, the capital of Obama's America, is a city run by gangs and politicians. It has 68,000 gang members, four times the number of police officers. Chicago politicians solicit the support of gang members in their campaigns, accepting laundered contributions from them, hiring their members and tipping them off about upcoming police raids. And their biggest favor to the gang bosses is doing nothing about the epidemic of gang violence. 80% of Chicago’s murders are gang-related. But in 1999 when a bill came up in the Illinois State Senate to charge anyone carrying out a firearm attack on school property as an adult, a law that would have largely affected gang members, the future leader of Obama's America voted present. Had he not voted present, it is doubtful that he would have been reelected in an area where gang leaders wield a great deal of influence. The majority of murders in the cities with the worst homicide rates are gang-related. And while it isn’t always possible to be certain whether a killing was gang-related, the majority of homicide victims in city after city have been found to have criminal records. In 2010, there were 11,078 firearm homicides in the United States and over 2,000 known gang-related killings, over 90% of which are carried out with firearms. Since 1981, Los Angeles alone has had 16,000 gang related homicides. That’s more than twice the number of Americans killed in Iraq and Afghanistan. This is what Obama's America looks like. It’s a place where life is cheap and illegal guns are as available as illegal drugs. It’s the war that we aren’t talking about, because it’s easier to talk about the inanimate objects being used to fight that war. There are, as John Edwards said, two Americas. America is a country that runs pretty well. And then there’s Obama's America. Not all of Obama's America is broken, but a lot of it is. America does not have a gun violence problem. Obama's America does. And Obama's America has a gun violence problem for the same reason that it has a drug problem and a broken family problem. Democratic leaders and machines, combined with social workers and justice crusaders have run Obama's America into the ground. Obama's American cities used to be the homes of industry and progress. Now they’re places where young Black and Hispanic men kill each other in growing numbers. America does not need gun control. It is a mostly law-abiding place. And gun control cannot help Obama's America. Not when its murder rate is driven by gangs who have no trouble obtaining anything; whether it’s legal in the United States or not. This country does not need to have a conversation about how many bullets should go in a clip. It does need to have a conversation about how many parents should go in a family. It needs to talk about the ghettos of Obama's America and have a serious conversation about broken families and generational dependency. Obama has become a role model to millions of people in the black community. If anyone can address these problems, it’s him. But instead of trying to solve the problems of Obama's America, instead of doing something about the high levels of unemployment, the broken families and the glamorization of drug dealing and violent crime, he wimped out and picked a fight with rural America. AIDS prevention was sabotaged by the claim that the disease was a general problem spreading through the population. It wasn’t. Neither is gun violence. Adam Lanza is as much of a poster boy for gun violence, as Ryan White was for AIDS. A better poster boy for gun violence might be Jay-Z, who boasts of having been a drug dealer and claims to have shot his brother at the age of 12. The drug dealer to millionaire rapper is the Horatio Alger story of Obama's America. And Jay-Z can be seen partying with Obama. If Obama really wants to get serious about gun violence, then all he has to do is turn to the man standing next to him. But Obama, like every Chicago politician before him, don’t want to end the violence. The death toll is profitable, not just for rappers writing bad poetry about dealing drugs and shooting rivals, but for the politicians atop that heap who score money and gain power by using the problems of Obama's America as some sort of call to conscience for the rest of the country. That’s what Obama is doing now. Hiding behind Newtown and adorable little kids is the grim specter of Obama's America death toll. It’s buried inside the gruesome figures of how many Americans are shot each year issued as an indictment against the entire country in general and gun owners in particular. But those numbers are not an indictment of America. They are an indictment of Democratic mayors and liberal social policy. They are an indictment of Obama. We need to set aside the same old tired social justice rhetoric and have a serious conversation about what is wrong with New Orleans, Detroit and Chicago. And we need to do it before it’s too late.</Msg><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1361229733682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 18:22:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361230091754-10</Id><Topic><Title>Speaking of awards...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361197076521</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 09:17:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “Echo thinks that all these awards they have won are something special, but he forgot that most of the awards are being given by their coworkers in the same industry.” I see…so peer recognition from professionals in the field of recognition is a bad thing, is it? And who would you have judge who should be recognized for an award for Journalism…migrant farm workers? “As they say in Texas, all hat and no cattle…” As they say in Texas, “Hell, what’s a little air pollution among friends? Is that tobacco juice on your lapel? Hey, there’s a rattlesnake round-up in Frognot this weekend…bring booze and guns. Hoo-Haw, let’s us secede from these lefties!”</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361230091754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 18:28:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361231727982-11</Id><Topic><Title>70B debt, 70B goodwill and 144% payout ratio</Title><Username>invstr_msg</Username><Timestamp>1361208197390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 12:23:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who are you? Ignored.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1361231727982</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 18:55:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361238344322-12</Id><Topic><Title>Baltimore City Police Academy Shut Down</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1361065864211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 20:51:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, we unfortunately have hired some Officers, over the last several years, who are illiterate, and should not be on the force. That is why, our Founders knew that your personal safety, rests with the individual. Hence, our rights should not be infringed.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1361238344322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 20:45:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361238774182-13</Id><Title>Pres on Golf Vacation Again</Title><Msg>Gas is up to $5 a gallon around many areas of the Country. Our Defense Department is scheduled to take a big hit, do to the automatic budget cuts. I'm worried. Will this guy ever start governing? We can cut some welfare folks a little to keep America safe. OBAMA, THE ELECTION IS OVER. TIME TO ACT!!!</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1361238774182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 20:52:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361247955118-14</Id><Topic><Title>70B debt, 70B goodwill and 144% payout ratio</Title><Username>invstr_msg</Username><Timestamp>1361208197390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 12:23:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do not ask just see the balance sheet. I am shorting this with a good reason if you need to know. the only place they have cashflow will be eat'n by paid cards and wi-fi coming near you from GOOG and FCC. think of wi-fi as the , this is just the start of building wi-fi throught the country.</Msg><Username>invstr_msg</Username><Timestamp>1361247955118</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 23:25:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>