<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367067599450-1</Id><Topic><Title>Journalism is Dead at Yohoo</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1367021559155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 20:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sounds like your already irritated,, must b that time of the month</Msg><Username>yp_steve_ardmore_416</Username><Timestamp>1367067599450</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 08:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367072353153-2</Id><Topic><Title>$37.25</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1364849217249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 16:46:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I was superstitious Mike, I wouldn't have stepped on the chalk line when I played baseball. Was just kidding you anyways about jinxing. Gotta take a break from the Trollers and anti-union clowns that we have to contend with and add some levity with guys like you that bring good posts to the board.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367072353153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 10:19:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367072879671-3</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are killing T</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842470940</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:27:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't thumb you down pep. I'll be happy to get back to you on this later with more on the subject. In a way, I'd prefer not too because the teaching profession is one i respect greatly. However, it goes beyond the profession. It is the teachers unions I have my complaint about and how the dues are allocated.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367072879671</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 10:27:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367073026920-4</Id><Title>There aint nothing going to stick to old "Mr. Slick"</Title><Msg>You really have to hand it to "Mr. Slick", the man has jewels the size of basket balls. In his Saturday address he said: o "This week, the sequester hurt travelers, who were stuck for hours in airports and on planes, and rightly frustrated by it. And, maybe because they fly home each weekend, the members of Congress who insisted these cuts take hold finally realized that they actually apply to them too," o "So Congress passed a temporary fix. A Band-Aid. But these cuts are scheduled to keep falling across other parts of the government that provide vital services for the American people," o "There is only one way to truly fix the sequester: by replacing it before it causes further damage," o They may not feel the pain felt by kids kicked off Head Start, or the 750,000 Americans projected to lose their jobs because of these cuts, or the long-term unemployed who will be further hurt by them. But that pain is real," So based upon the above remarks and his disdain for law makers, my expectation is that "Mr. Slick" will refuse to sign the bill when it is presented to him. That would show true leadership and the strength of his convictions. Or do you think he will use his time tested tactic of bad mouthing congress, quietly signing the bill into law, and then jetting off on Air Force 1 for a golf date with the Tiger. I guess we will see, but if I was a betting man I would pick the latter, because nothing sticks to old "Mr. Slick". "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1367073026920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 10:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367076530586-5</Id><Topic><Title>There aint nothing going to stick to old "Mr. Slick"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1367073026920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 10:30:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>of course he'll sign it, he's a spineless Trojan Horse. All talk, never missing a chance to give another "Preaching for Victims" and using even those opportunities to fund-raise.</Msg><Username>cantgthrtondirt</Username><Timestamp>1367076530586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:28:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367086400970-6</Id><Title>Mr. Slick ObaMessiah hides pension bailout in Transportation Bill !</Title><Msg>Buried in a transportation bill that President Obama signed on July 6, 2012, was a change to make it appear pension plans are better funded than they really are. The bill was called Map-21 "Moving Ahead for Progress in the 21st Century Act". (source: Mish Shedlock's blog) Allows pensions to value assets now ON A 25-YEAR INTEREST RATE AVERAGE.</Msg><Username>cantgthrtondirt</Username><Timestamp>1367086400970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 14:13:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367098399596-7</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. Slick ObaMessiah hides pension bailout in Transportation Bill !</Title><Username>cantgthrtondirt</Username><Timestamp>1367086400970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 14:13:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Review civics class, how a bill becomes law. Who thought of , wrote, and voted for any bill, before our President signs it? Write your congressman with your analysis, it means nmore than this here. What you say is just tall tales anyway, lies, from an obsession with Obama, who is not running for election. Have at it, means nothing.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367098399596</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 17:33:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367100074562-8</Id><Topic><Title>$37.25</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1364849217249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 16:46:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hope sooo !! thanks</Msg><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1367100074562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 18:01:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367105059871-9</Id><Topic><Title>Mass Gov Patrick Seals Records</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1367022719383</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 20:31:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well look at that jon has a new alias..(!!)</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367105059871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 19:24:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367108954579-10</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. Slick ObaMessiah hides pension bailout in Transportation Bill !</Title><Username>cantgthrtondirt</Username><Timestamp>1367086400970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 14:13:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What part of is a lie?</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367108954579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 20:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367110091738-11</Id><Title>Obama admin halts questioning to Boston bombing suspect</Title><Msg>Lawmakers are demanding to know why Tsarnaev, who has confessed to being involved in the planting of two bombs near the Boston Marathon finish line, was read his Miranda rights in the middle of his interrogation. Tsarnaev had been under interrogation for about 16 hours in his hospital room before a magistrate and representatives from the U.S. Attorney’s Office entered the room and read him his Miranda rights. He then stopped talking, according to sources briefed on the interrogation. Lawmakers have called for Tsarnaev to be considered an enemy combatant, but the Obama administration opted to try him in civilian criminal court proceedings instead.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367110091738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 20:48:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367110482460-12</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. Slick ObaMessiah hides pension bailout in Transportation Bill !</Title><Username>cantgthrtondirt</Username><Timestamp>1367086400970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 14:13:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's uncalled for.</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367110482460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 20:54:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367110544204-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin halts questioning to Boston bombing suspect</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367110091738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 20:48:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for this timely and informative post about ATT. Flagged.</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367110544204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 20:55:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367110573680-14</Id><Topic><Title>There aint nothing going to stick to old "Mr. Slick"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1367073026920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 10:30:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Off topic. Go elsewhere.</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367110573680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 20:56:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367110933432-15</Id><Title>Obama admin paying foreign labor unions</Title><Msg>Labor Department appears to be spending millions in taxpayer dollars to establish labor unions and promote collective bargaining in foreign countries. At a time when our federal budget is deteriorating rapidly it is troubling to us that the department is spending millions of dollars of taxpayer funds to establish labor unions and promote collective bargaining in foreign countries. The Obama admin recently awarded a Colombian labor organization $1.5 million to help workers improve their collective bargaining rights and $2.2 million to the Solidarity Center, an AFL-CIO organization, to strengthen unions in Haiti and Peru. In addition, the bureau awarded a $1.5 million grant to an international development companyto assist labor unions in Vietnam engage in collective bargaining</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367110933432</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 21:02:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367111342915-16</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin halts questioning to Boston bombing suspect</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367110091738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 20:48:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are welcome it is all about communication</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367111342915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 21:09:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367112153097-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin halts questioning to Boston bombing suspect</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367110091738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 20:48:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah right, Obama Obama Obama. hahahahaha</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367112153097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 21:22:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367112333433-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin paying foreign labor unions</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367110933432</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 21:02:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah right, One stupid post after another for you, for what? Makes you feel good? Nothing on TV? Obama Obama Obama hahahahahaha</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367112333433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 21:25:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367112595580-19</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. Slick ObaMessiah hides pension bailout in Transportation Bill !</Title><Username>cantgthrtondirt</Username><Timestamp>1367086400970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 14:13:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Start with the title. Read it. Anything else?</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367112595580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 21:29:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367112976531-20</Id><Topic><Title>Mass Gov Patrick Seals Records</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1367022719383</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 20:31:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are no Obama welfare phones. Don't exist, so there goes the rest of your conspiracy theory, right out the flaming window. George Bush started the current plan. Something like it has been ongoing for decades. Your Grandma probably gets the discount on her bill. Why don't you go read something with facts.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367112976531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 21:36:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367113843677-21</Id><Title>Obamacare key author calls it a train wreck and will quit</Title><Msg>Sen. Max Baucus (D-MT) will not seek re-election in 2014. As Chairman of the Senate Finance Committee, Sen. Baucus was one of the key authors of President Obama’s health care, yet called the implementation of the law a “huge train wreck coming down.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367113843677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 21:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367114064038-22</Id><Topic><Title>Obama admin halts questioning to Boston bombing suspect</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367110091738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 20:48:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting response. I quess you liberals find the Boston bombing funny</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367114064038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 21:54:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367115170166-23</Id><Topic><Title>Boston Attack</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1366769669831</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 22:14:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>John Boehner is that you?</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367115170166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 22:12:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367116298841-24</Id><Title>Obama admin secretly tries to avoid Obamacare</Title><Msg>No argument that Members of Congress do not want Obamacare to apply to them. Senate congressional Democrat leadership working in cahoots with Obama Administration officials—have been secretly negotiating for months trying to find a way to exempt Members of Congress and their staffs from being forced into Obamacare’s health insurance exchanges. Beginning on January 1, 2014, these exchanges, to be run by the federal government or the states will offer federally “qualified” insurance coverage for millions of Americans. Ordinary Americans must either sign up or face a tax penalty. Henry Chao, an Administration official involved with the implementation of the law hopes that Americans can avoid a “third-world experience.” There are two major reasons why Members of Congress want to exempt themselves and their staffs from the terms and conditions of the law: 1.They fear higher health care costs. Congressional leaders fear that being forced into the Obamacare exchanges will result in higher health care costs for themselves and their families and their aides. This is also true for millions of ordinary Americans. They could also lose their employer-based coverage, and they could also face higher costs. Also contrary to the President’s promises, independent analysts expect health insurance premiums to rise sharply, particularly for younger workers and their families. 2.They fear the impact on Capitol Hill employment. ordinary Americans who run businesses are also faced with anxieties, particularly whether they will be able to hire or retain valued employees or reduce full-time workers to part-time employees in order to avoid Obamacare’s mandatory costs.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367116298841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 22:31:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>