<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-14"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360824698572-1</Id><Title>The Street Report, (CRAMER) 2/12/2013</Title><Msg>Generally good, concise report. Buy rating with a target price of $44.30. Is this a credible report? Absolutely positively since with the stated target price, the stock would end up yielding 4%. IMO, the norm for high quality companies like AT&amp;T is more like 3.5%. The stock price may undergo some weaknesses during the next couple of days mainly because of the CTL's dividend reduction announcement of today and the excessive debt of that company.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360824698572</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 01:51:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360846932848-2</Id><Title>AMR, US Airways to Merge in an $11 Billion Deal</Title><Msg>We have now move from 4 major air lines to 3. I can not belieeve they are going to let this deal go through after the T deal failed. http://www.cnbc.com/id/100459636</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1360846932848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 08:02:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360848339733-3</Id><Topic><Title>AMR, US Airways to Merge in an $11 Billion Deal</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1360846932848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 08:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>American is bankrupt, dude. They don't have a choice but to approve a merger. Try comparing apples to apples next time.</Msg><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1360848339733</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 08:25:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360855721552-4</Id><Topic><Title>For chart believers</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360769956493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:39:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No I don't believe that but do the math. 4,000 to the 12 power comes out to 16 billion. Today I am losing a few bucks because I thought T would go up and it went down instead. By the end of the day it may be up. Who knows?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360855721552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 10:28:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360855760962-5</Id><Title>The borders have "never been stronger"</Title><Msg>The Hill reported yesterday: "Homeland Security Secretary Janet Napolitano insisted Wednesday that U.S. borders have “never been stronger” during a Senate hearing on immigration reform." Wow I know that made me feel better until I read about Chicago's new public enemy number 1 (Joaquin "El Chapo" Guzman ). It appears that Mr. Guzman has reached this heady status, because he has made Chicago the final destination for the bulk of his imported Mexican medical products that are used by the good citizens of Chicago for self medication. It just boggles the mind regarding the amount of self medication the good people of Chicago could be doing if Janet hadn't made the borders so strong. Thank you Janet for saving the good people of Chicago from themselves. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360855760962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 10:29:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360856209294-6</Id><Topic><Title>For chart believers</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360769956493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:39:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It has been 66 years since I left math in high school. I think I am getting too old to do the math. It should be 2 to the 12 power times $4,000 and that only comes out to 16 million.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360856209294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 10:36:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360856382961-7</Id><Topic><Title>The borders have "never been stronger"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360855760962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 10:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The borders are the same as they have always been. At this time, Obama has cost businesses so many jobs that there is no reason to leave unemployment across the border to come to unemployment on either side. So fewer are attempting to cross. Again Obama uses numbers to create a false impression. The presidency of deceit, not lying, intentional and directed deceit.</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1360856382961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 10:39:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360856568849-8</Id><Topic><Title>For chart believers</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360769956493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:39:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ricky must have plagiarized that from somewhere. agreeing with ricky and what ricky posts is the definition of gullibility.</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1360856568849</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 10:42:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360856859141-9</Id><Topic><Title>For chart believers</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360769956493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:39:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Regardless of which math you choose to use, ricky's typical kool aid math, or mathematics, you are dreaming!!!!!!! Wake up wilkes wake up</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1360856859141</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 10:47:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360857009856-10</Id><Topic><Title>The borders have "never been stronger"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360855760962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 10:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, tell me here is AZ that the borders are more secure. If it weren't for the GREAT Sheriff Joe Arpaio, we would be overrun with illegal aliens! All Hail to Sheriff Joe. Boo obama and his minions like janet napolitano (thank God she's gone from AZ! She is NOT missed!)</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1360857009856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 10:50:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360857362799-11</Id><Topic><Title>Retirement Offer?</Title><Username>kcckks</Username><Timestamp>1360728193378</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 23:03:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I retired 4 months ago. Didn't see a reason to stay. No regrets so far. I miss the work but not the stress. Took the lump sum and gave it to an investor and then left my 401k with fidelity. It's a scary financial decision but now that it's done I'm glad I left. When the spring rains hit, I may apply for a temp job to help out,, but then again,, why would I want to work in the bad weather?</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1360857362799</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 10:56:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360857385702-12</Id><Topic><Title>Obama seeks 29 new programs!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1360772898902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:28:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was watching the news last night. The amount of times he said "It won't add a single dime to the deficit" in the last 4 years was at least 20 times. They showed each one. What a joke this POTUS is.</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1360857385702</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 10:56:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360857687252-13</Id><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Msg>"After years of grueling recession, our businesses have created over 6 million new jobs." Per the Spinmeister: "What part of that don't you understand? Not only has Obama added 6 million jobs since the bottom of the recession, he turned around an economy that was shedding 900,000 jobs a month." So, what you are saying Spinmeister is you don't like the very left leaning Huff Post report that tends to poo-poo the President's stated 6 million job figure. At least the Huff Post folks can smell BS when it hits them in the face: Huff Post: "Private sector jobs have grown by 6.1 million since February 2010. But since he became president, the gain is a more modest 1.9 million. And when losses in public sector employment are added to the mix, his overall jobs record is a gain of 1.2 million." Tell me Spinmeister, what part of that don't you understand? How can the President take credit for jobs added during a turn around that started before he took office? I'm just wondering right along with the Huff Post folks!</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360858163525-14</Id><Topic><Title>The borders have "never been stronger"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360855760962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 10:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All part of the "New World Odor" plan to merge us with the rest of the world. Flood this country with every third world #$%$ and indigent. I just read that 8,000 per day are being added to the food stamp program.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1360858163525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:09:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360858683046-15</Id><Topic><Title>For chart believers</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360769956493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:39:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody believes you don't think it has anything to do with the chart. To double your money in one month thats around 20% returns in one week and 100% in a month. I don't think you could achieve that one time, but according to you, you can do it every month for 12 years to be a billionaire. If your research on at&amp;t is as bad as your math I'm going to do the opposite of you.</Msg><Username>tuckerleppa</Username><Timestamp>1360858683046</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:18:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360858770786-16</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tb, please be patient with spinning ricky. He needs to search the web and find a lobbyist site, appears his lobbyist site has not addressed this yet, to find a comment that he can plagiarize and make people think that his spin it truth. Lying is hard work you know, give him time! Ricky pay for your stuff!!!!!!!!! Stop spending what you don't have.</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1360858770786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:19:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360859096446-17</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh no say it isn't so! Are you saying that ricky and the "precious one" are cherry picking their facts in order to make themselves look good? Well I never! Isn't ricky the one that accuses some on this board of doing the very same thing? Oh my! Who would have thought? Well, maybe he just had a lapse in judgement. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360859096446</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:24:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360859409254-18</Id><Topic><Title>For chart believers</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360769956493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:39:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe in you uncle Wilkes,, just don't forget to put your favorite nephew in your will. I'll stop by, after the market closes, to fix your calculator and wash the car.</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1360859409254</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:30:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360860044515-19</Id><Topic><Title>The Street Report, (CRAMER) 2/12/2013</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360824698572</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 01:51:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With all of the money coming out of CenturyLink (CTL) today, I can see both Verizon and AT&amp;T going up in the next few days. The funds that believe in the telcom stocks will still want the money in that sector. But I don't quite see CTL going down much further, todays drop brought it down to the AT&amp;T level. On the downside to your post, Cramer seems to only get it right about 51% of the time, which is 2% more than I do.</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1360860044515</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:40:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360861635176-20</Id><Topic><Title>The Street Report, (CRAMER) 2/12/2013</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360824698572</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 01:51:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In reviewing the holdings of Investment Grade Corporate Bond ETF, I was rather surprised to see AT&amp;T bonds being one of their top 10 holdings but not VZ. I hope this question won't be on the final exam. It is possible that the fund diversification dictates that they only hold one but not both.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360861635176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 12:07:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360862043100-21</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"you don't like the very left leaning Huff Post report" I do take issue with the Huffington Post here. (which, btw, has gone downhill since AOL bought it) Obama never claimed that 6 million jobs had been created since he took office or that he created those jobs. He claimed that businesses have created 6 million jobs after years of grueling recession. Which they have. That's a good thing, isn't it? So which part of that don't you understand? The part where Obama says businesses created the jobs or the part where they were created after the recession, not from the beginning of his presidency? Seems to be both. The whole phrase went "whoosh"! Right over your partisan head. "How can the President take credit for jobs added during a turn around that started before he took office?" The Alzheimer's is kicking in already, eh? Ignoring the fact that the President, in fact, did not take credit for jobs but gave the credit to businesses, when do think this turnaround began? The recession officially ended in June, 2009. The economy began adding jobs in Oct. 2010. The private sector began adding jobs in March 2010. The economy lost the most jobs in March, 2009, with job losses shrinking and eventually turning to gains in Oct. 2010. Who do you think was President during each of these events? I say again, turning our economy from one shedding jobs to one creating jobs is a massive feat. Our economy is now creating over 1 million more jobs per month than it was in March, 2009. And lastly, for conservatives to complain about lost public sector jobs is just beyond the pale. Just like it was beyond the pale for you to complain about savings in Medicare. You are exactly what I think you are, tbfine. Pay for your stuff.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360862043100</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 12:14:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360862585944-22</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is widdle wicky ignoring the facts again. He looks at jobs being created ignoring those that are lost. Oh, keep in mind that the jobs created are not equal to the jobs lost. So while there may be an agreed to net gain of 1m plus jobs, the net jobs added are not equal as a tax revenue source to those jobs lost under Obama. ricky, spin away, regardless it is a net loss for our country from people like you spinning real data. Tax away and spin away baby. Glad you are increasing your contribution to ObamaCare while reducing the baby boomers contributions. Certainly that was not intended. Stand by wicky to get it in the rear from ObamaDoesntCare. "you asked for it" - now that would be a good name for a tv program wouldn't it? SIN RICKY SIN Some more. Your spinning comes back to haunt you. Pray for forgiveness your sinner!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! :-)</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1360862585944</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 12:23:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360862592657-23</Id><Topic><Title>The Street Report, (CRAMER) 2/12/2013</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360824698572</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 01:51:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't get why everyone bashes Cramer.</Msg><Username>tuckerleppa</Username><Timestamp>1360862592657</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 12:23:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360863773244-24</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I do take issue with the Huffington Post here. (which, btw, has gone downhill since AOL bought it)" Oh! It's AOL's fault that the Huff Post is beginning to see the light! I thought you were going to tell me the Tea Party infiltrated the Huff! By the way Ricky, have I mentioned lately how tired I am of paying for the stuff of other people?</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360863773244</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 12:42:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360865210899-25</Id><Topic><Title>The Street Report, (CRAMER) 2/12/2013</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360824698572</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 01:51:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor in communication skills.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360865210899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 13:06:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360865277367-26</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ricky says that all government posted statistics are the truth, the whole truth and nothing but the truth when they support his view of the world. That isn't spin, that is downright deliriously dizzy!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1360865277367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 13:07:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360865621974-27</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obama never claimed that 6 million jobs had been created since he took office or that he created those jobs. He claimed that businesses have created 6 million jobs after years of grueling recession." Now that is the most egregious spin of all. He claimed all during the campaign that his policies and actions are what was creating these jobs. His loans to green energy companies, his home refinance programs, his extension of UE benefits for longer and longer periods, along with Nancy's endorsement, helped the economy grow a provide more jobs. Without all those unemployed spending the benefits, their disability checks and welfare dollars we would still be in the tank. But he won't take credit for it. The he$$ he won't!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1360865621974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 13:13:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360866077557-28</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"He looks at jobs being created ignoring those that are lost." The BLS presents net jobs, Dan. You've tried to pull this little lie before too. You can try to spread all the lies you want Dan, but I'm a big believer in the idea that truth, justice and the American way always win out in the end. If Socrates is right and immorality is a result of intellectual mistakes, you must be a particularly decrepit old fool. BTW, Dan, it's pretty clear you're the one behind Cool Jon/Zon and at least one fake ricky. Have fun with that.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360866077557</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 13:21:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360866179211-29</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ricky blames the old folks for not paying for their stuff. His version of history forgets that most of these old folks have paid tax dollars into all the programs that he claims they are raping for 30 to 50 years of their working careers. His version also forgets that most of the modern inventions he enjoys were created by this same generation, or they gave many of the later inventors the skills, education, and imagination used to create the later examples of their progress. He like Obama thinks all good things come from younger people and the government. The problem is that most of the younger generations that he claims are paying for all of the older generation to still be alive and part of society are bigger leaches than the older generation ever was. Our debt and deficit problems are the fault of the older generations and their skills at stealing from the poor and never creating a business or wealth on their own skills and imagination. Ricky’s version of the world is revisionist history at it’s finest.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1360866179211</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 13:22:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360866459735-30</Id><Topic><Title>The borders have "never been stronger"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360855760962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 10:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder when was the last time was that Janet was on or near the border without a cluster of dozens complete with TV cameras and security? Of course she sees only the best and finest situations when on her photo ops. Reality is a thing she doesn't understand. I still don't understand why she got this job.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1360866459735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 13:27:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360866693483-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obama seeks 29 new programs!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1360772898902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:28:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He may be correct, at least in his fiscally stunted brain. He will simply ask the Fed to print a pile of money for him to use. Money in hand is a good thing, but then he doesn't consider how it has to be paid for. Obviously he doesn’t' get Ricky's pay for your stuff message. God help us if the liberals win a majority in the mid-terms, there will be no quarter shown to the American people.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1360866693483</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 13:31:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360869432675-32</Id><Topic><Title>Obama seeks 29 new programs!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1360772898902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:28:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>POTUS or POS?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360869432675</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 14:17:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360869532318-33</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPIN tRicky SPIN!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360869532318</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 14:18:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360869996398-34</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well Winholder, I know I started this thread but you folks are being pretty hard on poor Ricky. I think is his only real fault may be smoking things that tend to connect him to the Gods.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360869996398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 14:26:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360871300245-35</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No winholder. I consistently think they are the truth, good or bad. It is you with the consistency problem. I'm really just dealing with Dan, here, aren't I?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360871300245</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 14:48:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360872230440-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obama seeks 29 new programs!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1360772898902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:28:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>POS!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1360872230440</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 15:03:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360872487885-37</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But he won't take credit for it." I didn't say he won't take credit for creating jobs. I agree with you--he deserves some credit for the jobs created. However, Obama did not take credit in his SOTU address. Any statement to the contrary is false and clearly so. Businesses have created six million jobs since the end of a grueling recession--a recession in which we lost 8.8 million jobs. The turnaround in job losses began shortly after the Stimulus Act was passed. Bush left the economy in free fall. Obama turned it around.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360872487885</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 15:08:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360882809419-38</Id><Title>CNBC: ML Market Strategist</Title><Msg>1) Claims the market will go down; and 2) Goes on to say the untilities and telecoms are destined to be the worst performers and the stocks to avoid. Apparently, this young lady hasn't heard of the parameter called "BETA." Telecom and utilities have practically the lowest beta one can think of. If we are to believe her forecast of a steep market drop, then these two sectors are likely to drop the least. Typical beta for these type of stocks is 0.5 or less. Richard Bey said it the best "Where do they find these people?" I can't believe CNBC would put these kind of people before the camera.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360882809419</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 18:00:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360884199912-39</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC: ML Market Strategist</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360882809419</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 18:00:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder if that young lady would care to put a "wager" on the #2 part of that article. My opinion, the larger Telecoms will do "well". However for Electric Utilities, they will perform well but there are rumors of "cap &amp; trade" rearing it's ugly head again.</Msg><Username>coolin_out47</Username><Timestamp>1360884199912</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 18:23:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360887577084-40</Id><Topic><Title>Obama seeks 29 new programs!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1360772898902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:28:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Obama is a politician. Scratch your noodles folks ! All politicians usually promise more then they can deliver.</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1360887577084</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 19:19:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360889628309-41</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm pretty sure my main fault is paying the least bit of attention to you people.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360889628309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 19:53:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360899921661-42</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky the Spinmeister</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360857687252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 11:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a venal, nasty, small-minded tool that has no right to be in society.</Msg><Username>wledigmacsen</Username><Timestamp>1360899921661</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 22:45:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360900975294-43</Id><Title>Jon3retired = zonbac - TOOL</Title><Msg>Fits you to a "T" little jonnycakes. From the American Dictionary of Slang: A person, typically male, who says or does things that cause you to give them a 'what-are-you-even-doing-here' look. The 'what-are-you-even-doing-here' look is classified by a glare in the tool's direction and is usually accompanied by muttering of how big of a tool they are. The tool is usually someone who is unwelcome but no one has the balls to tell them to get lost. The tool is alwasys making comments that are out-of-place, out-of-line or just plain stupid. The tool is always trying too hard to fit in, and because of this, never will. However, the tool is useful because you can use them for things; money, rides, etc.</Msg><Username>wledigmacsen</Username><Timestamp>1360900975294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 23:02:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360901141540-44</Id><Topic><Title>coolin_out47...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360764138358</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:02:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, jonnycakes = zonbac is a cool tool!</Msg><Username>wledigmacsen</Username><Timestamp>1360901141540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 23:05:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>