<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-10"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360487244533-1</Id><Title>The major competitive advantage in telecom is going to be: SPECTRUM</Title><Msg>High tech gadgets will come and go whether it be Apple or whatever but all these devices will need the spectrum as a medium for the information pipeline. I tend to believe that Randall has got this one right coupled with the fact that the international markets will undergo the very same growth experienced in the U.S. so that those markets present significant opportunities. Having said that, one must also factor in the current as well as emerging competitors such #$%$, DISH, PCS and so on. But the very same can be said for the TV markets, lots of competition but guess what? The monthly bills keep going up. No reason to expect differently for the telecom markets. The CSCO article I posted previously predicted that monthly charges will go up by $40 during the next five years which translate to increase of $8.00 per month which is inline with the increases we are currently experiencing for the TV service. But wait, what about the intense competition? No problem, they are all moving in a lock step fashion. I think the telecom carriers will move their pricing in the very same fashion. Disclosure- I am long the AT&amp;T stock.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360487244533</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 04:07:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360496601347-2</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T</Title><Username>tarpon144</Username><Timestamp>1360449074853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 17:31:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No forest argument here. I suppose putting your money in the bank is then akin to watching your new car sink in a lake. Accidentally, of course. It's not a difficult choice these days.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360496601347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 06:43:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360501081379-3</Id><Title>Apple versus Samsung</Title><Msg>Today's article from yahoo finance goes into great details in explaining the competitive wars emerging between both companies and concludes Samsung to be the winner which explains the steep drop in share prices of Apple. I suppose one can safely say that the future for Apple is not what it used to be.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360501081379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 07:58:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360509328574-4</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T</Title><Username>tarpon144</Username><Timestamp>1360449074853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 17:31:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: AT&amp;T - Your "Topic Message" drew me in but I found nothing of value in your post. Not even a "Long-Term Sentiment Disclosure" .. just the babble part ! So for now I'll retreat and watch T grow, take it's usual dips, stalls and advances. At the end of the year I'll see it's benefits on my bottom line.</Msg><Username>coolin_out47</Username><Timestamp>1360509328574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 10:15:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360519871841-5</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. Frogg and Mr. Rat have dinner</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360350244047</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 14:04:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Sadly, frog-boy, by attempting to vilify those who disagree with you (did I mention, btw, that it is a substantial majority who voted accordingly, which you somehow find to be un-democratic), you once again reveal your ignorance." I wonder how much of the "substantial majority" was made up of the likes of Ohio democrat voter Melowese Richardson who freely admits that she voted more than once (i.e., once by absentee ballot, once at the polls, once for her grand daughter India [who then went to the poll and voted in person] once for Montez Richardson, and finally once for Markus Barron. As Mrs. Richardson said, when asked about the charges of voter fraud: “I’ll fight it for Mr. Obama and for Mr. Obama’s right to sit as president of the United States.” Yes my little friend the vote for the precious one was a landslide. Mr Romney never had a chance. Kind of reminds me of another democrat from here in Texas (known as landslide Johnson) who later became president. As far as living in fear, I think there may be some misunderstanding on your part. I have lived my life and am looking forward to my end days, but sometimes I do enjoy pointing out the obvious, especially to little fellows like you. So enjoy the kool aid my friend. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360519871841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:11:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360522939807-6</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. Frogg and Mr. Rat have dinner</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360350244047</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 14:04:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw this former poll worker's interview. What amazed me is how open she was about her fraud. Absolutely no quilt expressed; she was most proud of her accomplishment.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360522939807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 14:02:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360528571147-7</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. Frogg and Mr. Rat have dinner</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360350244047</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 14:04:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “I wonder how much of the "substantial majority" was made up of the likes of Ohio democrat voter Melowese Richardson…” - gremlin Melowese Richardson is the entire gist of your argument? How much, you ask? Well, let’s count them, shall we….Okay, that’s one, according to you. When you come up with the other 4,970,507 votes of the substantial majority that you lost by, come back and see us. “Mr. Romney never had a chance.” Oh, please! Suggesting that voter fraud was the cause of your embarrassing blow-out is an exercise in futility. You lost by 4%. So, according to you, one in every 25 votes cast (only for Obama, of course) was fraudulent?? It must be very painful, indeed, for the good people on your side who actually want to correct the multitude of mistakes in your platform and broaden your base, to have to watch you further discredit your side with your childish whining and bogus excuses. Where were you when the chads were hanging? That is a sorry and pitiful vision for the future of your party. Yesterday you were blaming the collectives…today it’s Melowese Richardson…tomorrow, who knows? You really need to listen to Bobby Jindall. His message is aimed directly at people like you.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360528571147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 15:36:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360531429040-8</Id><Title>t.bfine...</Title><Msg>... “I saw this former poll worker's interview. What amazed me is how open she was about her fraud. Absolutely no quilt expressed; she was most proud of her accomplishment.” t.bfine She didn’t express any quilt? What’s this about quilts? Gee, Melowese doesn’t sound Amish to me! Get serious. She flat out denied any attempt at fraud. Did you happen to see this part by any chance? Or did you conveniently skip over the facts, as you guys are want to do? “In Richardson’s case, she told the television station that she had not intended to commit vote fraud and merely showed up to vote in-person as she was unsure her absentee ballot would arrive in time to be counted. Richardson truthfully identified herself at the polls and voted in her own name.” In other words, as a poll worker for 25 years, this lady knows the rules, and she knows that if her absentee ballot arrived on time, only one vote would be counted. “Hamilton County Deputy Director of Elections Sally J. Krisel said, ‘Ohio has very clear laws about checking,’ so if a voter is found to have cast an absentee ballot and attempts to vote in person, only one vote is counted.” (The National Review story frog quotes)…”attempts to lump all types of voter fraud in together, but does not identify a single one of the 19 alleged cases in which a voter committed in-person impersonation of another voter.” You guys need to get serious and stop wasting people’s time with voter suppression, gerrymandering and your upcoming attempts at rigging the electoral vote. Why don’t you just broaden your base, expand your tent and give yourselves at least a chance? Otherwise, you’re doomed to more of the same. Remember, it’s a “majority rules” system, like it or not.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360531429040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:23:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360534543218-9</Id><Topic><Title>t.bfine...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360531429040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:23:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"(The National Review story frog quotes)…”attempts to lump all types of voter fraud in together, but does not identify a single one of the 19 alleged cases in which a voter committed in-person impersonation of another voter.” Actually had you watched the video, that was part of the National Review article, you would have seen Mrs. Richardson admit that she: o Voted once by absentee ballot o Voted once in person o Voted once by absentee ballot for her grand daughter India (which became two votes when India voted in person o Voted once by absentee ballot for a Montez Richardson, and finally o Voted once by absentee ballot for a Markus Barron Oh wait a minute, you are correct there was no attempt at voter fraud here, just a good citizen making sure her vote counted more than my single vote. Again Mr. Romney never had a chance. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360534543218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 17:15:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360536311038-10</Id><Topic><Title>t.bfine...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360531429040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:23:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...you're disgusting. Yeah, I watched the video. All four of those folks live in her apartment complex. One she has power of attorney for...the other's she was helping. There was absolutely no fraud involved. She is simply another dedicated, grass roots, organizer...something you folks who disregard polls, demographics and the middle class can't, or won't, comprehend. Boo-Hoo...We lost by 5 million votes, and it was all illegal. Grow up.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360536311038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 17:45:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360540053435-11</Id><Topic><Title>t.bfine...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360531429040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:23:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you had an ounce of credibilty, you just canned it. Of course she did not admit to fraud, but what she openly and so proudly said about how many times she voted made her FRAUD a blinding flash of the obvious. If you wish to be duped by her shrewd approach to voting, that's your choice. Spin it however you like. Forget about all the cronies she voted for, when she voted absentee for herself , then went to the poll and voted in person for herself she was betting the system would not pick it up. Furthermore, she was openly clearly proud of her effort. Concerned citizen my tail. For me, she represents the poster child of voter fraud.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360540053435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 18:47:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360547931496-12</Id><Topic><Title>7 Million to Lose Insurance Under Obamacare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1360256571061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:02:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, in our major cities, this has been going on for sometime. Way back in 89, I had to take my Mom (a cancer patient), to Johns Hopkins ER. The entire Department was over run with heroin addicts, with stomach cramps. Our Dem Governor, then Baltimore City Mayor, O'Malley, welcomes illegals, who have flooded our city with cheap, Mexican Brown heroin. Now, it's worse, our current Dem Mayor, Rawlings-Blake, has set a target of 10,000 illegal families, to repopulate Bmore. Seems its getting harder to get free Federal money with a shrinking poulation. None of these people pay taxes, but demand it all, free. We get the Government we vote for, therefore deserve. Can't way till the libs get it there way. Gun control, confiscation, is under way here. Yuppie libs make such an easy target for these illegal alien criminals, with their smart phones, and their save the world mentality.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1360547931496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 20:58:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360548694194-13</Id><Topic><Title>7 Million to Lose Insurance Under Obamacare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1360256571061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:02:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's starting to leak out now, the terrible truth. Obummer has begun his quest to take away the average worker's health care, via his employer. Here, in our help wanted ads (in the Baltimore Sun), employers now only want to offer a four day work week. This avoids having to provide health care benefits. Wait till he grants amnesty to 20 MILLION plus illegals, no lower skilled Brother will have a chance at a job. Speaking Spanish, being bil-lingual will mean most Government jobs will go to illegals. Riots will erupt, once lower skilled Americans finally figure it out.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1360548694194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 21:11:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360548944388-14</Id><Title>IRE...Bank of Ireland</Title><Msg>just sayin...</Msg><Username>stv_brent</Username><Timestamp>1360548944388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 21:15:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360549335551-15</Id><Topic><Title>Obama doesnt care shafts the middle class</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1360348194062</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 13:29:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, please if you can, replay Obama's Prayer Breakfast coverage. He has to sit, and listen to the truth, from Ben Carson. A real American Patriot of Color. It's the truth. Mouchelle, can't stand the truth. Watch her frown. I'm sure, Ben Carson would be taken out by a dr0ne strike, if these two had their way. Rush, among others, has covered on his show, that a family policy under Obummer in 2016 will cost 22k a year. Wait till the lib yups have to pay taxes on that amount. Ouch! Bet you, they didn't know they were the rich guy Bami was talking about taxing.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1360549335551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 21:22:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360550283213-16</Id><Topic><Title>t.bfine...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360531429040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:23:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So again folks we get a little more insight into the situational ethics of a democrat voter. This is why Mr. Romney never had a chance, because there is nothing a democrat can do that would cause another democrat to say "oh wow that is going too far", or "I can't be a party to that" etc.. You see when a Republican is found guilty of something immoral or illegal he or she is generally sent packing by the party. Again you will never see that kind of treatment when a democrat is involved (e.g., Bob Menendez, Bill (I did not have...) Clinton, Hillary (what does it matter) Clinton, Anthony (look at my twitter photo) Weiner, the list goes on). No on the contrary you will only get spin, stone walling and denial. Yes my friends our little Sir Echo has proven once again to be a true party tovarich and a kool aid drinker to boot. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360550283213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 21:38:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360551077663-17</Id><Topic><Title>sell T, buy CHL</Title><Username>sirmidnight</Username><Timestamp>1359304738651</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 11:38:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CHL outperformed T for the week.</Msg><Username>sirmidnight</Username><Timestamp>1360551077663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 21:51:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360551531335-18</Id><Title>Dorner, Crazed Lib, Likely at Doughnut Shop</Title><Msg>This guy is targeted by the Mexican LA Mayor. They prayed this guy would just kill himself, but he's got unfinished business. He doen't like loosing his job, for refusing to speak Spanish. Come to Maryland, we have no death penalty. All is forgiven. Please give yourself up. Our Governor O'Malley will reach out to you, and probably make you Chief of Police.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1360551531335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 21:58:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360551911557-19</Id><Title>My AT&amp;T uverse freezes, and is unreliable</Title><Msg>garbage;</Msg><Username>garroty</Username><Timestamp>1360551911557</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 22:05:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>