<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366376965751-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama covering up Saudi link to Boston bombing?</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1366307692141</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 13:54:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sean Hannity &amp; Glen Beck, just making stuff up.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366376965751</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 09:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366377039886-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama covering up Saudi link to Boston bombing?</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1366307692141</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 13:54:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your problem is you've heard about Obama's "untruthes" from Sean Hannity and Glen Beck. Until you learn to evaluate sources you will continue to be mislead, manipulated and used.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366377039886</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 09:10:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366380302921-3</Id><Title>Rick Perry praises and thanks President Obama</Title><Msg>when speaking about the texas explosion. I enjoyed that thoroughly. How it should be with people,</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1366380302921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:05:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366381246400-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama covering up Saudi link to Boston bombing?</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1366307692141</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 13:54:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, latest poll says 90% of Americans and 95% of NRA members LOVE Obama!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1366381246400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:20:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366382184319-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama covering up Saudi link to Boston bombing?</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1366307692141</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 13:54:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really bouche? Don't you think that at this time and in this thread you should be reevaluating your news sources rather than mocking others? Sean Hannity and Glen Beck lied to you. Do you understand that?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366382184319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:36:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366383113787-6</Id><Title>Obama supporters and misinformation</Title><Msg>Park ones politics and think. The Senate fails to pass legislation again, this time on gun control. Obama immediately blames Congress. Think about it. The President of the United States in his fifth year in office cannot properly identify which legislative body has responsibility for a single action (any action) and blames the other body. Like sheep his followers attack the other body. His own party fails to hold him accountable and fails to make anything happen. This President has repeatedly failed the public by not generating support within his party, that party, in case he forgot and his supporters forgot, is the Democratic Party. HE CAN'T GET IT DONE!!! Forget your politics for one moment. This guy is not involved and does not get things done! VERY VERY SAD!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! The failure is within the DEMOCRATIC PARTY which DOES NOT support the Democratic President. Democrats, the party of inaction and blaming. First two years of this President he had Democratic control of both houses and he did not accomplish any significant legislative initiatives. Unless you want to read it after what ever is in it passes. WOW! Close your eyes and maybe it will happen.</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1366383113787</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:51:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366383498560-7</Id><Topic><Title>Wonderful speech</Title><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1366245532638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 20:38:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama clearly is the best reading President we have had in some time. Good speech writers! Did you realize that it was the Senate that voted and not the Congress? Probably not!</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1366383498560</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:58:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366383782321-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama covering up Saudi link to Boston bombing?</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1366307692141</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 13:54:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No apologoies for these treasonous comments against America's President? Didn't think so, some people can't man up to their own behavior and mistakes. Keep it up on top to show what they are.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1366383782321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366383894032-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama supporters and misinformation</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1366383113787</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you kidding me? Democrats are responsible for Republican filibusters? They forced Republicans to sign the Norquist pledge? Also, you can't have it both ways. Either Obama and Democrats destroyed America with the health care law, stimulus, Dodd-Frank, etc, etc, etc or they've done nothing. It's not both. So please, pick one. You Tea Brains are running out of holes to hide in. We all know who you are now.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366383894032</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:04:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366384103441-10</Id><Topic><Title>Wonderful speech</Title><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1366245532638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 20:38:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Talking to yourself, Dan? Everyone knows that 56 Senators voted for the amendment and 44 opposed the amendment. That's how the amendment "lost".</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366384103441</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:08:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366384614556-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama supporters and misinformation</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1366383113787</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Shameful Day': Furious Obama blasts Senate for Vote that didn't go his Way! Why wasn't the headline: Americans win win huge victory over 2nd amendment rights!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1366384614556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:16:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366384893584-12</Id><Title>Wow, heard there is a massive promo coming to XSNX</Title><Msg>I just found out that XSNX is about to be promoted by some of the biggest IR groups. Grabbing some now</Msg><Username>jwalsh986</Username><Timestamp>1366384893584</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:21:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366386061512-13</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT .. a Democratic Senate ??</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1366239447721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 18:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You wanted a vote, you got it you lost. According to Obama that is the way of politics and when you lose, you shut up and go home. Why are complaining so loudly, we have all wanted a vote on a budget for years and Dirty Harry wouldn't allow it...why, because when you lose, you lose, shut up and go home.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1366386061512</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366386136725-14</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry praises and thanks President Obama</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1366380302921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Obama does well, he should be praised. The problem is that it happens so infrequently.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1366386136725</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:42:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366387687468-15</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT .. a Democratic Senate ??</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1366239447721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 18:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You people seem to have your ego tied into this thing. I didn't lose, you didn't win. The NRA won, America lost. As you watch what is unfolding in Boston today think really, really hard about the types of weapons you want readily available to people. Hopefully some of the 44 Senators who chose to block background checks will do a 180 and begin to support outright bans on military weapons, or get thrown out of office. Otherwise we should expect to see more and more heavily armed terrorists, psychos and criminals going on rampages throughout the country. We are giving these people these weapons. We are manufacturing them and putting them in their hands.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366387687468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 12:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366389356247-16</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry praises and thanks President Obama</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1366380302921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's hear some from your camp then. there has been none. We are waiting to hear some. To the extent that when he agrees with your own ideas, your camp turns against what you were for. Obamacare is one obvious example, plus many more including a congressman switching position as he was speaking on the floor. Just to never say anything good about a President. Anti American, unpatriotic, cowardly behavior. Let's hear some.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1366389356247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 12:35:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366389748935-17</Id><Title>T is an UNSTOPPABLE MONEY MAKING MACHINE</Title><Msg>Expect it to be at 55 by end of year, 100 in 2014</Msg><Username>cooki_moonster</Username><Timestamp>1366389748935</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 12:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366390707110-18</Id><Topic><Title>T is an UNSTOPPABLE MONEY MAKING MACHINE</Title><Username>cooki_moonster</Username><Timestamp>1366389748935</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 12:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Back at you. I quit trading and bet the farm on T. I'm 72 years old and suspect that T is going to be very popular in coming months. Still way cheap.</Msg><Username>bambusario</Username><Timestamp>1366390707110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 12:58:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366391010662-19</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry praises and thanks President Obama</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1366380302921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Just to never say anything good about a President. Anti American, unpatriotic, cowardly behavior." Really? What a joke of a statement for those that opposed nearly everything that Bush said or did. Under your scenario, that make most of the liberals in Congress guilty. But you weren't considering yourself anti-American, unpatriotic or cowardly were you? Didn't think so. It is not any of those things if the man is making mistake after mistake; well some call them mistakes, I think they are done intentionally and with malic toward this country. If anyone is anti-American and unpatriotic, our President only need to look in the mirror.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1366391010662</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:03:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366391083357-20</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry praises and thanks President Obama</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1366380302921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know, isn't it terrible! And after you Liberals treated George Bush so well! I believe the saying is "What goes around comes around!"</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1366391083357</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:04:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366391178189-21</Id><Topic><Title>T is an UNSTOPPABLE MONEY MAKING MACHINE</Title><Username>cooki_moonster</Username><Timestamp>1366389748935</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 12:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol...easy there moonster</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1366391178189</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:06:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366391493738-22</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry praises and thanks President Obama</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1366380302921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So the reason you filibuster everything is because you think people were mean to George Bush? I seem to remember quite a few budgets getting passed and a couple of authorizations for wars--despite the better judgement of just about anyone. But ok, I'll bite. I'm sorry if we hurt your feelings during the Bush years by pointing out just how horrible Republican policies were. But Democrats played ball. They did not filibuster Every. Little. Thing. So please, now that we've made nicey, will you pass legislation that you previously claimed to support? Pretty please? I'll be your best friend. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366391493738</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366392061780-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama supporters and misinformation</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1366383113787</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again, shouldn't you be directing your ire towards Hannity &amp; Beck? At this point you must realize they lied to you.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366392061780</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:21:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366392410513-24</Id><Topic><Title>Next week is very optimistic !</Title><Username>ronnierangel446</Username><Timestamp>1366301328913</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 12:08:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report , thanks !</Msg><Username>swopes.william</Username><Timestamp>1366392410513</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:26:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366393035209-25</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT .. a Democratic Senate ??</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1366239447721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 18:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“….why, because when you lose, you lose, shut up and go home…” – winholder Talk about a bodacious statement! Click on winnie’s posts since the ’08 election to see what a flaming hypocrite he is…you’ll see more crying than John Boehner peelin’ onions! “When Obama does well, he should be praised. The problem is that it happens so infrequently.” – windandale again Well, here are a few of the Obama Administration’s accomplishments listed by Paul Glastris at The Washington Monthly – and this was written a year ago. Personally, I’m proud that our President has accomplished all of these things, IN SPITE of those who represent the special interests who do everything in their power to preserve the status quo while obstructing any progress for the majority of the American people. We voted for change and, thankfully, we’re getting it. That your types don’t like it, means a job well done. And you haven’t seen anything yet. 1. Passed Health Care Reform 2. Passed the Stimulus 3. Passed Wall Street Reform4. Ended the War in Iraq: Ordered all U.S. military forces out of the country. Last troops left on December 18, 2011. 5. Began Drawdown of War in Afghanistan 6. Eliminated Osama bin laden 7. Turned Around U.S. Auto Industry 8. Recapitalized Banks 9. Repealed “Don’t Ask, Don’t Tell 10. Toppled Moammar Gaddafi 11. Told Mubarak to Go 12. Reversed Bush Torture Policies 13. Improved America’s Image Abroad 14. Kicked Banks Out of Federal Student Loan Program, Expanded Pell Grant Spending 15. Created Race to the Top 16. Boosted Fuel Efficiency Standards 17. Coordinated International Response to Financial Crisis 18. Passed Mini Stimuli 19. Began Asia “Pivot 20. Increased Support for Veterans 21. Tightened Sanctions on Iran 22. Created Conditions to Begin Closing Dirtiest Power Plants 23. Passed Credit Card Reforms 24. Eliminated Catch-22 in Pay Equality Laws 25. Protected Two Liberal Seats on the U.S. Supreme Court 26. Improved Food Safety System 27. Achieved New START Treaty 28. Expanded National Service 29. Expanded Wilderness and Watershed Protection 30. Gave the FDA Power to Regulate Tobacco 31. Pushed Federal Agencies to Be Green Leaders 32. Passed Fair Sentencing Act 33. Trimmed and Reoriented Missile Defense 34. Began Post-Post-9/11 Military Builddown 35. Let Space Shuttle Die and Killed Planned Moon Mission 36. Invested Heavily in Renewable Technology 37. Crafting Next-Generation School Tests 38. Cracked Down on Bad For-Profit Colleges 39. Improved School Nutrition 40. Expanded Hate Crimes Protections 41. Avoided Scandal 42. Brokered Agreement for Speedy Compensation to Victims of Gulf Oil Spill 43. Created Recovery.gov 44. Pushed Broadband Coverage 45. Expanded Health Coverage for Children 46. Recognized the Dangers of Carbon Dioxide 47. Expanded Stem Cell Research 48. Provided Payment to Wronged Minority Farmers 49. Helped South Sudan Declare Independence 50. Killed the F-22 “If anyone is anti-American and unpatriotic, our President only need to look in the mirror.” – Winnie If anyone is anti-American and unpatriotic, it’s cowards who anonymously say those kind of things about a very popular and duly elected president. You, winholder, should quit wasting your time here and go out and organize your community if you really want to accomplish something politically. That’s right, pal…a community organizer…contrary to what you’ve been told, that’s not the commie bogie man you fear…that’s grass roots politics in a democracy. Your side could learn a lot from what’s happened to you, but, apparently change is not in your vocabulary. Good luck in ’16. (’14, too, for that matter.)</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366393035209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:37:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366395949312-26</Id><Topic><Title>T is an UNSTOPPABLE MONEY MAKING MACHINE</Title><Username>cooki_moonster</Username><Timestamp>1366389748935</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 12:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is this a new high WOW, going to 50$?</Msg><Username>blair.wagner</Username><Timestamp>1366395949312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 14:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366400124054-27</Id><Title>Possible MSM interview with DHS Secretary:</Title><Msg>MSM: Well Madam Secretary, much has occurred over the last four days. What can you tell us about the Boston Marathon bombings? DHS Secretary: Well Chuck, as you know, this is an ongoing investigation, so I will be unable to provide much detail regarding the suspects or details about this "Man Caused Disaster". MSM: Madam Secretary from your experience in these matters can you provide any insight into a possible profile of the perpetrators? DHS Secretary: From the information I have, the perpetrators are most likely rich white men from the Boston suburbs, and there is no evidence to indicate that they are involved with Alcida or any radical Muslims. MSM: So is it possible that these rich white men are involved with the "Tea Party" movement or any other white supremacy groups? DHS Secretary: From the information I have, I can not say that these rich white men were not involved with the "Tea Party" movement or any other white supremacy group, but since the attack did occur on April 15 (i.e., tax day) I can not rule out the possible involvement by one or more of these groups including the NRA. MSM: Madam Secretary would you provide the American people with some final words? DHS Secretary: Sure Chuck, it should be clear to all Americans that the blame for events like these should be placed squarely on the shoulders of George W. Bush, the Republican party, the sequester, the NRA, Rush Limbaugh, Fox, and talk radio. If only we could get rid of all of these groups, America would be a safer and happier place to live. MSM: Thank you Madam Secretary. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366400124054</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:35:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366401229985-28</Id><Topic><Title>Possible MSM interview with DHS Secretary:</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366400124054</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:35:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What in the he** is the matter with you?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366401229985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:53:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366404815185-29</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry praises and thanks President Obama</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1366380302921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“I think they are done intentionally and with malic (sic) toward this country…” – winholder I would like to say that you guys have no clue…but, clearly you do. Colonel Mustard in the billiard room with the malic…!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366404815185</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 16:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366408605369-30</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry praises and thanks President Obama</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1366380302921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who? when? I thought it was taboo to talk about George. Actually my family never lets me forget I actually voted for George. I voted for Nixon too, the first time I ever voted, after Robert Kennedy was killed. I voted for Reagan even. Looking back on George, it was so obvious he was over his head, and spent money like there was no end to it. I will never vote for a republican again, not even dog catcher, after the way they treat Obama. It's just plain wrong. That's anti American. Some will still say he was born somewhere other than the USA, that's how bad they are. Now we get a great man, Obama, an intelligent, kind, honest man who handles easily the job, does a great job, and really is near perfect in every way as President, and all is said is negative from the right. You said he does get it right infrequently, so let's hear some praise for our President. Bet you won't.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1366408605369</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 17:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366411588715-31</Id><Topic><Title>June 41 calls are selling for 14 cents</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1366140217074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:23:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't let it get to you, that other Spinning tRicky is impersonating me too!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366411588715</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:46:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366413137110-32</Id><Topic><Title>Possible MSM interview with DHS Secretary:</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366400124054</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:35:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What in the he** is the matter with you?" So when I use the terms and phrases used by the administration, CNN, MSNBC, ABC, CBS, and the rest of the MSM to describe the events and suspects involved with terrorist attacks on American citizens, you ask what is the matter with me. I guess I am inclined to ask what is the matter with you when you can't see the dysfunction and duplicity of those that have been assigned the task of protecting the American people and providing them with news. But I guess if the only thing that you have allowed yourself to consume is the Kool Aid from your masters, then you should probably be forgiven regardless of how much the truth hurts. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366413137110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 19:12:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366417621319-33</Id><Topic><Title>Wonderful speech</Title><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1366245532638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 20:38:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many pressure cookers have you stockpiled, Lewcor? If I was you I would buy as many as I could before they are banned. Did you know pressure cooking anything was banned in the former U.S.S.R.? Look it up.</Msg><Username>mdeare2001</Username><Timestamp>1366417621319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366417961792-34</Id><Title>After Hours Quotes...</Title><Msg>...“This work contains many things which are new and interesting. Unfortunately, everything that is new is not interesting, and everything which is interesting, is not new.” – Lev Landau “Some men's words I remember so well that I must often use them to express my thought. Yes, because I perceive that we have heard the same truth, but they have heard it better.” – Ralph Waldo Emerson "Republicans did not have the votes for a filibuster, so there will be a debate about the gun bill. And given the recent rash of gun violence, Republicans said it was the least they could do. Literally, they had a meeting and said, 'What is the least we can do’?” - Bill Maher “I am trying to do two things: dare to be a radical and not be a fool, which, if I may judge by the exhibitions around me, is a matter of no small difficulty.” – James A. Garfield “His lack of education is more than compensated for by his keenly developed moral bankruptcy.” – Woody Allen "Iran is gearing up for a big presidential election in June. Yeah, this year it’s gonna be a tight race between Ahmadinejad and the guy they picked to lose to Ahmadinejad." - Jimmy Fallon “Adults are terribly confused, messed up people. That’s because they forget, really, that they don’t have to pretend all the time. Really, the fact is that you’re not an adult at all - you’re just a tall child holding a beer, having conversations you don’t understand… "The Middle East? Yeah, I know it was really bad. I wouldn’t have done that. A hysterectomy? Yeah, very painful, the shoulder is a very painful area." – Dylan Moran ”Did you ever hear one of these corny, positive messages on someone's answering machine? ‘Hi,it's a great day and I'm out enjoying it right now. I hope you are too. The thought for the day is: Share the love.‘ Beep. ‘Uh, yeah...this is the VD clinic calling....Speaking of being positive, your test results are back. Stop sharing the love‘." – Andy Rooney "A long list of celebrities and musicians have signed a letter to President Obama asking him to ease the nation's drug enforcement policy. Hollywood celebrities and musicians want the president to ease our drug laws – it's always the people you least expect." –Jay Leno “The universe is an intelligence test.” – Timothy Leary</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366417961792</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366418043428-35</Id><Topic><Title>After Hours Quotes...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366417961792</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:32:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“Aldous Huxley took the drug mescaline and then chronicled his experience in the book The Doors of Perception. Now, I don't actually think that's the first thing he wrote: he probably wrote 'my brain is melting' ten thousand times, but it was the book that the critics latched on to.“ – Bill Bailey “If the world were merely seductive, that would be easy. If it were merely challenging, that would be no problem. But I arise in the morning torn between a desire to improve (or save) the world and a desire to enjoy (or savor) the world. This makes it hard to plan the day.” – E.B. White “John Boehner said today he wants to take away North Korea's missiles, but he won't because that's a slippery slope from there to gun control.” – Bill Maher “Figure out what to do, then take a nap.“ – anonymous “It's peculiar and unnerving in a way to see so many young people walking around with cellphones and iPods in their ears and so wrapped up in media and video games. It robs them of their self-identity. It's a shame to see them so tuned out to real life. Of course they are free to do that, as if that's got anything to do with freedom. The cost of liberty is high, and young people should understand that before they start spending their life with all those gadgets.” – Bob Dylan "Things are still very tense in North Korea. In fact, world leaders are still waiting to see if Kim Jong-un is going to actually fire a missile after this week’s deadline came and went. Apparently what happened was he messed up and bought Mentos and regular Coke. " - Jimmy Fallon “We can see other people's behaviour, but not their experience.” – Ronald David Laing “I’m writing a book about Siamese Twins that are attached at the nose. It’s called, ‘Stop Staring at Me’!” – Zach Galafianakis “Margaret Thatcher died on Monday. Sara Palin was very sad about her passing, but at least now she said Charles can be king." - Bill Maher “When old men decided to barter young men for pride and profit, the transaction was called war." – Len Deighton</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366418043428</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:34:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366418291462-36</Id><Topic><Title>After Hours Quotes...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366417961792</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:32:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“You know, many a man realizes late in life that if when he was a boy he had known what he knows now, instead of being what he is he might be what he won't; but how few boys stop to think that if they knew what they don't know instead of being what they will be, they wouldn't be?” – Stephen Leacock “The only two places you will ever hear ‘Do you want whipped cream on that?’ are at Starbucks and a brothel.” – Whitney Cummings “I want Kim Jong-un to test a missile because it's always a spectacular disaster. He's the only Asian in the world that doesn't test well." –Bill Maher “The world is only as deep as we can see. This is why fools think themselves profound. This is why terror is the passion of revelation.” – R. Scott Bakker “I give women two types of orgasms. Fake and none.“ – Adam Corolla "Because of budget cuts, the Navy may have to cancel Fleet Week, where thousands of sailors dock in New York City. Of course if you want to see a bunch of people glad to be off a boat, you could just wait for a Carnival cruise to come in." - Jimmy Fallon “Where do the homeless have 90 percent of their accidents?” - anonymous “There was an Old Man with a beard, Who said, "It is just as I feared… Two Owls and a Hen, Four Larks and a Wren, Have all built their nests in my beard!" – Edward Lear “The Republicans say no to background checks because that is the death of freedom. They are sticking with the principle that asking for any kind of ID would be a horrible violation of the Constitution...unless it keeps black people from voting. Then, it is a fantastic idea." - Bill Maher “WINE, n.Fermented grape-juice known to the Women's Christian Union as ‘liquor,’ sometimes as ‘rum.’ Wine, madam, is God's next best gift to man.” - Ambrose Bierce, The Devil's Dictionary, 1911 “Have a good weekend, all.“ – echo2165 “The dead cannot cry out for justice; it is a duty of the living to do so for them,” – Lois McMaster Bujold</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366418291462</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:38:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366419144068-37</Id><Title>AHQ...3</Title><Msg>...“Many people consider the things government does for them to be social progress but they regard the things government does for others as socialism.” – Earl Warren “To the man on crutches, dressed in camouflage, who stole my wallet ... you can hide but you can't run.“ – Milton Jones "These people are mental. Congressman Joe Barton of Texas used Noah's Ark as evidence that global warming doesn't' exist. He said, 'If you're a believer in the Bible, one would have to say the Great Flood is an example of climate change and that certainly wasn't because mankind had overdeveloped hydrocarbon energy.' Can we forget Noah? This guy needs to start collecting two of every chromosome." - Bill Maher “To the category of the wonderful and uncanny we may also add that strange feeling we perceive in certain moments and situations when it seems as if we had already had exactly the same experience, or had previously found ourselves in the same situation. [...] I believe that it is wrong to designate the feeling of having experienced something before as an illusion. On the contrary, in such moments something is really touched that we have already experienced, only we cannot consciously recall the latter because it never was conscious. In short, the feeling of Déjà vu corresponds to the memory of an unconscious fantasy.” – Sigmund Freud “My father only hit me once…but he used a Volvo.” – Bob Monkhouse "According to a new study, our views on immigration are changing. For example, when asked if they support a path to citizenship, 40 percent of the respondents said, 'Si’.” - Jay Leno “The division between faith and reason is a half-measure, till it is frankly admitted that faith has to do with fiction, and reason with fact.” – Leslie Stephen “I have a lot of growing up to do. I realized that the other day in my fort.” – jon “President Obama hosted Republican senators for dinner at the White House. The president said he had to do without salt, pepper, and butter – because as you know, the Republicans refuse to pass anything." - Jay Leno “Not I, not any one else can travel that road for you, You must travel it for yourself. It is not far, it is within reach - Perhaps you have been on it since you were born and did not know…” – Walt Whitman</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366419144068</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:52:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366419528206-38</Id><Title>Final....</Title><Msg>...“This work contains many things which are new and interesting. Unfortunately, everything that is new is not interesting, and everything which is interesting, is not new.” – Lev Landau “Some men's words I remember so well that I must often use them to express my thought. Yes, because I perceive that we have heard the same truth, but they have heard it better.” – Ralph Waldo Emerson "Republicans did not have the votes for a filibuster, so there will be a debate about the gun bill. And given the recent rash of gun violence, Republicans said it was the least they could do. Literally, they had a meeting and said, 'What is the least we can do’?” - Bill Maher “I am trying to do two things: dare to be a radical and not be a fool, which, if I may judge by the exhibitions around me, is a matter of no small difficulty.” – James A. Garfield “His lack of education is more than compensated for by his keenly developed moral bankruptcy.” – Woody Allen "Iran is gearing up for a big presidential election in June. Yeah, this year it’s gonna be a tight race between Ahmadinejad and the guy they picked to lose to Ahmadinejad." - Jimmy Fallon “Adults are terribly confused, messed up people. That’s because they forget, really, that they don’t have to pretend all the time. Really, the fact is that you’re not an adult at all - you’re just a tall child holding a beer, having conversations you don’t understand… "The Middle East? Yeah, I know it was really bad. I wouldn’t have done that. A hysterectomy? Yeah, very painful, the shoulder is a very painful area." – Dylan Moran ”Did you ever hear one of these corny, positive messages on someone's answering machine? ‘Hi,it's a great day and I'm out enjoying it right now. I hope you are too. The thought for the day is: Share the love.‘ Beep. ‘Uh, yeah...this is the VD clinic calling....Speaking of being positive, your test results are back. Stop sharing the love‘." – Andy Rooney "A long list of celebrities and musicians have signed a letter to President Obama asking him to ease the nation's drug enforcement policy. Hollywood celebrities and musicians want the president to ease our drug laws – it's always the people you least expect." –Jay Leno “The universe is an intelligence test.” – Timothy Leary</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366419528206</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:58:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366423792367-39</Id><Topic><Title>Wonderful speech</Title><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1366245532638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 20:38:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who needs a pressure cooker? These turkeys read about it in a Jihadist manual. I've worked with explosives of several types years ago. Interesting thing about the "Shoe and Underware bombers. The Shoe Bomber had a wire stuck in the compound and tried to set it off with a match. Really smart guy. The under wear bomber did light his charge and was severely burned. GI's in Korea used a similar explosive (C-3) like sterno to cook their rations. These two apes were patsies.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1366423792367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 22:09:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366426130283-40</Id><Topic><Title>Oh no say it isn't so!</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1365866656934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:24:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tee hee..</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1366426130283</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 22:48:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366426903299-41</Id><Topic><Title>Wonderful speech</Title><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1366245532638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 20:38:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HAHAHAHAH. Whoever you are, you sure know how to get baby jonny all wound up with hilarious consequences. Have you noticed that most of its posts are disappearing as the day goes by? I guess the zonbac98 ID will go the way of the late (and far from great) jon3retired ID. The only constant in life is change...</Msg><Username>wledigmacsen</Username><Timestamp>1366426903299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 23:01:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>