<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-22"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358830853490-1</Id><Title>Premises Technicians MUST VOTE TWICE!</Title><Msg>Fellow Premises Technicians, Premises Technicians MUST VOTE TWICE! FIRST VOTE: If you have not voted on the contract offer, you must do so by this Saturday. Cast your vote at the Union Hall located at 1408 N Washington Ave. Dallas, TX. Not voting is your agreement to the terms of the contract. Do what it takes to get there. SECOND VOTE: Sadly, voting NO on this contract offer is not enough to stop it from being ratified. YOU MUST VOTE WITH YOUR MONEY! I am urging all Premises Technicians to immediately contact payroll and REVOKE your Authorization to DEDUCT UNION DUES from your pay check. IF YOU DO NOT TAKE ACTION, this POS contract will be ratified and we will NEVER receive the representation that we pay for. Certainly the lack of Stewardship or rather the lack of direction and support for our Stewards is a clear sign that complacence is what they want from us. WE ARE POORLY represented. Look at this contract, $0.60? When what we need by the end of this FOUR YEAR CONTRACT is $8.00! What kind of joke is this??? CAST TWO VOTES gentlemen! Call To Action!! Any member that can please volunteer to be at your garage by 7:am. Every Day! Greet everyone at the entrance of the building. Ask them if they have voted. Give them a printed copy of this email Address any schedule issues with the technician’s supervisor to ensure the opportunity to vote. Gentlemen, This is a good job; Make no mistake. This company was built by people just like you that took advantage of the opportunities this company has to offer. Those opportunities still exist for you! The difference is in the past they were well paid for a job well done. Since the mid 70's our wages have not kept pace with the times. Call it 'corporate greed' or what you like but we are grossly underpaid for the job we do. Also our right to bargain is under constant attack. We must act, waiting will cost us dearly. Read this article below, a link is included, and then VOTE TWICE! Your vote is your voice! Send a message to our union leaders that we want support in this fight for fair wages. VOTE TWICE! MONEY MATTERS! Premises Technician http://www.huffingtonpost.com/mobileweb/2012/05/02/ceo-pay-worker-pay_n_1471685.html It's good to be chief executive. American CEOs saw their pay spike 15 percent last year, after a 28 percent pay rise the year before, according to a report by GMI Ratings cited by The Guardian. Meanwhile, workers saw their inflation-adjusted wages fall 2 percent in 2011, according to the Labor Department. That's in line with a trend that dates back three decades. CEO pay spiked 725 percent between 1978 and 2011, while worker pay rose just 5.7 percent, according to a study by the Economic Policy Institute released on Wednesday. That means CEO pay grew 127 times faster than worker pay. Income inequality between CEOs and workers has consequently exploded, withCEOs last year earning 209.4 times morethan workers, compared to just 26.5 times more in 1978 -- meaning CEOs are taking home a larger percentage of company gains. That trend comes despite workers nearly doubling their productivity during the same time period, when compensation barely rose. Worker productivity spiked 93 percent between 1978 and 2011 on a per-hour basis, and 85 percent on a per-person basis, according to the Federal Reserve Bank of St. Louis. Meanwhile, workers saw their inflation-adjusted wages fall in recent years as corporations postponed giving raises while adding to their record corporate profits.</Msg><Username>cwa_renegade</Username><Timestamp>1358830853490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:00:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358843933023-2</Id><Topic><Title>Happy MLK Day!</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358814519155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:28:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually the MLK Day celebration that I attended was quite nice. It was the 9th annual MLK Day breakfast sponsored by the Austin College and Grayson County Rotary groups. There were prayers, speeches about the legacy of Dr. King, some choral singing, and the pancakes were pretty good too. I had several conversations with folks who had been around during those days, and we got to reminisce about the good times and bad. For me MLK Day has and I hope will always be a day of healing and retrospective thought, because during these days of devisive rhetoric and polorization, people need just a little time to sit down together and enjoy a good pancake. Hope yours was just as nice. "In your heart you know he is right" The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358843933023</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 03:38:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358861686559-3</Id><Topic><Title>T-Superbowl picks/opinions</Title><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1358770354243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 07:12:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I may have to go with the Ravens. Flacco is a UD graduate and so are my future in-laws and daughter. They are probably betting against him so I have to go the other way.</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1358861686559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 08:34:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358868226736-4</Id><Topic><Title>Premises Technicians MUST VOTE TWICE!</Title><Username>cwa_renegade</Username><Timestamp>1358830853490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:00:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Renegade, I only read part of your post before I found fault with it. I recently retired in the District 6 area. I went thru what you're going thru before the last contract was negotiated. ,, Here's what I know,, 1st,, you can't just 'contact' payroll. If I remember correctly, the procedure to stop union dues is somewhere between pages 78 - 96 in your contract book ( pages 92 sounds right) and it involves a wriitten and signed paper stating something to that looks like this " PLEASE STOP WITHDRAWING UNION DUES FROM MY CHECK" . That's really all it needs to say, print your name, date, payroll #, and any other vital data your think they may need, and then sign it and mail it to the address on the front of your paycheck stub. The process takes about 2 months, but there is a catch,,, you can only make this request with-in a specific time frame of each year. I don't remember the dates but they are in the contract book. If I remember correctly, it is a 4 week window. It's one of the things that I wanted changed in the new contract book. ,, 2nd ,, I have done this before, I went to my union hall and show dissatisfaction to their representation and that the same time warned them that if they didn't get their heads out of the #$%$ I would start a campaigne to show (and help) 10% of the members how to get out of the union each year until the changes happened. I was asked to sit down and be quiet or I would have to leave the Union meeting, I had a scheduled 5 minutes in that meeting to speak. The funny thing was after I sat down the Union President had the nerve to attack my comments by saying " As a member in good standing, we need to remind our brothers that by paying our dues, we guarantee a voice in this Union" ,, so I stood up again and said " LIAR, you just asked me to shut up or leave! " ,, I'm not condoning paying Union dues, and I showed a lot of people how to get out of the Union after that meeting ( even posted the rules on this message board ) ,, but here's the problem with not paying dues,, if you are not paying, then you can't even get into the Union Hall to express your complaint, even if it's only for 60 seconds. That 60 seconds that I got before they shut me down, was important. It opened eyes to what is going on. The CWA is only in it for the money. Contact your local and see how many contracts that they manage. The Communication Workers of America (CWA) negotiates many contracts, not just Telecommunications, but city workers and electricians. I have heard my local president tell the stewards that they need to hit the streets and get more members signed up. WHY? ,, because it's a business. Renegade, sorry I got on a soap box, but you have touched a nerve again.. I hope you are successful in getting the word out. The employees need to keep an eye on Randal Stephenson and the CWA. Both are only concerned with their own future.</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1358868226736</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:23:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358868759672-5</Id><Topic><Title>Happy MLK Day!</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358814519155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:28:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude, stop "reading" MLK day coverage on Fox. “I am now convinced that the simplest approach will prove to be the most effective -- the solution to poverty is to abolish it directly by a now widely discussed measure: the guaranteed income.... We are likely to find that the problems of housing and education, instead of preceding the elimination of poverty, will themselves be affected if poverty is first abolished.” --The Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King Jr., 1967 “...The richest nation on Earth has never allocated enough resources to build sufficient schools, to compensate adequately its teachers, and to surround them with the prestige our work justifies. We squander funds on highways, on the frenetic pursuit of recreation, on the overabundance of overkill armament, but we pauperize education.” --The Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King Jr., 1964</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358868759672</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:32:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358869099370-6</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T is going down but tomorrow brings many changes !</Title><Username>chappell.kenneth</Username><Timestamp>1358279476329</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:51:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report, thanks</Msg><Username>benjaminmartin945</Username><Timestamp>1358869099370</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:38:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358869471214-7</Id><Topic><Title>T-Superbowl picks/opinions</Title><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1358770354243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 07:12:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since you asked Cisco, I will share Maxine's opinion, "My idea of a Super Bowl is a toiliet that cleans itself."</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1358869471214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:44:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358870378470-8</Id><Topic><Title>Premises Technicians MUST VOTE TWICE!</Title><Username>cwa_renegade</Username><Timestamp>1358830853490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:00:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clarification: I do not advocate leaving the union. The purpose of the stop pay on union dues is to express our dissatisfaction for being ignored in this negotiation. You can reinstate your payment option later and dues should be deducted in arrears. I do not know if there are other payment options available, but for millions in dues I bet our union can come up with one. Out of respect for our union leaders and volunteers, and appreciation for all that they do to protect our bargaining rights, I will not be sending any more global emails. Please VOTE</Msg><Username>cwa_renegade</Username><Timestamp>1358870378470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:59:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358870576486-9</Id><Topic><Title>Premises Technicians MUST VOTE TWICE!</Title><Username>cwa_renegade</Username><Timestamp>1358830853490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:00:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you whopperk, I will check the book, my sentiment is shared by many and if we start treating our union like we are shareholders we just might get the representation we need.</Msg><Username>cwa_renegade</Username><Timestamp>1358870576486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:02:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358871839330-10</Id><Title>Large-scale network outage</Title><Msg>Apparently a majority of the east coast has had major loss of Uverse service over the past 24 hours. Very limited communication from the company. Rumors starting to swirl...</Msg><Username>bgf00</Username><Timestamp>1358871839330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:23:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358872404664-11</Id><Topic><Title>Premises Technicians MUST VOTE TWICE!</Title><Username>cwa_renegade</Username><Timestamp>1358830853490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:00:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the cwa stinks..we here in connecticut have once again been abandoned by the cwa union,,4 years ago it was one union one fight and all the districts settleted without waiting for each other..this year larry #$%$ cohen the president of the cwa came up with a table of 8 all vice pres. and they werent suppose to settle until we all reached agreement well we got screwed again ...all thats left without a contract is us in connecticut..3500 employees and we get #$%$ on again...</Msg><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1358872404664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:33:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358874310669-12</Id><Topic><Title>Happy MLK Day!</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358814519155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:28:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dr. Alveda King, niece of slain civil rights leader Martin Luther King-"Obama’s support of abortion, same-sex marriage, and free contraception under his unpopular Obamacare reform is difficult to reconcile with my uncle's legacy as a man of God" “I really hope that when the president — and those who handle the Bible — I hope they just, even if they just accidentally slip it open, to where it says ‘choose life,’ or ‘God hates the shedding of innocent blood’ or something like that, I’m hoping it will just reverberate, shake them up a little bit,” said King, a pastoral associate and director of African-American outreach for Priests for Life and Gospel of Life Ministries. We are less free under Obama Obama has removed religious freedom by forcing those who oppose abortions to fund it through Obamacare. Obama is leading the attack on our second amendment rights. Obama has attacked our Freedom of speech - Obama took on the role of censor-in-chief. Days after the Benghazi attack, the administration told YouTube to take down the video in question and had the person responsible for the video arrested and to this day he still remains in jail without any formal charges. The president took it upon himself to determine what should be removed from the Internet — just as Vladimir Putin or the Chinese government might.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1358874310669</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:05:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358875275481-13</Id><Topic><Title>Economic Lies...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1358345360485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:09:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most economics is pure BS. You and others NEVER mention the privately owned "Fed" which has a monopoly on the issue of interest bearing currency. (For them). Reich is part of the cabal behind this racket.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1358875275481</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:21:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358876407492-14</Id><Topic><Title>Happy MLK Day!</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358814519155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:28:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It was not a superficial whiff of "christian" or "patriotism" or "right" without meaning that Dr. King embraced." Not sure what you are talking about, If you had not noticed Dr. King's was a reverend, he was first and foremost a man of God who preached God's word. There was nothing superficial about his references to the words of the Bible. Dr. King was a Christian first everything else was secondary including his citizenship. His desire was to align the laws and people of the land in which he lived with what the Bible teaches us. Why did you not give the word Christian the respect it commands and capitalize it?</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1358876407492</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:40:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358877041450-15</Id><Topic><Title>Happy MLK Day!</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358814519155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:28:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obama has removed religious freedom by forcing those who oppose abortions to fund it through Obamacare." Hogwash. The same provisions preventing Federal funding of abortions that have always been in place remain in place under Obamacare. "Obama is leading the attack on our second amendment rights." Hogwash. There is no attack on our second amendment rights. There are reasonable attempt to regulate that right. "had the person responsible for the video arrested and to this day he still remains in jail without any formal charges. " And finish it up with a bald-faced lie. Disgusting.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358877041450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:50:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358877377128-16</Id><Topic><Title>Happy MLK Day!</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358814519155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:28:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There was nothing superficial about his references to the words of the Bible." Of course there wasn't. I was referring to your superficial understanding of "christian". Where did the Bible teach you to lie? Where did it teach to pretend to be someone else? To you "christian" is a superficial trapping. To men of God, "Christian" is a way of life. You are no man of God. You are a charlatan. Stop worrying about capitalization and worry about your actions.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358877377128</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:56:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358880580733-17</Id><Topic><Title>Economic Lies...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1358345360485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:09:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Most economics is pure BS." Oh, of course. Unless it's a conspiracy theory it's pure BS, eh? The economists at the privately-owned Fed have done a pretty d*** good job with that currency monopoly. It's partisans and nutjobs like you that are gumming up the fiscal half of the equation.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358880580733</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:49:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358880660506-18</Id><Topic><Title>Happy MLK Day!</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358814519155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:28:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They gave to us a Republic, a government of, and by, and for the people, entrusting each generation to keep safe our founding creed. " And our modern day politicians have taken it away and turned government service at higher levels into near royalty. They don't hold themselves accountable to the people they are supposed to represent and have little in common with them. They support actions that are in the interests of their large campaign donors, reelection, and their own individual wealth. This is proven by the existence of the wealth 'government servants' leaving government that were not wealthy when they arrived. Obama's view of the world and our interaction with our government only exacerbate these problems.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358880660506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:51:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358881164146-19</Id><Topic><Title>Top 5 causes of accidental death in the US</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358687253589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>December 29, 2012 marked the 122nd Anniversary of the murder of 297 Sioux Indians at Wounded Knee Creek on the Pine Ridge Indian Reservation in South Dakota. These 297 people, in their winter camp, were murdered by federal agents and members of the 7th Cavalry who had come to confiscate their firearms for their own safety and protection. The slaughter began after the majority of the Sioux had peacefully turned in their firearms. The Calvary began shooting, and managed to wipe out the entire camp. 200 of the 297 victims were women and children. About 40 members of the 7th Cavalry were killed, but over half of them were victims of fratricide from the Hotchkiss guns of their overzealous comrades-in-arms. Twenty members of the 7th Cavalry’s death squad were deemed National Heroes and were awarded the Medal of Honor for their acts of [cowardice] heroism. We hear very little of Wounded Knee today. It is usually not mentioned in our history classes or books. What little that does exist about Wounded Knee is normally a sanitized Official Government Explanation. And there are several historically inaccurate depictions of the events leading up to the massacre, which appear in movie scripts and are not the least bit representative of the actual events that took place that day. Wounded Knee was among the first federally backed gun confiscation attempts in United States history. It ended in the senseless murder of 297 people. Before you jump on the emotionally charged bandwagon for gun control, take a moment to reflect on the real purpose of the Second Amendment, the right of the people to take up arms in defense of themselves, their families, and property in the face of invading armies or an oppressive government. The argument that the Second Amendment only applies to hunting and target shooting is asinine. When the United States Constitution was drafted, hunting was an everyday chore carried out by men and women to put meat on the table each night, and target shooting was an unheard of concept. Musket balls were a precious commodity and were certainly not wasted on target shooting. The Second Amendment was written by people who fled oppressive and tyrannical regimes in Europe, and it refers to the right of American citizens to be armed for defensive purposes, should such tyranny arise in the United States. As time goes forward, the average citizen in the United States continually loses little chunks of personal freedom or liberty. Far too many times, unjust gun control bills were passed and signed into law under the guise of for your safety or for protection. The Patriot Act signed into law by G.W. Bush, was expanded, and continues under Barack Obama. It is just one of many examples of American citizens being stripped of their rights and privacy for safety. Now, the Right to Keep and Bear Arms is on the table, and will, most likely be attacked to facilitate the path for the removal of our firearms, all in the name of our safety. Before any American citizen blindly accepts whatever new firearms legislation that is about to be doled out, they should stop and think about something for just one minute. Evil does exist in our world. It always has and always will. Throughout history evil people have committed evil acts. In the Bible one of the first stories is that of Cain killing Abel. We cannot legislate evil into extinction. Good people will abide by the law, and the criminal element will always find a way around it. Evil exists all around us, but looking back at the historical record of the past 200 years, across the globe, where is evil and malevolence most often found? In the hands of those with the power, the governments. Those greatest human tragedies on record and the largest loss of innocent human life can be attributed to governments. Whom do the governments always target? Scapegoats and enemies within their own borders….but only after they have been disarmed to the point where they no longer pose a threat. Ask any Native American, and they will tell you it was inferior technology and lack of arms that contributed to their demise. Ask any Armenian why it was so easy for the Turks to exterminate millions of them, and they will answer we were disarmed before it happened. Ask any Jew what Hitler’s first step prior to the mass murders of the Holocaust was confiscation of firearms from the people. Wounded Knee is the prime example of why the Second Amendment exists, and why we should vehemently resist any attempts to infringe on our Rights to Bear Arms. Without the Second Amendment we will be totally stripped of any ability to defend our families and ourselves.</Msg><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1358881164146</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:59:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358881578780-20</Id><Topic><Title>Danny Glover teaches constitutional law at Texas A &amp; M University</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358679621880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 06:00:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can someone explain how the President’s proposed actions will actually stop incidents like what happened in that school? How will it stop someone with evil on their minds, with the full intent to hide their plans from walking into a school with a legally or illegally obtained weapon and doing great harm? No, the constant false argument about automatic weapons allowing them to kill more people in less time doesn't work. How will any of the actions planned stop the manic from strolling into a public place and committing their horrendous acts? I betting you can’t, because their plans won’t stop what happened.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358881578780</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:06:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358881748095-21</Id><Topic><Title>Premises Technicians MUST VOTE TWICE!</Title><Username>cwa_renegade</Username><Timestamp>1358830853490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:00:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again Renegade, my intent was to get people to stop paying their dues, but what I found out was that you are only a "member in good standing" if you're dues are up to date. I agree if you can get change started, then by all means reinstate your dues. We had a strong Union representation when I started working for the company in the 80's and it can be that way again if change can happen. 'CTMUSCLE" has a post that is a good example of how weak and greedy the Union is right now. After 3 years of showing people how to hit the CWA in the pocket book to get their attention I retired thinking the only way this is going to change is to try to convince enough people to join the IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers). I never researched how to do it but that is a thought. Or maybe the "Teamsters Union", I'm sure with a phone call to one of those local presidents, they could tell you the procedure. The threat of knowing to change to the IBEW might open the CWA's eyes.</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1358881748095</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:09:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358881833039-22</Id><Topic><Title>Danny Glover</Title><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358808488801</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 17:48:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Glover has no credentials." There is the truth. The man has no credentials, education, or expertise to be considered any sort of reliable speaker on Constitutional law, the meaning of any aspects of the Constitution. Clear enough for you? Just another actor with a public stage working hard to make a fool of himself. Don’t get me wrong, I enjoy his acting; he should stick to it!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358881833039</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:10:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358882381343-23</Id><Topic><Title>Danny Glover</Title><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358808488801</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 17:48:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love how the right wing nuts give a thumbs down to what happens to be the truth. I guess it's just masturbation to them.</Msg><Username>freakedout35</Username><Timestamp>1358882381343</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:19:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358882642615-24</Id><Topic><Title>Danny Glover teaches constitutional law at Texas A &amp; M University</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358679621880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 06:00:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>vanzinf you add nothing to the conversation with your stupidity.</Msg><Username>freakedout35</Username><Timestamp>1358882642615</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:24:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358882700459-25</Id><Topic><Title>Danny Glover</Title><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358808488801</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 17:48:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ok!!!!! one of the nut jobs just game me a thumbs down. get out the towel.</Msg><Username>freakedout35</Username><Timestamp>1358882700459</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:25:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358883136619-26</Id><Topic><Title>Danny Glover teaches constitutional law at Texas A &amp; M University</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358679621880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 06:00:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does this have to do with T?</Msg><Username>tossitoutguy</Username><Timestamp>1358883136619</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:32:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358884737505-27</Id><Topic><Title>Danny Glover</Title><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358808488801</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 17:48:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well golly gee am I embarrassed. Are you telling me that when Mr. Glover was invited to speak at Texas A&amp;M about the genesis of the second ammendment, that he was just some actor from hollywood. Wow I must admit my surprise that an educational institution of the stature of this great university would not have had the forsight to have investigated whether Mr. Glover's words had any educational value or credibility. All I can say is thanks ellerbe for pointing out my error in judgement. You have truly put me in my place, and I will try and do better next time. You have made my day. "In your heart you know he is right" The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358884737505</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:58:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358885438507-28</Id><Topic><Title>Danny Glover</Title><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358808488801</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 17:48:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"when Mr. Glover was invited to speak at Texas A&amp;M about the genesis of the second ammendment," Get over yourselves, will ya. He wasn't invited to speak about the genesis of the second amendment. He was invited to speak at a small, MLK day "breakfast". The topic came up during the discussion. For you, Froggie, to be criticizing someone for expressing an opinion without necessarily having the qualifications to back it up is just absurd. The funny thing is Mr. Glover's statement is correct. But that doesn't matter to you at all, does it?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358885438507</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:10:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358886099113-29</Id><Title>The REAL Killer, List Of School Shootings Known To Be Linked To SSRI's</Title><Msg>Why have we not demanded that SSRI (Selective Serotonin Re-uptake Inhibitors) be banned? Eric Harris age 17 (first on Zoloft then Luvox) and Dylan Klebold aged 18 (Colombine school shooting in Littleton, Colorado), killed 12 students and 1 teacher, and wounded 23 others, before killing themselves. Klebold's medical records have never been made available to the public. Jeff Weise, age 16, had been prescribed 60 mg/day of Prozac (three times the average starting dose for adults!) when he shot his grandfather, his grandfather's girlfriend and many fellow students at Red Lake, Minnesota. He then shot himself. 10 dead, 12 wounded. Cory Baadsgaard, age 16, Wahluke (Washington state) High School, was on Paxil (which caused him to have hallucinations) when he took a rifle to his high school and held 23 classmates hostage. He has no memory of the event. Chris Fetters, age 13, killed his favorite aunt while taking Prozac. Christopher Pittman, age 12, murdered both his grandparents while taking Zoloft. Mathew Miller, age 13, hung himself in his bedroom closet after taking Zoloft for 6 days. Jarred Viktor, age 15, stabbed his grandmother 61 times after 5 days on Paxil. Kip Kinkel, age 15, (on Prozac and Ritalin) shot his parents while they slept then went to school and opened fire killing 2 classmates and injuring 22 shortly after beginning Prozac treatment. Luke Woodham, age 16 (Prozac) killed his mother and then killed two students, wounding six others. A boy in Pocatello, ID (Zoloft) in 1998 had a Zoloft-induced seizure that caused an armed stand off at his school. Michael Carneal (Ritalin), age 14, opened fire on students at a high school prayer meeting in West Paducah, Kentucky. Three teenagers were killed, five others were wounded.. A young man in Huntsville, Alabama (Ritalin) went psychotic chopping up his parents with an ax and also killing one sibling and almost murdering another. Andrew Golden, age 11, (Ritalin) and Mitchell Johnson, aged 14, (Ritalin) shot 15 people, killing four students, one teacher, and wounding 10 others. TJ Solomon, age 15, (Ritalin) high school student in Conyers, Georgia opened fire on and wounded six of his class mates. Rod Mathews, age 14, (Ritalin) beat a classmate to death with a bat. James Wilson, age 19, (various psychiatric drugs) from Breenwood, South Carolina, took a .22 caliber revolver into an elementary school killing two young girls, and wounding seven other children and two teachers. Elizabeth Bush, age 13, (Paxil) was responsible for a school shooting in Pennsylvania Jason Hoffman (Effexor and Celexa) – school shooting in El Cajon, California Jarred Viktor, age 15, (Paxil), after five days on Paxil he stabbed his grandmother 61 times. Chris Shanahan, age 15 (Paxil) in Rigby, ID who out of the blue killed a woman. Jeff Franklin (Prozac and Ritalin), Huntsville, AL, killed his parents as they came home from work using a sledge hammer, hatchet, butcher knife and mechanic's file, then attacked his younger brothers and sister. Neal Furrow (Prozac) in LA Jewish school shooting reported to have been court-ordered to be on Prozac along with several other medications. Kevin Rider, age 14, was withdrawing from Prozac when he died from a gunshot wound to his head. Initially it was ruled a suicide, but two years later, the investigation into his death was opened as a possible homicide. The prime suspect, also age 14, had been taking Zoloft and other SSRI antidepressants. Alex Kim, age 13, hung himself shortly after his Lexapro prescription had been doubled. Diane Routhier was prescribed Welbutrin for gallstone problems. Six days later, after suffering many adverse effects of the drug, she shot herself. Billy Willkomm, an accomplished wrestler and a University of Florida student, was prescribed Prozac at the age of 17. His family found him dead of suicide – hanging from a tall ladder at the family's Gulf Shore Boulevard home in July 2002. Kara Jaye Anne Fuller-Otter, age 12, was on Paxil when she hung herself from a hook in her closet. Kara's parents said "…. the damn doctor wouldn't take her off it and I asked him to when we went in on the second visit. I told him I thought she was having some sort of reaction to Paxil..." Gareth Christian, Vancouver, age 18, was on Paxil when he committed suicide in 2002, (Gareth's father could not accept his son's death and killed himself.) Julie Woodward, age 17, was on Zoloft when she hung herself in her family's detached garage. Matthew Miller was 13 when he saw a psychiatrist because he was having difficulty at school. The psychiatrist gave him samples of Zoloft. Seven days later his mother found him dead, hanging by a belt from a laundry hook in his closet. Kurt Danysh, age 18, and on Prozac, killed his father with a shotgun. He is now behind prison bars, and writes letters, trying to warn the world that SSRI drugs can kill. Woody _____, age 37, committed suicide while in his 5th week of taking Zoloft. Shortly before his death his physician suggested doubling the dose of the drug. He had seen his physician only for insomnia. He had never been depressed, nor did he have any history of any mental illness symptoms. A boy from Houston, age 10, shot and killed his father after his Prozac dosage was increased. Hammad Memon, age 15, shot and killed a fellow middle school student. He had been diagnosed with ADHD and depression and was taking Zoloft and "other drugs for the conditions." Matti Saari, a 22-year-old culinary student, shot and killed 9 students and a teacher, and wounded another student, before killing himself. Saari was taking an SSRI and a benzodiazapine. Steven Kazmierczak, age 27, shot and killed five people and wounded 21 others before killing himself in a Northern Illinois University auditorium. According to his girlfriend, he had recently been taking Prozac, Xanax and Ambien. Toxicology results showed that he still had trace amounts of Xanax in his system. Finnish gunman Pekka-Eric Auvinen, age 18, had been taking antidepressants before he killed eight people and wounded a dozen more at Jokela High School – then he committed suicide. Asa #$%$ from Cleveland, age 14, shot and wounded four before taking his own life. Court records show #$%$ was on Trazodone. Jon Romano, age 16, on medication for depression, fired a shotgun at a teacher in his New York high school. CALL TO ACTION: The only way Americans are going to halt this latest gun-grabber attack on the Bill of Rights is to force the issue of SSRI-caused violence into the public eye. You (ALL of us) need to forward these articles about SSRIs and violence, and the fact that the Connecticut shooter was on these medications, to all your local media, all your family and friends, every public forum you can find, and specially to flood the offices of members of Congress (who already had hearings into this very problem). Right now that fancy software the government bought to fake thousands of online identities is cranked up full-tilt; unless We The People match them post for post, fact for myth, the gun-grabbers will win through attrition.</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1358886099113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:21:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358886864043-30</Id><Topic><Title>Danny Glover</Title><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358808488801</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 17:48:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow am I embarrassed. You mean it was just an MLK Day breakfast held on January 17, and it was just a comment over flapjacks? As far as criticizing Mr. Glover's opinions, I think you have over interpreted my comments, because none of my statements have ever been critical in nature of Mr. Glover, nor should they be construed as such. "In your heart you know he is right" The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358886864043</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:34:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358888829789-31</Id><Title>Will AT&amp;T keep Alltel network open after June?</Title><Msg>It's making money. Couldn't they make a deal with VZW? Don't we need to make up $4B somewhere?</Msg><Username>omartba</Username><Timestamp>1358888829789</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:07:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358891284986-32</Id><Topic><Title>T- anyone awake at the wheel? geez, $4b for nothing and now</Title><Username>elmaestro111</Username><Timestamp>1358798227201</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 14:57:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stephenson, the disastrous CEO of AT&amp;T, must do. He's a dud.</Msg><Username>timetraveler2u</Username><Timestamp>1358891284986</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:48:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358892414479-33</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T is going down but tomorrow brings many changes !</Title><Username>chappell.kenneth</Username><Timestamp>1358279476329</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:51:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>important report</Msg><Username>michaelthompson258</Username><Timestamp>1358892414479</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:06:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358892760364-34</Id><Topic><Title>Danny Glover</Title><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358808488801</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 17:48:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said Danny Glover was a professor of Constitutional Law at A&amp;M and had made certain comments to his students. You are a lier. And you have no shame.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358892760364</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:12:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358893027166-35</Id><Title>Back to the mid $34's by Friday.......finally.</Title><Msg>Just my opinion of course. However, seems like I've been wrong quite a bit lately. GLTA</Msg><Username>twoforfunjustask</Username><Timestamp>1358893027166</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:17:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358893935949-36</Id><Topic><Title>Back to the mid $34's by Friday.......finally.</Title><Username>twoforfunjustask</Username><Timestamp>1358893027166</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, I believe that you may be correct for a change.</Msg><Username>finallyasmartone</Username><Timestamp>1358893935949</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:32:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358894287647-37</Id><Topic><Title>Premises Technicians MUST VOTE TWICE!</Title><Username>cwa_renegade</Username><Timestamp>1358830853490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:00:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a stock board not a union cry baby board! Don't like your working conditions? Quit!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358894287647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:38:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358895111474-38</Id><Title>Harry Reid gets caught stealing pens from the White House</Title><Msg>If you haven't seen the video please do take a moment to give it a watch. For me the fact that old light fingers Harry would take his shot at a little five finger discount in the White House was not the most precious part of the moment, on the contrary the fact that he was clearly ratted out by Chuck Schumer made the episode a classic. Again if you haven't seen the video, IMHO it is worth the watch. "In your heart you know he is right" The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358895111474</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:51:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358895118934-39</Id><Topic><Title>Top 5 causes of accidental death in the US</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358687253589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And how many abortions? Aren't most of those killings intentional?</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1358895118934</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:51:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358896657575-40</Id><Topic><Title>Top 5 causes of accidental death in the US</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358687253589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the use of rubbers. Preventing all those lives. LOL</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358896657575</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:17:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358905232093-41</Id><Topic><Title>T- anyone awake at the wheel? geez, $4b for nothing and now</Title><Username>elmaestro111</Username><Timestamp>1358798227201</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 14:57:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This morning Verizon posted a record 4Q loss on a similar pension adjustment and its share price was up 0.40 at the close. Bad management indeed.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1358905232093</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:40:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358906238252-42</Id><Topic><Title>Top 5 causes of accidental death in the US</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358687253589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weren't you recently arrested? Assault with a dead weapon?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358906238252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:57:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358910120163-43</Id><Topic><Title>Top 5 causes of accidental death in the US</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358687253589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Iran gets to have as many nuclear bombs as they want? Why? because 20 people were choked to death in Iran? 100 were stabbed? How are these related? Where is the limit? Our military has nukes, you should have the right to have nukes? Who cares about estimated percentage of gang related blah blah blah. I count one little 7 year old girl shot many times with a bushmaster, as enough reason. Take them all away. Melt them all down.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1358910120163</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:02:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>