<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369052747585-1</Id><Topic><Title>IRS Black Ops unit of Obama SS attacks conservatives.</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1368633032316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:50:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“The Obama admin is out of control…” – spamo_1 Oh, really? At what point do you clowns realize that the American people are fed up with your bogus swiftboat/bogie-man/Birther mentality and repeated efforts to obstruct everything this administration does. Out of control? Apparently most folks disagree with you. “Washington, May 20 (ANI): President Barack Obama's approval rating has not been hurt by recent scandals, a new poll has shown. The poll conducted by CNN and ORC International found that 53 percent of Americans approve of the job Obama is doing as compared to 45 percent who disapprove. The number remains virtually unchanged from polls taken before the scandals hit. The CNN poll also found that 71 percent of Americans believe the actions of the IRS employees who targeted tea party groups were unacceptable. However, 6 in 10 respondents said they trusted the president's statements on the issue.” So keep wasting everybody’s time with your childish tantrums. Your feigned indignation over Benghazi after what happened under your watch in Iraq is a joke. But stay the course...See how that plays out for you in 2014 mid-term elections.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1369052747585</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:25:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369056035684-2</Id><Topic><Title>Bobbie Woodward</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368906387703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 15:46:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or it was exactly what it looks like. As Ezra Klein describes it the talking point edits were "a bureaucratic knife fight between the State Department and the CIA" with little involvement from the White House. Although I'd call it more of a jostling. The CIA belief at the time was that extremists had infiltrated protests based on the video. That is what Susan Rice and the Obama administration relayed. There's just nothing there. What is the supposed scandal at this point. What happened at Benghazi? Whether Susan Rice should have said Al Quada while the FBI was urgining her not to? Who edited the talking points? Whether John Carney correctly related who edited the talking points? What level of triviality are we going to focus on here? With all three of these supposed scandals, which have you partisan freaks calling for impeachment, there's nothing there.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369056035684</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:20:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369056206849-3</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S., especially the South has almost been destroyed</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369005998527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad to see you weren't the one to hit the lottery. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369056206849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:23:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369057473453-4</Id><Topic><Title>A new request from the White House.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368738680728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 17:11:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what you are really upset about is that you have to pay for your stuff and your monthly government check went down. Good to know you're a well-informed greedy old guy.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369057473453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:44:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369057589419-5</Id><Topic><Title>California does something right..(!!)</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1368990343979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 15:05:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They can pretty much do that now with shell casing scars, barrel twists etc. aka firearms forensics" Only if they have the gun.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369057589419</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:46:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369057672447-6</Id><Topic><Title>Bobbie Woodward</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368906387703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 15:46:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What level of triviality are we going to focus on here?" How about the 'triviality' of four people dying while the incompetent in our government did NOTHING. And now the 'triviality' of continuing to lie about who did, said or didn't do anything. Certainly not impeachable, but the country deserves to have the full truth regardless of the political consequences. As a once-off incident, if you disregard the four deaths, which you shouldn't, it isn't that much. Now add it to the other issues surrounding this administration since its inception and you get a very clear picture of incompetence, arrogance, and deceit. That’s a list of things I would much prefer not to find in my government.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1369057672447</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:47:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369057744418-7</Id><Topic><Title>California does something right..(!!)</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1368990343979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 15:05:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reminds me of the new Subaru ads for "Partial Zero Emissions Vehicles". My feeling is they only run those in America.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369057744418</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:49:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369058005551-8</Id><Topic><Title>I tend to agree</Title><Username>mayor3004</Username><Timestamp>1368998977883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 17:29:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It also appears that the Justice department did get a warrant, but the law also requires them to tell the AP that they had the warrant and were collecting the data. They did not do that. They kept it a secret.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1369058005551</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:53:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369058548360-9</Id><Topic><Title>A new request from the White House.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368738680728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 17:11:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"So what you are really upset about is that you have to pay for your stuff" Once again you are full of it. I am no longer amazed by how easily and frequently you make stuff up. For the record, I never complained to begin with. Show me in this string of posts where I complained. The fact is, assuming you can handle a fact, a modest increase in my monthly Medicare obligation is fine. You do know, however, what I am upset about is paying for more and more for the stuff of other people.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1369058548360</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:02:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369058636932-10</Id><Topic><Title>California does something right..(!!)</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1368990343979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 15:05:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly!</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1369058636932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369058709706-11</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S., especially the South has almost been destroyed</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369005998527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>White Europeans built the US into the greatest country in the world. Now minorities from every failed country and culture, some of which never made it out of hunter gatherer status are taking over and making the US into an image of their beloved failed homelands.</Msg><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1369058709706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:05:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060041833-12</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S., especially the South has almost been destroyed</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369005998527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tea Brains: Jealous racist idiots dependent on government checks in their old age. Does that about sum it up?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369060041833</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:27:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060517698-13</Id><Topic><Title>A new request from the White House.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368738680728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 17:11:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahh, forgive me, I will rephrase. You are not upset about having to pay a little bit more for your highly subsidized government insurance. I like it. One small step for a man, one giant leap for Tea Brain kind! In 30 years you may even be willing to pay for your stuff!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369060517698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060524577-14</Id><Topic><Title>California does something right..(!!)</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1368990343979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 15:05:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jon is far too occupied with writing illiterate, foul-mouthed, racist, anti-gay nonsense to spend time actually thinking about what he is writing. That would diminish his output. and might lead to him feeling like he was getting less attention than he craves.</Msg><Username>hotdoggitwiggie</Username><Timestamp>1369060524577</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:35:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060575351-15</Id><Topic><Title>California does something right..(!!)</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1368990343979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 15:05:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think he's just really, really dumb.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369060575351</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:36:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060712155-16</Id><Topic><Title>A new request from the White House.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368738680728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 17:11:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" one giant leap for Tea Brain kind" The giant step for the Tea Party kind is when you sicked the IRS on them.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1369060712155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060723947-17</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S., especially the South has almost been destroyed</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369005998527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That sound about right. You could throw in a few more adjectives, but there's no sense in overloading the wagon.</Msg><Username>hotdoggitwiggie</Username><Timestamp>1369060723947</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:38:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060806460-18</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S., especially the South has almost been destroyed</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369005998527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep making stuff up. It helps the Tea Party.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1369060806460</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060867922-19</Id><Topic><Title>California does something right..(!!)</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1368990343979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 15:05:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUT echo .. can we depend on the 'gun', OR the criminal owner to file a "forwarding address" with the Post Office ... of which 'P.O. Box' he has moved to ?? Yep .. you and 'icky' must be father &amp; son !!</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1369060867922</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:41:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369061406555-20</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S., especially the South has almost been destroyed</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369005998527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't post this stuff. Nor am I part of the idiot parade that cheerleads for these guys. You people are what you are and you demonstrate it over and over and over again. That is called reality. It paints quite a different picture than the ego massage Rush &amp; Fox provide you people on a daily basis. What would you have me do? Ignore it? Pretend you guys are something else? Lie through my teeth?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369061406555</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:50:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369061448459-21</Id><Title>OK - break it up, nothing to see here people.</Title><Msg>Just another down day for ATT. Nothing unusual going on here. This stock peaked a month or so ago and doesn't look like it's going to do anything but drift lower. Why would anyone want to buy a stock with decreasing earnings in a market that's going nuts to the upside like this? Apparently nobody does. Too many good opportunities out there. Dead $$$ here. Be satisfied with your dividend and a declining share price going forward - or sell and find a stock that actually has a chance to go up in a bull market. This stock has shot its load for a long while.</Msg><Username>smithersj1234</Username><Timestamp>1369061448459</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:50:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369061717453-22</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S., especially the South has almost been destroyed</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369005998527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Lie through my teeth?" Ah, a glimmer of truth.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1369061717453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:55:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369062295431-23</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S., especially the South has almost been destroyed</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369005998527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok, I'll rephrase: What would you have me do? Ignore it? Pretend you guys are something else? Take snippets of quotes completely out of context and pretend they reflect something real? I think I've summed up the Tea Brains again! Like I said, you people are what you are and you demonstrate it over and over again. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369062295431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:04:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369062712843-24</Id><Topic><Title>A new request from the White House.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368738680728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 17:11:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes! Get those Tea Brains to *finally* to pay for their stuff! You are making much greater progress than I expected. You may earn that Tea Brain Fine monkier yet.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369062712843</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:11:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369063787758-25</Id><Topic><Title>I tend to agree</Title><Username>mayor3004</Username><Timestamp>1368998977883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 17:29:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. Everything the Justice Department did was legal under the PATRIOT Act and other measures meant to increase surveillance powers post-9/11. They did issue a subpoena, which is different than a warrant. They used a National Security exemption that exists in the law to avoid informing the AP. It is important to note that just about every high level person in the Justice Department had recused themselves from the process because they had been questioned about the leak--including the person who normally oversees these types of subpoenas. So you had lower level people pursuing a leak as doggedly as they could within the law, without the political checks from the executive in place to temper their efforts. The real question here is how much legal authority to surveil should DOJ have? Should we depend on the good graces of the President and political appointees to protect us from government overreach or should these protections be written into the law?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369063787758</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:29:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369063887791-26</Id><Topic><Title>I tend to agree</Title><Username>mayor3004</Username><Timestamp>1368998977883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 17:29:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems to me you're as dumb as ever. No wonder you don't want to compete on a level playing field with others. You will surely lose. Heck, you're a loser even with decades of white privilege under your belt.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369063887791</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:31:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369064904247-27</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S., especially the South has almost been destroyed</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369005998527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coloreds aren't "racist?" Try walking down a street late at night in their neighborhoods if you are White. I experienced many assaults from my "colored brothers" while in school. It was seldom one but usually two or three. I retaliated on one the next day. The "liberal" school adminstrator called the cops and they were going to lock me up but ignore the attack on me the prvious day by three of them. One reason I dropped out of school. I did quite well with a GED and could live OK without any government money. I will take it as I paid for it.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369064904247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:48:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369065250882-28</Id><Topic><Title>Bobbie Woodward</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368906387703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 15:46:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must have an orgasm every time the Kenyan is on TV!</Msg><Username>nyx45o</Username><Timestamp>1369065250882</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:54:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369065399102-29</Id><Topic><Title>Bobbie Woodward</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368906387703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 15:46:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your mother must be so proud.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369065399102</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:56:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369065945973-30</Id><Topic><Title>Bobbie Woodward</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368906387703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 15:46:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ricky, you, like many people who are now commenting on Benghazi, lack credibility. You probably believe all 12 versions put out by the White house.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369065945973</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369067257763-31</Id><Title>Obama hates honest elections</Title><Msg>In 2010 Catherine Engelbrecht established an organization named "True The Vote". The purpose was to recruit and train people to monitor the 2012 election. She applied to the IRS for 501(c)4 status so her donators could get a tax deduction. Her organization had no political affiliation and was not advocating any party or candidate. Her husbands business in 20 years had never been visited by any bureaucrat but since 2010 has been hounded 17 times by the IRS, FBI, OSHA, and BATF. The cost of supplying answers to all their question has been hundreds of thousands of dollars. She still has not received her 501(c)4. The time required prevented her from being very effective in preventing fraud in the election but her organization has been helpful in prosecuting 38 people for fraudulent activities.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369067257763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:27:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369068237898-32</Id><Title>T doing better today</Title><Msg>Friday it took almost all day for T to get above the previous day's close. Today it only took 3 hours. Volume is only about half of average volume but at least the move is in the right direction after a pretty scary drop in the first half hour.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369068237898</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:43:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369070720079-33</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hates honest elections</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369067257763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It can't be true that Obama doesn't want fair elections. He doesn't know what his government is doing. There are those that believe in hands on management, some practice management by wandering around...Obama manages by not knowing what anyone in his administration is actually doing.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1369070720079</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369071200759-34</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S., especially the South has almost been destroyed</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369005998527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More of your 'let’s paint everyone I disagree with, with a just one brush and all in the same color. I won't accuse you of discrimination because I think you're too simple minded to understand the word. Don't look now but most of those folks getting the checks you demonize were set up to receive those checks and continue to receive them with no oversight or controls were awarded that advantage by liberal Democrats. They continue to aggressively support that position, including for those that never paid a dime or very few dimes in the way of supporting taxes. Are you getting confused by all the spinning of your political hero's?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1369071200759</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369071448947-35</Id><Topic><Title>I tend to agree</Title><Username>mayor3004</Username><Timestamp>1368998977883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 17:29:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again the question remains that in looking for a 'leak' in either the CIA or NSA did they subpoena the records of reporters that may or may not have received the leaked information instead of doing so with the phone records of those with access to the information that was leaded? If they look at those records, they sure aren't sharing that information. They screwed up, and got caught. Obama is not mad that the IRS and Justice scandals happened, only that they got caught.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1369071448947</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:37:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369071500450-36</Id><Topic><Title>T doing better today</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369068237898</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:43:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>going the wrong way again. thinking very seriously about selling and taking my profit. buy back again in the 35.50 to 36.00 range on market pull-back. if it ever happens?</Msg><Username>charlesvermillion</Username><Timestamp>1369071500450</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:38:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369071666190-37</Id><Topic><Title>California does something right..(!!)</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1368990343979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 15:05:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought the government said that the CO movie shooting and the school shooting at Sandy Hook were done with long guns. Didn't the guy in AZ also use a rifle? Didn't the Columbine kids use 'assault weapons? Most gun crimes are committed by folks that had no intention of following the laws on the books. Most, not all of them obtained their guns through illegal means.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1369071666190</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369071755605-38</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hates honest elections</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369067257763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True the Vote is a branch of the Texas Tea Party. This is why honest people feel the need to scrutinize Tea Brains--you lie consistently. It should be understood that we are not dealing with the Girl Scouts here. We're dealing with hardline extremists who, in the case of True the Vote, work to disenfranchise voters. This is America, so even Tea Brains deserve equal protection under the law. But True the Vote does not deserve 501(c)4 status and it should not lie (as it did to the IRS and to you) about its political purpose. Even though the targeting was inappropriate, it is cases like these that make it understandable that workers dealing with an influx of 501(c)4 applications would use Tea Brains as a shortcut.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369071755605</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:42:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369072515790-39</Id><Topic><Title>California does something right..(!!)</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1368990343979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 15:05:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I thought the government said. . ." You thought the government said? When the leaves change colors in the fall, do you start yelling "I thought the government said leaves are green!"?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369072515790</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:55:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369073919824-40</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S., especially the South has almost been destroyed</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369005998527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“One reason I dropped out of school.” – lewcor Well, that, and after failing the second, fifth and sixth grades, the seventh grade twice, eighth twice, ninth three times and repeating your sophomore year 4 times, you found the embarrassment of being a 31 year old junior in high school overbearing, and dropped out to embark on your scintillating landscaping/fast-foodservice and Sanitation Department career. Good job, lew.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1369073919824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:18:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369074201508-41</Id><Topic><Title>I tend to agree</Title><Username>mayor3004</Username><Timestamp>1368998977883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 17:29:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. Punctuation. I have no idea what you are trying to say in that first sentence. 2. "They screwed up, and got caught." Screwed up and got caught? C'mon man. At least understand the basics before commenting. They did not "get caught". In both cases the agencies involved released the information themselves. The Justice Department advised the AP about the wiretapping after the investigation was complete, as required by law. The head of the Tax Exempt Section of the IRS mentioned an ongoing investigation by the Inspector General's office in a Q&amp;A session. The IG's office was set to release its report on the matter. Here you have transparency in government--agencies releasing information about themselves--and you people pounce on them and want them jailed. It's shameful the way you people act.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369074201508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:23:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369074221447-42</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hates honest elections</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369067257763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you think it is OK to harass people you think may be part of another party? The only people they were attempting to disenfranchise were those who were not eligible to vote.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369074221447</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:23:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369074473946-43</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hates honest elections</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369067257763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think of it this way Wilkes, all lefties including ricky are so busy trying to cover their tracks these days they don't have time to screw anything else up.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1369074473946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:27:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369074784939-44</Id><Topic><Title>I tend to agree</Title><Username>mayor3004</Username><Timestamp>1368998977883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 17:29:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPIN tRicky SPIN!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369074784939</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:33:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369074843639-45</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hates honest elections</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369067257763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"So you think it is OK to harass people you think may be part of another party?" Are you asking me or True the Vote? That is exactly what True the Vote does. Do you think they check the voting status of Tea Brains? Clearly I have said such profiling is inappropriate. However, that does not justify a branch of the Texas Tea Party trying to pass itself off as a non-partisan charity organization. That is fraud and that is lying. There is ample evidence that such fraud and lying is rampant in the Tea Party. I am sure the Cincinnati office of the IRS chose further scrutiny of Tea Party groups for that reason. But the profiling was still inappropriate.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369074843639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:34:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369074856767-46</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S., especially the South has almost been destroyed</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369005998527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With the way the Kenyan is hiding his school records, you have to be talking about him!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369074856767</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:34:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369075009395-47</Id><Topic><Title>T doing better today</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369068237898</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:43:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>T is trading at the 50 DMA and the Stochastic is in an up trend. Probably not a good time to sell. June and July were very good months for T last year.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369075009395</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369076094404-48</Id><Topic><Title>IRS Black Ops unit of Obama SS attacks conservatives.</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1368633032316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:50:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"wants no one for any reason to be profiled or discriminated against think what the IRS was doing was not only legal but right?" No winholder. I think profiling and discrimination was wrong in this case too. Maybe even violated someone's civil rights. Why do I think that, even when it is a political party I don't like being targeted? Because I'm not a frickin' hypocrite. See the difference between me &amp; you, winholder?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369076094404</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369076289776-49</Id><Topic><Title>T doing better today</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369068237898</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:43:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong again - T hasn't been positive all day and is in fact getting smacked around yet again.</Msg><Username>smithersj1234</Username><Timestamp>1369076289776</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369076431734-50</Id><Topic><Title>T doing better today</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369068237898</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:43:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good move - even if it doesn't go down to $35 (it will) there are so many better opportunities out there. This is going nowhere fast.</Msg><Username>smithersj1234</Username><Timestamp>1369076431734</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:00:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369076477065-51</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hates honest elections</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369067257763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The part that concerns me is: I think he knows exactly what he is doing and how to get away with it.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369076477065</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:01:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369076742606-52</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hates honest elections</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369067257763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Do you think they check the voting status of Tea Brains?" Yes. Tea Party people only vote once. That other vote I put in the ballot box really was for my sister-in-law.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369076742606</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369077634910-53</Id><Topic><Title>IRS Black Ops unit of Obama SS attacks conservatives.</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1368633032316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:50:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not a hypocrite, but definetly a SPINNER!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369077634910</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369078007331-54</Id><Title>cwa 1298 union sucks</Title><Msg>i belong to the worst union ever,the cwa 1298 union.....they just said yes to a contract offer from att ...we vote in 3 weeks,its the same offer that they made to us from day 1 which was 16 months ago...im happy to be employed by att but my union just downright stinks..................and ill be voting NO.....</Msg><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1369078007331</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:26:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369078634916-55</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hates honest elections</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369067257763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, I see. He's both blundering idiot who can manage anything and a diabolical mastermind controlling everything! Oh that Obama, a boogeyman in every way imaginable!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369078634916</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:37:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369079330436-56</Id><Topic><Title>Verizon aided the government in tapping into AP reporters</Title><Username>deebuck53</Username><Timestamp>1368806853243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 12:07:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The CIA did seize AP" The CIA? Seriously? Did they also send black helicopters to hover over AP Headquarters? It was the FBI and the Department of Justice, using legally obtained subpoenas.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369079330436</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:48:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369079555080-57</Id><Topic><Title>Verizon aided the government in tapping into AP reporters</Title><Username>deebuck53</Username><Timestamp>1368806853243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 12:07:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>correct</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1369079555080</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:52:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369079899482-58</Id><Title>YIPES!! Another day another thrashing for ATT.</Title><Msg>It's like Groundhog Day. One beat down after another. Relentless. Amazing what can happen to a stock with one horrible earnings miss. If it's followed by ANOTHER nasty quarter this stock will be dead meat for a LONG LONG time. A 5% dividend is meaningless when the stock goes down 1% every day.</Msg><Username>smithersj1234</Username><Timestamp>1369079899482</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:58:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369081109697-59</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hates honest elections</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369067257763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"He's both a blundering idiot who can't manage anything and a diabolical mastermind controlling everything!" Funny, I remember someone saying that exact same thing about Bush years ago! Interesting how what goes around comes around. Oh Ricky, I fixed your spelling when I quoted you. Hope you don't mind.</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1369081109697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:18:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369083314863-60</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hates honest elections</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369067257763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This is why honest people feel the need to scrutinize Tea Brains". And who are these "honest People". Attorney General Eric Holder, who of course heads the Justice Department, has done everything in his power to prevent voter identification laws from being implemented. Another example of your tax dollars at work. One should expect the DOJ to be the most interested in preventing voter fraud; but not Eric.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369083314863</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:55:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369084172731-61</Id><Topic><Title>YIPES!! Another day another thrashing for ATT.</Title><Username>smithersj1234</Username><Timestamp>1369079899482</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:58:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Analysts estimated 64 cents a share for Q-1 and that is what AT&amp;T reported. So why the "one horrible earnings miss". Incidentally, T is only down 40 cents from where it was when the 45 cent dividend was paid. Hardly 1% per day.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369084172731</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:09:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369084354750-62</Id><Topic><Title>cwa 1298 union sucks</Title><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1369078007331</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:26:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like you are getting nothing for your Union dues. Why not vote them out and keep the dues.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369084354750</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:12:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369085762738-63</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hates honest elections</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369067257763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, he knows exactly what he wants to do, what kind of atmosphere he wants to create, it's the blundering idiots that are doing his bidding is where the incompetence takes place. They are a professional idiocy version of you and Echo, blinded by the light of a greater fool.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1369085762738</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:36:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369090757835-64</Id><Topic><Title>T doing better today</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369068237898</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:43:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing could be more meaningless than how a stock price performed a year ago.</Msg><Username>smithersj1234</Username><Timestamp>1369090757835</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369092125941-65</Id><Title>Gonna be another long night</Title><Msg>My heart goes out to those folks in OK tonight. Sitting here is the MetroMess we have a tornado on the ground about 70 miles north and west of us and another they think on the ground about 90 miles south and west. We are under warnings until about 10 p.m.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1369092125941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:22:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369093023894-66</Id><Topic><Title>Gonna be another long night</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1369092125941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:22:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm surprised that tRicky or Obama hasn't blamed Bush yet!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369093023894</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:37:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369096164251-67</Id><Topic><Title>Gonna be another long night</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1369092125941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:22:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure Obama will promise to find out who is responsible and bring them to justice. Terrorists attacks like these cannot be allowed to continue.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369096164251</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:29:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369098807727-68</Id><Topic><Title>Gonna be another long night</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1369092125941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:22:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've been through a couple tornados, one in Kansas and one in Missouri. I've seen the resulting destruction up close but, I have never seen anything like I'm seeing in the coverage of this one. I hope everyone that can help financially or otherwise will do so. The Oklahoma folks are going to need a lot of help.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1369098807727</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 21:13:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369101762871-69</Id><Topic><Title>Gonna be another long night</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1369092125941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:22:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seriously? You cannot even keep it together for two rounds of comments on a tragedy before your OCD forces you to bring up "ricky" (who you also named yourself after). Get his phone number already! Tool.</Msg><Username>hotdoggitwiggie</Username><Timestamp>1369101762871</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:02:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369101811359-70</Id><Topic><Title>Gonna be another long night</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1369092125941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:22:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are old enough to know better than to take a comment about a tragedy and turn it into something idiotic as you have just done.</Msg><Username>hotdoggitwiggie</Username><Timestamp>1369101811359</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:03:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369105480276-71</Id><Title>IRS</Title><Msg>Good lord if you are a registered Republican keep your powder dry...for ole uncle obama may be coming after you .In a few weeks General counsel Ruemmler told of the IRS scandal concerning the Tea Party to GUESS WHO the presidents CHIEF OF STAFF Mister old McDonough. Yet with weeks passing this information was not shared within the White House ,especially to the president....OH PLEEEEASEEE ! The idiot in charge statement was ..."I found out about it listening to the news ." If that is true (which it is not ) then this guy is a true CHUMP . The STENCH of this is beyond belief ,I believe the clown in charge thinks he is above the law due to the color of his skin . I believe he thinks no one would dare attack or question his policy because they would today be labeled or questioned as being racist . The media continues to kow tow to a totally inept speech maker . All talk ...NO LEADERSHIP !!!!</Msg><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1369105480276</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369105979091-72</Id><Topic><Title>IRS</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1369105480276</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:04:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are so, so, sooooo right. I thank GOD every day that I have my guns and my food horde..(!!). It is going to get REALLY bad now. I am really afraid and went out today and spent my social security check on ammo..(!!). This is absolutely the beginning of the beginning of the end..(!!)</Msg><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1369105979091</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369106159257-73</Id><Topic><Title>Gonna be another long night</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1369092125941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:22:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow..Wilksie..51 Americans dead and you think it's a reason for a joke. I have so much respect for you. Maybe I am not looking at this right. Maybe it really is a big funny..teehee..(??)</Msg><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1369106159257</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:15:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369106821253-74</Id><Topic><Title>Gonna be another long night</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1369092125941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:22:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Been trying to contact a friend in Broken Arrow, OK. No luck so far. Hope he and his wife are OK. I'll take an earthquake any day over a tornado. Been through any number of them in Ca.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369106821253</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369106962901-75</Id><Topic><Title>Bobbie Woodward</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368906387703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 15:46:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You so mean..(!!)</Msg><Username>cloudviewest</Username><Timestamp>1369106962901</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:29:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>