<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-23"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366690049978-1</Id><Topic><Title>I Trade T With 98.7% Accuracy</Title><Username>outlawtamika65</Username><Timestamp>1366686709397</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:11:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This APP is pretty legit I downloaded it and it shows trend signals and buy sell and hold points for up to like 2 years and if you test it its ACTUALLY pretty accurate ... Good job I'm surprised!</Msg><Username>smarkel94</Username><Timestamp>1366690049978</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 00:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366717647951-2</Id><Topic><Title>Oh no say it isn't so!</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1365866656934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:24:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“Again, there is no proof of man made global warming…I simply blew holes in your off topic nonsense.” – carolharold Speaking of off topic nonsense…whatever, or whomever for that matter, you are blowing, has absolutely no relevancy to the veracity of the scientific community’s opinion that global warming is real and a result of man’s activities. Obviously, the main thing you are blowing is hot air for the carbon based fuel industry. “…in fact about 97 percent of American scientists say that climate change is happening…” That’s ninety-seven percent, carol! If you are here simply to argue that 97% is not 100%, that’s a foolish and weak argument. If you, on the other hand, are here to argue that 97% equates to “no proof of man-made global warming”, you go well beyond looking foolish. You then fall into the category of those trying to deceive the public for the benefit of the special interests who benefit by causing the climate change…and for that, your children’s children will suffer, and you should be very ashamed. Pimping for the fossil fuel industry is not blowing holes in the scientific community by any stretch of the imagination. Climate Change: Public Skeptical, Scientists Sure By Richard Harris, NPR, 2011 The American public is less likely to believe in global warming than it was just five years ago. Yet, paradoxically, scientists are more confident than ever that climate change is real and caused largely by human activities. Something a bit strange is happening with public opinion and climate change. Anthony Leiserowitz, who directs the Yale University Project on Climate Change Communication, delved into this in a recent poll. He not only asked citizens what they thought of climate change, he also asked them to estimate how climate scientists feel about global warming. ‘Only 13 percent of Americans got the correct answer, which is that in fact about 97 percent of American scientists say that climate change is happening, and about a third of Americans just simply say they don't know,’ he said. Most Americans are unaware that the National Academy of Sciences, known for its cautious and even-handed reviews of the state of science, is firmly on board with climate change. It has been for years Ralph Cicerone, president of the National Academy, paraphrased its most recent report on the subject. ‘The consensus statement is that climate changes are being observed, are certainly real, they seem to be increasing, and that humans are mostly likely the cause of all or most of these changes,’ he said. That's not just the view of the U.S. National Academies. There's also a consensus statement from the presidents of science academies from around the world, including the academies of China, the United Kingdom, India, Japan, Russia, France, Brazil, the list goes on.”</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366717647951</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 07:47:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366721623735-3</Id><Topic><Title>I Trade T With 98.7% Accuracy</Title><Username>outlawtamika65</Username><Timestamp>1366686709397</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:11:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Need 100% accuracy.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366721623735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 08:53:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366722143992-4</Id><Title>Check it on Bigcharts 900SMA vs dow, s&amp;P.. At OMG levels compared to the index</Title><Msg>watch out should be selling the rips</Msg><Username>testpilot1003</Username><Timestamp>1366722143992</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 09:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366722633956-5</Id><Topic><Title>ANY Pensioners missed a check yet?</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366636001125</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:06:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whopper. You were on my ignore list. Possibly by accident. Only because my Yahoo daily posting email alerts displays the first few sentences of your intelligent response, did i read rest of what you wrote yesterday. So I brought you back from banishment and see I may have made a mistake. My apology. I'm well aware of what you write regarding pension options. My posting was directed to a Troller who said (in essence) the underfunding was so serious that retiree's would be left holding the bag. I think the idiot who wrote that got the JCP board confused with T. Sadly, that dimwit does not not know about insurance and safeguards that protects things like that from happening. I'm not here to spread nonsense like he and his ilk do. You and I are on the same page regarding the sustainability of not only the pension, but the excellent dividend we enjoy. Sorry again for the misunderstanding. Looking forward to a good earnings report later today and continued price appreciation.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366722633956</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 09:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366723353495-6</Id><Topic><Title>lol @ this over priced pig. what about that massive pension hole?</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1366605363542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 00:36:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.................kind of like where is US government going to get money for YOUR SS</Msg><Username>infn444</Username><Timestamp>1366723353495</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 09:22:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366724936753-7</Id><Topic><Title>Oh no say it isn't so!</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1365866656934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:24:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It is you with the off topic nonsense" Me? And here I thought I was responding to you and Froggie. "Wouldn't the ENTIRE community include 100% of such scientists?" I don't care. Jesus. The scientific community has reached a broad scientific consensus. If you don't know what a scientific consensus is or how it is reached, look it up. But you are arguing with the collective judgement of the entire scientific community. No one's been left out. Everyone's done their research and had their say. Just about every major scientific organization has issued a statement supporting the conclusion that global warming is real and it is man-made. Even the American Association of Petroleum Geologists has withdrawn its dissent. That is who you are arguing with. The entire scientific community. Not me.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366724936753</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 09:48:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366726372053-8</Id><Topic><Title>I Trade T With 98.7% Accuracy</Title><Username>outlawtamika65</Username><Timestamp>1366686709397</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:11:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Free spam is still spam. This sounds too good to be true and there is a 98.7% chance that there is a catch to it.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1366726372053</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 10:12:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366727224337-9</Id><Title>MISM is the next big gainer</Title><Msg>Have you checked out the chart on MISM. It looks prime to make a huge run to atleast double its current price.</Msg><Username>joconnor357</Username><Timestamp>1366727224337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 10:27:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366727311515-10</Id><Topic><Title>MISM is the next big gainer</Title><Username>joconnor357</Username><Timestamp>1366727224337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 10:27:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's the current price?</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366727311515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 10:28:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366727373042-11</Id><Topic><Title>Getting back to AT@T</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359989166973</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 09:46:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is beginning to look like my "ridiculous" forecast when we were at $35 is within a dollar and we are not even to May yet. Maybe it isn't "ridiculous" after all.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1366727373042</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 10:29:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366728040232-12</Id><Topic><Title>ANY Pensioners missed a check yet?</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366636001125</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:06:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do it all the time Zon. Ignore and report. It's kind of like a bowel movement when I do it. Gets rid of the waste. I not sure what...if anything Yahoo does about it. The spamming stuff is another matter. it keeps resurfacing in different forms. Like cockroaches. Can't seem to exterminate them. As for the Trollers, that species does get eliminated. At least from my view of the board. I only see them in a limited form courtesy of Yahoo updates. That's how I caught the karaoke guys response which was a good one after reading the entire response.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366728040232</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 10:40:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366728864542-13</Id><Topic><Title>Getting back to AT@T</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359989166973</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 09:46:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wilkie, this looks like a time capsule. We don't see you for a week and you resurrect your on the money 40.00 price call from February. I remember that post clearly. Bollinger Bands and all. Not to forget the Stochastic's, 200 DMA, etc. So now that we know you weren't ridiculous with that prediction, how about an update on your ADP that I have asked you for several times? You're not shorting are you? Today's action is not terribly impressive. Indexes through the roof and only lukewarm price movement so far. How do you account for the lack of stock price increase with an in-line report due later today? Do we zoom past 40 tomorrow, or what?</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366728864542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 10:54:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366731415204-14</Id><Title>MISM looks ready to take off. Check it out</Title><Msg>Hearing a rumor that MISM is about to get pumped</Msg><Username>dillardthomas732</Username><Timestamp>1366731415204</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 11:36:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366731480680-15</Id><Title>MISM looks prime for a breakout</Title><Msg>I heard there is a massive promo coming into MISM. Keep an eye on it</Msg><Username>brooksj565</Username><Timestamp>1366731480680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 11:38:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366732291677-16</Id><Topic><Title>ANY Pensioners missed a check yet?</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366636001125</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:06:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Been retired since 1983. Never have had any problem. Benefits office has always been very good at handling any questions.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1366732291677</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 11:51:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366732420824-17</Id><Topic><Title>MISM looks prime for a breakout</Title><Username>brooksj565</Username><Timestamp>1366731480680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 11:38:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, thanks for the information. At 3.8 cents per share, zero earnings per share it should bread out any moment........OR NOT. Go spam this somewhere else.</Msg><Username>tealcarver</Username><Timestamp>1366732420824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 11:53:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366732641829-18</Id><Topic><Title>MISM looks ready to take off. Check it out</Title><Username>dillardthomas732</Username><Timestamp>1366731415204</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 11:36:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are on every board pushing this 3.8 cent stock. I am sure if everyone on every board buys a thousand shares you could get the stock high enough to make a profit. Keep posting your spam, it might just work.</Msg><Username>tealcarver</Username><Timestamp>1366732641829</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 11:57:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366732959548-19</Id><Topic><Title>MISM looks prime for a breakout</Title><Username>brooksj565</Username><Timestamp>1366731480680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 11:38:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OOPS , my bad for the thumbs down 'teal' .. I was on a robo "spam" reporting run .. I was just too quick on the thumbs down on you (sorry) - but did NOT hit the spam button on you</Msg><Username>coolin_out47</Username><Timestamp>1366732959548</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 12:02:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366733952720-20</Id><Topic><Title>MISM looks ready to take off. Check it out</Title><Username>dillardthomas732</Username><Timestamp>1366731415204</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 11:36:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the time it took you to write your response, you could have saved a few seconds and did the ignore/report button and be done with it. Let this kind of #$%$ join the echoes, crewfeces and Ricky's et al of the world.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366733952720</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 12:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366734485324-21</Id><Topic><Title>Oh no say it isn't so!</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1365866656934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:24:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, you are telling me the "entire" scientific community does not believe there is man made global warming. I know you don't care but saying such a thing destroyed your off topic statement. Again, the topic here is T. Reminding you of that fact is not off topic.</Msg><Username>carolharold123</Username><Timestamp>1366734485324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 12:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366734691565-22</Id><Title>Looks like I have found another winner. Check out MISM</Title><Msg>Looks like volume and momentum are really starting to pick up on MISM. I bet MISMwont stay this cheap for long</Msg><Username>brooksj565</Username><Timestamp>1366734691565</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 12:31:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366735067109-23</Id><Title>PRICE TARGET $50!!</Title><Msg>OPPORTUNITY</Msg><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1366735067109</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 12:37:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366735643876-24</Id><Topic><Title>ANY Pensioners missed a check yet?</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366636001125</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:06:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>20+ years and no problems? Nice to hear that Lew. Just keep an eye on it. Can't say you weren't warned by a professional Troller...</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366735643876</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 12:47:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366736248225-25</Id><Title>MISM looks prime for a breakout</Title><Msg>Do some DD on MISM. I think with the right momentum we could soar past $1</Msg><Username>fjulian885</Username><Timestamp>1366736248225</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 12:57:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366736347319-26</Id><Title>Very disappointing action so far today...</Title><Msg>...hoping for a strong close a tick or so above $39.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1366736347319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 12:59:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366736656358-27</Id><Title>BLOWOUT EARNINGS AFTER THE CLOSE ON TO 50</Title><Msg>ENJOY!!!</Msg><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1366736656358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 13:04:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366737741450-28</Id><Topic><Title>Bought because of the Divy. Felt like a conservative move at the time for my 401K</Title><Username>chops2191</Username><Timestamp>1366443269503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 03:34:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exceeding my expectations by far for the type of investment I thought I was making. In hind sight, I wish I choosen to get "conservative" with a larger percentage of my portfolio.</Msg><Username>chops2191</Username><Timestamp>1366737741450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366738254272-29</Id><Topic><Title>Bought because of the Divy. Felt like a conservative move at the time for my 401K</Title><Username>chops2191</Username><Timestamp>1366443269503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 03:34:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd be interested in the two thumbs downers as to what they would do differently Lew. I've done something similar to your strategy and have reaped similar benefits. Last I looked, cd's were paying somewhere in the 1% range and below that for shorter terms. Maybe the 2 anonymous jerks would care to share their wisdom. Dimwits that thumb down posts that are as good as yours are real #$%$ that have no clear path to successful planning or investing and should have their computer priveledges revoked. Trollers need to get some semblance of a life.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366738254272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 13:30:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366739366421-30</Id><Title>Always have to be careful if you use stops...</Title><Msg>...fake tweet on terrorist attack drops market like a rock a little while ago...if you had a stop loss for T at $38.40 or so you would be an ex- ATT shareholder right now.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1366739366421</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 13:49:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366739439693-31</Id><Topic><Title>Oh no say it isn't so!</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1365866656934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:24:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares about "my off topic statement" and whether you "destroyed" or not. You are missing the point. What we are discussing is a broad scientific consensus. Destroy that. Do you think anyone cares if I used the word entire properly or not? I don't. The scientific community is as sure as it gets about this. THAT is what you have to deal with.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366739439693</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 13:50:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366746153085-32</Id><Topic><Title>Getting back to AT@T</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359989166973</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 09:46:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If ADP stands for Actual Daily Performance, it has not been good. I keep thinking T has gone up too fast too long and I bought protective puts. They ended up protecting me from making much profit. My play-trade account is up less than $100 from what it was a week ago. Right now my May 40 calls are the only bright spot in my portfolio.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1366746153085</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 15:42:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366746667602-33</Id><Topic><Title>Getting back to AT@T</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359989166973</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 09:46:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so do you think this thing will mover more than 1.40 off of 39 by may expiration?</Msg><Username>jtwick</Username><Timestamp>1366746667602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 15:51:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366747185731-34</Id><Topic><Title>Oh no say it isn't so!</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1365866656934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:24:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's right, nobody cares what you say. I avoid using absolutes but in your case you are right. Nobody cares what you say.</Msg><Username>carolharold123</Username><Timestamp>1366747185731</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 15:59:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366747500030-35</Id><Topic><Title>Getting back to AT@T</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359989166973</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 09:46:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you mean move down...yes.</Msg><Username>jeff8888nj</Username><Timestamp>1366747500030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366747639262-36</Id><Title>Did T cook the books on earnings?</Title><Msg>Top line revenue missed! So that .34 expected earnings is suspect! I think you will see a sell off now.</Msg><Username>buyrightone</Username><Timestamp>1366747639262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366747790086-37</Id><Topic><Title>Oh no say it isn't so!</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1365866656934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:24:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kick the habit Ricky, stop drinking that kool aid.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1366747790086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:09:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366747974102-38</Id><Topic><Title>Oh no say it isn't so!</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1365866656934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:24:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good. Now, considering the broad scientific consensus, what additional proof do you think is required? How much more proof should the policy community wait for before taking meaningful action to reduce greenhouse gas emissions?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366747974102</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:12:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366748102037-39</Id><Title>Let errr</Title><Msg>Drop, I want in big time on this.</Msg><Username>augie9876</Username><Timestamp>1366748102037</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:15:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366748849690-40</Id><Topic><Title>Let errr</Title><Username>augie9876</Username><Timestamp>1366748102037</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:15:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazing, these are the times you need to take advantage of. People that really do not know what they are doing are selling a great company with a good dividend and giving us a chance to accumulate off of their stupidity. I LOVE IT!</Msg><Username>augie9876</Username><Timestamp>1366748849690</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:27:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366748869377-41</Id><Topic><Title>ANY Pensioners missed a check yet?</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366636001125</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:06:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's a "troller"</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1366748869377</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:27:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366749619431-42</Id><Topic><Title>ANY Pensioners missed a check yet?</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366636001125</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:06:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Type this in your browser: "troller on public message boards" Wiki explains it quite well.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366749619431</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:40:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366749987310-43</Id><Title>I will take those earnings</Title><Msg>That is not bad with all the competition out there. The impressive part is their tablets are excellent which is why they are selling.</Msg><Username>obama_is_no_hero</Username><Timestamp>1366749987310</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:46:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366750043304-44</Id><Topic><Title>Tough AH beatdown</Title><Username>young4ever399</Username><Timestamp>1366749969154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:46:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not a chance. The street is not too concerned with the slight miss.</Msg><Username>born_in_a_cage</Username><Timestamp>1366750043304</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:47:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366750430923-45</Id><Topic><Title>Tough AH beatdown</Title><Username>young4ever399</Username><Timestamp>1366749969154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:46:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah....not that much....temporary setback.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1366750430923</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:53:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366751513203-46</Id><Topic><Title>Tough AH beatdown</Title><Username>young4ever399</Username><Timestamp>1366749969154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:46:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AH often ends up being irrelevant.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1366751513203</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 17:11:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366754614298-47</Id><Topic><Title>Oh no say it isn't so!</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1365866656934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:24:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So all this arguing about the scientific community and you don't care because, in your opinion, the state of medicine (which is not a science) has not advanced since blood-letting? Gee, somebody better tell NASA to cancel those missions because the world is flat! I don't know what to tell you except I am concerned about the state of STEM education in this country. The scientific method is what rid us of unscientific beliefs like blood-letting. The reason you use electric cars is because the internal combustion engine is inefficient at producing energy and at reducing pollutants. Big power plants are much more efficient. Plus, electric cars can recycle energy lost through braking and other sources (which is what makes hybrids so efficient). Ethanol is not a particularly superior energy source, but not for the reasons you mentioned. You have to burn oil and coal too, so what's the difference? The difference is oil &amp; coal are fossil fuels made up entirely of stored carbon. Ethanol is made from living plants. When you get more oil, you are releasing alot of stored carbon. When you get more ethanol you are recycling carbon already in the atmosphere. Whatever you return to the atmosphere is carbon you already removed from the atmosphere. Understand?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366754614298</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 18:03:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366755486875-48</Id><Title>T is a very cheap priced Monopoly....like the old days</Title><Msg>history repeats itself</Msg><Username>clipper5158</Username><Timestamp>1366755486875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 18:18:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366756399957-49</Id><Topic><Title>Tough AH beatdown</Title><Username>young4ever399</Username><Timestamp>1366749969154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 16:46:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOD!!!!!!!!!!!!!! $36 = 5% and I would love to buy more right there at $36. Come on down!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1366756399957</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 18:33:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366756720724-50</Id><Title>Oh what a web we weave...</Title><Msg>Just out today an interim congressional report regarding the administrations bungling and subsequent cover up of events prior, during and after the murder of American citizens on September 11, 2012 in Benghazi, Libya. The primary findings include the following: o Reductions of security levels prior to the attacks in Benghazi were approved at the highest levels of the State Department, up to and including Secretary Clinton. This fact contradicts her testimony before the House Foreign Affairs Committee on January 23, 2013. o In the days following the attacks, White House and senior State Department officials altered accurate talking points drafted by the Intelligence Community in order to protect the State Department. o Contrary to Administration rhetoric, the talking points were not edited to protect classified information. Concern for classified information is never mentioned in email traffic among senior Administration officials. o The Administration willfully perpetuated a deliberately misleading and incomplete narrative that the attacks evolved from a political demonstration caused by a YouTube video. IMHO, on one hand you have to hand it to the administration for its ability to stonewall, obfuscate and misrepresent the facts during a presidential campaign, but on the other, there may be some Americans left who, when they find out the truth, may have some uneasy feelings about an administration that through its actions willfully facilitated the deaths of a US Ambassador and three other American citizens, and then covered up the whole affair through stonewalling and deception. As Hillary was so famous to say "who cares...?" To be honest, I don't really know anymore. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366756720724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 18:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366759012550-51</Id><Topic><Title>Oh what a web we weave...</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366756720724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 18:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're gonna #$%$ off a liberal!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1366759012550</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 19:16:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366760147386-52</Id><Topic><Title>Bought because of the Divy. Felt like a conservative move at the time for my 401K</Title><Username>chops2191</Username><Timestamp>1366443269503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 03:34:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buying T at $28 was a good move, but those still on the sidelines may be better served waiting for T to pull back. However, other opportunities to buy low and sell high exist at the moment.</Msg><Username>beta_seeker</Username><Timestamp>1366760147386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 19:35:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366763210626-53</Id><Topic><Title>Oh what a web we weave...</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1366756720724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 18:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude...get by one lie before you start another.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1366763210626</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 20:26:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366765451578-54</Id><Topic><Title>Bought because of the Divy. Felt like a conservative move at the time for my 401K</Title><Username>chops2191</Username><Timestamp>1366443269503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 03:34:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See how fast it dropped with the rumor today? Perilous.</Msg><Username>gedownonit24me</Username><Timestamp>1366765451578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 21:04:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366766932120-55</Id><Title>I am Leaving ATT after 10 Years , going to T mobile</Title><Msg>I keep paying more and more for going over data plan, they do not have a unlimited plan, so im going to T Mobile in July 4 phones, Bye bye ATT it was nice while it lasted</Msg><Username>goodeal4u2002</Username><Timestamp>1366766932120</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 21:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366766991275-56</Id><Title>this was todays email from them</Title><Msg>: Data Usage Alert - Nearing Plan Limit: Data Usage = 204.0 MB</Msg><Username>goodeal4u2002</Username><Timestamp>1366766991275</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 21:29:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366767048734-57</Id><Title>AT&amp;T revenue disappoints as it loses cellphone subscribers</Title><Msg>AT&amp;T revenue disappoints as it loses cellphone subscribers</Msg><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1366767048734</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 21:30:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366768493121-58</Id><Topic><Title>Oh no say it isn't so!</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1365866656934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:24:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting how leftists resort to name calling when they can't respond intelligently to scientific studies. Is it in the commie playbook? I think it is. I used to subscribe to several commie rags years ago. This is exactly the program they sponsored.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1366768493121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 21:54:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366768508023-59</Id><Title>First, Randall told us earnings would grow in high single digits,</Title><Msg>and now, it is low single digits. Wait a few more months, it will be no growth. In the meantime, he is busy buying spectrum, establishing alliances, upgrading the network, buying shares, not sure where all funding is going to come from, just like the old Bell Labs mentality where there is an access to unlimited funds while credit downgrade looms on the horizon, anytime now. You folks need to be patient. Look for the stock to sink to $34.00 plus tax.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1366768508023</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 21:55:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366769669831-60</Id><Title>Boston Attack</Title><Msg>We are about to give passes/citizenship to millions of gang members. This is no time to take the peace loving American Citizens weapons. We need them to protect our families. Why did Obama refuse to allow the FBI to investigate these killers. Political correctness costs these atheletes their lives and limbs. It's time we impeach El Presidente.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1366769669831</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 22:14:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>