<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-21"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361445522773-1</Id><Topic><Title>Take a look at this report before you loose your $</Title><Username>angelclark491</Username><Timestamp>1361393917136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:58:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good update. thx.</Msg><Username>mikereed921</Username><Timestamp>1361445522773</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:18:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361455923375-2</Id><Topic><Title>Universal Orlando dropping health coverage for workers over ObamaCare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1361386388575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"hopefully no one in America will have insurance" That may be a good thing. My parents talk of having a baby costing one weeks pay; anyone could afford that. With the advent of medical insurance, providers kept raising fees as insurance kept paying whatever they charged. No one cared; insurance took care of it. This created an upward death spiral until fees got so high that those without insurance can't afford the fees and those insured can't afford the premiums. I used to get an eye exam and new glasses every three years, cost me about $200. Then Ameritech offered eye care insurance. Now glasses cost over $600 and guess what? My co-pay is $200. Anytime "someone else" is paying the bill, there is no incentive or reason to keep costs in check. Look at how congress spends taxpayer money. College costs are following the same path. As long as student loans are paying the bills; colleges will keep raising costs.</Msg><Username>heavypbx</Username><Timestamp>1361455923375</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:12:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361458409157-3</Id><Title>So much for my instincts..</Title><Msg>#$%$ happened to this? 36 once again seems like a mile away. Soembody is #$%$ around with this stock imo.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1361458409157</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:53:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361459087631-4</Id><Topic><Title>If $85.3 billion is cut from a $3 trillion plus budget will America cease to exist?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361310833197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:53:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Lie, lie, lie. You people are #$%$" I really shouldn't bother, but here are some facts for the rest of the board: The battle over raising the debt ceiling consumed Washington in the summer of 2011, with Republicans refusing to agree to raise it unless spending was cut by an equivalent amount. Obama pressed but failed to get an agreement on raising revenue as part of the package. On July 12, 2011, after the debt ceiling talks failed the White House staff asked National Economic Council Director Gene Sperling to develop the details for a compulsory trigger if they didn’t cut spending or raise taxes in an amount at least equivalent to the debt ceiling increase. Sperling explained “A trigger would lock in our commitment, even though we disagree on the composition of how to get to the cuts, it would lock us in. The form of the automatic sequester would punish both sides. We’d have to September to avert any sequester” — a legal obligation to make spending cuts. President Obama then added "This would be an enforcement mechanism." On July 26,2011 at 2:30 p.m., [White House Budget director Jack] Lew and [White House legislative affairs director Rob] Nabors went to the Senate to meet with [Senator Majority Leader Harry] Reid and his chief of staff, David Krone. Mr. Lew said to Mr. Reid “We have an idea for a trigger,” Mr Reid responded “What’s the idea,”. Mr. Lew responded “Sequestration.” According to the report Mr. Reid bent down and put his head between his knees, almost as if he was going to throw up or was having a heart attack. He sat back up and looked at the ceiling. “A couple of weeks ago,” he said, “my staff said to me that there is one more possible” enforcement mechanism: sequestration. He said he told them, “Get the hell out of here. That’s insane. The White House surely will come up with a plan that will save the day. And you come to me with sequestration?” Mr. Lew told Mr. Reid that it could work, then he explained the details: It would be designed so that half the threatened cuts would be from the Defense Department….The idea was to make all of the threatened cuts so unthinkable and onerous that the supercommittee [tasked with making additional cuts] would do its work and come up with its own deficit reduction plan. Lew and Nabors went through a laundry list of programs that would face cuts. “This is ridiculous,” Reid said. That’s the beauty of a sequester, they said, it’s so ridiculous that no one ever wants it to happen. It was the bomb that no one wanted to drop. It actually would be an action-forcing event. “I get it,” Reid said finally. On July 30, 2011 the president and [White House chief of staff William] Daley were on the patio outside Daley’s office with [adviser David] Plouffe, [Treasury Secretary Timothy] Geithner, Lew and Sperling when they got word that Biden was making progress with [Senate Minority Leader Mitch] McConnell. It looked as if Republicans were ready to agree to a Defense/non-Defense sequester in the trigger. Plouffe couldn’t believe it. These guys were so afraid of increasing revenues that they’re willing to put Defense on the chopping block? Republicans’ revenue phobia was so intense that they would sell out the Pentagon. “This is a deal we can probably live with,” Obama said, willing to do almost anything to salvage something and prevent catastrophe. Around 9 p.m. Boehner’s staff got their first real look at the proposal negotiated by Biden and McConnell. [Boehner policy director Brett] Loper had been in regular contact with [McConnell deputy chief of staff] Rohit Kumar about the progress of the negotiations, but now he had paper, so he drafted the Republican staff from the House Budget Committee and they pulled an all-nighter trying to understand the plan and to identify its shortcomings. It was a challenge, because nobody in the office had operated under the Gramm-Rudman-Hollings rules, which dated back to the 1980s. Loper spent the night trying to get his arms around the proposal. Bottom line: The White House came up with the idea and got Mr. Reid, Mr. McConnell and Mr. Boehner to sign on to their plan. I really don't like being called a liar, especially by someone who is so uninformed. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361459087631</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:04:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361460595006-5</Id><Topic><Title>If $85.3 billion is cut from a $3 trillion plus budget will America cease to exist?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361310833197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:53:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again I really shouldn't bother, but it is obvious that you have never heard of something called the "loaded labor rate" which is the employee's hourly rate plus employee benefits, capital expenses, and other overhead. Even with your figure of $75,000 I think you will find that the average "loaded labor rate" is still $100,000. By your last post you have demonstrated just how ignorant you are about how business works. If you had ever made a payroll you would have known this simple fact. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361460595006</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:29:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361460980256-6</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Benghazi was obviously a failure, but I prefer my failures be thwarted prior to the banging on the desk stage. That means funding the state department, better planning, and, most of all, using US Marines to provide embassy security instead of contractors. That said, if this is the worst national security failure of the Obama administration and the Clinton state department, we're doing quite well. I, and many others, believe that Clinton's efforts have gone a long way to ensuring that to be the case.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361460980256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:36:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361461796721-7</Id><Topic><Title>If $85.3 billion is cut from a $3 trillion plus budget will America cease to exist?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361310833197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:53:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"In your heart you know he is right." You are correct sir. When we developed the cost of products and services we used a 50% loading factor applied to the hourly labor rate to reflect the true cost of labor. The loading factor recognized pension and all other benefit obligations as well as supervision costs the firm took on when it hired a person. The loaded labor rate reflected the true labor cost to the business. I might add that a 50% factor is very conservative. I've seen it as high as 90% depending on benefit costs . To put it another way, if we priced a labor intensive product reflecting only the direct labor cost you likely would be setting the price below the true cost of the service. Contrary to what Junior Samples said many years ago, you don't make it up in volume.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1361461796721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:49:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361461957723-8</Id><Topic><Title>Pres on Golf Vacation Again</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1361238774182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 20:52:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama will forever be in the history books as being elected President two terms, while we all are only dust. One of the great Presidents, a history lesson in American values, patriotism, dilgence, and courage.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1361461957723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:52:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361462223882-9</Id><Title>And The Recovery Continues!!!!</Title><Msg>NEW YORK (Reuters) - Stocks opened lower on Thursday, extending the previous session's steep decline following a bigger-than-expected rise in weekly jobless claims. Wow, yet another 'unexpected' rise in joblessness! With all these experts in Washington and all their knowledge of how to create jobs, how is it that they are continually surprised by bad news?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361462223882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:57:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361463256559-10</Id><Title>It’s a man-bites-dog story.</Title><Msg>It’s a man-bites-dog story. It’s about the world upside-down. It’s about the most unexpected surprise ever. Like a lottery. It’s about an American politician giving money back to the government! It’s U.S. Sen. Rand Paul, R-Ky., who said he is setting an example for a federal government teetering on the edge of mandatory budget cuts. He is giving money back – a lot of it. Well, a lot for most Americans. The Courier-Journal out of Louisville reports the U.S. senator is returning $600,000 to the U.S. Treasury for this year. It was money that had been allocated to him to run his Senate office. But the paper says he saved the money by watching the expenses for his office needs. For two years, Paul said, the amount returned totals $1.1 million. “It’s the only budget I control,” he told a news conference in Louisville. “It’s not enough, but it’s a start.” According to the Courier-Journal, Paul said, “We are frugal from top to bottom.” He said he and his staff watch every purchase, and keep close track of expenses on travel, and also on “computers, paper, ink cartridges. Everything we buy.” The reported added that Paul believes he is being true to a campaign pledge to cut federal spending. “It’s not an enormous savings,” he said. But he said it would add up if the federal government watched expenses as closely. He also said he’s introduce legislation to create bonuses for federal civil service employees based on what funds they save in their allocations. Hey Ricky, when was the last time a Democrat did this?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361463256559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:14:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361463416260-11</Id><Topic><Title>Pres on Golf Vacation Again</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1361238774182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 20:52:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, it was Democrats who caused the debt ceiling disaster. Yeah, pretty much. The problem continutes in that they don't seem to want to do much about it but continue to increase it. Cut spending? Wow, what good Democrat in their right minds would ever concieve of such and idea?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361463416260</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:16:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361463600822-12</Id><Topic><Title>And The Recovery Continues!!!!</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361462223882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:57:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes winholder, you are exactly right. In one week in February 2013 initial jobless claims, which pace at about 360,000 a week, came in 7,000 claims higher than a panel of economists expected. Why haven't you been announcing the claims figures the past few weeks? Will you announce them next week? You're such a hack.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361463600822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:20:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361464049746-13</Id><Topic><Title>If $85.3 billion is cut from a $3 trillion plus budget will America cease to exist?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361310833197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:53:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has been campaigning, planning, and conniving about the recent election since a few hours after his first swearing in ceremony. The thoughts of this most recent election have not left his warped mind since he was elected the first time, the time in IL! What is your angry reply to the words he spoke in November of 2011 on this subject? How do reconcile those comments with his comments this week? Is it that he is just not perceptive enough to have seen this latest 'crisis' coming? Are he and his staff really that inept? They didn’t even see this last round of ‘unexpected’ increases in the jobless numbers, so perhaps they really are that inept.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361464049746</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:27:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361464246092-14</Id><Topic><Title>So much for my instincts..</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1361458409157</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:53:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama made a speech and the Fed quit buying for a few days. The stock market is no longer an investment tool, it is a slot machine.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361464246092</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:30:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361464350518-15</Id><Topic><Title>And The Recovery Continues!!!!</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361462223882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:57:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh but wait, the weekend is coming and they will be revised while no one is paying attention. Such is life in the fast lane of government statistics.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361464350518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:32:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361464503953-16</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? You're standing up for the 'gal' that was in charge of the department that created this mess, got people killed and then said 'what does it matter now!' Really?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361464503953</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:35:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361464575059-17</Id><Topic><Title>The Fed.!!</Title><Username>coolin_out47</Username><Timestamp>1361390274120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:57:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He had better be very careful, bad mouthing the boss can get you fired.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361464575059</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:36:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361465998883-18</Id><Topic><Title>And The Recovery Continues!!!!</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361462223882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:57:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, of course. If next week is good it's a lie. What else was announced in labor news today, win? A 0.2% increase in hourly wages in January. Flat CPI. Lowest Q4 mass layoffs, separations and initial claimants since at least 2008. No T-message board threads for those gems? You're such a hack.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361465998883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:59:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361466734444-19</Id><Topic><Title>The Fed.!!</Title><Username>coolin_out47</Username><Timestamp>1361390274120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:57:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, it is getting increasingly expensive to nurture an ever growing number of government dependents. By the way, have I mentioned lately how tired I am of paying for the stuff of other people?</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1361466734444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:12:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361469599878-20</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “You're standing up for the 'gal' that was in charge of the department that created this mess, got people killed and then said 'what does it matter now!'” - windandalejon Typical…The State Department did not create the mess in Libya, nor did The Secretary get people killed…and more than anything, you know full well her “what does it matter” statement was not a callous statement about the deaths of 4 Americans, as you imply. It referred to the people who attacked the embassy. I realize you were some pencil-pushing, Air Force REMF (or was that you as Dale?)…and have about as much knowledge about defending an embassy as you did about who was going to win the last election. But you, nevertheless, insist you know (apparently because Rush told you) they were “terrorists.” What differentiates a terrorist in civilian clothes who attacks an embassy from a civilian who does the same thing? If you haven’t noticed, most of our enemies no longer wear uniforms or openly represent countries. To the Israeli’s, the Palestinians are terrorists, and vice versa. To both major sects of Islam, the other side are terrorists. Just the other day, Pakistani’s are blowing each other up. To many in the world, drones are terrorists. You’d like people to think you have some clue as to who is, and who isn’t a terrorist – as though you have some inside track about who attacked the embassy. Your inside track is simply old, worn out neo-con Benghazi propaganda, which was a desperate, last ditch effort at swiftboating another election in your favor. Anyone following these boards need only to call up your posts over the last few years, to realize, as we all do, that you have seldom if ever, been right on anything you’ve posted. And we can tally up all the lies you’ve been caught in, but that never stops you. Once again, your volume of posts on sequestration reveals just how desperate you are. (And, perhaps, for the first time, you guys have learned to pay attention to the polls.) And as difficult as it has been for you Tea Baggers to accept an African American in the White House, you better get used to being unhappy for quite some time…because that “gal” that you knuckle-dragging, chauvinistic, ignorant pawns of Wall Street despise, is probably going to be your President until over a decade from now. Maybe you guys should all secede together, move to South Africa with all your guns and intolerance, and start a new apartheid colony. Because the real deal is, windandale, you’ve missed the word on the street from your own party. They want to drop the extremist nonsense, smarten the base up a bit, and stop acting the way you have on this board for years. Personally, I hope you don’t, but consistently being made fools of takes its toll, one would assume.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361469599878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:59:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361471105600-21</Id><Topic><Title>The Fed.!!</Title><Username>coolin_out47</Username><Timestamp>1361390274120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:57:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll tell you what, tb. You agree to get rid of all your old age entitlements and I'll agree to give up the safety net entitlements. Who do you think will come out ahead in that deal?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361471105600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:25:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361472887936-22</Id><Topic><Title>It’s a man-bites-dog story.</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361463256559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:14:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Hey Ricky, when was the last time a Democrat did this?" Same time as Rand Paul. Every Senator does this. Rand Paul just decided to hold a press conference about it. The two biggest savers this year (by percent of budget returned) were Richard Shelby (R-AL) &amp; Daniel Akaka (D-HI). The two lowest were Moran (R-KS) &amp; Begich (D-AK). Don't mistake Paul's media hype for substance. The budget bonus idea is something that's worked well in several states but it has drawbacks. After all, the Dept. of the Interior, for instance, could just stop fighting fires to save money and get a bonus. I'd rather see some measure of effectiveness and efficiency (similar to creating profits) result in bonuses than simply not spending. (This latter, btw, is what Gore's Reinventing Government began to accomplish, along the lines of some of Thatcher's reforms in the UK). In the meantime, though, I think there's room for this simpler idea to have some benefit.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361472887936</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:54:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361473178265-23</Id><Topic><Title>It’s a man-bites-dog story.</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361463256559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:14:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, the difference between winholder's perspective on Senate Office Budget savings and my perspective is the difference between the conservative media and the legitimate media. I read this story on Politico about a week ago, and it covered the full story. Winholder is watching Greta Van Sustern on Fox and he's dumber for it.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361473178265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:59:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361474261625-24</Id><Topic><Title>Pres on Golf Vacation Again</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1361238774182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 20:52:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are right Ricky.... Others? there was outrage over the war and spending during Presidents Bush's term? Right.... All I seem to remember is his heavy spending and The "Mission Accomplished" photo op that had to cost us millions just to fly him in a military jet to land on an aircraft carrier. No, the sabre rattling Rebublicans were not outraged with Bush, only interested when the other side is in office to throw mud. Politics as usual.</Msg><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1361474261625</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:17:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361475939244-25</Id><Topic><Title>The Fed.!!</Title><Username>coolin_out47</Username><Timestamp>1361390274120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:57:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I mock tbfine on this because for all his talk about cutting spending and entitlements, he quit the AARP because they supported the savings Obama found in Medicare. Just savings, no benefit cuts, mind you. Like most of these Tea Brains, TB doesn't care about spending, deficits or his country at all. He just wants to contribute as little as possible and get as much as possible.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361475939244</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:45:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361476845933-26</Id><Title>The next crisis</Title><Msg>According to news sources, I think they have just defined the next high dollar 'crisis' we will have to solve immediately by throwing more money at it. The Health Care Bill requires many other agencies to be involved in health care, particularly the IRS, but their antiquated computer systems won't allow them to do what the bill requires. Gee, you would have thought someone might have looked into that before they signed the bill. Oh I forget, they didn't read it first, they just passed it.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361476845933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:00:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361477110129-27</Id><Topic><Title>The Fed.!!</Title><Username>coolin_out47</Username><Timestamp>1361390274120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:57:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And on an almost daily basis the media, the Congressional Budget Office or some other government entity finds a new cost or a new difference in what was projected. The folks that voted for this bill don't have a clue what the cost is going to be, how it will be paid for, or what the impact on the citizens of this country will be. They are guessing and that is part of the reason for all the new 'revelations' week after week. This was a pig in a poke and now we the people are being poked, hard! But of course to Ricky, as news of higher costs or other problems are simply Tea Party lies.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361477110129</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:05:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361477224892-28</Id><Topic><Title>It’s a man-bites-dog story.</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361463256559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:14:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong yet again trench mouth, I have never watched Greta, on any channel.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361477224892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:07:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361477468710-29</Id><Topic><Title>It’s a man-bites-dog story.</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361463256559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:14:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's what you got out of this? You're man Rand Paul pretty much lied to you, along with whatever right-wing media you get your information from, and you're worried about Greta Van Sustern? Brietbart, Hannity, Limbaugh, Beck. Pick a name. It doesn't make a difference. Whatever or whoever you watch/read/follow, you're dumber for it.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361477468710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:11:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361477492967-30</Id><Topic><Title>The next crisis</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361476845933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:00:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You haven't made enough of a fool out of yourself today?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361477492967</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:11:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361477636245-31</Id><Topic><Title>The Fed.!!</Title><Username>coolin_out47</Username><Timestamp>1361390274120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:57:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"are simply Tea Party lies." And you're dumber for it.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361477636245</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:13:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361480898000-32</Id><Topic><Title>The Fed.!!</Title><Username>coolin_out47</Username><Timestamp>1361390274120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:57:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well Ricky, try this on. I paid over $40K in federal income taxes and property taxes last year. Lord knows how many other taxes and hidden taxes I put into the pot on top of that. I'm in the red big time, even after netting out those "old age entitlements" you carp about. So, here is my deal Ricky. I'll gadly give up my old age entitlements if a can become one your buddies and stop paying just federal income taxes. I'd like to join the 47%. Even then, I'll still be in the red.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1361480898000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:08:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361483169248-33</Id><Topic><Title>The Fed.!!</Title><Username>coolin_out47</Username><Timestamp>1361390274120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:57:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fine, but you also have to pay for everything the Federal government provides you as you go. No interstates, no ports, no parks without paying the unsubsidized price. Likewise, no hospitals, no parks, no levy protection unless you pay the capital costs. No internet, not phone, no computer, no energy unless you pay your share of R&amp;D. I'll personally pay to import smog from Berlin just for you, unless you pay your share of the EPA budget. When you go to the grocery store, be sure to carry your own measuring devices. No one is standardizing weights and measures for you. Be sure to carry a separate one for gas. All your pharmaceuticals--black market and untested only. Hire your own personal body guards too--no police protection, and if a terrorist says they're just going to blow up your house, we'll instruct our soldiers to let the through. And, btw, you're not getting the group, non-profit price for any of this stuff. You get the individual, profit motive rate. I think you'll blow through that 40 grand pretty quickly. Then maybe you can think about finding a unlicensed doctor who didn't complete a residency in a US Teaching Hospital. One more thing: Only OTC stocks for you. Better hire your own accountant and auditor to make sure those books are in order, because you can't sue in US courts if their not.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361483169248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:46:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361486512920-34</Id><Topic><Title>The Fed.!!</Title><Username>coolin_out47</Username><Timestamp>1361390274120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:57:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah, now you raise the bar. Typical. It was old age entitlements, a deal I said I'd take. Now we have no internet, no phone, no energy, no hospitals, no parks, no levy protection, etc,etc, etc. Typical Ricky. I'll stop helping footing the bill for that stuff when you do Ricky. Better yet, why don't we get the growing number of takers to help just a bit.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1361486512920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 17:41:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361488361713-35</Id><Topic><Title>Universal Orlando dropping health coverage for workers over ObamaCare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1361386388575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see your point. I had a self storage business at one time. A semi backed into part of the fence. I had insurance to cover it as we didn't get a good camera of the plates. I got bids to repair it. Two bids were around $1000 with my insurance as a claim;OR $500 out of my pocket and pay cash. Well guess what? My insurance deductible was $500. So if I had filed a claim my insurance claim would have risen.....I reached into my pocket and pulled out 5 bills and filed no claim......insurance is often a racket</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1361488361713</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:12:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361498438953-36</Id><Topic><Title>The next crisis</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361476845933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:00:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet if you stuck your hands down the back of your pants you would find one of your gay liberal buddies trying to get in.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1361498438953</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 21:00:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361500796173-37</Id><Topic><Title>Pres on Golf Vacation Again</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1361238774182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 20:52:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>anybody who thinks Ronnie Reagan actually did much work as President is naive. He did spend much time memorizing his speeches. And his photo ops at his California were just that---publicity seeking</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1361500796173</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 21:39:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>