<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-25"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361782213963-1</Id><Title>T takes over Onstar in 2014.</Title><Msg>T takes over Onstar in 2014.</Msg><Username>cmwalace</Username><Timestamp>1361782213963</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 03:50:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361782323454-2</Id><Topic><Title>T takes over Onstar in 2014.</Title><Username>cmwalace</Username><Timestamp>1361782213963</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 03:50:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/news/general-motors-selects-ts-4g-050100807.html</Msg><Username>cmwalace</Username><Timestamp>1361782323454</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 03:52:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361792036719-3</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, like Clinton killed the town meeting</Msg><Username>frn89yggo</Username><Timestamp>1361792036719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 06:33:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361799267020-4</Id><Title>Has the gun control agenda changed since the civil war?</Title><Msg>Stacy Swimp, president and CFO of the Frederick Douglass Society, pointed out on Friday at the National Press Club in Washington, D.C., that gun control dates back to laws before and after the Civil War that prohibited or restricted African Americans from owning firearms. And stated that: “History is [rife] with examples. There’s a direct correlation between gun control and black people control,” IMHO the only thing that I would add is that those that desire gun control today also desire all people control, otherwise not much has changed (i.e., the same types of people that pushed for gun control during the 19th century are the same types that are pushing for it today, and for the same reasons). "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361799267020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 08:34:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361802264933-5</Id><Topic><Title>Universal Orlando dropping health coverage for workers over ObamaCare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1361386388575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What makes him extreme? The fact that he's black? It certainly isn't his policies or his politics. Then again, you people accuse Clinton, Gore and Chuck Hegel (a Republican) of being left-wing extremists. You think anything left of deranged nutcase is totalitarian Communist.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361802264933</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 09:24:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361802471708-6</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've heard the lies from the right about benghazi so many times, you actually believe it. It is a shame you and the right make politics out of a tragedy. You just proved politics is the reason by looking forward to 2016 and convicting Hilary on the spot. Don't worry, your party will be toast then as well. Unless you change the way you operate, which is never going to happen. Bad sport,sore loser, and sour grapes. The People have caught on to the tea party, and we don't like it.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1361802471708</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 09:27:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361803143703-7</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What does it matter now what it was called", dishonest person changing meaning. You left out the words "what it was called" that were the meaning of her statement, which totally put the tea bags in their place which is why they change it. Can't win honestly, don't win at all, but don't be dishonest. Terrorists, bag ladies out for a walk, jehovah's witnesses coming to the door, what they are called doesn't matter now. We the People don't like the tea party and we are voting accordingly.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1361803143703</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 09:39:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361803898235-8</Id><Title>The BIG news that is lifting AT&amp;T</Title><Msg>" AT&amp;T*, the leader in emerging devices and telematics services, today announced an agreement with OnStar, LLC, a subsidiary of General Motors Corporation (GM), to wirelessly deliver an enhanced suite of safety, security, diagnostic and infotainment services to most Chevrolet, Buick, GMC and Cadillac vehicles, beginning in 2014 in the United States and Canada."</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361803898235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 09:51:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361804433887-9</Id><Topic><Title>Pres Obama's name will be in the history books forever, children will study his words and discuss early 21st century America. When an African American President was elected two terms to office by the people.</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1361646120079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 14:02:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who are "all the Marxists" that will be in the history books? What freedoms have declined for you? The President will be remembered as a President. A President who is proving to be one of the great ones, and his words wil be studied for generations.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1361804433887</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:00:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361805771114-10</Id><Topic><Title>Pres Obama's name will be in the history books forever, children will study his words and discuss early 21st century America. When an African American President was elected two terms to office by the people.</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1361646120079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 14:02:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing great about Obama are his words. His actions in supporting the Muslim Brotherhood's takeover of Egypt, Libya, and Syria as well as the United States will make his name live in infamy.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361805771114</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:22:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361806166344-11</Id><Topic><Title>The BIG news that is lifting AT&amp;T</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361803898235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 09:51:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah BIG news. Worth all of 20 cents so far.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1361806166344</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:29:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361806348000-12</Id><Topic><Title>How's that good old liberal tolerance working for you?</Title><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1361562557529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:49:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And thank you for joining the ranks of ignored fools.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1361806348000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:32:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361806833675-13</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are so right!! The unions, supported by liberals, have priced our labor out of the market creating the unemployment. Their solution; Raise the minimum wage. Where in the Constitution does it say that Congress shall have the right to set prices for anything?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361806833675</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:40:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361806909742-14</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You've heard the lies from the right about benghazi so many times, you actually believe it." First I want to know how you can submit a post without capitalizing the word Benghazi and not have been put down by the infamous grammar and spelling czar of the board? What he$$ Echo? Second your comment is incorrect. What we have heard from the left are excuses and cries to leave them alone to 'investigate', etc. What we haven't heard from the left or this government is the full truth of what really happened and how it was allowed to happen on their watch.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361806909742</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:41:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361807010809-15</Id><Topic><Title>How's that good old liberal tolerance working for you?</Title><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1361562557529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:49:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I never caught Fox News in an intentional lie," Yeah. And palm trees grow in Wisconsin.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361807010809</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:43:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361807244409-16</Id><Topic><Title>Has the gun control agenda changed since the civil war?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361799267020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 08:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Carney, the trained monkey they push out on a daily basis says that the government has no intention to take guns from law-abiding citizens. You need to parse his word very carefully. When the government demands that all guns, regardless of size, caliber, or when they were obtained MUST be registered with the Federal government, and you don't register them...you will no longer be considered a law-abiding citizens thus they have the right to confiscate your weapons. Our government is the best, or worst, depending on your perspective, at saying things they don't really mean and not meaning what they really say. Staff memeber don't just write position memo's without someone having planted the idea or asked for a version for review.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361807244409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:47:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361807623734-17</Id><Topic><Title>How's that good old liberal tolerance working for you?</Title><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1361562557529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:49:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's comments like these that show what hacks you are. Yes, Benghazi was bad. Yes, gunwalking was bad. They were specific, limited instances that lead to specific, limited failures--including a limited number of deaths. Compare these to the policy of legal sales of assault rifles, which is a systemic failure that sends far, far more guns to cartels and smugglers. Compare these to the misguided abandonment of Afghanistan and invasion of Iraq, and the systemic failures in those operations--which were directly attributable to (at best) wrong-headed leadership. Sure, Obama, Holder and Clinton make mistakes. At that level, mistakes can have dire consequences, including deaths. Republican policies are ongoing systemic failures that lead to tens of thousands of deaths. You don't care about mistakes that lead to deaths. You don't care how many people the misguided policies of Republicans have killed and continue to kill. Between your comments here and Froggie reveling every time a child is killed in Chicago, we know exactly what you are.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361807623734</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:53:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361808021946-18</Id><Topic><Title>Universal Orlando dropping health coverage for workers over ObamaCare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1361386388575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great. Just what we need. More toilet humor. Why don't you both grow up?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361808021946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 11:00:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361809280471-19</Id><Topic><Title>Universal Orlando dropping health coverage for workers over ObamaCare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1361386388575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are not smoking anything. Those Obama stickers say IMPEACH OBAMA.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361809280471</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 11:21:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361809488471-20</Id><Topic><Title>Universal Orlando dropping health coverage for workers over ObamaCare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1361386388575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the classic sign of a Democrat is, if you plan to do something wrong, charge your opponent with it first.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361809488471</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 11:24:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361810256755-21</Id><Topic><Title>How's that good old liberal tolerance working for you?</Title><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1361562557529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:49:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All faux news does is lie about their obsession, Pres Obama. Just like you. I never have seen Obama lie, not once, he is an honest guy.. I don't claim Obama is a Christian, he is one all on his own without me.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1361810256755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 11:37:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361811609026-22</Id><Topic><Title>$ T Featured on MAD MONEY</Title><Username>kevinlee899</Username><Timestamp>1361805521276</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:18:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good info. thx.</Msg><Username>nickreed198</Username><Timestamp>1361811609026</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 12:00:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361814057819-23</Id><Title>Buy PULS now..MAJOR BREAK OUT....PULS is up 20% and is a NYSE stock</Title><Msg>Currently PULS is trading at 0.40 cents per share...Thanks me later!!!</Msg><Username>stevem1969_99</Username><Timestamp>1361814057819</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 12:40:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361814344371-24</Id><Topic><Title>The BIG news that is lifting AT&amp;T</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361803898235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 09:51:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At the high it was up 40 cents but now it is down to yesterday's closing price. I guess it takes REALLY good news to move very much for a big company like AT&amp;T. The chart shows that T has been trading just above the 200 DMA all through February but today was the first time over $36 since October. We still have 3 months to reach my "$40 by May" forecast but it is going to require better performance than February to make it.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361814344371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 12:45:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361815343734-25</Id><Topic><Title>T takes over Onstar in 2014.</Title><Username>cmwalace</Username><Timestamp>1361782213963</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 03:50:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will never buy a GM car because : A-They still make a lousy product. B. I don't appreciate that my car is a spy.</Msg><Username>jpmax6</Username><Timestamp>1361815343734</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 13:02:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361816056399-26</Id><Topic><Title>The BIG news that is lifting AT&amp;T</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361803898235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 09:51:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VZ loses the On Star contract and goes up nearly 40 cents so far. Best stick to your daily $100 daily profit strategy futures trading krap instead of forecasting.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1361816056399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 13:14:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361817784589-27</Id><Topic><Title>Has the gun control agenda changed since the civil war?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361799267020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 08:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When the government demands that all guns, regardless of size, caliber, or when they were obtained MUST be registered with the Federal government." Obama has repeatedly said that he is not proposing and would oppose any effort to create a Federal gun registry. A Federal gun registry is already banned under the National Firearms Act. The only trained monkey here is you, winholder. Your hack handlers send you the party line and you repost it here. Like clockwork.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361817784589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 13:43:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361818303562-28</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe there is some hope for the good people of Chicago</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361595142569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 23:52:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"how this ruling affects the party's plans to disarm the American people." There are no such plans. Limitations on concealed carry are not part of any proposals from Obama administration. This decision only affects a law peculiar to the State of Illinois, and places limits on one of their efforts to deal with gangs and violence in Chicago. Froggie is a fear-monger and a liar.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361818303562</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 13:51:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361818893520-29</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe there is some hope for the good people of Chicago</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361595142569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 23:52:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad it wasn't one of your frog children who were at the school. That would change your mind, right now you are a typical unconerned with others as long as I am fine, right wing nut job.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1361818893520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 14:01:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361818953095-30</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Article 1, Section 8, Claus 3: To regulate Commerce with foreign Nations, and among the several States, and with the Indian Tribes. Article 1, Section 8, Claus 18: The Congress shall have Power - To make all Laws which shall be necessary and proper for carrying into Execution the foregoing Powers, and all other Powers vested by this Constitution in the Government of the United States, or in any Department or Officer thereof.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361818953095</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 14:02:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361820868293-31</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Accomplishments</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361625594937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:19:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Bush and Paulson threatened congress with martial law in the US and a world wide depression if they didnt sign TARP" BS. I could not find any record of this list from New Yorker Magazine, either.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361820868293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 14:34:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361821145539-32</Id><Topic><Title>Has the gun control agenda changed since the civil war?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361799267020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 08:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Win, did you see the ABC news report regarding the DOJ memo that talks about the need for "gun confiscation" and "national gun registration". The report points out that this is not the official policy of our "dear leader" but suggests that it is just a work in progress. Interesting that the administration does not deny the memo, but will not go on record to discuss its content. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361821145539</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 14:39:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361821262238-33</Id><Topic><Title>The next crisis</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361476845933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:00:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, I'm not quite sure what problem you are talking about here. They are going to create exchanges. Monies were allocated for this. Do you think they shouldn't use computers? Do you think the IRS should never upgrade their computers?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361821262238</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 14:41:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361821669060-34</Id><Topic><Title>Has the gun control agenda changed since the civil war?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361799267020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 08:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean this one: "The National Rifle Association is using a Justice Department memo it obtained to argue in ads that the Obama administration believes its gun control plans won't work unless the government seizes firearms and requires national gun registration — ideas the White House has not proposed and does not support. The NRA's assertion and its obtaining of the memo in the first place underscore the no-holds-barred battle under way as Washington's fight over gun restrictions heats up. The memo, under the name of one of the Justice Department's leading crime researchers, critiques the effectiveness of gun control proposals, including some of President Barack Obama's. A Justice Department official called the memo an unfinished review of gun violence research and said it does not represent administration policy." More proof that Froggie is a lying hack. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361821669060</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 14:47:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361823444999-35</Id><Topic><Title>Has the gun control agenda changed since the civil war?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361799267020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 08:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"More proof that Froggie is a lying hack. . ." Yes that looks like part of the article. What part of my post did you find untrue? "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361823444999</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 15:17:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361823784774-36</Id><Topic><Title>$ T Featured on MAD MONEY</Title><Username>kevinlee899</Username><Timestamp>1361805521276</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:18:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>interesting report. thx.</Msg><Username>blackmike975</Username><Timestamp>1361823784774</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 15:23:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361824520788-37</Id><Topic><Title>Has the gun control agenda changed since the civil war?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361799267020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 08:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you can believe his administration, one might think you’re correct. But can you? This certainly is not the 'open' administration of his campaign promises. If there is no intention to move in that direction, why is the DOJ writing memo's about how to achieve that goal? I don't think Obama has the horsepower to get such a bill passed, but the fact that his administration is studying that as a solution to obtain their objective does say that they have considered such a move. I firmly believe that if he thought he could issue and Presidential proclamation and get away with it, he would have done so already. But, for the question asked, where is there a lie in the post string? The memo exists, it was written by someone in this administration and at someone request. So where is the lie? It isn’t a lie, just an embarrassing fact that they were caught doing writing it.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361824520788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 15:35:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361825063042-38</Id><Topic><Title>The next crisis</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361476845933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:00:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, quite the contrary, I think the IRS should have been one of the first computer systems after the Defense department to upgrade. The Defense department has spent billions trying to upgrade theirs and still don't have the upgraded systems working as designed and have given up with the current project in spite of the loss of billions of dollars. More government efficiency examples. The subject was that the IRS and the health care systems of the government were designed to perform certain tasks under this new wonderful health care plan and not all of a sudden the existing computer systems are compatible with each other or don't have the processing horsepower to do the job. When you design a new process, one might think that will the genius that is resident in the Congress and their overloaded staff's someone would have considered if the process would be feasible before moving to implement the changes. Just another fine example of the idiocy, waste, corruption, and poor performance in Washington. If you really they to follow the story lines, instead of posting political spin, your post might not receive as many thumbs down selections.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361825063042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 15:44:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361825352097-39</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe there is some hope for the good people of Chicago</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361595142569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 23:52:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Children, children, recess is over.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361825352097</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 15:49:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361825785567-40</Id><Topic><Title>Has the gun control agenda changed since the civil war?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361799267020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 08:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let me beat Sir Echo of the grammar police to the punch, that sentence should have read 'and at someone's request'. God forbid that he might have to read close enough and not be confused by the typo.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361825785567</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 15:56:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361825991860-41</Id><Topic><Title>The next crisis</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361476845933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:00:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When the IRS decided to efile and do direct deposit they had to invest in new computing equipment. Should they not have done that? Should we not take on new defense projects because they may require computer or software upgrades? This is 2013. The exchanges have a capital budget. Computers and software are part of that. Systems need to be continuously upgraded. Get used to it. "If you really they to follow the story lines, instead of posting political spin, your post might not receive as many thumbs down selections." HA! Clearly the opposite of that is true.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361825991860</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 15:59:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361828547514-42</Id><Topic><Title>Has the gun control agenda changed since the civil war?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361799267020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 08:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If there is no intention to move in that direction, why is the DOJ writing memo's about how to achieve that goal?" "If you can believe his administration" What bunk. The conservative media lies to you, not the president. "why is the DOJ writing memo's" It was a DOJ researcher's preliminary critique of policy options, including the administration's options, by one DOJ researcher. There was no recommendation. There was no "how to". Other researchers have produced other memos with differing analyses that the NRA did not choose to make into ads. Believe it or not, people like me do this sort of stuff all the time. It's called considering the options. "I firmly believe" Who cares what you believe? You're a trained monkey. "just an embarrassing fact" Of course. Because researching policy matters is embarrassing. Why research? Policies should simply channeled fully formed from corporate lobbyists through Rush Limbaugh and directly into your head. Don't think. Don't research. Don't consider. Just repeat. Good trained monkey! You should be embarrassed winholder. You are embarrassing yourself.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361828547514</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 16:42:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361829431369-43</Id><Topic><Title>The next crisis</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361476845933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:00:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the pubs idea which i agree with is everything for free. except health care food stampds education. the free stuff is army roads beachs in front of their house free oil rigs</Msg><Username>blacklicorice1234</Username><Timestamp>1361829431369</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 16:57:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361834167690-44</Id><Topic><Title>The next crisis</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361476845933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:00:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apples and oranges Ricky, apples and oranges. The subject was the ability of the IRS computer systems to do they tracking of those not following the rules and enforcing the fines, etc. That has nothing to do with efile. Nice try at deflection, but no cigar.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361834167690</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 18:16:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361834711485-45</Id><Topic><Title>The BIG news that is lifting AT&amp;T</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361803898235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 09:51:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is good news for T but it will take time for it to hit the profit page.</Msg><Username>fire2ball</Username><Timestamp>1361834711485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 18:25:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361835967556-46</Id><Title>will we in connecticut ever get a contract cwa union has let us down again......</Title><Msg>well here we are once again in connecticut without a contract,our cwa union said we would all fight together this year 200,000 strong in our fight,they said it would be like 3 years ago when it was 1 union 1 fight,and all the districts fell like dominos,this year was table of 8 all vp from every district and we would stick togeether....guess what another #$%$ sandwich from larry cohen the president of the cwa national in dc....we are all alone again 3500 employees without a contract our local cwa 1298 tells us we will fight on...what a joke they are...so in the end what will we get in connecticut...hopefully not another #$%$ sandwich from our union.....</Msg><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1361835967556</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 18:46:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361836215521-47</Id><Topic><Title>Is AAPL better than T?</Title><Username>latrobejana</Username><Timestamp>1361829115071</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 16:51:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok cool. Thank you for sharing this.</Msg><Username>opprioriapril</Username><Timestamp>1361836215521</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 18:50:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361837049835-48</Id><Topic><Title>Is AAPL better than T?</Title><Username>latrobejana</Username><Timestamp>1361829115071</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 16:51:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ LINK IS TO NASTY PORN!!!! ████████████...</Msg><Username>zion_will_up_huge</Username><Timestamp>1361837049835</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 19:04:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361837168949-49</Id><Topic><Title>Is AAPL better than T?</Title><Username>latrobejana</Username><Timestamp>1361829115071</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 16:51:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ LINK IS TO NASTY PORN!!!! ████████████...</Msg><Username>zion_will_up_huge</Username><Timestamp>1361837168949</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 19:06:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361838671466-50</Id><Topic><Title>The next crisis</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361476845933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:00:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think that "ricky18201" really understands your post or response winholder.</Msg><Username>defilip1</Username><Timestamp>1361838671466</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 19:31:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361839984775-51</Id><Title>Verizon loses deal to AT&amp;T and Verizon up AT&amp;T down. Weird</Title><Msg>so verizon loses OnStar Deal to AT&amp;T and Verizon is up and T is down?? Who sells a stock that has a new deal and 5% dividends?</Msg><Username>hey_rob69</Username><Timestamp>1361839984775</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 19:53:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>