<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358166777159-1</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like some people in Mexico understand that guns are not just for hunting</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358076072441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 06:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well Echo, Good Morning! If you mean that I am. 'midway between extremes; average a medium size', then I am a medium. I do wish that I had the 'power to communicate with the spirits of the dead or with agents of another world or dimension'. If I was that kind of medium perhaps I would never lose a sports bet or would have never invested in a betamax! As it stands, I do like to listen to both sides of a discussion. My ability to effect change on most of these discussions is inconsequential so I do not post them.</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1358166777159</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 07:32:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358168717605-2</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like some people in Mexico understand that guns are not just for hunting</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358076072441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 06:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Federalist Papers were a series of writings published in a New York Newspaper by Hamilton and Madison advocating the adoption of the Constitution in 1786-1787. They advocated a strong centralized government. There was not a supreme court yet ( since there was no constitution -the Constitution was ratified in 1791) so the courts never clarified The Federalist Papers. By the way, The Federalist opposed having a Bill of Rights included in the Constitution. However, the Constitution would not have gotten the votes for ratification without their inclusion. jon3, you are completely illerate. A well regulated Militia, being necessary to the security of a free State, the right of the people to keep and bear Arms, shall not be infringed. How does the above give the right to Latino Drug Dealers to conduct business with AR-15s with magazines or deranged folks the right to shoot 20 kids with military type weapons? jon3. In American it is alright to be uneducated and stupid but most folks like you just keep their mouths shut so others wont know.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358168717605</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 08:05:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358174365809-3</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like some people in Mexico understand that guns are not just for hunting</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358076072441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 06:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Does the justice department (Eric Holder and his people) get to chose what federal laws they enforce?" Of course they do! By way of example, it is a felony to provide false info on an application for a gun. In a NYT's report today Justice Dept data shows 80,000 gun applications were denied in 2010 due to inaccurate info regarding criminal backgrounds. Of those 80,000, 44 were charged with a crime. In response to a question concerning the few folks charged with a crime, an unnamed government official stated that the "government must prioritize its use of resources".</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1358174365809</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 09:39:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358175792921-4</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans in Washington</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1358045743645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:55:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe you better cool it. You are displaying your ignorance. The Brown Shirts were the most obvious felons in Germany, but the real culprits were all those, like you, that insisted "everything is fine. Just go along."</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1358175792921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:03:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358181516511-5</Id><Topic><Title>See EGGO .. live, in action today !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1358181341429</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 11:35:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jon3---Tell us more about the Federalist Papers and the Supreme Court . LOL</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358181516511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 11:38:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358182189536-6</Id><Title>The 545 responsible</Title><Msg>545 vs. 300,000,000 People -By Charlie Reese Politicians are the only people in the world who create problems and then campaign against them. Have you ever wondered, if both the Democrats and the Republicans are against deficits, WHY do we have deficits? Have you ever wondered, if all the politicians are against inflation and high taxes, WHY do we have inflation and high taxes? You and I don’t propose a federal budget. The President does. You and I don’t have the Constitutional authority to vote on appropriations. The House of Representatives does. You and I don’t write the tax code, Congress does. You and I don’t set fiscal policy, Congress does. You and I don’t control monetary policy, the Federal Reserve Bank does. One hundred senators, 435 congressmen, one President, and nine Supreme Court justices equates to 545 human beings out of the 300 million are directly, legally, morally, and individually responsible for the domestic problems that plague this country. I excluded the members of the Federal Reserve Board because that problem was created by the Congress. In 1913, Congress delegated its Constitutional duty to provide a sound currency to a federally chartered, but private, central bank. I excluded all the special interests and lobbyists for a sound reason. They have no legal authority. They have no ability to coerce a senator, a congressman, or a President to do one cotton-picking thing. I don’t care if they offer a politician $1 million dollars in cash. The politician has the power to accept or reject it. No matter what the lobbyist promises, it is the legislator’s responsibility to determine how he votes. Those 545 human beings spend much of their energy convincing you that what they did is not their fault. They cooperate in this common con regardless of party. What separates a politician from a normal human being is an excessive amount of gall. No normal human being would have the gall of a Speaker, who stood up and criticized the President for creating deficits. The President can only propose a budget. He cannot force the Congress to accept it. The Constitution, which is the supreme law of the land, gives sole responsibility to the House of Representatives for originating and approving appropriations and taxes. Who is the speaker of the House? John Boehner. He is the leader of the majority party. He and fellow House members, not the President, can approve any budget they want. If the President vetoes it, they can pass it over his veto if they agree to. It seems inconceivable to me that a nation of 300 million cannot replace 545 people who stand convicted — by present facts — of incompetence and irresponsibility. I can’t think of a single domestic problem that is not traceable directly to those 545 people. When you fully grasp the plain truth that 545 people exercise the power of the federal government, then it must follow that what exists is what they want to exist. If the tax code is unfair, it’s because they want it unfair. If the budget is in the red, it’s because they want it in the red. If the Army &amp; Marines are in Iraq and Afghanistan it’s because they want them in Iraq and Afghanistan … If they do not receive social security but are on an elite retirement plan not available to the people, it’s because they want it that way. There are no insoluble government problems. Do not let these 545 people shift the blame to bureaucrats, whom they hire and whose jobs they can abolish; to lobbyists, whose gifts and advice they can reject; to regulators, to whom they give the power to regulate and from whom they can take this power. Above all, do not let them con you into the belief that there exists disembodied mystical forces like “the economy,” “inflation,” or “politics” that prevent them from doing what they take an oath to do. Those 545 people, and they alone, are responsible. They, and they alone, have the power. They, and they alone, should be held accountable by the people who are their bosses. Provided the voters have the gumption to manage their own employees</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358182189536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 11:49:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358182690478-7</Id><Topic><Title>second amendment</Title><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358103212548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 13:53:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How can even some of you take that to mean that a Litano gang member has the right to run around with an AK-15 shooting folks or others walking around with magazine clips shooting kids in school." You're confused. Yes, right now, in most states he has the right to own or possess an AK-15 or many other weapons...however you're incorrect and stupid to suggest that he has the right to go around 'shooting folks or others walking around with magazine clips shooting kids in school'. I am not sure I understand the difference between folks and others walking around, animals I guess? When you calm down enough to make sense you might begin to realize that you're off the mark yet again. There could be and likely should be some rule changes regarding guns and gun ownership, but this knee jerk reaction or 'crisis' that this administration has created is not the methodology that should be used. Calm, thoughtful, long-term solutions are what are required, not crisis management decisions driven by political gain. I think we can dispense with your Constitutional advice and deal with the advice of those with the education and experience to do so, although I am not sure the current group on Congress is our best choice.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358182690478</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 11:58:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358183094648-8</Id><Topic><Title>second amendment</Title><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358103212548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 13:53:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The Supreme Court has ,at various times, ruled that slavery was allowed in the Constitution, that harbering a slave was illegal, that seperate but equal was equal, that women do not have the right to vote, that American Indians do not have the right to vote, that Japanese-American Citizens can be arrested without a trial and held indefinately, that Japanese-American Citizen's property can be confiscated without proper compensation, that habius corps can be suspended whenever the poweres that be deem it necessary, etc, etc." More historical histrionics on your part. The Supreme Court and Congress were the source of those insane decisions, not the Constitution. It is the often mind warping and strange things that Congress, often with the direction and suggestion of Presidents that misshape the meanings and teaching of the Constitution. To blame the Constitution for these acts of foolishness is, well, foolish. You should also slow down and make good use of a spell check tool. I am still not entirely sure how to ‘harber’ someone.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358183094648</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:04:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358183664073-9</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like some people in Mexico understand that guns are not just for hunting</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358076072441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 06:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Echo you narrow minded soul, you're getting to be a bit of a one-trick pony; anyone and everyone that disagrees with your slanted view of the world must be a ‘another Tea Party nutball’. You need to find more varied excuses for your attacks on differing opinions; this one has worn out its welcome and logic.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358183664073</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:14:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358184121714-10</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like some people in Mexico understand that guns are not just for hunting</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358076072441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 06:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How can that mean that every drug dealer/gang member/thug gets to walk around with an AK-15 with magazine clips? Or how can that mean that any inbalanced person can use an Army type gun to shoot 20 children." Yet again poor example with which to make your case; my guess would be that 'every drug dealer/gang member/thug' walking around with a gun has not come into possession of that weapon by any legal means. They did not purchase these weapons from a legitimate source and most assuredly didn't pass any background checks. As for the 'inbalanced' persons with access to a weapon, surely you would agree that a mother with a son known to have mental issues and takes him target shooting and didn't secure those weapons a bit unbalanced as well correct? I don't hear a sudden outcry for better parenting skills being mandatory and need Federal laws changed to enforce such actions, do you?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358184121714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:22:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358184564504-11</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like some people in Mexico understand that guns are not just for hunting</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358076072441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 06:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Echo, if you didn't go off and assume so much you might have a point. I believe that the point was that people in Mexico were taking up arms and arresting people, not Americans and then only because they felt their Federal government has let them down and not providing the protection they desired or were promised. The failure or the overstepping of governments has led to a great many insurrections in history. The second amendment seems to provide Americans with a bit of security against such overstepping of our government and this current administration seems have a tendency for showing that overstepping when they don't get what they want is not objectionable to them.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358184564504</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:29:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358184957700-12</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like some people in Mexico understand that guns are not just for hunting</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358076072441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 06:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We have a system of laws in place. If you decide to make up your own, then I guess anyone else who disagrees with you can do the same thing to you." And we have an administration that picks and chooses which of those duly passed laws they will enforce and which they won't. If it is the law of the land, then it is the law of the land, individual administrators of those laws should not be allowed to arbitrarily elect which they like, and which they don't. If you want law and order, then you have to have law and order; it is not a capricious choice of whoever is currently in charge. Currently the second amendment is the law of the land. If the people want it different, they will demand the changes in Washington. The problem seems to be that Washington doesn’t spend much time listening to the people lately.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358184957700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:35:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358185256569-13</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like some people in Mexico understand that guns are not just for hunting</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358076072441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 06:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"By way of example, it is a felony to provide false info on an application for a gun." Where those example of the non-prosecuted guilty of providing 'false' information or simply 'incorrect' information? Could that be the reason many of them were not taken to court? Do you any data in relation to how many 'corrected' their forms and were later approved? No? Didn’t' think so. Ready, fire, aim!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358185256569</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:40:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358185510608-14</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans in Washington</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1358045743645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:55:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They were known as Brown Shirts in Germany: uneducated, unemployed hooligans who disrupted any meeting they disagreed." Oh, you mean like those people camped out in parks in NYC and other places protesting because they had no money because the rich people had stolen all theirs? Those same unemployed nitwits that blamed rich people for not having jobs instead of a political party responsible for the housing collapse that started much of our current economic difficulties? Those same people?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358185510608</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:45:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358185599635-15</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans in Washington</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1358045743645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:55:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Brown Shirts were just the tools of the corrupt government. Can you say we don't have a corrupt government, I mean with a straight face?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358185599635</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:46:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358185921255-16</Id><Topic><Title>And a fine time was had by all...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357840216734</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 12:50:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, but with our economy still in the shi%%er, a Congress that still thinks this is 6th grade recess and a President that wants to be King and the best you fools can do is argue about the use of the word cammie? You should both apologize to everyone else!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358185921255</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:52:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358186034896-17</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid the new hero of the right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1357790625707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:03:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obama rated as the 4th best president ever ********************************* Hard to dispute unbiased research. A study group recently released its findings as to the best presidents of the United States of America ." And who pray tell in this unbaised study group? Why are they hard to dispute?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358186034896</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:53:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358186403851-18</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Failure</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1358112008055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:20:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It is amazing that people think we cannot afford to pay for doctors, hospitals, and medication somehow think that we can afford to pay for doctors, hospitals, medications and a government bureaucracy to administer it." Thomas Sowell.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358186403851</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 13:00:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358186776805-19</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (3)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357961091198</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 22:24:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“By our readiness to allow arms to be purchased at will and fired at whim; by allowing our movie and television screens to teach our children that the hero is one who masters the art of shooting and the technique of killing; by allowing all of these developments, we have created an atmosphere in which violence and hatred have become popular pastimes.” – Martin Luther King, Jr. Yet the Democrats that insist all guns are evil and should be banned, say nothing of their large campaign contributors that write, produce and sell these same types of movies by the thousands. It is a ponderment!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358186776805</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 13:06:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358186943604-20</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357961099977</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 22:24:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Make no mistake -- they're coming for our guns. And we freedom-loving gun lovers are totally defenseless! Other than, you know, the guns." – Stephen Colbert And this is precisely why we should be allowed to keep them.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358186943604</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 13:09:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358187319094-21</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (2)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357960284445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 22:11:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HERE ARE A LOT OF GOOD IDEAS Something like this would be a damn good start. When a company falls on difficult times, one of the things that seems to happen is they reduce their staff and workers. The remaining workers must find ways to continue to do a good job or risk that their job would be eliminated as well. Wall street and the media normally congratulate the CEO for making this type of "tough decision". Our government should not be immune from similar risks. Therefore: Reduce the House of Representatives from the current 435 members to 218members. Reduce Senate members from 100 to 50 (one per State). Then, reduce their remaining staff by 25%. Accomplish this over the next 8 years (two steps/two elections) and of course this would require some redistricting. Some Yearly Monetary Gains Include: $44,108,400 for elimination of base pay for congress. (267 members X $165,200 pay/member/yr.) $437,100,000 for elimination of their staff. (Estimate $1.3 Million in staff per each member of the House, and $3 Million in staff per each member of the Senate every year) $108,350,000 for the reduction in remaining staff by 25%. $7,500,000,000reduction in pork barrel earmarks each year. (Those members whose jobs are gone. Current estimates for total government pork earmarks are at $15 Billion/yr). The remaining representatives would need to work smarter and improve efficiencies. It might even be in their best interests to work together for the good of our country! We may also expect that smaller committees might lead to a more efficient resolution of issues as well. It might even be easier to keep track of what your representative is doing. Congress has more tools available to do their jobs than it had back in 1911 when the current number of representatives was established. (Telephone, computers, cell phones to name a few) Note: Congress does not hesitate to head home for extended weekends, holidays and recesses, when what the nation needs is a real fix for economic problems. Also, we had 3 senators who were not doing their jobs for the 18+ months (on the campaign trail) and still they all accepted full pay. Minnesota survived very well with only one senator for the first half of this year. These facts alone support a reduction in senators and congress. Summary of opportunity: $44,108,400 reduction of congress members. $282,100,000 for elimination of the reduced house member staff. $150,000,000 for elimination of reduced senate member staff. $70,850,000 for 25% reduction of staff for remaining house members. $37,500,000 for 25% reduction of staff for remaining senate members. $7,500,000,000 reduction in pork added to bills by the reduction of congress members. $8,084,558,400 per year, estimated total savings. (That's 8-BILLION just to start!) Corporate America does these types of cuts all the time. There's even a name for it. "Downsizing." ------------------------------ Also, if Congress persons were required to serve 20, 25 or 30 years (like everyone else) in order to collect retirement benefits, taxpayers could save a bundle. --------------------------------------- IF you are happy with Washington spends our taxes, be happy. Otherwise, it's time to "downsize" Congress. -------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- .Serving in Congress is an honor, not a career. The Founding Fathers envisioned citizen legislators, so ours should serve their term(s), then go home and back to work.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358187319094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 13:15:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358189970834-22</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Failure</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1358112008055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:20:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pay more taxes to USA problem! ARE YOU WILLING TO DO?</Msg><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1358189970834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 13:59:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358190755494-23</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Failure</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1358112008055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:20:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WASHINGTON CALLING, SEND MORE MONEY</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1358190755494</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 14:12:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358191036512-24</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Failure</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1358112008055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:20:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm willing to if they will cut spending in half and start to pay off the national debt. They haven't even had a budget for the past four years; but still they spend.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1358191036512</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 14:17:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358191796392-25</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans in Washington</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1358045743645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:55:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"decent white folks.." LOL The Brown Shirts were decent white folks too.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358191796392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 14:29:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358191994008-26</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid the new hero of the right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1357790625707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:03:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you have your own white country again who will do the work for you overweight rednecks?</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358191994008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 14:33:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358194838379-27</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Failure</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1358112008055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:20:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am willing to pay higher tax rates when the government gets serious about fiscal responsibility and quits playing political games with our nation’s economy. I don't want to hear anymore about a grand bargain or a deficit committee because no one on either side of the equation had any intentions of abiding by any of their suggestions. This is about power. The people that control the money have the power and both parties are after the power as their end game and their only goal past reelection. The Democrats have turned down all offers at cost reductions and are now saying they aren't through increasing taxes, but they still refuse to even discuss cost cuts. Much of that attitude was very apparent in the so-called Sandi Relief Bill. When the spending that was included in that fiasco was made public, every member of Congress who submitted the additional spending not related to Sandi should have been extremely embarrassed along with anyone member that was set to vote for it. The NJ governor was simply making political headlines because no one had talked about him for a few weeks. It is a sad joke. Obama now says he will not negotiate (which has typically been his stance) about the debt ceiling because we have to pay our bills. If we cut spending, increase revenue, and mind our spending habits with any measure of common sense and honesty, we can pay our bills. Since when does the President get to say he won't negotiate and he will do as he wishes? Congress creates, writes, and passes the laws of this country and he has the power to veto if he has the votes behind him to make it stand. Quit dictating and lead and govern, which I don't think he understand how. The economy is still, or should be the leading issue for this Congress and President, but now he says gun control and immigration are his first priorities. He can even make up his mind about his priorities. What a joke, a sad joke but still a sad excuse for leadrship all around.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358194838379</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 15:20:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358195189411-28</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like some people in Mexico understand that guns are not just for hunting</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358076072441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 06:21:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They *always* have the authority to prioritize the laws they execute " They get to prioritize the laws they will make as their primary focus in their law enforcement efforts, but when a law is broken, they don't get the right to choose to ignore the law and the violation of those same laws.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358195189411</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 15:26:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358197205092-29</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Failure</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1358112008055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:20:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must say "they " about 10 times in your post. Who is they?</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358197205092</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 16:00:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358198403780-30</Id><Topic><Title>Buying opportunity today?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357920668549</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 11:11:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep....another buying opportunity</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1358198403780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 16:20:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358199595979-31</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Failure</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1358112008055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:20:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read his first sentence. It's not that hard.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1358199595979</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 16:39:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358200181472-32</Id><Topic><Title>The clock is ticking</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1358186374410</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:59:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is a sad human being that has nothing more to be proud of than the color of his skin. You couldn't make yourself white but you can make yourself helpful. Your post is not helpful. try again!!!</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1358200181472</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 16:49:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358201320476-33</Id><Topic><Title>Buying opportunity today?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357920668549</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 11:11:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, so I goofed again. The March 34 calls are down to 90 cents and it looks like T is going lower. I originally thought in December that T would not take off until February because that is what happened last year. Now I am going back to that. The pattern this year looks very similar to January last year. I am not buying any more calls until T starts moving up as will be indicated by the Stochastic.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1358201320476</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 17:08:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358202408629-34</Id><Topic><Title>The 545 responsible</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1358182189536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 11:49:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I only wish the 545 were the only problem. We voted them into office over and over again and I see no cure for it in the future. We allow them to control our schools who train the teachers for the next generation. The only solution I see is wide spread home schooling over a very extended period of time. I doubt that it will happen.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1358202408629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 17:26:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358202795697-35</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Failure</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1358112008055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:20:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They", is anybody who has a part in taking the money which I (or you) loaned those buttheads at low, or no interest rates over the last 45 years. Much of this does fall on the Republican side, who I was foolish enough to think ("they") would do the right thing. "They" are the ones who are unwillng to compromise on the behalf of all of us. Fed, Dems, and GOP. 'They suck and should be removed ASAP. Obama needs to call Boehner, Reid, and McConnell into a padded room, with pencils and paper, and solve this favorably on behalf of us Americans, or they don't leave the room to even take a leak.</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1358202795697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 17:33:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358202810565-36</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Failure</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1358112008055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:20:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They" is US. We can blame Congress or we can change Congress. Much easier to blame. Just take the periods out of the subject line and you will have it right.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1358202810565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 17:33:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358203944318-37</Id><Title>Romney wins "Lie of the Year"</Title><Msg>In Romney's entry for lie of the year (as reported by PolitiFact on December 12, 2012) he claimed that the president had "sold chrysler to italians who were going to build jeeps in china" January 14, 2013, Chrysler CEO Sergio Marchionne announced that the automaker plans to build Jeeps in China and later in Russia Romney never had a chance "In your heart you know he is right" The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358203944318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 17:52:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358204044189-38</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid the new hero of the right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1357790625707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:03:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am afraid his sense is very common. He only reads the headlines and that is very common. Had he read the whole post he would learn there are 42 Presidents ahead of Obama and Carter.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1358204044189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 17:54:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358204380186-39</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (2)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357960284445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 22:11:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... Winholder view: “Corporate America does these types of cuts all the time. There's even a name for it. ‘Downsizing’." Romney view: “Bain Capital is an investment partnership which was formed to invest in startup companies and ongoing companies…and hopefully, five to eight years later, to harvest them at a significant profit.” Rick Perry view: (Bain) engages in vulture capitalism.” President Obama view: “If you’re head of a large equity firm or hedge fund, your job is to make money. It’s not to create jobs. It’s not even to create successful businesses. It’s to make sure you’re maximizing returns for your investor.” My view: Downsizing? Oh, you mean CANNIBALIZING? Union busting? Off shoring jobs? Americans’ view: 51% to an ironically embarrassing 47% And one last thing, winholder. When you post a lengthy piece that you had nothing whatsoever to do with creating, it’s absolutely pathetic that you don’t source it. Trying to make folks think you wrote “The Proposal”, which has appeared on numerous right wing websites since ’09 is most befitting of you.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1358204380186</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 17:59:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358205478706-40</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins "Lie of the Year"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358203944318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 17:52:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So rather than build them here and export them, our dear president will allow this? You liberals reap what you sow!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358205478706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 18:17:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358205845526-41</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S. military</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1358191647032</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 14:27:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why don't you put your gun where the sun don't shine.</Msg><Username>orri1934</Username><Timestamp>1358205845526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 18:24:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358211024141-42</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S. military</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1358191647032</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 14:27:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've stated before, you do not want to confront police or military. But, do go talk to your local "liberals" and show them the evil of their ways.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1358211024141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 19:50:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358219828258-43</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S. military</Title><Username>lavendersin</Username><Timestamp>1358191647032</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 14:27:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Yep, that`s my opinion" And what do you think that's worth?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358219828258</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 22:17:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358220576543-44</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins "Lie of the Year"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1358203944318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 17:52:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another cheap lie posted by Froggie. Yes Chrysler is building Jeeps in China. Romney claimed Jeep was going to shutdown factories in America and shift the jobs to China. Chrysler is hiring to build Jeeps in Detroit and expanding the Jeep brand into China. That's what they said they were going to do back in October when Romney lied the first time and that's what they are doing now. Romney wanted to let Detroit die. So did you, I suppose. Then we'd all be buying Chinese cars made in China. Jeep wouldn't exist. I guess that's one vision of what America is all about. I have a different vision.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358220576543</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 22:29:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358220869515-45</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid the new hero of the right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1357790625707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:03:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>!!! Wow! Look up, you might see something.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358220869515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 22:34:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358220955086-46</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid the new hero of the right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1357790625707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:03:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, this thread explains quite a bit.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358220955086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 22:35:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>