<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366443269503-1</Id><Title>Bought because of the Divy. Felt like a conservative move at the time for my 401K</Title><Msg>Got in with a 1000 shrs in March 2011 at $28.14. With my DRIPS, I now have about 1100 shrs worth a little over $42K. Not bad for a conservative investment. If your on the sidelines, don't be afraid to get in. Just providing a real life example as a public service.</Msg><Username>chops2191</Username><Timestamp>1366443269503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 03:34:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366467092251-2</Id><Topic><Title>Bought because of the Divy. Felt like a conservative move at the time for my 401K</Title><Username>chops2191</Username><Timestamp>1366443269503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 03:34:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wise decision.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366467092251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:11:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366476205147-3</Id><Topic><Title>Bought because of the Divy. Felt like a conservative move at the time for my 401K</Title><Username>chops2191</Username><Timestamp>1366443269503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 03:34:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've done the same thing over a longer period. I now have 6,200 shares I do this with other shares and mutual funds as well. So far I've been able to get by without drawing any down. DRIPPing is a good way to take guesswork out of your investing. I would plan on using it for no less than ten years.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1366476205147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:43:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366480014495-4</Id><Title>Tuesdays earnings report</Title><Msg>What do you guys who own the stock think will happen after the results are announced next week? VZ didn't have a gang-buster type report and picked up over 3 bucks a share and was still going strong after hours. None of the numbers i read showed improvement that warranted such a run-up, but it did skyrocket. The biggest thing seemed to be the 200 day moving average breakout. Other than that, it was decent at best. You trollers and clowns that are hung up on the NRA, Obama, politics, conspiracies, and all the other off-topic #$%$ you blab about, don't bother responding. I won't see it and sensible investors aren't interested in your opinions either.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366480014495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:46:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366485759930-5</Id><Topic><Title>Tuesdays earnings report</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366480014495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:46:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think new money is targeting telecoms. T and VZ are top picks. It's the dividend and the stability. Telecoms are best growth story any market, any country. T runs the biggest weekly payroll in US, has largest fleet of service vehicles--and they are currently buying back three million shares after doing the same last year. People are waking up. Why trade the market when there's a buy and hold like T.</Msg><Username>bambusario</Username><Timestamp>1366485759930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 15:22:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366485944920-6</Id><Topic><Title>Tuesdays earnings report</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366480014495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:46:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: They are currently buying back THREE HUNDRED million shares.</Msg><Username>bambusario</Username><Timestamp>1366485944920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 15:25:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>