<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357830150627-1</Id><Topic><Title>They remove some of these crackpot posts before one can respond...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357740395747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:06:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jon, you seem to think you live in a tyranny of the tantrum. You don't. You live in democratic republic with a Constitution. No matter how many tantrums you and Alex Jones throw, you don't get to decide unilaterally whether assault rifles are legal. Just like you don't get to decide what caliber firearms are legal, or whether fully automatic guns are legal and whether or not you can keep a howitzer in your back yard pointing at the neighbors house. We are not going to live in a society run by the paranoid and the senile.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357830150627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 10:02:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357831247740-2</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid the new hero of the right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1357790625707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:03:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The puks are sucking on "ripple" tea bags.</Msg><Username>orri1934</Username><Timestamp>1357831247740</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 10:20:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357832105030-3</Id><Topic><Title>45 cent dividend; 65 cent drop</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357662643665</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:30:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what's keeping "T" down, should we not be moving up already?</Msg><Username>dynnyd</Username><Timestamp>1357832105030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 10:35:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357832349194-4</Id><Topic><Title>They remove some of these crackpot posts before one can respond...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357740395747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:06:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We all ready live in a society of the paranoid and the senile. Look at the ages and the actions of the Congress of these United States of America. They are the source of the majority of our problems and certainly of our recent rage of 'crises'. The biggest problem seems to be they understand how to define the results of their actions as a crisis, but haven’t quite figured out the successful management of those same crises. The media and many posters are inaccurate in their assumptions that these ‘solutions’ are knee jerk reactions to the latest crisis; these are well planned reactions to create the style and breath of government our current President envisions as the ‘change’ he wants.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1357832349194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 10:39:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357833514125-5</Id><Topic><Title>They remove some of these crackpot posts before one can respond...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357740395747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:06:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We need a law that allows Congress to meet only one week every quarter and limits the size of any law proposed to one legal size page. The KISS system (Keep It Simple, I'm Stupid).</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357833514125</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 10:58:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357834236353-6</Id><Topic><Title>They remove some of these crackpot posts before one can respond...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357740395747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:06:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"limits the size of any law proposed to one legal size page" Great. They'll pass 500,000 laws a session.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357834236353</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 11:10:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357834737657-7</Id><Title>BUY NOW FOR 50 TARGET!!</Title><Msg>full steam ahead and sweet dividend!!</Msg><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1357834737657</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 11:18:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357835024224-8</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid the new hero of the right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1357790625707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:03:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, it does not, Frogg. The law does prohibit insurance companies from denying insurance based on firearm ownership or from charging higher premiums based on firearms ownership. Firearm ownership is treated like a pre-existing condition. Which means the PPACA guarantees we all have to pay for the actuarially important probability that you're going to accidentally shoot yourself or one of your kids. There is another section that (quite inexplicably) prohibits prevention and wellness programs from collecting information on gun ownership as part of their quality control activities.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357835024224</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 11:23:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357835741353-9</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky Response</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1357504498552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 15:34:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"In my view, extending the benefit ages would have been more economy neutral." Of course you do. But not for those age 55 and older, right? Just your kids &amp; grandkids. What I would like to do is make such an extension apply to all, including current retirees. We'll just make you go for three or five years without benefits starting today, since you all utterly failed to pay for your benefits AND loaded us all up with debt. Me? I'm quite willing to pay it forward. The payroll tax cut was temporary and needs to expire. What gets me is the utter hypocrisy of people like you. You are what I think you are. You want to maximize your own government benefits and minimize your own contribution. You want to tax working people, and keep your unearned income untaxed (0% even!). You'll put as much burden on others as you can, including your children and grandchildren. There's nothing special about you. You're all too typical. You're a taker. You've just taken more than most.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357835741353</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 11:35:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357836462603-10</Id><Topic><Title>More Obamanomic Results</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1357396765440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 09:39:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Who is trying to cut productive government work?" I don't really have much interest in discussing whether this or that program is good use of public resources. Any enterprise, including government and business, needs it's share of failures if it is going to evolve. I say productive government work as opposed to transfer payments, particular ly transfer payments to non-productive persons. Investments in infrastructure, human capital, R&amp;D, and a safety net to facilitate the labor market are productive. What we can't do is think the entire purpose of the government is to support a lavish lifestyle for retirees. If you saved for retirement, great! If you didn't, you get the basics. What has happened is that boomers have created a huge unfunded liability for themselves and thrown a massive debt on top of it, and they expect their children to bear this burden--both through taxes on themselves and by. Your good with finances, Wilkes. I'm sure you can look at the Federal budget and see where there's ample fat available for trimming. It's not the Department of Energy that is eating up the budget.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357836462603</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 11:47:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357836711033-11</Id><Topic><Title>More Obamanomic Results</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1357396765440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 09:39:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're comparing the duly elected President of the United States to a petty dictator like Kim Jung Un? Why don't you go to N. Korea? Then maybe you'll see a difference.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357836711033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 11:51:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357836752500-12</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Had It "HALF RIGHT" !!</Title><Username>jon3retired</Username><Timestamp>1357836109009</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 11:41:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Their called Obamunists.</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1357836752500</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 11:52:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357836856362-13</Id><Topic><Title>More Obamanomic Results</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1357396765440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 09:39:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Bingo! THANKS! " You're welcome. Clearly, smaller government and excessively low taxes have not led to job growth.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357836856362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 11:54:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357838829055-14</Id><Topic><Title>More Obamanomic Results</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1357396765440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 09:39:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There is a lack of demand because there are still so many out of work." That is one reason. Wages for middle class workers are stagnant or declining as well. Too much wealth is concentrated in the investing class. Bernanke referred to it as the global savings glut. "The fiscal cliff bill raised taxes on everyone and increased our debt even more" No, it absolutely did not raise our debt. It shrank the deficit. "You can talk of grand bargains all you want but the Democrats have flat refused to have any meaningful discussion about cost reductions as has the President." That is clearly untrue. They have put multiple offers on the table for meaningful cuts. Romney attacked Obama for the $740 billion in savings he found in Medicare. It was Republicans who refused to specify the cuts they wanted, and it was Boehner who could not get even his own bill past the Tea Party. I don't know how much more evidence that could be produced to show where the sticking point is here. But then again, I don't know how much more evidence could be produced to show Obama was born in Hawaii but you don't believe that early. I also don't know why the rank and file persist with the myth that Republicans lower spending. You had six years of complete government control by Republicans and they raised spending in every facet of government--food stamps, Medicare Part D, defense. And not just small increases, large ones. Medicare Part D was the largest expansion in Medicare since its inception. Why on earth you would think Republicans are interested in spending cuts or low deficits is beyond me. There is simply no evidence for that. They have never cared about spending cuts or running a deficit. There is plenty of rhetoric, but when the rubber hits the road they care about low taxes for the wealthy and that's it. "Obama just changed the way people have to respond in order to get visas for trailing family members without even consulting Congress, he simply changed the way the government will follow or not follow the existing laws. The man is working toward a dictatorship and no that he has been reelected; he isn't even being subtle about it." The executive branch always has latitude in deciding how laws are implemented and what the priorities are. I would be quite willing to discuss the overuse of executive orders and executive privilege. But that is something that was begun during the Bush administration. Remember Cheney's theory of the unitary executive? Look it up. Obama has embraced it to a degree. But as long as we have a dysfunctional Congress that gives undue power to a stonewalling minority of the minority, the president will have to take executive action. This is a bad precedent to set but it is a problem of American democracy--not a problem of Obama. In February Obama will be faced with the choice of paying for what Congress decided to spend or letting the Tea Party unilaterally decide what Congress will spend and what our tax policy will be. I imagine, and I hope, that he will continue to pay our bills even if the Tea Party decides to try to use the debt ceiling as a gun to the nation's head. It is a much worse precedent to let the minority of the minority hijack the government. And the fact is, if the Congress has passed two contradictory laws, it is the role of the president to decide which one to implement. He has to either pay for the stuff Congress has directed him to pay for or abide by the debt ceiling. He cannot do both.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357838829055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 12:27:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357839039833-15</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky Response</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1357504498552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 15:34:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's great, Jon. Maybe I'll try that. Stop paying all but one of my bills and when the creditors come point out that I paid one of them. Pay for your stuff, Jon. ALL of your stuff.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357839039833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 12:30:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357839175421-16</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky Response</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1357504498552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 15:34:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What I'm getting from S.S. is Only what I've paid in... with no interest!!" You are 100% full of #$%$. You are an idiot. You have no idea how the system works.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1357839175421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 12:32:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357839406166-17</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid the new hero of the right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1357790625707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:03:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jon, there is nothing in the PPACA that says "the government," nor any segment thereof, can or cannot collect information on gun ownership. Clearly, some governments (local and state) do collect this information in the permitting process. The Federal government IS prohibited from collecting information on gun ownership. But it is not through the PPACA. This is just another lie spread by hacks and posted here by Froggie.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357839406166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 12:36:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357839909062-18</Id><Title>Will NOK and RIMM come back strong in 2013 and 2014 ??</Title><Msg>I have feeling they will be back</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357839909062</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 12:45:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357839912424-19</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky Response</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1357504498552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 15:34:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't preach to me. Tell it to your buddies, Nancy and Harry. They don't have the guts to tackle the issue. I'm sure not holding them up.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1357839912424</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 12:45:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357840216734-20</Id><Title>And a fine time was had by all...</Title><Msg>... Little Feat Invites You Down Into the Basement for a Good-time Jam (review) Chuck Yarbourough, Cleveland Plain Dealer, Jan. 12th 11:42 a.m. “Picture yourself in your basement, listening to a bunch of your old high school and college buddies jam and sharing a few brews and, um, whatever. The guys with the instruments are having a blast, and the friends who tagged along for the impromptu party are having even more fun. Now just imagine if those guys on the guitars, keyboards, bass, drums and percussion were really, REALLY good. Like, scary good. Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to a Little Feat show. The six guys in the band -- keyboardist Billy Payne, guitarist-mandolinist-trumpeter Fred Tackett, guitarist Paul Barrere, percussionist Sam Clayton, bassist Kenny Gradney and drummer Gabe Ford – invited a sold-out Kent Stage into their basement Wednesday night. For two hours, the guys dug out the old hits, like “Church Going Down,’’ with some chill vocals by Tackett, aided by killer harmonies from Payne, Barrere and Clayton, and showcased songs off their new CD, “Rooster Rag,’’ including the title cut. How much of a jam was it? Well, the band’s biggest hit, “Dixie Chicken,’’ took almost half an hour, interspersed with solos from each of the players. And when we say solos, we mean solos. Only drummer Ford, who got started with the band as the tech for original drummer , the late Richie Hayward, never left the stage. In some ways, neither did another missing member, co-founder Lowell George, who died of heart failure at the age of 34 in 1979. A multi-instrumentalist known for his slide guitar, George was the co-writer of “Dixie Chicken.’’ Barrere took the slide parts and lead vocals in the song Wednesday night, but it was as if George’s ghost was singing harmony. The band is full of crackerjack musicians, including Payne, who doesn’t get nearly the credit he deserves for his keyboard work. His lush arpeggios throughout the night – and especially on “Rag Top Down,’’ off the new CD -- were equal to any at a Van Cliburn piano competition. Gradney’s shifting between slap and finger-picking bass added a layer of diversity to a set list that ranged from island-feel tunes like “My Juanita’’ to the down-and-dirty blues of “Spanish Moon.’’ Of course, the jazzy jams just had to include “Don’t Bogart That Joint,’’ and added to the party atmosphere. Both Barrere and Tackett sported guitar straps with the signature “leaf’’ on them, and Barrere joked that his “license’’ for what cops call “a green leafy substance,’’ while good in Oregon and Washington, is useless in Ohio. The Buckeye state still bans the use of both medical and medicinal marijuana. Little Feat had a lot of help from a crowd that SEEMED to have some experience in the practice. About the only thing missing in the smoke-free Kent Stage was a pungent cloud. As a result, everybody left the basement with a nice contact high, even it was just musically induced.”</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357840216734</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 12:50:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357840889536-21</Id><Topic><Title>45 cent dividend; 65 cent drop</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357662643665</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:30:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>T is up 20 cents from yesterday's close. The Stochastic is moving down but that is based on past performance. Trading has been above the 50 DMA all of this year after trading below it since early October of last year. We may not reach $40 until August or September, but I think we are on our way. The after dividend drop is almost over. Of course there will be pull backs along the way.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357840889536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 13:01:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357842432121-22</Id><Topic><Title>And a fine time was had by all...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357840216734</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 12:50:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What has that got to do with the price of AT&amp;T stock? Where they all calling their friends on their cell phones?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357842432121</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 13:27:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357848155760-23</Id><Topic><Title>They remove some of these crackpot posts before one can respond...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357740395747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:06:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “Another previous (sic) case .. an armed intruder entered a school and started shooting. The wounded assistant principle ran to his vehicle, grabbed his rifle, returned to the school and shot the intruder !!” jon You’re probably referring to the case in Mississippi in the late 90’s. The AP was not wounded and he grabbed a pistol out of his car, not a rifle. And he had the pistol on school property in violation of the law. The student involved used a lever action deer rifle, with limited firing capacity. He managed to kill two and wound seven. He had left the building and was in his car when he was apprehended by the AP. Students today are well versed in reactions to these situations. They know the difference between hard lockdown and soft lockdown, and many schools can now monitor all areas of the school with video. Thus the progress of an intruder can be monitored, and the kids are trained to get out if they can or barricade themselves where possible. The big difference today is that they no longer are told to lie down, be docile and die. They are told when the inevitability of their demise is in front of them, to attack, in force, with everything possible. The shooter you mentioned (with a lever action that probably made him reload every three shots or so) probably could have been overwhelmed, as could someone with even a fully auto when he changes mags. You must remember, jon…it’s kinda like when the basketball team pantsed you in the locker room, gave you a wedgie and threw you into the Home Ec room in your shorts. Until very recently, in nearly all sane areas of this country, schools were designated as gun-free zones, meaning guns were not allowed anywhere on or near school premises...by anyone, students or faculty alike. Granted, in some areas with gun nuts like you (Texas, Georgia, among others) they are looking at changing some of those restrictions. Obviously, those who know anything about education are not in favor of letting you cowboys take over (But then again, you think the Dept. Of Ed. and the NEA are a Communist plot, so this won’t matter to you. I’d say guns should be welcomed in certain places of education – the trailer parks where you hillbillies home school your mutant offspring. I have no problem with well trained and armed security people on a campus if the district so chooses. But glamorizing Ramboesque tales as you do, does little to address the problem, and suggesting that teachers carry weapons onto school is downright goofy. 12/24/12 PE dot co Teachers: “Keep Guns out of Educators Hands” “National Education Association President Dennis Van Roekel and American Federation of Teachers President Randi Weingarten say they want no part of teachers being armed with weapons as a means to prevent tragedies such as the Dec. 14 shootings of 26 people at an elementary school in Connecticut…’Guns have no place in our schools. Period’.” And this in Indiana: An Indiana state law that makes schools gun-free zones exempts anyone who has been employed or authorized by a school “to act as a security guard…” School safety consultant Chuck Hibbert, a former Indiana state trooper, said, “I guess theoretically, the school district could designate everyone (as security officers) if they wanted to be that crazy…arming teachers could have serious consequences. For example, where would a teacher keep a gun — in his or her desk or in a holster? What if the teacher had to break up a fight? A student might be able to take the gun away. And if a gun is fired, where should the teacher aim to avoid a stray bullet hitting someone?” “I don’t think that proliferation of firearms on school property is good for kids,” said Nate Schnellenberger, president of the Indiana State Teachers Association. But jon thinks it makes good sense...so that should be the kiss of death for that lame idea. Hey, jon, how about introducing legislation that requires every teacher, administrator, custodian, cafeteria worker and bus drivers to carry a Louisville Slugger at all times? BTW, have your bat statistics shown up yet? We’re still waiting. Your bat stats are as bogus as Barry Bonds’. Hey, is that a gun in your pocket or are you just telling more potatoes in your underwear stories?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357848155760</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 15:02:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357851194809-24</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky Response</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1357504498552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 15:34:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And that, folks, is how you completely miss a point.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357851194809</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 15:53:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357852538629-25</Id><Topic><Title>A Georgia mom hides her kids and shoots an intruder 5 times</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1357517052024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 19:04:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The bans (aka tight policies) only apply to "law-biding citizens"" No Jon. The bans apply to everyone.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357852538629</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 16:15:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357853460802-26</Id><Topic><Title>US shipping crude to Canada</Title><Username>windyfrostt</Username><Timestamp>1357440784340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 21:53:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gasoline companies don't tend to build new refineries, they expand and upgrade existing refineries and refining capacity has grown over the years. If refining capacity was the bottleneck then the price of oil would have little affect on the price of gas. Clearly that's not the case. The "new" refineries you refer to in PA are oil refineries that are being converted to handle natural gas from the Marcellus Shale. They will make propane and ethane, not gasoline.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1357853460802</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 16:31:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357854874741-27</Id><Topic><Title>Give them hell CWA</Title><Username>wilson-timothy8303</Username><Timestamp>1357335893073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 16:44:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Purge the the unions and replace them with young, smart college kids that want to work and not #$%$ about how bad their jobs are......pretty sure they could be trained in 4-6 weeks....</Msg><Username>ugabulldog4u</Username><Timestamp>1357854874741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 16:54:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357856580806-28</Id><Topic><Title>Ricky Response</Title><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1357504498552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 15:34:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you think you are getting from SS only what you paid in, you have no idea how the system works or what you paid in. Even by compounding, most people have gotten out more they paid in by age 77. My father-in-law is 92 and retired at 62. Even with compounding he had taken more than his share by about age 73. My Mother , who is 93, and did not begin working until she was about 45, had taken hers by age 75. There are many folks who get disability at 45 or 50 and are a huge drain on the system. They pull out of the fund too. Go back to day one for yourself and see what you paid in, use a compounding factor and tell us what you now have in your account. It is virtually impossible to have have anything left after age 83 if you live that long. SS is a combination of an annuity/ savings plan/insurance policy.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1357856580806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 17:23:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357858415223-29</Id><Topic><Title>Give them hell CWA</Title><Username>wilson-timothy8303</Username><Timestamp>1357335893073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 16:44:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've a better idea. Vote the CWA out and sell the company to the employees. Each employee gets stock in the company and pays for it with the payroll deduction that formerly went to the Union.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1357858415223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 17:53:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357860009672-30</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid the new hero of the right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1357790625707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:03:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>H.R. 3590---767 ‘‘(c) PROTECTION OF SECOND AMENDMENT GUN RIGHTS.— ‘‘(1) WELLNESS AND PREVENTION PROGRAMS.—A wellness and health promotion activity implemented under subsection (a)(1)(D) may not require the disclosure or collection of any information relating to— ‘‘(A) the presence or storage of a lawfully-possessed firearm or ammunition in the residence or on the property of an individual; or ‘‘(B) the lawful use, possession, or storage of a firearm or ammunition by an individual. ‘‘(2) LIMITATION ON DATA COLLECTION.—None of the authorities provided to the Secretary under the Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act or an amendment made by that Act shall be construed to authorize or may be used for the collection of any information relating to— ‘‘(A) the lawful ownership or possession of a firearm or ammunition; ‘‘(B) the lawful use of a firearm or ammunition; or ‘‘(C) the lawful storage of a firearm or ammunition. This is what I found. "In your heart you know he is right" The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1357860009672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 18:20:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357860700856-31</Id><Topic><Title>And a fine time was had by all...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357840216734</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 12:50:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “Let me ask the audience…” What is this…The Price is Right? “…or is he in his mid-sixties doing this.” – pistolpackinjon Hey, Goofy. Most of the guys in the band are around my age, and some older – the people in the audience, comparable, although Little Feat brings out everyone who knows music, unlike you. But, get serious, son. Your favorites are aging, as well. David Cassidy will turn 63 soon. Wayne Newton is almost 71, although he doesn’t look a day over 108. Even Donnie Osmond is pushin’ 60. Pat Boone is archaic, and a spokesman for your pals. I bet you are a big Abba fan. They’re almost 70. Who’s the last concert you saw? The Backstreet Boys? Milli Vanilli? (P.S. R&amp;R in Bangkok, March, 66)</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1357860700856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 18:31:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357866944436-32</Id><Topic><Title>Give them hell CWA</Title><Username>wilson-timothy8303</Username><Timestamp>1357335893073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 16:44:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome idea....</Msg><Username>ugabulldog4u</Username><Timestamp>1357866944436</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 20:15:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>