<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-23"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361618227807-1</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was you traitors called republicans that had no problem cutting funding for embassies and consulates. HYPOCRITES!</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361618227807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 06:17:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361618575264-2</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe there is some hope for the good people of Chicago</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361595142569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 23:52:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey fagyes, gets a little expensive to get your kids to make comments, doesn't it? Is that the only way they make their allowance? Hopefully they won't be tainted for life with your hatred.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361618575264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 06:22:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361618896767-3</Id><Topic><Title>How's that good old liberal tolerance working for you?</Title><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1361562557529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:49:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These reich-wing clowns have many ID's. That's typical of a lowlife republican, has to cheat to win. Where were these a**holes when Bush was destroying this country?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361618896767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 06:28:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361619207914-4</Id><Topic><Title>Randall to appear on CNBC, Monday, Fewbruary 25th, 6:00am EST</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1361563279430</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:01:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's going to apologize for losing 4 billion dollars on the TMobile deal.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361619207914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 06:33:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361622206363-5</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And as difficult as it has been for you Tea Baggers to accept an African American in the White House, you better get used to being unhappy for quite some time…because that “gal” that you knuckle-dragging, chauvinistic, ignorant pawns of Wall Street despise, is probably going to be your President until over a decade from now. Maybe you guys should all secede together, move to South Africa with all your guns and intolerance, and start a new apartheid colony. Ah, the race card again. I don't dislike Obama as President because he is black, but because he is a dishonest, liberal socialist with a demented ideaology. I thought Hillary was the better choice when they ran against each other...not a good choice but a better choice than Obama. When you racist clowns get over the fact that he is simply a poor leader, perhaps you might see the forest for the trees.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361622206363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 07:23:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361622809877-6</Id><Topic><Title>After Hours Quotes...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361586860760</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 21:34:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Wants To Be Next Pope WASHINGTON, DC - Sources close to the White House have learned that Barack Obama is planning to run for the office of Pope when the College of Cardinals convenes to elect a successor to ailing Benedict XVI at the end of this month. Calling on the promise of Equality for All, Obama is said to firmly believe that the time has come for a non-Catholic to occupy the Vatican's highest office. Foreseeing a looming citizenship issue he states that he has discovered an Italian birth certificate that proves he was born in Rome before he was born in Kenya. "That Hawaiian birth certificate never has been worth what I paid for it anyway", he noted. Continuing, he concluded, "And there's no way that a handful of cardinals could be more expensive to buy than 10 million voters in Michigan." Further questions should be directed to Obama's Papal Campaign Manager, Abdul Azeem Khan.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361622809877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 07:33:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361625594937-7</Id><Title>Republican Accomplishments</Title><Msg>From New Yorker Magazine: Republicans inherited a surplus from Clinton. Republicans started 2 wars and cut taxes for the first time in recorded human history. Republicans gave out huge taxcuts with not only no government cuts but huge expansion When Treasury Sec Paul Oneill warned of huge debt he was fired. with Cheney saying, "You know, Paul, Reagan proved deficits don't matter." Bush Fired anouther top economic adavisor Larry Lindsey for Saying the War Might Cost $100 Billion a low ball estimate Republicans created the huge boondoggle comically redundant "Homeland Security" Republicans passed Medicare Part D with no cost controls and ompletely unfinded Republicans allowed the too big to fail banks defraud the world and bring US to the brink of another great Depression Bush and Paulson threatened congress with martial law in the US and a world wide depression if they didnt sign TARP Paulson Former CEO of Goldman Sacs not only gave Goldmans the lions share of TARP but put them in charge it. Republicans are not only dishonest ,delusional and hypocritical to a depraved degree they seem to be constitutionally incapable of honesty.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361625594937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:19:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361625874131-8</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361586853080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 21:34:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you a Democrat, a Republican, or a Southerner? Here is a little test that will help you decide. The answer can be found by posing the following question: You're walking down a deserted street with your wife and two small children. Suddenly, a Terrorist with a huge knife comes around the corner, locks eyes with you, screams obscenities, raises the knife, and charges at you... You are carrying a Kimber 1911 cal. 45 ACP, and you are an expert shot. You have mere seconds before he reaches you and your family. What do you do? THINK CAREFULLY AND THEN SCROLL DOWN: Democrat's Answer: • Well, that's not enough information to answer the question! • What is a Kimber 1911 cal. 45 ACP? • Does the man look poor or oppressed? • Is he really a terrorist? Am I guilty of profiling? • Have I ever done anything to him that would inspire him to attack? • Could we run away? • What does my wife think? • What about the kids? • Could I possibly swing the gun like a club and knock the knife out of his hand? • What does the law say about this situation? • Does the pistol have appropriate safety built into it? • Why am I carrying a loaded gun anyway, and what kind of message does this send to society and to my children? • Is it possible he'd be happy with just killing me? • Does he definitely want to kill me, or would he be content just to wound me? • If I were to grab his knees and hold on, could my family get away while he was stabbing me? • Should I call 9-1-1? • Why is this street so deserted? • We need to raise taxes, have paint &amp; weed day. • Can we make this a happier, healthier street that would discourage such behavior. • I need to debate this with some friends for a few days and try to come to a consensus. • This is all so confusing! ............ ......... ......... ......... ......... ......... ......... ......... ... Republican's Answer: BANG! ............ ......... ......... ......... ......... ......... ......... ...... Southerner's Answer: BANG! BANG! BANG! BANG! BANG! BANG! BANG! BANG! BANG ! BANG! BANG! BANG! Click..... (Sounds of reloading) BANG! BANG! BANG! BANG! BANG! BANG! BANG! BANG! BANG! Click Daughter: 'Nice grouping, Daddy!' 'Were those the Winchester Silver Tips or Hollow Points?! Son: 'Can I shoot the next one?!' Wife: 'You are NOT taking that to a Taxidermist!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361625874131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:24:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361626017779-9</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (final)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361586853080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 21:34:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What was your answer, ricky?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361626017779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:26:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361627147703-10</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Accomplishments</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361625594937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:19:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And obama and the democrats are too stupid to learn from that!!</Msg><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1361627147703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:45:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361629289612-11</Id><Title>Go Long Bottom!</Title><Msg>I really appreciate the quality of thought that goes into there analysis and the results this site is getting for us! I've been watching the market closely now that I'm retired and I now understand how difficult it is to predict, even at the broad ETF level, especially at this particular point in time. The analysis they provide has been extremely helpful and maybe it can help you. copy and paste and put info this link EXPERT-ANALYST</Msg><Username>robinhenry939</Username><Timestamp>1361629289612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 09:21:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361634707000-12</Id><Topic><Title>How's that good old liberal tolerance working for you?</Title><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1361562557529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:49:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Hey, did you see Marco Rubio at the State of the Union response doing his ventriloquist act last week? " Yep, I saw it and will note that Rubio's encounter with water didn't kill a young lady.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1361634707000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 10:51:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361636001777-13</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Best put on your flak jacket, you are about to be called a lot of names.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1361636001777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 11:13:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361639330812-14</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spelling corrections for the new guy.You don't change! I told you last time that you were block and you believed me. Your dumber than dirt. This is not a English class it's a message board.You don't remember me from about 6 months ago, your memory is as long as your pecker.You sit behind your computer and insult these good people because you have nothing to contribute. You have no social skills or manners.If you had the balls to insult me to my face i will knock you on your #$%$.</Msg><Username>ls3487</Username><Timestamp>1361639330812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:08:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361639383440-15</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe there is some hope for the good people of Chicago</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361595142569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 23:52:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another profound statement from someone who is obviously one of the party's most inspiring and learned thinkers. Thank you for your love and support. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361639383440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:09:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361646120079-16</Id><Title>Pres Obama's name will be in the history books forever, children will study his words and discuss early 21st century America. When an African American President was elected two terms to office by the people.</Title><Msg>While we have an hours time in the limelight on a T message board, forgotton the next day.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1361646120079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 14:02:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361652449224-17</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe there is some hope for the good people of Chicago</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361595142569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 23:52:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fagyes and zombie89, same person. Must get old answering your own comments.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361652449224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 15:47:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361652634800-18</Id><Topic><Title>Pres Obama's name will be in the history books forever, children will study his words and discuss early 21st century America. When an African American President was elected two terms to office by the people.</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1361646120079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 14:02:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like Dubya that lied this country into war and did not pay for it. The first President to cut taxes when we were at war. George W Bush the worst President in history.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361652634800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 15:50:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361657323754-19</Id><Topic><Title>Pres Obama's name will be in the history books forever, children will study his words and discuss early 21st century America. When an African American President was elected two terms to office by the people.</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1361646120079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 14:02:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"YES HE WILL" "Yes we can" Obama is rapidly becoming one of the most beloved of Presidents. Not in your circles, but to the majority of the People. His name and words will be studied for generations. Ours will fade away after leaving page one of this backwater message board. He will NEVER be known as the king of smoke and mirrors and unethical, because, well, it's not true. The opposite is true, and the majority know it.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1361657323754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 17:08:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361657874484-20</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It may appear to be an Obama design but it is not. The change in the design didn't cost taxpayers a cent.</Msg><Username>carolharold123</Username><Timestamp>1361657874484</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 17:17:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361663181138-21</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pres has no idea this exists. He is way above this, his words will live on forever, yours are about to disappear forever on page two. I like it like that. Your efforts to bash him are of no consequence. Yiour audience here is a half dozen bored people who want to burn time rather than do some chore.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1361663181138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 18:46:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361668130420-22</Id><Topic><Title>Universal Orlando dropping health coverage for workers over ObamaCare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1361386388575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Low information voters are allowing the Dem Socialist party, to destroy the world's greatest healthcare system. Does Sandra Fluck know what Obami just did to women? She got flocked. I'm hearing they want to do pap smears once, every five years. The way some gals sleep around these days, cervical cancer will skyrocket. Should have read that bill. Oh well.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1361668130420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 20:08:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361668806726-23</Id><Topic><Title>Universal Orlando dropping health coverage for workers over ObamaCare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1361386388575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One reason a family health plan will cost 20 plus k in 2013, ( and still only cover 60% of your cost), is that with all the illegals, we now have to pay for translators for anyone not willing to speak English. One Spanish youg man called into a talk show I was listening to. He complained that the hospital said it was no longer necessary that he come to the Doctor with his Mom. Why, under Obamacare everyone gets a translator. They were basically saying, by showing up, he wasn't following the plan. Obamacare will destroy our healthcare with red tape. I'm seeing more cars running around with Obami stickers on them. What are these people smoking?</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1361668806726</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 20:20:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361669959552-24</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe there is some hope for the good people of Chicago</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361595142569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 23:52:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not really, jon3retired but I personally am very flattered that you are spending so much time thinking about me in your own little (and by "little", I mean "tiny") sexy way.</Msg><Username>renfrewterwi11iger</Username><Timestamp>1361669959552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 20:39:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361681864258-25</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Accomplishments</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361625594937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:19:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We all saw how dishonest they were in the last election, especially that candidate they had. They give tax deductions to companies for the costs of taking work to china, while claiming the govt spends too much on seniors and poor people. Romney prospered very well on that govt handout loophole. Thank God the majority of us weren't fooled like the ones we see on here posting garbage about Obama 24/7. As if it means anything, they are so ignorant they can't see their own stupidity. The more they bash Obama the more likely they will lose upcoming elections. It's like they can't turn the spigot off already that's flooding the house.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1361681864258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 23:57:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>