<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368677133211-1</Id><Topic><Title>THIS STOCK IS DONE FOR THE YEAR GOING TO 35 LOWER IF ANOTHER BAD REPORT IAM OUT !!!</Title><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1368544473830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:14:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you think T and VZ are not trading in tandem with each other, look at the five big trades just before 3 PM today. Each was at the same time and they traded about 3 times as many shares of T as they did VZ. Each of the five were about 900,000 shares of T and nearly 300,000 of VZ</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368677133211</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 00:05:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368677890608-2</Id><Topic><Title>IRS Black Ops unit of Obama SS attacks conservatives.</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1368633032316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:50:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congress passes the laws that the IRS enforces. One of the laws is that Political contributions are not deductible so why are we criticizing the IRS for not giving 501(c)4 status to the T-Party. Are they not Political? I think all this is a smoke screen that Obama hopes will take some heat off of Benghazi.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368677890608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 00:18:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368678517758-3</Id><Topic><Title>IRS Black Ops unit of Obama SS attacks conservatives.</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1368633032316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:50:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You bring up an excellent point. Union dues are deductible even though they are VERY political. Many of the IRS regulations are subject to interpretation making it very difficult to administer. We would do well to throw income tax out and replace it with a Federal Sales Tax collected by the states and passed on to the federal government provided the federal government is operating within the federal constitution.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368678517758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 00:28:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368706849634-4</Id><Topic><Title>Tea party, right wing extreme, GOP congress, etc's defintion of proof</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368209230720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The IRS did not target conservative or patriotic groups. They targeted groups that put "Tea Party" or "Patriot" in their name because, apparently, those groups tend to commit tax fraud". Looks more like IRS tax "investigation" fraud given the acting IRS director "resigned" just 4 days after the you know what hit the fan..</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1368706849634</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 08:20:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368708636942-5</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“To see someone call Benghazi a lie and pretend Iraq wasn't is simply mind-boggling…” Would you expect anything less from the folks who wanted everyone to believe that Oliver North was trading arms for hostages with arch-enemy Iran to fund an unconstitutional war in Central America (thus violating the Boland Amendment) while destroying documents and banging Fawn Hall in the basement of the White House, all supposedly unbeknownst to the man upstairs who was just eating jelly beans, napping or being advised by his wife’s astrologer? Fourteen indictments and eleven convictions later, the next President, who was Vice President at the time but also claimed to be “out of the loop”, having just been defeated in his re-election bid, somehow found justification in granting pardons to this band of traitors. But Benghazi is on scale with starting illegal wars? How many forget that The International Court of Justice ruled that during Iran-Contra The United States had violated international law in 16 decisions, including encouraging human rights violations in Nicaragua? You people are so obviously desperate that you continue to make comedic spectacles of yourselves at every opportunity. There are serious issues facing this country that the majority of citizens would like to see continue to be addressed by the President they elected. Continuing with your “obstruct any and everything” for political gain with high-school-dropout-car-thieves- turned- millionaires like Darrell Issa leading the way, will most certainly backfire in the ‘14 elections. But you also lately have done nothing to convince anybody that you learn anything from your mistakes. So keep at it.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1368708636942</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368708763688-6</Id><Title>Wow, heard there is a massive promo coming to MISM</Title><Msg>Hearing a rumor that MISM is about to get pumped</Msg><Username>jeremiah.boone3475</Username><Timestamp>1368708763688</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 08:52:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368708786086-7</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think it is more a matter of many of us are living in the now.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1368708786086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 08:53:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368709026723-8</Id><Topic><Title>The frog and the scorpion</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368654675412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 17:51:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...It would appear to me that the real moral of the story is simply that frogs, by and large, are overwhelmingly gullible, naive and stupid creatures. Your posts repeatedly confirm that. In our hearts, we know that’s right.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1368709026723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 08:57:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368709439918-9</Id><Topic><Title>The frog and the scorpion</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368654675412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 17:51:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yet another in a long string of "highroad" responses. When all else fails, call people names.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1368709439918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 09:03:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368709711395-10</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...Is living in the now spending all day posting lies on message boards with multiple aliases? It would appear to me that your version of living in the now is judging others while conveniently forgetting about vastly far worse transgressions against humanity. Yellow cake uranium is living in the now for the familes of the many thousands of Americans who lost their lives based on lies.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1368709711395</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 09:08:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368709971640-11</Id><Topic><Title>IRS Black Ops unit of Obama SS attacks conservatives.</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1368633032316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:50:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem was they specifically targeted these groups for extra scrutiny and not other political groups. Additionally the issue here is whether the groups would have to disclose their donors or not, not whether they would get a tax deduction--it is campaign finance law not tax law. My feeling is that the 501(c)4 category should not exist at all, or should still require donor disclosure. Of course, that is only the tip of the iceberg on what I think about campaign finance reform. Of course, fake ricky's comments are what I have come to expect from self-described conservatives these days. Outlandish and incendiary. This is why you people have no credibility.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1368709971640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 09:12:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368710015582-12</Id><Topic><Title>The frog and the scorpion</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368654675412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 17:51:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well echo .. if you want to see stupid - read your own posts then look in your mirror</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1368710015582</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 09:13:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368710393126-13</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" multiple aliases" Name calling, then deflection. Typical and as usual wrong. As to the charge of spending all day posting lies, you write what amounts to a book everytime you touch a keyboard. A cursery review of past posts will prove you obviously have a heck of lot more time than I do to concoct stories.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1368710393126</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 09:19:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368710479502-14</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Would you expect anything less" Oh my faith in humanity diminishes every day. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1368710479502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 09:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368710541829-15</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lew .. we can either read that .. or just check the headlines from New Orleans Mothersday Parade.</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1368710541829</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 09:22:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368711099309-16</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“When all else fails, call people names.” By “fails”, I assume you mean what you resort to when you lose an election. Exactly. That (The Kenyan, the Socialist, etc.) combined with voter suppression, filibusters, normal gerrymandering as well as the new effort to gerrymander the Electoral College seems to sum up your efforts when all else fails. “…Name calling, then deflection…you obviously have a heck of lot more time than I do to concoct stories.” –t.bfine Perhaps, but, again, I have only one alias. Didn’t I just respond to winholder’s repetitive use of “deflection” to accuse others of deflecting?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1368711099309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 09:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368711982479-17</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I generalize past your 2009 cut-off date. You may like to pretend it never happened but you have a responsibility to the soldiers you killed. Like it or not I will hold you people responsible for your actions.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1368711982479</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 09:46:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368712819873-18</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now icky .. lets talk about the one YOU KILLED !!</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1368712819873</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 10:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368712932049-19</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Iraq is well beyond whatever happened with Benghazi." Now there is a childish argument if I ever heard one. Lies are lies and pointing out a greater lie does not make a lie the truth. Let's just stick to the problem at hand even though Obama is trying to divert us into problems at the IRS that have existed since 1916.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368712932049</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 10:02:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368713053956-20</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How is what the Republicans are doing today, in your opinion, is much different from what the Democrats did, and are still doing to Bush?" That's not even a question, winholder. It's not "oh, Democrats did something so Republicans can too." It is someone lied, persistently for months for the purpose of starting a war of choice. What is the proper response to that, Democrat or Republican? And what is the proper response to less than perfectly clear information for about an ongoing national security issue? And then, what is the proper response when the same people who lied in 2003 write a report that is clearly a lie? What is the proper response who did nothing in 2003 but who now pretend Benghazi is an impeachable or jail-worthy event? And finally, what is the proper response to people like you, so partisan, so willfully gullible, so invested in decades old lies, as to become a party to evil?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1368713053956</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 10:04:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368714339188-21</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“Now there is a childish argument if I ever heard one. Lies are lies…” – wilkes Childish arguments are suggesting that two grown adults having a mutually consensual liaison are an impeachable offense (particularly when several of the main accusers are hypocritically involved in the exact same thing), while intentionally lying to start a war that kills hundreds of thousands of people is no big deal. Oh, that’s right, it wasn’t the BJ…it was the perjury about it. Right! Of course he lied about it…what would you do if you were stupid enough to do that while President…come right out and admit it when your wife didn’t know about it? Was that really, really immature and stupid? You betcha’. But not anywhere as immature and stupid as trying to make it an impeachable offense, while ignoring Watergate, Iran-Contra, or Yellow cake uranium. Many Presidents have had illicit affairs…but nobody died over it and nobody was impeached. You guys are the poster children for childish arguments.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1368714339188</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 10:25:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368715391955-22</Id><Topic><Title>THIS STOCK IS DONE FOR THE YEAR GOING TO 35 LOWER IF ANOTHER BAD REPORT IAM OUT !!!</Title><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1368544473830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:14:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The price may be down a few pennies this morning but only the little folks are selling. Except for the open today there has not been a minute over 100,000 shares. The price is $1.40 above the 200 DMA and slightly above the 50 DMA so the trend is still up. No reason to believe that we will not go higher this year.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368715391955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 10:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368715830594-23</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Lies are lies and pointing out a greater lie does not make a lie the truth." There were no lies with Benghazi. At worst you had confusion/reduced transparency for about a week during an ongoing situation. Compared to knowing and persistent lies for months and years for the purpose of starting a war of choice? I think I can make a value judgement there about which is worse. Next thing you know you'll be comparing this to fun with cigars in the Oval Office. You are still attempting to normalize what Bush did. By no means is it comparable to Benghazi. It is comparable to the Gulf of Tonkin incident, or the sinking of the USS Maine prior to the Spanish-American War. Those are the only two comparable experiences in our history.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1368715830594</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 10:50:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368716244624-24</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, there's no doubt in my mind that you're all about what you can get--or get away with--right now. With no regard for the future or appreciation of the past. Except, of course, the idealized version you all hold about whatever decade it was when you went to high school.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1368716244624</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 10:57:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368717696906-25</Id><Title>ATT gets the award</Title><Msg>That tv ad with the kids on it shows the ATT mentality.No one can understand it.It is one of the worst tv ads that i have ever seen.It shows the low degree of IQ that ATT thinks the viewers must have.ATT was once a great company.Now it is a dinosaur sinking in the tar pits.</Msg><Username>uwin2day4gd</Username><Timestamp>1368717696906</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:21:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368718342526-26</Id><Title>ATT wireless is like trying to talk to a wall</Title><Msg>I got tired of saying ,can you hear me now?Customers service was terrible.Verizon is light years ahead of ATT.I will never do ATT again.I feel so sorry for any ATT wireless customer.I think ATT should give them all free ladders to get better reception.No that would only help them for painting.Walking into an ATT store you feel like you need a flak jacket from previous customers screaming at the top of their lungs.Never again.</Msg><Username>uwin2day4gd</Username><Timestamp>1368718342526</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:32:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368718548567-27</Id><Title>Off topic comments and their writers need to be deleted by Yahoo</Title><Msg>And soon.</Msg><Username>uwin2day4gd</Username><Timestamp>1368718548567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:35:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368719862438-28</Id><Topic><Title>The frog and the scorpion</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368654675412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 17:51:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Aesop Fables have many good lessons about human behaviour. I read them in grade school. Their points are lost on most people. The book of Proverbs in the Bible also has many good points.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1368719862438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:57:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368719953703-29</Id><Title>OH RICKY</Title><Msg>The Wars that you continue to use as an excuse to blame President .Bush is totally bogus .The wars in two countries have cost us some 4500 lives...each one precious...each one I hope not forgotten .You blame the Republicans yet you seem to forget the filth of Vietnam where 10,262 lives were lost in six months from February to July 1968...yes the ilk of your democratic Gods ...mister kennedy and johnson ...you want history then read it PUNK ...just don't spew your socialistic garbage . The senate voted to invade Iraq and YES YOUR PARTY CONTROLLED THE SENATE AT THE TIME !!!! So little ricky ...stick it in your ear !!!</Msg><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368719953703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:59:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368720671423-30</Id><Topic><Title>OH RICKY</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368719953703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't mess with ricky or he will go back to the "Civil" War under our first Republican President.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368720671423</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 12:11:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368720851660-31</Id><Topic><Title>ATT gets the award</Title><Username>uwin2day4gd</Username><Timestamp>1368717696906</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:21:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah but now it is an international dinosaur serving emerging economies where telephones where rare because there were no telephone lines and now everyone wants one with all the bells and whistles. It will be a long time before this dinosaur becomes extinct. Fortunately I have not seen the ad. I have Dish satellite with hopper.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368720851660</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 12:14:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368721053988-32</Id><Topic><Title>ATT wireless is like trying to talk to a wall</Title><Username>uwin2day4gd</Username><Timestamp>1368718342526</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:32:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess it depends on where you is. AT&amp;T works fine for me.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368721053988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 12:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368721074783-33</Id><Topic><Title>OH RICKY</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368719953703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"each one I hope not forgotten." 4,702 soldiers died in Iraq. 2,201 have died in Afghanistan so far. You forgot about 2,500. I was not alive in 1968, but my father was in country. Most of the politicians involved are now dead. If you don't like what the Democrats did back then, why on earth would you like it when Republicans did something similar in 2003?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1368721074783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 12:17:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368721135292-34</Id><Topic><Title>Off topic comments and their writers need to be deleted by Yahoo</Title><Username>uwin2day4gd</Username><Timestamp>1368718548567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:35:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And what does your post have to do with AT&amp;T?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368721135292</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 12:18:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368721522947-35</Id><Topic><Title>OH RICKY</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368719953703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I was not alive in 1968". Those were "the good old days". As for me, I didn't even like what Hitler did back in the 1930s and now I see Obama repeating it.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368721522947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 12:25:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368724610776-36</Id><Topic><Title>OH RICKY</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368719953703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does Obama know how much you love him? Should Moochelle be worried?</Msg><Username>nyx45o</Username><Timestamp>1368724610776</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 13:16:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368724828304-37</Id><Topic><Title>OH RICKY</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368719953703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It may be time to have some pity on our little friend ricky. He has carried the water for our "dear leader" for so long now that regardless of what the "Old Slickster" does poor little ricky will never be able to see the truth. IMHO you have to hand it to little ricky, because if nothing else you will never be able to question his loyalty even when it is obvious that his loyalty has been unfounded by the actions of his hero. So let's all get together and give our little friend a cheer, and hope that when all of the wheels fall off "Old Mr. Slicks" political wagon, that little ricky will be able to recover, and rejoin the rest of us who are able to see the truth with clear eyes. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368724828304</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 13:20:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368724838731-38</Id><Topic><Title>OH RICKY</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368719953703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, we were attacked in 2001, by Al-Quada, which does provide justification for the invasion of Afghanistan, the attack in Pakistan that killed Bin Laden, and the ongoing drone strikes against Al-Quada and affiliated groups. Bush' lie was that Iraq was affiliated with Al-Quada and participated in 9/11. It was not and did not. So I am not entirely sure why you think being attacked by a terrorist group justifies the invasion of an unrelated country or, if it does, lying about the nature of that justification. "you want total joy for everyone" I do? I wasn't aware. Seems like another one of your Lyndon Johnson policies that was happened before I was born and ended before I was 30. I'll settle for you paying for that little stint of "socialism" as you call it. While your at it you can cut back on that Medicare &amp; Soc. Sec. too.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1368724838731</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 13:20:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368725367009-39</Id><Topic><Title>OH RICKY</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368719953703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What the hell does anything he said have to do with socialism? You tea party nuts have really gone off the deep end. Bush invaded Iraq because the neocons pushed him around and 3,600 Americans died for NO REASON. If that doesn't bother you then you are a heartless zombie.</Msg><Username>freakedout35</Username><Timestamp>1368725367009</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 13:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368725458579-40</Id><Topic><Title>Off topic comments and their writers need to be deleted by Yahoo</Title><Username>uwin2day4gd</Username><Timestamp>1368718548567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:35:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"And what does your post have to do with AT&amp;T?" Now I know how stupid you guys are.</Msg><Username>freakedout35</Username><Timestamp>1368725458579</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 13:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368726464844-41</Id><Topic><Title>Off topic comments and their writers need to be deleted by Yahoo</Title><Username>uwin2day4gd</Username><Timestamp>1368718548567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:35:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, please stick to the political topic being discussed.</Msg><Username>spamo_1</Username><Timestamp>1368726464844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 13:47:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368726780263-42</Id><Topic><Title>OH RICKY</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368719953703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tRicky, you signed on with the wrong ID again!</Msg><Username>nyx45o</Username><Timestamp>1368726780263</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 13:53:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368727403166-43</Id><Topic><Title>OH RICKY</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368719953703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4,702 Americans died in Iraq. They did get rid of a dictator and provide the people of Iraq a shot a democracy--in spite of poor leadership early in the occupation. Despite the fact the war was not justified, those who worked and fought there accomplished quite a bit, especially once Gates, Petreaus and Crocker entered the picture.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1368727403166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 14:03:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368728434994-44</Id><Topic><Title>OH RICKY</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368719953703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey ricky if the war wasn't justified then why did the democrats in the senate approve of it....I mean these are your elected Gods . Funny isn't it when things go south all of a sudden politicians make (up) excuses how they were tricked and lied to...gee what leaders you have . I guess Colin Powell is a liar also huh rico for he endorsed the Iraq conflict...maybe it is just you who has a problem (a big one) dealing with the realities of life.</Msg><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368728434994</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 14:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368732387174-45</Id><Topic><Title>OH RICKY</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368719953703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ricky's bashing of Bush and talking about his brave father going to Vietnam or just more deflection from the facts of the day. Obama's poor leadership, or his excellent but corrupt leadership has caused his administration to be so arrogant (like him) that they are screwing up by the numbers. He is standing back and claiming ignorance of anything that is happening within his house and expecting the low information crowd to believe it. It is simply political grandstanding and subterfuge Ricky in support of the same things happening in Washington. They are all running scared now.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1368732387174</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 15:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368732731549-46</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DEFLECTION ALERT, DEFLECTION ALERT!!!!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1368732731549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 15:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368732787315-47</Id><Topic><Title>Finally we find out "What difference...does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1368234064090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DEFLECTION ALERT, DEFLECTION ALERT!!!!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1368732787315</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 15:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368733114954-48</Id><Topic><Title>OH RICKY</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368719953703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You forgot about 2,500." I guess by that you mean the Americans who lost their lives in the WTC attack to which the Obama solution would have been to do nothing and apologize for upsetting the terrorists who launched this attack against our nation.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1368733114954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 15:38:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368733139287-49</Id><Topic><Title>IRS Black Ops unit of Obama SS attacks conservatives.</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1368633032316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:50:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree the issue is were the rules applied to all 501(c) applicants or just some? Apparently it was not applied across the board. The Koch’s were investigate, but was Soros? Highly unlikely. I also agree that these 501 groups should not exist, but that does not excuse the corrupt application of the rules because someone in Washington didn't like them either. You obey the law or work to change it; you don't ignore it...unless of course you are Obama or Holder. I would suggest that the folks that applied the rules indiscriminately are those without credibility along with those in leadership positions that insist they know nothing about it. What fantasy!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1368733139287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 15:38:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368733252268-50</Id><Topic><Title>IRS Black Ops unit of Obama SS attacks conservatives.</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1368633032316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:50:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I think the IRS asking the tea party for proof of tax exempt qualifications is exactly what the tea party would want to have done to anyone else”, Indeed they should have expected anyone else to be subjected to the same inquiries; the problem is that they weren't. And then those misapplying the rules are lying about it.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1368733252268</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 15:40:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368733597261-51</Id><Topic><Title>Tea party, right wing extreme, GOP congress, etc's defintion of proof</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368209230720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What was it that Obama made a point of several times during his first election campaign? Oh yeah, The Buck Stops Here and I will be fair, honest and transparent. He has been none of that and he steers clear of the Buck like the plague. Fortunately he is becoming more and more transparent as time move on. We all are beginning to see right through his agenda and his tactics.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1368733597261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 15:46:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368733695692-52</Id><Topic><Title>Tea party, right wing extreme, GOP congress, etc's defintion of proof</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368209230720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They make it sound like this administration is taking corrective action...the guys term was to be complete on June first anyway.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1368733695692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 15:48:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368733751309-53</Id><Title>A T &amp; T</Title><Msg>Anyone on this board actually interested in the stock/performance? I think 90% of you need to move to a political blog somewhere.</Msg><Username>kentclark51</Username><Timestamp>1368733751309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 15:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368733830870-54</Id><Topic><Title>Tea party, right wing extreme, GOP congress, etc's defintion of proof</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368209230720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But to call these groups conservative or patriotic is simply inaccurate. " Yes, but only in your not so humble, liberal opinion which few on this board appreciate as having much value. Do you ever look at how many thumbs down your posts receive? That would be one clue that most consider you WRONG!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1368733830870</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 15:50:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368733881580-55</Id><Topic><Title>Tea party, right wing extreme, GOP congress, etc's defintion of proof</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368209230720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DEFLECTION ALERT. DEFLECTION ALERT!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1368733881580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 15:51:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368734133076-56</Id><Topic><Title>IRS Black Ops unit of Obama SS attacks conservatives.</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1368633032316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:50:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who said the tea party doesn't have their tax exempt status? Looking at it doesn't mean it was taken away. The whole issue brought up now is good. The tea party doesn't like tax cheats, and the exempt status is full of them. We need to stop the guy in his house claiming he is a charity to china or something, and those kinds of things. Tax exempt world has a figure of 3.6 trillion dollars in exempted income nationwide. I am sure there are many billions in unpaid taxes being scammed. That shouldn't include all the deductions made by people on their own taxes for donating. It's a doube whammy on our revenue. Donated money is deducted from income, and the income to the receiver isn't taxed. Instead of attacking Obama for things he hasn't done, why doesn't the congress work on this issue.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368734133076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 15:55:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368734767502-57</Id><Topic><Title>A T &amp; T</Title><Username>kentclark51</Username><Timestamp>1368733751309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 15:49:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today's performance is not worth talking about although we did beat the DOW by 9 hundredths of a percentage point. Now are you happy?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368734767502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 16:06:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368736136659-58</Id><Topic><Title>Tea party, right wing extreme, GOP congress, etc's defintion of proof</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368209230720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“Do you ever look at how many thumbs down your posts receive?” - winholder Oh, Good God, he didn’t really say that, did he? Trollin’ for newbies again, huh, winfrog? It’s 4:20, goofy…do you know where all your aliases are? You are one warped individual.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1368736136659</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 16:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368738313231-59</Id><Topic><Title>Off topic comments and their writers need to be deleted by Yahoo</Title><Username>uwin2day4gd</Username><Timestamp>1368718548567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:35:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ja wohl mein fuhrer. It's true, people should only talk about things you like to hear, and it is your place to be the police in such matters. It must very very difficult to NOT READ or use IGNORE, but you can do it if you try.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368738313231</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 17:05:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368738680728-60</Id><Title>A new request from the White House.</Title><Msg>"We're asking people like you to speak out, to let us know if you're one of the 85 percent of Americans who've already benefitted from the health care law, and make a public stand in support of Obamacare." 85%???? Obama must have had a dream. Maybe he forgot to put the decimal point in front of .85%.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368738680728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 17:11:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368740174256-61</Id><Topic><Title>Tea party, right wing extreme, GOP congress, etc's defintion of proof</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368209230720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What happened, you forget to change ID's. That comment was directed at Ricky.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1368740174256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 17:36:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368744642425-62</Id><Topic><Title>A new request from the White House.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368738680728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 17:11:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do we go to speak out. I would like to express feelings about the 35% increase in premimums and higher deductable with more increases on the way. Not to mention emergency rooms having been turned into free clinics for anythig but emergencies. I would also like to speak about how Obama wants Obamacare for everyone but wants no part of it for himself same with all democrats in congress who forced it on us who now want no part of it.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1368744642425</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 18:50:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368746874092-63</Id><Topic><Title>A new request from the White House.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368738680728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 17:11:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"emergency rooms having been turned into free clinics for anythig but emergencies" You're a few decades behind, one of the reasons to have a new health care law was to address this long standing problem. Health care was broken and unsustainable, now we have progress towards a solution. Next year congress gets to go on the exchange like everyone else, what's your problem. As time goes on we can work toward further solutions. Postive, upbeat, optimistic thinking to how to solve problems rather than pessimistic, negative, depressing adherence to what didn't work. If you have a plan nothing changes. My plan went up $6/mo this year, the lowest increase I can remember. Medicare premiums went down this year.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368746874092</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 19:27:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368757634664-64</Id><Topic><Title>OH RICKY</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1368719953703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh icky .. is that fake marine 'echo' your father (??) , you two certainly seem to have the same disposition.</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1368757634664</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 22:27:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368759381390-65</Id><Topic><Title>A new request from the White House.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368738680728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 17:11:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Medicare premiums went down this year." Then i am being cheated because mine went up $9.40.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1368759381390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 22:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>