<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365250729095-1</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice work!</Msg><Username>edwardnicholas46</Username><Timestamp>1365250729095</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 08:18:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365254478735-2</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very helpful!</Msg><Username>sword_raymond</Username><Timestamp>1365254478735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 09:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365258291938-3</Id><Topic><Title>A Topic For AFTERHOURS (here)</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1365179248706</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah Zon, I learned a long time ago that in order to protect my family and self, don't count on someone else. That point has been made perfectly clear by the last two presidential elections.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1365258291938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 10:24:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365258791272-4</Id><Topic><Title>A Topic For AFTERHOURS (here)</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1365179248706</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not true dave! If you are like ricky and on the dole, having someone else pay your way, then you would be an Obama supporter, and would be counting on the stupidity of the American taxpayer to receive your transfer payments. ricky and his kind need to pay their own way. good that you are taking the lead for your families well-being!</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1365258791272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 10:33:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365258970417-5</Id><Topic><Title>49.1 million A.H. volume?</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1365117157264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 19:12:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>haven't looked at the data. though my initial belief would be a combination of the buyback and divi chasers. do you think the dol will approve the t plan to invest in wireless to support pension needs? Approval along with the buyback should give institutional investors a very strong sense of confidence.</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1365258970417</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 10:36:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365259108184-6</Id><Topic><Title>With no jobs can t maintain?</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1365196207250</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 17:10:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ricky is a prime example of someone who relies on the government and supports that reliance by attacking anyone, or any recommendation for fiscal and personal responsibility. Poor ricky! ricky pay your own way!</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1365259108184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 10:38:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365260128924-7</Id><Topic><Title>Not too shabby.</Title><Username>themightyslug</Username><Timestamp>1365111628790</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 17:40:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My retirement couldn't be better Wilkie. I planned on it from day one when I signed on with Pacific Telephone and didn't let anything stop me. But I gotta disagree with you about lasting long in NYC. I'm originally from NJ and wouldn't live there or anyplace else for that matter. We're I to lose over 300K as you say you did, not being able afford NYC may very well be true. Fact is, I didn't lose. By not jerking around with your system of daily and weekly option crapshoots, I sunk my money in the company's generous 401 and invested straight in stock with maximum supplemental contributions week in and week out for 22 1/2 years. Combined with the cash-out I took, the maximum yearly personal IRA contributions i made, my 401 and ultimately combining and converting everything to Roth, it doesn't take a genius to attain a goal. So all things being equal Wilkie, yes, I could get by in NYC. Maybe not Coto De Caza, but certainly NYC. So the 300K you lost came back to bite you. My plan paid my mortgage off, sent our son through private HS and Chapman University....graduating debt-free and leaves plenty to pass on to him when we check out. It really ain't that difficult if you plan and prepare by not gambling. I was thinking about asking you if you were accepting clients a few weeks ago. But when you came clean to only netting 66 bucks a day, I decided to pass. If nothing else, your casino tactic probably keeps you sharp at 84. I commend you for that. P.S. I think you know I was only putting you on about Bombay Beach. I'm actually in Mission Viejo.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1365260128924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 10:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365261536440-8</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks you very muuch!</Msg><Username>jackson_meghan</Username><Timestamp>1365261536440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 11:18:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365264965673-9</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very useful!</Msg><Username>rishjuliane</Username><Timestamp>1365264965673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 12:16:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365269280346-10</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank for this report!</Msg><Username>campbelljames833</Username><Timestamp>1365269280346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 13:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365273153037-11</Id><Topic><Title>Is FDIC planning to eliminate insured deposits with this plan?</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1365006049779</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:20:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe where you live putting money in a safe with a home alarm system works. Armed robbers rule the streets in Florida cities, and for that matter probably most major U.S. cities. Armed to kill robbers really do not care about cameras and monitored alarm systems. They cover their faces and wear hoodies, and are in and out before police arrive. Also, many U.S. regions are cutting back on police due to limited budgets, with slower police response, if any at all. Years ago, before the budget woes, when I lived in St Paul MN the back window of my brand new car was knocked out. I called the police to report it, and they honestly were not at all interested. I can only imagine what type of response you would get there today if your cash filled safe was stolen. Heck, at that time in St Paul, cars were being loaded on truck beds in plain sight and stolen. Oh how I hate Minnesota. In comparison, Florida is a paradise, that`s how much I hate it.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1365273153037</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 14:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365273893747-12</Id><Topic><Title>White supremacists or White HATERS in TX?</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1365193552982</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:25:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who are the many government officials who seem rather scared (like that hair sprayed woman, Rick Perry) actually scared of? A criminal elite perpetrating one massacre after another against Whites in order to further their agenda or White 'supremacist' (many of whom are probably monitored and directed by CIA-FBI agents). White 'supremacists' who probably aren`t at all supremacists, just poor Whites getting kicked around, kicked down and kicked out of American life. Prepare if you are White. You, your children and grandchildren are targeted for elimination, IMO, unless you are one of the 1%.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1365273893747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 14:44:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365274492024-13</Id><Title>AT&amp;T shareholer meeting</Title><Msg>Why is AT&amp;T having its shareholder meeting in Cheyenne WY? Shouldn`t all of these corporate promoters of multi-culturalism and a multi-racial multi-ethnic U.S. have their major meetings in the very heart of large metropolitan cities made up of primarily multitudes of various colored people, what they constantly promote in their commercials and actions? Instead of some little hick town away from all the wonderful multicultural action? Maybe downtown NY, Chicago, Los Angeles or maybe even downtown Detroit? Same with the Federal Reserve? Why do they so often head to Jackson Hole Wy for their meetings? Shouldn`t they be meeting in the heart of Detroit or one of the multi-cultural cities they played a huge role in creating? So they can enjoy the results of their efforts?</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1365274492024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 14:54:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365287529763-14</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good job</Msg><Username>jefflorenz366</Username><Timestamp>1365287529763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 18:32:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365288851042-15</Id><Title>March Madness Online Streaming Up 158%</Title><Msg>There have so far been 45 million online streams of the NCAA March Madness Basketball Tournament games up 158% year-over-year and 60% of them were streamed to tablets and smartphones! Concurrent (CCUR) is an undiscovered and extremely undervalued low floater that will capitalize most on this booming market! CCUR's MediaHawk multi-screen platform can deliver video in any format, to any screen, over any network, at any time. CCUR was the 1st company to introduce video on demand (VOD) technology 13 years ago and they currently hold a 30% market share of the VOD market with 212 VOD deployments across 4 continents, reaching a total of 50mm VOD homes! CCUR's clients include 4 of the 6 largest cable TV companies in the U.S. CCUR made a run from $7 to over $200 during the original VOD boom and now we are about to experience a new huge boom of cable TV companies upgrading their VOD infrastructure to support multi-screen video delivery to tablets/smartphones. CCUR just signed Virgin Media (VMED) the largest cable TV company in the UK as their new huge multi-screen client. CCUR will be powering VMED's Virgin TV Anywhere service that allows their subscribers to watch TV and on demand content on their tablets/smartphones. CCUR is powering a similar multi-screen video service for the largest cable TV company in Japan! CCUR closed last week at an extremely undervalued $7.24 per share with 9.2mm shares outstanding, a market cap of $66.6mm, $24.6mm in cash, no debt, and an enterprise value of $42mm or just 0.67X its trailing twelve month revenue of $62.59mm! CCUR's EPS has been ramping up big, doubling the past two quarters in a row on a quarter-to-quarter basis! CCUR's closest comparison Seachange (SEAC) is trading with an enterprise value/revenue ratio of 1.81, which would value CCUR at $15, meaning CCUR could double fast from these levels.</Msg><Username>bbajf591</Username><Timestamp>1365288851042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 18:54:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>