<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364140511989-1</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Keystone pipeline ever be approved?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1363902082055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess I will have to agree since: o The state department has ok'ed the pipeline o The state of Kansas has ok'ed the pipeline o The US congress has ok'ed the pipeline o The US senate has ok'ed the pipelin There appears to be only one ok left. I wonder when we can expect that last ok? Maybe you are correct (i.e., in the next two or three weeks). I guess we will see. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364140511989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364143672894-2</Id><Title>AT&amp;T Wireless is the worst partner for Blackberry ...!!!!</Title><Msg>WSJ ... Business section Sat/Sun March 23rd about the dismal responce of AT&amp;T to the US alunch of BB Z10 phone.The jist of the article is played out across the US AT&amp;T Stores. AT&amp;T couldn"t care less about the BB Phone Launch. Blackberry needs partners that can energise the consumer and demonstrate the AWESOME experience of using the features of the BB Z10 phone. The paltform is a refreshing diference from andriod or apple. A great eco-system when properly marketed. The culture of AT&amp;T is the problem. This comapny has had serious issues since they bought NCR and other tech companies only to create massive one time write offs into the billions. Management is the problem..</Msg><Username>capwent</Username><Timestamp>1364143672894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:47:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364143966065-3</Id><Title>AT&amp;T Message board for AT&amp;T messages Please ... FOCUS !!!</Title><Msg>Keystone Pipeline may be important / Obama issues / Coffee companies / Ryan Budget .. NONE of THIS Belongs on this Message Board. Come on guys .. Lets Focus on AT&amp;T!</Msg><Username>capwent</Username><Timestamp>1364143966065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:52:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364145045380-4</Id><Title>The MONSTER is BACK! .. Judge GREEN rolling over in his grave!</Title><Msg>Years ago the monster was dismembered to create competition for the consumer. Yes home phone service was never the same!. Quietly and deliberately "The MONSTER" has risen from the ashes .. resurrected and now The DIGITAL / WIRELESS MONSTER! What you get as the consunmer is wireless service that is really pricey .. the service coverage stinks.. store staff is totally appethetic ... their cable service is second rate and many plans to confuse and distract you. TV Marketing is working overtime convincing the public AT&amp;T is the best.... SHEEP going over the edge of the digital cliff ! in the words of Ross Perot the big sucking sound your hearing .....is your wallet being sucked dry with substandard technology... substandard service .. and a culture that is one of the most siloed in the country if not the world. Have you ever tried to navigate one of the many AT&amp;T websites? Its a Mess .. built by committee to justify mid level management jobs and data points. They know nothing of the human or user interface on any level .. This is a CULTURE issue from the top down!.</Msg><Username>capwent</Username><Timestamp>1364145045380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:10:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364180558099-5</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Wireless is the worst partner for Blackberry ...!!!!</Title><Username>capwent</Username><Timestamp>1364143672894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:47:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree AT&amp;T management is a problem</Msg><Username>capwent</Username><Timestamp>1364180558099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 23:02:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364180766192-6</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Message board for AT&amp;T messages Please ... FOCUS !!!</Title><Username>capwent</Username><Timestamp>1364143966065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:52:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a novel concept. Maybe we could go to a political message board to find people interested in talking about AT&amp;T. Someone alluded to the next dividend not being safe. CTL lowered theirs and boy oh boy did their share price take a beating. T is buying stock back at an accelerated rate. This seems like a sign of enough cash to ensure the next dividend.</Msg><Username>robstocks55</Username><Timestamp>1364180766192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 23:06:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>