<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-11"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360584769837-1</Id><Title>DISH</Title><Msg>Based on Randall's presentation of yesterday, linkage of DISH with AT&amp;T in some shape and form seems very probable. Randall has an unlimted appetite for what else, SPECTRUM with which I wholeheartedly agree.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360584769837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 07:12:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360589454797-2</Id><Topic><Title>DISH</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360584769837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 07:12:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed C_S.</Msg><Username>dmcamilla</Username><Timestamp>1360589454797</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:30:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360590580697-3</Id><Topic><Title>DISH</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360584769837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 07:12:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree that Randall is lusting for DISH's unused spectrum which, by the way, DISH says it fully intends to use for its planned build out of a commercial LTE network. That said, if they are courting each other, T &amp; DISH would have to find some creative way to implement the linkage. I say that because I don't see a merger in the cards given the regulatory approval that would be required by the current cast of characters in D.C. Since DISH does not seem overly interested in parting with any of its spectrum, I'm not sure what the linkage would look like.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360590580697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:49:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360591769757-4</Id><Topic><Title>Dorner, Crazed Lib, Likely at Doughnut Shop</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1360551531335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 21:58:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's one of your people, jon2retard. How's the Prius?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1360591769757</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:09:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360592827143-5</Id><Topic><Title>DISH</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360584769837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 07:12:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As you correctly pointed out, a merger of any kind is simply out of the question but there can be other ways to utilize both companies combined strengths. Surely DISH isn't going to start their operations from ground zero. They have to link with an established major telecom services provider where the choices narrow down to two. On an altogether different front, I expect AT&amp;T to make a major announcement in international markets, possible buyout of firms owned/controlled by Carlos Salinas (I hope I got his last name correct). Often times, Randall speaks of Carlos very highly.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360592827143</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:27:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360593764932-6</Id><Topic><Title>t.bfine...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360531429040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:23:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One she has power of attorney for...the other's she was helping. You 'help' people vote by obtaining an absentee ballot for them or taking them to the polls, you don't 'help' by voting for them. You can slant this anyway you like, but she voted for people she wasn't. You can say she way just 'helping' but she broke the law in doing so. If you don't like the law, work to change it, don't violate it. It really is that simple.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1360593764932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:42:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360594739259-7</Id><Title>More threats when 'compromise' isn't achieved</Title><Msg>As part of Obama and his liberal buddies plan to reach reasonable gun control solutions, they have resorted to threats instead. His buddy Rahm Emanuel has sent letters to the Bank of America and TD Bank urging them to stop doing business with Smith &amp; Wesson and Strum Ruger &amp; Co. under the veiled threat that their business with the City of Chicago could suffer if they don't. Senator Cruz has responded by sending a letter to these banks reminding them that private companies don’t' work for elected officials and that elected official work for private citizens. The mob rule is showing its ugly face again, and by mob I don't mean a large crowd.</Msg><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1360594739259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:58:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360595114118-8</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. Frogg and Mr. Rat have dinner</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360350244047</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 14:04:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There certainly more than 5 million voters out there that are not intelligent enough to have made an intelligent choice simply because of their lack of mental skills. There are more than 5 million voters out there that vote only on what they hear in a 30-second sound bite. There are more than 5 million voters out there that voted simply on the basis of race and the amount of free stuff they get from the government and don't want that to change. If you're saying that a 5 million edge is proof that the majority of thinking American's wanted Obama, you need a new class in statistics.</Msg><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1360595114118</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:05:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360605731840-9</Id><Topic><Title>More threats when 'compromise' isn't achieved</Title><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1360594739259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:58:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They know what MOB means in Chicago. I am afraid it has national implications now that they have one of their leaders as President. I don't think Justice Roberts made that decision on his own.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360605731840</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:02:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360606682186-10</Id><Topic><Title>More threats when 'compromise' isn't achieved</Title><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1360594739259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:58:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Senator Cruz is correct, elected officials do work for private citizens. Does Senator Cruz work for the banks or the gun lobby? It does not seem to be private citizens as Rahm does. Another case of Republicans showing their true stripes. Forget the voters. Banks are private citizens. Could you explain why you think the elected Mayor of Chicago should not use his office or the Chicago budget to influence the actions of corporations for the benefit of the private citizens whom he works for, who own his office, and who finance that budget? I'd really like to know.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360606682186</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:18:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360607958952-11</Id><Topic><Title>CEO OF T NEEDS TO WAKE UP........AND BUY ALL AVAIL SHARES</Title><Username>thebigpitcher17</Username><Timestamp>1360593714119</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:41:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better send him an e-mail just in case he isn't following the Yahoo message board today. THAT IS ONE DYNAMIC COMPANY and could probably be bought for 4 Billion.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360607958952</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:39:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360608645348-12</Id><Topic><Title>t.bfine...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360531429040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:23:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The tea party, their supporters, and their Congressman are frauds.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1360608645348</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:50:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360617859744-13</Id><Topic><Title>t.bfine...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360531429040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:23:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If any of this was possible, which it isn't, the republicans, not the dems, would be first in line to do it. The votes are once, if you send in an absentee, you aren't counted again. That's how it works. None of you nut jobs on the right take the time to actually learn how things work, you just react to things you ant to hear. If this were true, which it totally is not, we would have always had republicans winning. But they don't win, they're losers, and continue to lose worse.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1360617859744</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:24:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360628106628-14</Id><Topic><Title>More threats when 'compromise' isn't achieved</Title><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1360594739259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:58:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How stupid. I wish you well.</Msg><Username>rcub5d</Username><Timestamp>1360628106628</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 19:15:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360629174512-15</Id><Topic><Title>7 Million to Lose Insurance Under Obamacare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1360256571061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:02:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is greWe get the Government we vote for, therefore deserve.at to have robfisk back. Comedy has been missing. The board is too much sour apples. But he unwittingly (how else) speaks the truth for once. with this: "We get the Government we vote for, therefore deserve." I am sure he would agree that when we had GWB (I know, I know) making torture cool and destroyin jobs at the rate of up to 600,000 per month along with enriching the real repubs this is what we deserved. Now that Obama (of course the president does everything) is repairing the economy and executing the job the right wing wanted with the war on terrists (that is how he said it), rob is incensed. Que?</Msg><Username>rcub5d</Username><Timestamp>1360629174512</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 19:32:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360632848514-16</Id><Topic><Title>More threats when 'compromise' isn't achieved</Title><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1360594739259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:58:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor old lewcorpse.</Msg><Username>wledigmacsen</Username><Timestamp>1360632848514</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:34:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360633276837-17</Id><Topic><Title>7 Million to Lose Insurance Under Obamacare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1360256571061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:02:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You an jon and your 10 aliases nattering loudly at the IHOP over your "Senior Scrambles" (or "Seneyour Scrmables" as jon calls them) does not constitute a "riot".. (!!)</Msg><Username>wledigmacsen</Username><Timestamp>1360633276837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:41:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360634354454-18</Id><Topic><Title>More threats when 'compromise' isn't achieved</Title><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1360594739259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:58:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And how does shaking down a couple of large banks benefit the citizens of Chicago? This is supposed to be a free country.</Msg><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1360634354454</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:59:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360637709161-19</Id><Topic><Title>t.bfine...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360531429040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:23:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"For me, she represents the poster child of voter fraud." Lord I hope so. What do you have? Five people legally allowed to vote. Five votes counted, all for the people they wanted to vote for? The horror! Yeah, she was pushing the limits--maybe even crossed them. But reall? That's the worst the entire conservative movement can find? The worst of a whole 19 case they've uncovered? I hope you're right--she is the poster child. BTW, not one of the voter suppression initiatives you guys push would have stopped this. She was caught without suppressing one vote. I am glad you conservatives have gone nutso on this stuff. Now that you've put it in the spotlight I feel better about the integrity of our voting system than I ever have. After all these years I don't see how any reasonable person can look at the evidence and conclude you guys are interested in anything but voter suppression. The funny thing about you Tea brains is you'd be crying to high heaven if we tried to make it more difficult for any one of these voters to get AR-15s.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360637709161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:55:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360638361120-20</Id><Topic><Title>More threats when 'compromise' isn't achieved</Title><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1360594739259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:58:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shaking them down? Really? He wrote a letter stating the city of Chicago may take it's business elsewhere. Rahm's like Mitt: he likes firing people. It is not a tactic I would necessarily prefer, but Rahm is a hard-nosed fighter. He's fighting on behalf of the private citizens who elected him and they'll make that call. What absolutely shocks me is Senator Cruz' comments that Rahm should work for the banks and not the people of Chicago. Crazy.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360638361120</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:06:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360639246253-21</Id><Topic><Title>7 Million to Lose Insurance Under Obamacare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1360256571061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:02:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Utter BS. Student loan rates were lowered from 6.8% to 3.4% in 2007--when Bush was president. (Look up "The College Cost Reduction and Access Act of 2007") The ACA cut out the middleman from the student loan program, ending subsidies paid to banks. That is where the savings came from--to cover some of the exchange subsidies. It had absolutely nothing to do with interest rates. More lies from Tea Brains.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360639246253</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:20:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360639898368-22</Id><Topic><Title>Check out PACEF - new dividend and merger - see Press Release</Title><Username>mentges</Username><Timestamp>1360349143468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 13:45:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then buy it and hold it. Follow your own advice pal.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1360639898368</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:31:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360641261433-23</Id><Topic><Title>7 Million to Lose Insurance Under Obamacare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1360256571061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:02:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" it has everything to do with Obamacare that brougt about changes that will cause employers to drop employee coverage and lay people off to avoid the expense of Obamacare." Tell me what that mechanism is again? Currently there is a tax loophole that benefits business. That has been enough to create our employer-based health insurance system. Obamacare adds a penalty for not providing insurance to employers as well. This increases the incentive to employers to provide insurance. Understand? A benefit plus a penalty is a stronger incentive to provide insurance than a benefit alone. It is not a weaker one as conservatives have shrilly tried to argue. "Jonathan Gruber, the architect of the plan, acknowledged that insurance premiums would rise considerably " Jesus, Dan, when will you learn that I am very familiar with Gruber's work. Jon Gruber said no such thing. Jon Gruber posted a lengthy response pinpointing exactly what was wrong with the Daily Caller's article--the article which is driving this particular lie. Here's the one quote you need: "6) Finally, this all ignores tax credits. After tax credits, premiums fall substantially, on average, in each state." Put this in quotes and search for it on Google, and you'll find the source for Gruber's quote here. "an IRS report released last week showing that the cheapest health insurance plan under ObamaCare will cost a family $20,000 in 2016: " An IRS report used $20,000 as a hypothetical price in a few examples showing the effect of a proposed regulation. ALL the examples it used were of the $5,000, $10,000 &amp; $20,000 variety. Look up "RIN 1545-BL36" for the document. You're a liar, Dan. Complete #$%$.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360641261433</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:54:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360642771474-24</Id><Topic><Title>t.bfine...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360531429040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:23:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you ricky for making my case. As I said before, there is nothing a democrat can do that would cause another democrat to find fault with their comrade-in-arms. Yes ricky you are amazing, and are an outstanding representative of the moral decay of your clan. But the really amazing thing is that because you are so self absorbed, you are unable to recognize your own moral turpitude. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360642771474</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:19:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360643978114-25</Id><Topic><Title>More threats when 'compromise' isn't achieved</Title><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1360594739259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:58:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Does Senator Cruz work for the banks or the gun lobby?" Senator Cruz works for the people and is doing a fine job by trying to bring jobs to his great state. I hope he is successful, companies and their workers should move away from hostile political leaders like ballerina boy who are against people trying to make a honest living. "Could you explain why you think the elected Mayor of Chicago should not use his office or the Chicago budget to influence the actions of corporations for the benefit of the private citizens whom he works for, who own his office and who finance that budget?" How is pushing business to another state for the benefit of the private citizens you are supposed to represent?</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1360643978114</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:39:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>