<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361261770976-1</Id><Topic><Title>Pres on Golf Vacation Again</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1361238774182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 20:52:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical neo con reply, jon2retard, worries about the Defense Department cuts. You guys love war. Where are the WMDs your AWOL hero Dubya promised? Oh, he is still under his desk looking for them.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361261770976</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 03:16:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361279635972-2</Id><Topic><Title>Speaking of awards...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361197076521</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 09:17:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"As they say in Texas, “Hell, what’s a little air pollution among friends?" Well Echo, perhaps contrary to your thinking, we aren't idiots down here. Last month, the Texas comptroller kicked off the 2013 legislative session projecting an $8.8 billion budget surplus for the coming fiscal period. Gov Perry, in his state of the state address, urged legislators to give some of the money back to the state's tax payers. Unheard of, right? A politician that cares about the folks footing the "bills". I'm sure you find that insane. And before you hit me with some areas where Texas isn't number one, I'll tell you right up front we don't believe in being number one at all cost. Are there areas where we can improve, sure. But, this state is governed in a fiscally sane way prudently balancing the needs of its citizens. If we don't have the money, we don't spend it. If we have the money, we don't spend it all. We don't see the state's businesses and taxpaying citizens as bottomless pits of money. Call us whatever you like, but I'm proud to live here and it is well documented that others from around the country are increasingly seeking us out as they try to escape fiscal insanity.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1361279635972</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 08:13:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361279839508-3</Id><Topic><Title>wow... this is what i am talking about!</Title><Username>emiwilliam660</Username><Timestamp>1361279288032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 08:08:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spam reported.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1361279839508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 08:17:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361285581243-4</Id><Topic><Title>Ban Democrats from guns</Title><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1361229733682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 18:22:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Waiting in line for the bus, a Pennsylvania kindergartener tells her pals she's going to shoot them with a Hello Kitty toy that makes soap bubbles. -In Maryland, two 6-year-old boys pretend their fingers are guns during a playground game of cops and robbers. In Massachusetts, a 5-year-old boy attending an after-school program makes a gun out of Legos and points it at other students while "simulating the sound of gunfire," as one school official put it. - GETTYSBURG, Pa. (AP) — Police in Pennsylvania say a student's report of a gunshot being fired was instead the sound of a newspaper hitting the sidewalk. Gettysburg police Chief Joseph Dougherty says a Gettysburg College student had reported that someone in a white sedan fired a shot early Saturday morning. But Dougherty says police investigated and determined the sound came from a newspaper delivery driver throwing a paper from her vehicle. No, but we don't over react, we don't overreact...just keep repeating it and new gun laws will suddenly appear and not change a thing. So Lib’s, how many gun deaths are attributed to legally purchased weapons? How many of those are attributed to ‘assault’ weapons? How many are attributed to illegally purchased or stolen weapons? How many are caused by normally law-abiding citizens versus previously convicted criminals?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361285581243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 09:53:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361285787644-5</Id><Topic><Title>Is POTUS reading the T message board?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361057564896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 18:32:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He wouldn't stoop to the level of reading most anything in the public domain, his royal highness has 'people' to do that for him and then explain it to him.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361285787644</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 09:56:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361286019700-6</Id><Topic><Title>After Hours Quotes...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361018726647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 07:45:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“If you want to have good ideas you must have many ideas. Most of them will be wrong, and what you have to learn is which ones to throw away.” – Linus Pauling Echo has a steep learning curve, but his is still trying!</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361286019700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:00:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361287020093-7</Id><Topic><Title>They're gone again?</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1360963675161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 16:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps they are running around the country looking for the Senate's budget. It's been missing for over 1387 days and Harry's code of leadership wants taxpayers to send more money to feed his black hole.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1361287020093</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:17:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361288262458-8</Id><Topic><Title>They're gone again?</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1360963675161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 16:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because Limbaugh told them to take a break.Worthless puks!</Msg><Username>orri1934</Username><Timestamp>1361288262458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:37:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361288379625-9</Id><Topic><Title>Speaking of awards...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361197076521</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 09:17:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “Well Echo, perhaps contrary to your thinking, we aren't idiots down here.” I never said that you were ALL idiots down there. I was referring to pinhighshot, who attempted to criticize the Polk Awards with no clue what he was talking about. He is a MSM conspiracy lunatic like the others I referenced in my post. He is an idiot. The Frogg agrees with him. The Frogg is an idiot. Jon, who spent Monday searching his pantry for fruitcakes, only to find The Frogg, also agrees with him. Jon, likewise, is an idiot. Windandale, et. al., all of whom refuse to accept that the very short-lived impact of The Tea Party has ridiculed itself into oblivion, with part of that being the denial of legitimate news sources in favor of Rush, Glen Beck &amp; Fox, are all idiots…as are the aforementioned sources…and Ann Coulter is the Queen of all idiots. Not ALL idiots live in Texas, but some do. Rick Perry governs the biggest state polluter in America – call that business friendly if you like – One fourth of kids in Texas live in poverty, while the state ranks a lowly 42nd for educational attainment and income while ranking FIRST in the disparity between rich and poor. “…it is well documented that others from around the country are increasingly seeking us out…” Given the above, we can readily see why and who they might be…oil companies, anti-regulatory industrialist polluters, and others of the 2% who think 47% of Americans are bums. Rick Perry also thinks global warming is a hoax, embraces intolerant fundamentalist paranoia, is a former Democrat and would like to see the great state of Texas secede from The United States. Rick Perry also made a fool out of himself in the debates, thus proving he is an idiot. Texas Congressman Steve Stockman wants to impeach President Obama if any executive orders are issued to strengthened gun control laws. Mr. Stockman also embarrassed your state by fawning over noted psycho, Ted Nugent, inviting this clown (who threatened the President as well as telling NRA members to "ride into that battlefield and chop [Democrats'] heads off in November" to the State of the Union address. Texas Congressman Stockman is an idiot. Ted Nugent, although not from Texas, is also an idiot. And, t.bfine, when you agree with those above, I can only conclude that you are also an idiot. However, often you are far more moderate and in your recent diatribe, you stated that you actually agree with many elements of additional gun control regulation. That certainly does not jibe with the other idiots listed, and you cannot have it both ways. You know as well as I do, that universal registration of handguns is a very good thing embraced by nine out of ten Americans, and in no way infringes on the 2nd Amendment. Why do you find it impossible to comment on that when the windanjon’s on this board intentionally lie about it? Then again, last year you said that all the Democrats in Texas would be shot. Now, THAT was idiotic! In your defense, you’ve got some great music in Austin.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361288379625</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:39:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361288425832-10</Id><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Msg>The first amendment allows us to communicate but redesigning the message board has made it almost impossible. Obama must have something to do with it, or am I just getting paranoid?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361288476367-11</Id><Topic><Title>They're gone again?</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1360963675161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 16:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, they go home to gather up money from the gun folks and other worthless pucks. ( R. Maddow hailed their #$%$ this time)</Msg><Username>orri1934</Username><Timestamp>1361288476367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:41:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361288881492-12</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you're thinking he has had it with the constant bashing (as reported by his buddy Ricky) that he takes here? Very well could be!</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1361288881492</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:48:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361291687805-13</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once you figure out how it works it's not too bad. Guess they have their reasons but I wish they would quit changing it.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1361291687805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 11:34:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361291906659-14</Id><Topic><Title>They're gone again?</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1360963675161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 16:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will Rogers once said that the country was safe when Congress was in recess. I agree 100%. Rogers was a smart old guy. I'd like to find a book with a lot of his writings. There actually may be a handful of people in Congress that can be trusted. The rest? They should be put in prison for high crimes and misdemeaners.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1361291906659</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 11:38:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361293570973-15</Id><Title>Let's see if T can finally...</Title><Msg>..break through $35.60-$35.65 and close above that. I'm no technical guy but my instincts tell me that if it does it could take off nicely from there. But it has to break through the brick wall first...and not crash right back down like it always does.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1361293570973</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 12:06:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361296115666-16</Id><Topic><Title>VOLUME HEATING UP ON *ILNS* MONSTER MOVE ..</Title><Username>southpeir</Username><Timestamp>1361289599570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:59:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SOOOO .. your ILNS is down 12 cents a share at 12:10 today ... so $10 will get you 500 shares .. (chuckles)</Msg><Username>coolin_out47</Username><Timestamp>1361296115666</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 12:48:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361299320947-17</Id><Topic><Title>Speaking of awards...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361197076521</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 09:17:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just another sanctimonious liberal rant that all who disagree with his view of the world are idiots. They say the narrowest road in the universe is the one between your ears and Echo's road is shrinking as we speak and is already as narrow as a thread. I guess the vision of most of his posts being awarded a thumbs down via Yahoo is not much of a clue as to his acceptance or lack thereof. Some have to be shamed into better behavior and with some it just never works.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1361299320947</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 13:42:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361304547911-18</Id><Topic><Title>Baltimore City Police Academy Shut Down</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1361065864211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 20:51:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know all about ignorant. robfisk aka jon2retard aka jerkbac98</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361304547911</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 15:09:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361304849344-19</Id><Topic><Title>Speaking of awards...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361197076521</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 09:17:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jerkbac98 aka robfisk aka jon2retard. Get tired answering your own posts?</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361304849344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 15:14:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361305400689-20</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Little envious of his detailed factual posts? thought so. Lie , distort is all you neo con phony patriots got. Cant stand that black family in your White House, can you. 4 more years then you old white bigots can deal with a Democrat woman for 8 years. Better start seeing your doctors for some meds.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361305400689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 15:23:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361306887811-21</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I assume you're talking about the gal that let 4 Americans die in Benghazi.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1361306887811</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 15:48:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361308623464-22</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “I assume you're talking about the gal that let 4 Americans die in Benghazi.” – t.bfine “you cannot have it both ways…Why do you find it impossible to comment on that…?” – posed earlier, but ignored. It’s like the Republican candidates afraid of appearing too moderate for the Tea Folks. And in two replies, you ignore the issue, but call The Secretary of State (at the time), “the gal”??? The gal???? The wife???? Where have we heard that before? Nah, you guys had no war on women, right? As long as they are kept in their place like the minorities, gays, poor people, etc. “The gal”? Now that sounds like a typical idiot from Texas. “Let’s mosey on down to the saloon and find us some cow-gals, pod-ner!” Some day somebody on your side is going to have to stand up to the extremes in your party, or you folks are cooked for at least another decade.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361308623464</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:17:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361308840898-23</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He could be right if we conservatives don't get united into the Constitution Party. The Republican Party has been bought by the same gang that destroyed the Democratic Party and will probably never win an election again. I think there are enough voters "longing to be free" to win an election if presented with a clear choice like Rand Paul, Dr Carlson, or Sarah Palin; none of these would get on the Republican ticket. All of these would be winners on the Constitution Party platform.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361308840898</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:20:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361309298009-24</Id><Topic><Title>Let's see if T can finally...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1361293570973</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 12:06:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Closed above $35.60 for the first time since last October and volume has been normal the past two sessions. I expect $36 by Friday at least as an inter day if not a close.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361309298009</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:28:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361309804542-25</Id><Topic><Title>They're gone again?</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1360963675161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 16:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That has to be the stupidest remark I've ever seen anyone on this board write! And I've been reading this board for at least 10 years! Climb back under you're rock!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1361309804542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:36:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361309914685-26</Id><Topic><Title>Is POTUS reading the T message board?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361057564896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 18:32:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I heard that Obama had a large office with 250 employees monitoring the message boards during the last campaign. It wouldn't surprise me if he incorporated it into the DHS and is watching everything we post. ..!.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361309914685</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:38:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361310833197-27</Id><Title>If $85.3 billion is cut from a $3 trillion plus budget will America cease to exist?</Title><Msg>Our federal government spends about $11 billion per day. The sequestration cuts about $233,698,630.00 from that daily expense. So according to our "dear leader" in his speech today, if the federal government only has $10.76 billion to spend on a daily basis, then people will get cancer, law enforcement will stop doing their jobs, children will stop being educated, our "dear leader" may have to take fewer multi million dollar vacations, and other draconian effects. Who would have thought that $233 million would have had such a major effect on America's ability to perform its functions? Why can't Republicans understand that our "dear leader" is a reasonable man and is willing to go the extra mile if only they will raise taxes a little bit more on the rich? "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361310833197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:53:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361313978814-28</Id><Topic><Title>Let's see if T can finally...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1361293570973</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 12:06:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great...volume actually pretty low today..but I'll gladly take it.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1361313978814</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 17:46:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361314844621-29</Id><Topic><Title>Ban Democrats from guns</Title><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1361229733682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 18:22:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just love "intellegentsia" that pick on minor misspellings of words and grammar mistakes. Usually it's because they can't find fault with the argument.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1361314844621</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 18:00:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361329724406-30</Id><Title>These message boards suck</Title><Msg>Has anyone figured how to navigate these message boards?</Msg><Username>billyray368</Username><Timestamp>1361329724406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 22:08:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361330012901-31</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paranoid. Gullible. Senile. Nuts. Whatever you want to call it.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361330012901</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 22:13:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361330165163-32</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The majority of Americans think the people you mentioned are paranoid, senile, nuts, whatever you want to call it, and that their followers are gullible old fools. They're right.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361330165163</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 22:16:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361330242192-33</Id><Topic><Title>Ia Obama redesigning the message board?</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361288425832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe you said the same about Herman Cain, Michelle Bachman, Christine O'Donnell, Sarah Palin, Rick Perry, Allen West. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361330242192</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 22:17:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361330324997-34</Id><Topic><Title>Is POTUS reading the T message board?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361057564896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 18:32:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I heard you're a gullible old fool. It's on the internet. It must be true!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361330324997</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 22:18:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361330393907-35</Id><Topic><Title>Is POTUS reading the T message board?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361057564896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 18:32:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you seriously think *anyone* cares what you morons say on a yahoo MB?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361330393907</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 22:19:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361330542920-36</Id><Topic><Title>They're gone again?</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1360963675161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 16:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Believe it or not, they go back to their districts to see what their voters are thinking, particularly about major legislation.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361330542920</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 22:22:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>