<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361943986577-1</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Accomplishments</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361625594937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:19:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the problem is that we have not had a true economic policy in years. I also think that aggregated income will be the key to global economic growth. Th raise in incomes and the expansion of incomes should the most important point of any plan for growth. Central to all economic theories is the growth income levels and the expansion of incomes. Taxes are created through incomess and consumption/demand is also related to incomes. Savings and investments are also directly related to incomes. We can theorize the Laffer Curve in many different ways but the fact is that a decrease overall incomes will result in a decrease tax revenues. High unemployment will make this worse with aggregated incomes decreasing and very little effort to redistribute wealth from the higher income brackets to the poor and middle class.. We should be maximizing income levels with a balanced tax policy to close the deficit gap instead of engaging in policies that promote self interest. of a few or a pure capitalist system. The increase and expansion aggregated income levels is the the key. Put the money in the hands of many who consume and pay taxes, they will put pressure on supply which with create demand and more household incomes.</Msg><Username>bass9189</Username><Timestamp>1361943986577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 00:46:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361945792386-2</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The truth is that they don't have ti make a lot of cuts. A slight increase in taxes and a effort to expand incomes through investments will help. They need to find new projects/ investments to increase income levels. The expansion of incomes is the key to economic growth. They must get people back to work, even if it is at lower wages. I don't think we can afford to fall into a classical trap where people refuse to work at lower wages ( 3.5 percent of the unemployed....these are the people of concern...A 4 percent unemployment rate is in theory closer to full employment). We need to get people back to work to generate aggregate income. This is the key.</Msg><Username>bass9189</Username><Timestamp>1361945792386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 01:16:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361963339760-3</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey fagyes, your boy John #$%$ loved sequestration he got 98% of what he wanted. Did you forget that? http://www.businessinsider.com/john-boehner-2011-sequestration-2013-2</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361963339760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 06:08:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361965324545-4</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Accomplishments</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361625594937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:19:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem is that we have no true patriots elected to serve the country and care about the well being of the nation. They all envision themselves in an all-you-you can eat buffet, care less about the outcome. The net result of all this mess will translate into lowered standard of living as years go by.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1361965324545</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 06:42:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361966445394-5</Id><Title>IBM Backs Network Functions Virtualization to help Carriers Speed New Services to Customers****</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-backs-network-functions-virtualization-100000274.html</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1361966445394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 07:00:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361969912535-6</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for reminding me about Speaker Boehner's position on sequestration. I guess you missed the point of my post, I'll try again. What is going to happen if sequestration is invoked, and the American people realize that all that happened was that spending by the government was kept at the 2012 levels? Another way of saying this is, instead of increasing government spending by 2.2% for 2013, the government kept the spending levels the same. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361969912535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 07:58:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361974433716-7</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like you'll get your wish. A 2% payroll tax increase and a bunch of laid off and furloughed teachers, police officers and TSA workers. In exchange for what? A nominal increase in marginal rates for a few of the insanely wealthy. Good for you Froggie. And good for Boehner. A small minority of nutjobs have managed leverage one good election year into gutting the American middle class. Simply by being complete a**holes. We should have gone over the cliff on Jan. 1. Obama is far too nice to you people. I'm voting for Rahm in 2016. We need someone willing to bash some Tea Brains.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361974433716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:13:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361975734210-8</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Accomplishments</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361625594937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:19:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The problem is that we have no true patriots elected to serve the country and care about the well being of the nation." I think we do. You have to look at what Obama and the Democrats are offering here. They are offering cuts to entitlements and closing tax loopholes to preserve investment in infrastructure and the economy. Moderate Republicans would go along with this. I think 95% of Americans would think this Grand Bargain would be great. The Tea Brains, however, are demanding that this be accompanied by lower tax rates--because they won't accept anything that "raises revenue" one cent--except for the 2% increase in the payroll tax cut they demanded in exchange for raising taxes on those earning more than $400,000. What they have really pushed for and gotten is cuts to spending on the economy and infrastructure, low taxes and loopholes for the wealthy, taxes on the poor and middle class (what they call broadening the tax base) and high spending on entitlements, particularly those for the elderly. If you read the posts here, that is exactly what the Tea Brains say they want. And they've gotten it, despite being a minority of the minority.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361975734210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:35:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361976595178-9</Id><Title>What if Republicans...?</Title><Msg>The Republicans can't win against obama's media machine; it will always be their fault. What if the Republicans just gave up and voted "present" to anything obama and the dems want. What would happen to the country in the next two years, good or bad? If the country survives; in two years, at the mid term elections, one party will be history.</Msg><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1361976595178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:49:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361976994724-10</Id><Topic><Title>What if Republicans...?</Title><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1361976595178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's media machine? Great, another trained monkey dittoing the conservative media tripe.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361976994724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:56:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361977053138-11</Id><Topic><Title>The status quo won't get it done</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361905483547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:04:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, but Obama is the labeler-in-chief on this one. Just listen to the speeches he is making all across the country instead of being in Washington doing his job of LEADING...a word he likely can't spell without his teleprompter. Nice try at deflection Ricky Jr.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361977053138</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:57:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361977055929-12</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES AT&amp;T</Title><Username>whitlockjohn510</Username><Timestamp>1361876686315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 06:04:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful report</Msg><Username>roberthawkins100</Username><Timestamp>1361977055929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:57:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361977169269-13</Id><Topic><Title>What if Republicans...?</Title><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1361976595178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just because it comes from conservatives doesn't mean it is 'tripe'. Your brush is getting very broad again. It just means you don't agree with them.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361977169269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:59:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361977352768-14</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Accomplishments</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361625594937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:19:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The last offer from the Democrats was to stall the spending cuts and increase revenue by closing tax loop holes. Why wasn't closing tax loop holes part of the last agreement? Because they know they can't get all they want at once, they will hold back and force their desires into being with the next crisis, then the next, then the next. In this administration there is no shortage of crisis situations of which to take full advantage.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361977352768</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361977535537-15</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Accomplishments</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1361625594937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:19:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I think the problem is that we have not had a true economic policy in years." He$$, we haven't had a budget in three years and you expect an economic policy? But I regress, they do have an economic policy...increase taxes so we can spend more and create more dependency on the government for everything, not just those outlined in the Constitution. Oh I forgot, liberals think the Constitution is outdated and should be either rewritten or changed dramatically.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361977535537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:05:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361977700132-16</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does your mother know what kind of mouth you have? Shout a bit louder, she can't hear you from the basement. Isn't it time for Jr. High to start? What are you still doing home...skipping again today?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361977700132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:08:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361977749035-17</Id><Topic><Title>What if Republicans...?</Title><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1361976595178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I posed an honest question. I would like to know what you think would happen to the country if the democrats got everything they wanted?</Msg><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1361977749035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:09:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361977755913-18</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is the latest straight from the cry babies desk. I just got this e-mail this morning. "There's a good chance you and your family will be directly affected by the disastrous budget cuts scheduled to take effect on Friday. These budget cuts -- known as the sequester -- take a sledgehammer to the budget and indiscriminately cut critical programs vital to middle-class families and economic growth." Obama reminds me of the fable of the shepherd that cried WOLF when there was no wolf. I guess he learned it from his "goat herder father" which is another of Obama's fables.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361977755913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:09:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361978116307-19</Id><Topic><Title>$ T Featured on MAD MONEY</Title><Username>kevinlee899</Username><Timestamp>1361805521276</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:18:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Important report</Msg><Username>mickblack265</Username><Timestamp>1361978116307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:15:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361978119179-20</Id><Topic><Title>$ T Featured on MAD MONEY</Title><Username>kevinlee899</Username><Timestamp>1361805521276</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:18:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Type message</Msg><Username>mickblack265</Username><Timestamp>1361978119179</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:15:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361978127475-21</Id><Topic><Title>Millions Said to Be Wasted on U.S. Rural Broadband Expansion</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1361892413168</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:26:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is the liberal line, it was only (some small number) percent of the program and in the big picture it gets lost in the rounding. The problem being that the 'rounding' gets to be a larger and larger number every year with little or no action being taken to punish the 'over spenders' or the flat out crooks that created much of government 'overspending'. In Washington overspending is not a crime, it is not a failing of fiscal responsibility, it is a way of life. A way of life Obama promised to change in his first campaign 'promises' later known as holograms. The media, the voters, some of their own members sign this song relentlessly but it all falls on deaf ears…sorry not deaf ears, just ears stuffed with ‘government’ money that came from the taxpayers.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361978127475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:15:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361978130723-22</Id><Topic><Title>$ T Featured on MAD MONEY</Title><Username>kevinlee899</Username><Timestamp>1361805521276</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:18:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Important report</Msg><Username>mickblack265</Username><Timestamp>1361978130723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:15:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361978467444-23</Id><Topic><Title>The next crisis</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361476845933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:00:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes he does. That is why he works so hard to deflect and confuse the issue being discussed.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361978467444</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:21:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361978510942-24</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I find it difficult to reconcile your obvious excellent education with your complete lack of intelligence. The Federal Government has little to do with paying teachers or police officers and, as for TSA workers, they should fire all of them and just empower the flight crew of each airplane to refuse boarding to anyone they want to exclude.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361978510942</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:21:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361978913028-25</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>‘A nominal increase in marginal rates for a few of the insanely wealthy.’ I guess I missed something, how does cutting spending equate to an increase in marginal rates for a few of the insanely wealthy? The 'gutting' of the American middle class began with an enormously high unemployment rate that still exists. It began with forcing banks to give folks with little or no money huge loans on huge homes they had no opportunity to every repay. In the process they took down the real estate market and the ownership of many homes that people could actually afford, until they lost their jobs that is. Some in this government have listened to the screaming about how we can’t continue to tax and spend more and more than we take in or can afford while some have considered this a fairy tale and want to continue down the path to financial doom of the nation.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361978913028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:28:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361979140081-26</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw a local news story last night about the concern that a man had about his 'free' childcare and what impact it would have on his poor family. The local entity that provides this service stands to lose $1.5M dollars in Federal aid from their $50M budget. This was reported to be a devastating loss and had this poor man visibly upset, as they showed him answering his smart phone while getting into a late model four-door Chevy pickup truck. I suspect they might need a new TV producer for that show soon.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361979140081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:32:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361979174718-27</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHAT "BUDGET"??? Obama has never had a budget and wouldn't pay any more attention to it than he does to the Constitution if he did have one. .47 of every dollar spent at the Federal level is borrowed money. Try running your household that way and see what happens.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361979174718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:32:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361979394431-28</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, thanks alot Janet, you stupid DIKE BEECH! Ruining AZ from afar! Guess she didn't do enough damage when she was here! This admenstration is the worst ever. Obummer needs to be impeached!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1361979394431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:36:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361979767400-29</Id><Topic><Title>What if Republicans...?</Title><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1361976595178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the Democrats got everything they wanted there would never be another election. We would join a one world government and have little influence in how it operated.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361979767400</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:42:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361980250244-30</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES AT&amp;T</Title><Username>whitlockjohn510</Username><Timestamp>1361876686315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 06:04:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome</Msg><Username>wendell.obrian</Username><Timestamp>1361980250244</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:50:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361981366679-31</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“This admenstration (sic) is the worst ever.” – bouch Worst EVER, jon?? Oh, I’m so sorry. Have you tried Midol? How about a dictionary?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1361981366679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:09:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361982658329-32</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>John don't live in AZ. And I hate this black man! It's just a matter of time. Nobody can be so Arrogant without doing something so stupid that it's going to #$%$ off most of us Real Americans. Worst president ever, history will prove!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1361982658329</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:30:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361983526793-33</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure ya did, winholder, sure ya did. Just like you saw an article about the coming computer crisis. More lies &amp; bs.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361983526793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:45:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361983645845-34</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I find it difficult to reconcile your obvious excellent education with your complete lack of intelligence." Wilkes, the reason is because you are senile.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361983645845</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:47:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361983698516-35</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read my post again. This time try for comprehension.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361983698516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:48:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361984427559-36</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go back to the circle jerk you, echo and lvetteintherear were having!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1361984427559</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:00:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361984684856-37</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES AT&amp;T</Title><Username>whitlockjohn510</Username><Timestamp>1361876686315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 06:04:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I subscribed</Msg><Username>duane.krebs</Username><Timestamp>1361984684856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:04:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361985899973-38</Id><Title>Barchart just put buy on YTRV</Title><Msg>$$$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>btolink</Username><Timestamp>1361985899973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:24:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361988255490-39</Id><Topic><Title>$ T Featured on MAD MONEY</Title><Username>kevinlee899</Username><Timestamp>1361805521276</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:18:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ LINK IS TO NASTY PORN!!!! ████████████..</Msg><Username>zion_will_up_huge</Username><Timestamp>1361988255490</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:04:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361988452393-40</Id><Topic><Title>$ T Featured on MAD MONEY</Title><Username>kevinlee899</Username><Timestamp>1361805521276</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:18:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great update.</Msg><Username>collinsnick755</Username><Timestamp>1361988452393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:07:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361991645421-41</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Win, help me here. On January 1, 2013 didn't the senate and the house raise taxes on those hated rich people? On January 1, 2013 didn't the senate and the house raise the payroll tax on all working Americans by some 2%? On January 1, 2013 didn't the new Obamacare taxes take effect? On January 1, 2013 didn't the agreed to tax bill also contain increased spending, but no spending cuts? Oh dear I lost my head, that was January 1, 2013, the American people are supposed to forget that taxes were increased on all Americans with no spending cuts, Now that's what I call a real balanced approach. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361991645421</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:00:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361992998517-42</Id><Topic><Title>Will the American people care when they find out the truth about sequestration?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361930514108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:01:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If instead of all this finger pointing and threatening of the American people, they would just stop all payments to the members of Congress, their staff, the President and his staff, including cabinet members, this circular firing squad nonsense would be resolved almost overnight. The wrong people are being threatened and the wrong people will suffer for the actions and inactions of these fools.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1361992998517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:23:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361993177726-43</Id><Topic><Title>What if Republicans...?</Title><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1361976595178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ricky doesn't answer questions about what he thinks, because he doesn't, he just spouts the latest Democratic Party talking points or the same dribble that comes from the liberal media. I wouldn't hold my breath.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361993177726</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:26:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361993304595-44</Id><Topic><Title>What if Republicans...?</Title><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1361976595178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a really nasty individual and seem to have the personality of a busted up speed bump. At least Echo can be a bit entertaining in his holier than thou rants. You fail even that measure.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361993304595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:28:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361994002020-45</Id><Title>Based on the email I got from the "Organizing for Action" group ricky must be right</Title><Msg>Here is the email: "Prepare yourself for job layoffs, reduced access to early education, slower emergency response, slashed health care, and more people living on the street. This Friday is the final deadline for congressional Republicans to stop disastrous automatic spending cuts (known as the "sequester") that will hurt everyday Americans -- including you. These budget cuts will take a sledgehammer to the budget, and indiscriminately cut critical programs vital to economic growth and middle class families. If Congress fails to act, we'd see budget cuts pretty much across the board to critical services that teachers, first responders, seniors, children, and our men and women in uniform rely on every day. It sounds bad because it is. And with all these cuts on the line, why are congressional Republicans refusing to budge? Because to do so, they'd have to close tax loopholes for millionaires and billionaires, oil companies, vacation homes, and private jet owners. I'm not kidding. It's on each of us to speak up. Share what these budget cuts could mean to you -- or someone you know -- today. Congress needs to hear it. President Obama has offered a balanced plan to reduce our deficit, asking the wealthy to pay their fair share so that we can protect programs that are incredibly important for working and middle-class Americans. But congressional Republicans so far are refusing to compromise. Here are some of the consequences if Congress fails to act by Friday: -- 10,000 teachers would be laid off, $400 million would be cut from Head Start, the program that makes sure at-risk preschoolers are ready for kindergarten, and 70,000 kids would be kicked out of the early-education program completely. -- The budget for firemen and other first responders to react when natural disasters strike would be cut by $35 million. -- Nutrition programs that help make sure seniors don't go hungry would be cut by $43 million. -- A program that helps provide housing for the formerly homeless, including many veterans, would be shuttered, putting them at risk of going back on the street. -- A number of programs that help the most vulnerable families and children would be slashed -- including the Special Supplemental Nutrition Program for Women, Infants, and Children dropping 600,000 women alone. Right now, each of us has a responsibility to step up and make sure Congress hears our voices. Whether you'd be directly affected by these sequester cuts, or whether they'd affect a senior, veteran, or teacher you know, please share what they mean to you. Let's keep the pressure on congressional Republicans to do the right thing. Thanks, Stephanie Stephanie Cutter Organizing for Action" "Lordy me Oprah" it sure looks like those awful Republicans have done it again. For the life of me I can't understand why they just can't shutup and drink the Kool Aid. I guess in this case you know in your heart that ricky is right. The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361994002020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:40:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361994634125-46</Id><Topic><Title>What if Republicans...?</Title><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1361976595178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You began with a false premise and you answered your own question. I thought it was rhetorical. My answer is I have no idea and don't really care. I am a moderate and a pragmatist. I imagine every one of those Republicans would get thrown out of office in the next election. Right now a large block of Republicans are looking to punt their fiscal powers over to the President, just so they don't have to take political flak for instituting the spending cuts they demand. In my mind, that is about the same scenario as you described. We should throw each and every one of those Republicans out of office at the next election.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361994634125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:50:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361994685525-47</Id><Topic><Title>What if Republicans...?</Title><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1361976595178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you answer his question, winholder? No, you did not.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361994685525</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:51:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361995755132-48</Id><Topic><Title>Has the gun control agenda changed since the civil war?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361799267020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 08:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is it we can sent F16's to the Muslim Brotherhood, but the government won't trust its citizens with a common hunting rifle?</Msg><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1361995755132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:09:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361995823653-49</Id><Topic><Title>What if Republicans...?</Title><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1361976595178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He didn't ask me the question. Nice deflection though.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361995823653</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:10:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361996028528-50</Id><Topic><Title>What if Republicans...?</Title><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1361976595178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trough out both Republicans and Democrats and elect the Constitution Party candidates. Just imagine a congress adhering to the Constitution. They would impeach Obama in a heart beat for gun running to our enemies.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1361996028528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:13:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361996043405-51</Id><Topic><Title>Based on the email I got from the "Organizing for Action" group ricky must be right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361994002020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:40:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And free prophlyatics for Ricky, Echo and Lvettintherear to avoid the spreading of aids would be cutoff also.</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1361996043405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:14:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361997132280-52</Id><Topic><Title>Based on the email I got from the "Organizing for Action" group ricky must be right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361994002020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:40:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why things won’t change within our government! If you are elected to represent the people of the United States in our Federal government or even a local or state government there are certain expectations that you are demanded to be devoted to, other than the legal rules around age, residence, etc. You must honestly represent your thoughts and principles about how you think the government should operate, what laws, fiscal strategies, foreign affairs, and other convictions you support or do not support. You must share what your intentions are with regard to voting for or against these issues. If you alter your position, you must justify the change and ask if the people that elected you desire you to step aside. If you change your position on a particular matter in order to gain a trade off for a position or positions you have committed to support, you must weigh the decision a determine if the position you’re giving up balances the scales with the new one you supported. Did your trade off result in an equal or higher benefit to the people of the United States and particularly the constituents that elected you? If you did so to gain any personal or career advantages, then you should resign or be recalled. You must SAY WHAT YOU MEAN AND MEAN WHAT YOU SAY. If you ‘misstated’ your views during the election or substantially change them after winning, then you must explain to the voters the logic behind your change in position or you are guilty of fraud and should be removed from office and punished if necessary. To do otherwise you are not ‘representing’ your electorate in the manner you described to them during your campaign. You must commit that no outside influence, other than those of the people who elected you and the citizens of the United States will temp you to change your stated positions. If tempted, you must refuse the temptation. The most significant problem in our government is that there are no, or a very small number of such people in our government. If you do not represent the people who elected you in the manner you described in your campaign, then you are a criminal, a fraud, and a cheat.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1361997132280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:32:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361997400035-53</Id><Topic><Title>Based on the email I got from the "Organizing for Action" group ricky must be right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361994002020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:40:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What they don't share is the total still left in those budgets that are being impacted. They don't tell you that they still have enough to perform the functions at the same level as last year. What they neglect to add is that many of these programs should have been cut completely, not just cut back because they are not providing the benefit expected from the dollars allocated in the first place. What they fail to add is that this is the process that companies and families have to fight through on a daily basis. They fail to add that the Royalty in Washington is to never be denied what they desire or they will make you pay. This is sad political theater at its worst.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361997400035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:36:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361997500658-54</Id><Topic><Title>Based on the email I got from the "Organizing for Action" group ricky must be right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361994002020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:40:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In case you've forgotten, Froggie, the Tea Brains designed these cuts to be so distasteful that Congress would HAVE to act to stave them off. I am not certain why you think they'll be a cakewalk.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361997500658</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:38:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361997612100-55</Id><Topic><Title>What if Republicans...?</Title><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1361976595178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He didn't ask me either. Nice deflection though.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361997612100</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:40:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361999247035-56</Id><Topic><Title>The status quo won't get it done</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361905483547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:04:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is a bit of a crisis. When the Tea Brains pushed the SuperCommittee as part of their debt ceiling fiasco, they intended these cuts to be so bad it would force even them to compromise. Now they're pretending its no big deal. Well, it is a big deal. Especially when lumped on top of the payroll tax increase they got in Dec. How many furlough days, lay offs and tax increases can working people take?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1361999247035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:07:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361999450909-57</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES AT&amp;T</Title><Username>whitlockjohn510</Username><Timestamp>1361876686315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 06:04:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good news</Msg><Username>rubenjones55</Username><Timestamp>1361999450909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:10:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361999723027-58</Id><Topic><Title>$ T Featured on MAD MONEY</Title><Username>kevinlee899</Username><Timestamp>1361805521276</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 10:18:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good update.</Msg><Username>daniel.smith363</Username><Timestamp>1361999723027</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:15:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362001019674-59</Id><Topic><Title>Based on the email I got from the "Organizing for Action" group ricky must be right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361994002020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:40:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A famous Senator (Daniel Patrick Moynihan) once said: "Everyone is entitled to their own opinions, but they are not entitled to their own facts." So your statement: "In case you've forgotten, Froggie, the Tea Brains designed these cuts to be so distasteful that Congress would HAVE to act to stave them off. " is factually incorrect. It is well documented that the so called "sequestration" was the brain child of the President and his staff as reported in the Washington Post: "On July 12, 2011 the White House staff turned to [White House national economic council director Gene] Sperling for details about a compulsory trigger if they didn’t cut spending or raise taxes in an amount at least equivalent to the debt ceiling increase. “A trigger would lock in our commitment,” Sperling explained. “Even though we disagree on the composition of how to get to the cuts, it would lock us in. The form of the automatic sequester would punish both sides. We’d have to September to avert any sequester” — a legal obligation to make spending cuts. I know this fact goes against all that you believe and have been told by your "dear leader" and his party, but sometimes you need to put on your big boy pants and admit you are wrong. I know that you still believe, like your "dear leader", that "If you tell a lie big enough and keep repeating it, people will eventually come to believe it." You could be right. I guess we will see, but there are still many people who know the truth, and the truth will set them free. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1362001019674</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:36:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362001232034-60</Id><Topic><Title>Has the gun control agenda changed since the civil war?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361799267020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 08:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you just looking for attention, because the real world shuns you? Your posts are so ridiculous there is no other explanation. Maybe if one yours had been shot and their brains scattered on the walls, you wold have stoppet to think awhile. maybe ak yourself some questions, and realize yiu were wrong. Since everything is away from you, how easy and callous it is to ignore the reality of overpowered weapons alowed to the public. You just don't think.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1362001232034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:40:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362001536253-61</Id><Topic><Title>Has the gun control agenda changed since the civil war?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361799267020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 08:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not about Gun control, it's about people control!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1362001536253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:45:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362002264954-62</Id><Topic><Title>Has the gun control agenda changed since the civil war?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361799267020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 08:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have had 2 of my friends shot an killed in a home invasion here in Phoenix by a gang, most likely illegal aliens. My friends didn't have guns but if they did I'm sure the outcome would have been different. But their dead, so we will never know. As for the cops, they came, mopped up, filled out their silly little paperwork and after that could not care a less. No one has been caught, charged and probably not ever persued. The cops don't care. But they care if you're driving without a seat belt! That's $150 in revenue.</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1362002264954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:57:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362002501003-63</Id><Topic><Title>Has the gun control agenda changed since the civil war?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361799267020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 08:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee Froggie, why let their actual positions and actions get in the way when you can just make sh** up? You should try reality. Call me nuts, but I think Americans take moderate, pragmatic steps without fearing secret invasion by the "progressive agenda" or the "fascist agenda" or whatever agenda you dream up. You're one step away from complete loon here. If you're worried about an "agenda" it should be the Tea Brain "agenda".</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1362002501003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:01:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362003415001-64</Id><Topic><Title>Based on the email I got from the "Organizing for Action" group ricky must be right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361994002020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:40:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey win, Did you see this one from the "Washington Post": Education Secretary Arne Duncan said Sunday on CBS’s “Face the Nation.” : “There are literally teachers now who are getting pink slips, who are getting notices that they can’t come back this fall,” But on Wednesday when he was asked (during a White House press briefing) if he could come up with an example of where "sequestration" was causing the issuance of pink slips. Duncan named a single county in West Virginia and acknowledged, “whether it’s all sequester-related, I don’t know.” It turns out that Officials in Kanawha County, West Virginia say that the “transfer notices” sent to at least 104 educators had more to do with a separate matter that involves a change in the way West Virginia allocates federal dollars designated for poor children. The transfer notices are required by state law and give teachers a warning that they may be moved to a different position next school year. They don’t necessarily mean a teacher has been laid off, said Pam Padon, director of federal programs and Title 1 for the Kanawha County public schools. “It’s not like we’re cutting people’s jobs at this point.” She said those 104 notices will ultimately result in the elimination of about five to six teaching jobs, which were likely to be cut regardless of the sequester. In addition, the county notified all of its Head Start teachers that they may be out of a job, not because of sequestration, but because the Obama administration had recently labeled the Kanawha County program “deficient”, a designation that requires it to compete for funding instead of getting an automatic renewal. And there came a day when the real wolf showed up, and ate the little boy who yelled wolf once too often. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1362003415001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:16:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362004999403-65</Id><Topic><Title>Based on the email I got from the "Organizing for Action" group ricky must be right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361994002020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:40:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares? It's what you Tea Brains demanded to not send our country into bankruptcy , remember? Do you remember the debt ceiling debacle at all? If a #$%$ comes to rob you and you say "take whatever you want, just don't hurt my family" was it you who demanded they take whatever they want? These cuts are what the Tea Brains demanded, or they'd send our country into bankruptcy. Obama wanted to pay our bills, remember?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1362004999403</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:43:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362006821028-66</Id><Topic><Title>Based on the email I got from the "Organizing for Action" group ricky must be right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361994002020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:40:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, OK ricky I give up. Senator Moynihan's quote should be edited: In the case of ricky the quote should read: "Ricky is entitled to his own opinions, and is entitled to his own facts." Hope this makes you happy. As far as your statement: These cuts are what the Tea Brains demanded, or they'd send our country into bankruptcy. Obama wanted to pay our bills, remember? To some degree you are correct, Republicans are trying to get spending cuts, because they understand that when our "dear leader" use the old canard of a "balanced approach", what that really means is let us raise taxes now and we will talk about spending cuts later. Historically later never comes. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1362006821028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 18:13:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362010998557-67</Id><Title>GUN CONTROL</Title><Msg>In the health bill they screwed up it say there is no way the us gov.can take our guns even with a pres, ex, order. May they should have read it. What a bunch of fools.</Msg><Username>vetteman1939</Username><Timestamp>1362010998557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:23:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362011211479-68</Id><Topic><Title>Based on the email I got from the "Organizing for Action" group ricky must be right</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361994002020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:40:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Who cares?" Well it is obvious that the White House cares. Because CNN just reported that Bob Woodward (who chronicled the White house's involvement with developing "sequestration") stated: A "very senior person" at the White House warned him that he would "regret doing this," (i.e., continue reporting about the origins of sequestration) So I retract everything that I said, and ricky is right. "In your heart you know ricky is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1362011211479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:26:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362017070106-69</Id><Title>Treasury Secretary Lew is an Obamanation</Title><Msg>This guy has more money hidden off shore than Romney ever dreamed of. Aren't we sending the wrong message to investors. Pay your fair share Lew!</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1362017070106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 21:04:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362017458598-70</Id><Title>Hagel supported by Screwy Louie Con</Title><Msg>Farrakhan, that is. Tells you all you need to know.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1362017458598</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 21:10:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362024774409-71</Id><Topic><Title>Has the gun control agenda changed since the civil war?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1361799267020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 08:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Policies should simply channeled fully formed from corporate lobbyists.' And all too often that is the case. The talent in Washington, at least in the elected official kingdom is not smart enough to develop those policies on their own. By the way, Mr. Grammar, that is an incorrect use of the word channeled. Have a wonderful night dreaming of King Obama.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1362024774409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 23:12:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362024962962-72</Id><Topic><Title>The status quo won't get it done</Title><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1361905483547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:04:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another attempt at sanity that has failed miserably. Good show.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1362024962962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 23:16:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362025098226-73</Id><Topic><Title>What if Republicans...?</Title><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1361976595178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have rightfully earned the infamous 'ignore' feature being implemented on your sorry #$%$ Have a good life in your MR home.</Msg><Username>willy_etter</Username><Timestamp>1362025098226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 23:18:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>