<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-13"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360747704112-1</Id><Title>AAPL stock price prediction</Title><Msg>The stock price is in a meltdown right now. By the end of March 2013, the stock price will drop to below the $370 mark, no matter what Apple does unless they announce a totally new revolutionary product. Adding bells-and-whistles to the I-Phone will not do. Tim Cook wasn't able to do any damage control, if anything, he made the situation much worse. Again, it is appropriate to ask, if Apple isn't a hardware manufacturer, exactly what is it? A fruit stand?</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360747704112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 04:28:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360762219511-2</Id><Topic><Title>After the landslide vote in November, are the American people starting to suffer from buyers remorse?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360714177910</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:09:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Please explain that one." A dumbed down America and an ever growing number of takers.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360762219511</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:30:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360764138358-3</Id><Title>coolin_out47...</Title><Msg>... !! (exposed) (??) (ya nosey ole whoopie cushion) "whacko's” – coolin_out47 Doctor Jekyll, who often battles internally with the good and evil within himself, creates a potion to attempt to mask his personal hidden evil. In so doing, however, he transforms himself into the evil Mr. Hyde. jon, on the other hand, having already transformed himself into zonbac98, like Jekyll becomes dependent on his personal choice of magic elixir, a mixture of Mountain Dew, grain alcohol, Red Bull, Southern Comfort, nectar of bee pollen, Jack Daniels, ground up Cialis, chlorpromazine, Rogaine and prune juice, with a Pamabrom chaser for bloating and puffiness, served in a 55 gallon drum with a real beach umbrella and a spiked watermelon on a Confederate Civil War (replica) sword, given to him at a gun show by Doris Ziffel. After consuming two or three of these, as he did last night, he further transforms himself into coolin_out47, which unlike Jekyll’s transformation from good to evil, results in his plummeting from merely insidious stupidity to downright chowderheaded asininity. Fortunately for jon, no one knows about this secret metamorphosis…well, other than his “puppy”…and his Doctor…oh, and his parole officer also knows…and his friends at his group therapy sessions in the ward…and then there’s all you guys…but, other than that, it’s jon’s little secret. Sh-h-h-h-h-h!”(!!)??”(giggle) “snark”Tee-Hee</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360764138358</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:02:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360769080147-4</Id><Topic><Title>More threats when 'compromise' isn't achieved</Title><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1360594739259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:58:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe that Chick-fil-et is a business and provides jobs but the Chicago Mayor doesn't want them because their president doesn't approve of the gay life style so the company "doesn't come up to the Chicago Standards".</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360769080147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:24:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360769129996-5</Id><Topic><Title>After the landslide vote in November, are the American people starting to suffer from buyers remorse?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360714177910</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:09:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know I am! And I didn't even vote for the worst ever president of the United States!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1360769129996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:25:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360769358970-6</Id><Topic><Title>Uncle Joe sure has a way with words</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360675475336</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 08:24:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was about as long, as disjointed, confusing, makes little or no sense rant as I have seen in years! Put down the bottle or your blow and cool out.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1360769358970</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:29:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360769487457-7</Id><Topic><Title>More threats when 'compromise' isn't achieved</Title><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1360594739259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:58:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“The problem with ideology is, if you've got an ideology, you've already got your mind made up. You know all the answers and that makes evidence irrelevant and arguments a waste of time. You tend to govern by assertion and attacks.” – Bill Clinton, 2006 Pretty much tells the story of the Obama years.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1360769487457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:31:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360769956493-8</Id><Title>For chart believers</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/echarts?s=T#symbol=t;range=1y;compare=;indicator=dividend+sma%2850,200%29+bollinger+volume+stochasticslow;charttype=candlestick;crosshair=on;ohlcvalues=1;logscale=off;source=undefined; The chart seems to indicate that the run up this morning may be followed by one more before a pull back to around the $34. If you plan to hold through the minor pull back, you can make some extra income by selling the March $34 calls for $1.80 and buying them back for $.90 later this month. JMHO</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360769956493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:39:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360771657961-9</Id><Topic><Title>After the landslide vote in November, are the American people starting to suffer from buyers remorse?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360714177910</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:09:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That woman that got 30 Obama Phones got her phone bill the other day and she REALLY has buyers remorse. She now think Obama should be impeached.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360771657961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:07:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360772898902-10</Id><Title>Obama seeks 29 new programs!</Title><Msg>“Let me repeat: Nothing I’m proposing tonight should increase our deficit by a single dime.” It will be more like another 6 Trillion!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1360772898902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:28:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360773089145-11</Id><Topic><Title>After the landslide vote in November, are the American people starting to suffer from buyers remorse?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360714177910</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:09:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, Maybe you would like to fill us in on all of the ones where the approve was higher than the disapprove. Should be an interesting list. By the way the Gallup three day rolling average for February 13, does show an approval rating of 52% with a disapproval of 42% Another landslide "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360773089145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:31:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360774579410-12</Id><Topic><Title>After the landslide vote in November, are the American people starting to suffer from buyers remorse?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360714177910</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:09:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>6 milion more jobs=Obama. Takers=GWB failed, rich first, economic policies. Dumbed down =segregationist neofascist party, aka the tea party. The two parallel little lines means equals.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1360774579410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:56:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360775981155-13</Id><Topic><Title>After the landslide vote in November, are the American people starting to suffer from buyers remorse?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360714177910</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:09:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"6 milion more jobs" Really! Try this: Huff Post Fact Check, Feb. 13, 2013 "OBAMA: "After years of grueling recession, our businesses have created over 6 million new jobs." THE FACTS: That's in the ballpark, as far as it goes. But Obama starts his count not when he took office, but from the point in his first term when job losses were the highest. In doing so, he ignores the 5 million or so jobs that were lost on his watch, up to that point. Private sector jobs have grown by 6.1 million since February 2010. But since he became president, the gain is a more modest 1.9 million. And when losses in public sector employment are added to the mix, his overall jobs record is a gain of 1.2 million." Somehow I'm not smelling the same roses you are. As I said earlier, a dumbed down America.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360775981155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:19:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360780196820-14</Id><Topic><Title>Retirement Offer?</Title><Username>kcckks</Username><Timestamp>1360728193378</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 23:03:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Their offer for the future appears to be: You can quit now, while you still have a retirement, or we will make it miserable for you to keep working. On top of that, we will figure out ways to take away 20-40% of your retirement. It is age discrimination, but you will not be able to prove it.</Msg><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1360780196820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:29:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360780786270-15</Id><Topic><Title>Major T Pre Promotion Report!</Title><Username>jasonbrown668</Username><Timestamp>1360762764174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:39:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful info</Msg><Username>skinner.ellis</Username><Timestamp>1360780786270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:39:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360783204182-16</Id><Topic><Title>Major T Pre Promotion Report!</Title><Username>jasonbrown668</Username><Timestamp>1360762764174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:39:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great one!</Msg><Username>annanovak575</Username><Timestamp>1360783204182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:20:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360784479061-17</Id><Topic><Title>After the landslide vote in November, are the American people starting to suffer from buyers remorse?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360714177910</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:09:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That all depends on how you present the numbers. Were they new jobs? Were they simply rehires of those that lost their jobs in the last four years? Were they all low paying jobs and the reason behind his push for the increase in the minimum wage? Most of the 'fact' checker sites; both liberal and conservative have expressed doubts around the legitimacy of that number and many others of his claims, like the increase in mileage being doubled since he came into office. His claims of the successes of the ‘green’ energy efforts he touts are deceptive at best and an outlandish lie typically. They can present the UE numbers anyway they want, the fact remains is that there are more people out of work today than any time in our history and certainly since he took office. He has failed at nearly every campaign promise and he refuses to lead, only to campaign forever. Why, when our economy is still failing does he need to fly all around the country to give a speech that most don't believe anyway? Why can't he make those same speeches from Washington? Does he not understand the philosophy of unnecessary spending and conserving what bits of the nation’s treasury he can? Housing prices are increasing but people still don’t have jobs to afford a home. He wants to find new ways to get voters into homes…the Democratic Party efforts to increase home ownership in the past is a large part of the reason for our current economic conditions. Does he want to repeat those? My God why? His speech last night was full of factual errors, highflying political platitudes and empty promises and call for more spending. He could be successful without revising the tax codes if he were smart...we don't need more taxes, we need more taxpayers.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1360784479061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:41:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360784557069-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama seeks 29 new programs!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1360772898902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:28:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee, where have we heard that campaign promise before? Oh yeah, a little over four years ago. My how time flies when you down and out.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1360784557069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:42:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360784720796-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama seeks 29 new programs!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1360772898902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:28:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He learned that dime thing from Bill Clinton. It is a true statement but 99% of people don't analyze what is being said. I turned his speech off after about 5 minutes. I couldn't stand all those idiots clapping every time he told another lie.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360784720796</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:45:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360785897420-20</Id><Topic><Title>For chart believers</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360769956493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:39:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No chart believers on this board?? I make one or two hundred dollars a day with only a $4,000 investment by watching the charts on AT&amp;T. A month ago I only had $2,000. I use the weekly options and don't win them all but enough to average over $100 a day. I figure that if I double my money every month for a year I will have 16 Billion, less taxes. Well, if I can just get back the $300,000 I have lost in the stock market I will be happy; and it will be tax free.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360785897420</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:04:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360786580866-21</Id><Topic><Title>For chart believers</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360769956493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:39:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know about charts but I know $35.60 is a brick wall for this stock.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1360786580866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:16:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360788311010-22</Id><Topic><Title>For chart believers</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360769956493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:39:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$35.81 was the high today and I sold 35.5 calls for 30 cents and bought them back for 20 cents. Had I been more patient I could have bought them back for 9 cents now. I don't usually trade in and out in the same day because, if you do it three times in a week they lock up your account. Day trading requires at least $25,000. I don't expect T to go above $36 until after a pull back to near $34. but I expect to be above $36 by the end of the month.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360788311010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:45:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360791711558-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama seeks 29 new programs!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1360772898902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:28:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He says we can't cut our way to prosperity. We can't spend our way to prosperity either, particularly when we will soon be struggling to pay the interest on the money we have already overspent. Most of his plans call for increased spending. How can he claim it won't cost anymore? What he means is that it won't cost anymore than he has already planned to spend. Just another political shell game and he thinks we aren't smart enough to see it. He may be correct because collectively we haven't been smart enough to stop it.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1360791711558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:41:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360796536853-24</Id><Topic><Title>Major T Pre Promotion Report!</Title><Username>jasonbrown668</Username><Timestamp>1360762764174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:39:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAMMER !!</Msg><Username>daxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360796536853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:02:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360796546696-25</Id><Topic><Title>Major T Pre Promotion Report!</Title><Username>jasonbrown668</Username><Timestamp>1360762764174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:39:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAMMER !!</Msg><Username>daxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360796546696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:02:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360799612974-26</Id><Title>Another low volume session....</Title><Msg>...5th straight under 20mil - before that only 1 day all year under 20mil - ?????????</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1360799612974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:53:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360801233781-27</Id><Topic><Title>Another low volume session....</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1360799612974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:53:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At 2:25 to 2:30 700,000 shares traded but volume was low most of the day. The last hour, when the price was low, volume picked up considerably. So we do have some support. I think we are due for a correction back to about $34 before we resume the climb to $40 in May. JMHO</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360801233781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:20:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360806568118-28</Id><Topic><Title>Retirement Offer?</Title><Username>kcckks</Username><Timestamp>1360728193378</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 23:03:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sad, but true. It appears if you are retirement eligible, the longer you stay, the less retirement lump sum. The union sold these folks out.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1360806568118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:49:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360808352884-29</Id><Topic><Title>After the landslide vote in November, are the American people starting to suffer from buyers remorse?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360714177910</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:09:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"After years of grueling recession, our businesses have created over 6 million new jobs." What part of that don't you understand? Not only has Obama added 6 million jobs since the bottom of the recession, he turned around an economy that was shedding 900,000 jobs a month.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360808352884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:19:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360809030665-30</Id><Topic><Title>After the landslide vote in November, are the American people starting to suffer from buyers remorse?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360714177910</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:09:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the fact remains is that there are more people out of work today than any time in our history " What an idiotic statement. There were more unemployed people in 2012. And before that, 2011. We number of unemployed peaked in 2010, just before Obama's efforts turned the economy around and added 6 million private sector jobs. I thought the employment numbers were all lies, anyway, winholder?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360809030665</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:30:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360809205182-31</Id><Topic><Title>For chart believers</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360769956493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:39:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You made $2000 in a month, and you think you'll turn it into $16 billion in a year? Be careful with that. You're very gullible.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360809205182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:33:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360812376298-32</Id><Topic><Title>For chart believers</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360769956493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:39:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't really care about intra day highs - I'm talking about closing prices.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1360812376298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:26:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>