<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372824069388-1</Id><Topic><Title>Wow! Negative for the day again</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372790593889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 14:43:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hahahahahahah</Msg><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1372824069388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 00:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372855749737-2</Id><Topic><Title>You got to hand it to old Mr. Slick</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372810076081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 20:07:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well Frogg, I heard Axelrod just the morning say the decision to delay had nothing to do with the up coming midterm election. So, there you have it. The truth and nothing but the truth.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1372855749737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372857137116-3</Id><Topic><Title>You got to hand it to old Mr. Slick</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372810076081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 20:07:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“Well Frogg, I heard Axelrod just the morning say the decision to delay had nothing to do with the up coming (sic) midterm election. So, there you have it. The truth and nothing but the truth.” – t.bfine Typical...much ado about nothing. Hey, boys, your own Chamber of Commerce and The National Retail Federation seems to disagree with you...obviously you and frogboy seem to think you know more about business than they do, because they called it ”the right and wise approach”. It seems you really don’t care what the subject is, but if it comes from this Administration, it’s gotta’ be bad. How pathetically un-American. “Business groups including the U.S. Chamber of Commerce -- which largely opposed the health care law called the Affordable Care Act, or ACA -- have long sought a delay in the rules requiring them to report on their employees' health coverage and to pay penalties. ‘They're not ready, we're not ready, and rather than plow ahead, they're going to take the right and wise approach,’ said Neil Trautwein, employee benefits policy counsel for the National Retail Federation. ‘The last thing the administration or the business community needs is for the ACA to come out of the gate sideways.’ – Huff Post Business, 7/2</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1372857137116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:12:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372857860313-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare to hit low income earners the hardest</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1371226801124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This just may be what brings down the NObama administration. This will turn out to be an utter failure and when the "low informed" voter figures it out the worm turns big time.</Msg><Username>igurumo</Username><Timestamp>1372857860313</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:24:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372860040634-5</Id><Topic><Title>Situation worsens for White South Africans</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372661795393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 02:56:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hahahahahahaha, you saying it won't make it come true, hahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1372860040634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:00:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372861538869-6</Id><Topic><Title>hail the duckheads</Title><Username>insider117</Username><Timestamp>1372774037567</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 10:07:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes......ex--date coming soon. Must own by the close this Friday (5th) to qualify to receive the dividend.</Msg><Username>buyingtime4me</Username><Timestamp>1372861538869</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:25:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372862583305-7</Id><Topic><Title>You got to hand it to old Mr. Slick</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372810076081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 20:07:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Echo, do you think Obama made the postponement decision or did he learn of it from a newspaper?</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1372862583305</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:43:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372863880136-8</Id><Topic><Title>Situation worsens for White South Africans</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372661795393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 02:56:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There are still 14M more people out of work that there were in 2001" No there's not. The number of unemployed now is just over 11 million now (and declining) so you are clearly lying.. There are, however, almost 8 million more people employed now than in 2001. Your need to lie about how bad things are is very telling. It's either pathological or Obama is a much better president than you want people to know.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1372863880136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372866070814-9</Id><Topic><Title>You got to hand it to old Mr. Slick</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372810076081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 20:07:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously you were unable to comprehend my previous post, so I will try again: If you actually read my last post, you would have read that I actually praised our "dear leader" for postponing the 2014 implementation activities until 2015. Further I applauded his political aplomb for recognizing the political ramifications that would result from the 2014 implementation. As for the U.S. Chamber of Commerce and the National Retail Federation their positions and words are well founded and have merit. As far as my comments regarding the Republican leadership I stand by those words and still maintain that they feckless and sorely wanting in their abilities to play in the "Big Boy" arena with the current occupier of 1600 Pennsylvania Ave. As far as your comment: Typical...much ado about nothing. ... Really! Really! You indicate much ado about nothing even after you include the comments from the U.S. Chamber of Commerce and the National Retail Federation. Sometimes I don't think you read your own posts. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372866070814</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:41:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372867127359-10</Id><Topic><Title>You got to hand it to old Mr. Slick</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372810076081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 20:07:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even Ron Paul &amp; Family INC nauseate me. In retrospect, I think he was similar to Dennis Kucinich, a loud critic of the U.S. govt but an entrenched party operative. They could lecture and vote in opposition to the majority simply because they were no threat to the majority vote. Both made it appear as though freedom and democracy exists. Real useful tools, imo, probably willing tools</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372867127359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:58:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372867630432-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare to hit low income earners the hardest</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1371226801124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are the low informed voter.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1372867630432</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:07:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372868572898-12</Id><Topic><Title>Situation worsens for White South Africans</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372661795393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 02:56:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is White genocide occurring in South Africa while the colored fella occupying the White House visits there to be among HIS people. A $100,000,000 was spent on him and his family`s visit to their ancestors` land. Did he even mention the White slaughter? His silence during the visit was an implied, yet bold, statement that the slaughter is of no importance to him, maybe even a statement of approval. Prepare if you are White. The colored fella and his kind are taking over the country and government, you are being pushed out of your own country.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372868572898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:22:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372870161539-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare to hit low income earners the hardest</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1371226801124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I had Kaiser-Permanente from 1971 til last year. Never had an increase in my co-pays. I'm sure my company and later SS did get increases on the primary premium. I'm in Arizona and have another insurer. Just got notification of a 20% increase in my premium Plus, I pay a large deductible until I pay a certain amount each year. I and my family got excellent care through Kaiser all those years. Health insurers get in bed with state pols and pass laws that make it almost impossible for HMO's like Kaiser to come into their states. I think it was probably the insurers behind Obama Care. "Our?" representatives voted on a bill they knew nothing about. A criminal act as far as I'm concerned.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1372870161539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372870367972-14</Id><Topic><Title>Will Egypt Lead The WAY !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372726911171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.... IS IT TRUE, early reports indicate the 'heavely armed' 'Egyptian troops now have control of Morsi's headquarters .. and are going through the mooslim brotha-hood documents !! BTW .. has anyone 'ever' heard Obama publicly denounce Sharia Law ??</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372870367972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:52:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372871012971-15</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare to hit low income earners the hardest</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1371226801124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt Obama(or whoever he is) understood or even read the Affordable Care Act. He strikes me as too stupid and too lazy to have ever come up with such a wonderful plan for the insurance companies. Has he ever discussed it without a teleprompter?</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372871012971</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:03:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372871833144-16</Id><Title>What`s so important about Snowden? Nothing?</Title><Msg>I don`t get it. Why is there so much controversy about Snowden`s supposed disclosures? I thought everyone already knew that everything they did on the internet, phone and in public places was probably being watched and possibly recorded. Is something else going on that the news medias, both mainstream and alternative, are trying to distract from? It`s not like Snowden`s revelations are gonna bring down the colored fella. No way, those who installed him will never remove him. He can do whatever he wants, golf all day, vacation, whatever, as long as he does not cross his benefactors. He is an in your face 24/7 reminder to Whites that they are being kicked out of their own country, which I think was the main reason he was installed. The criminal elite get to enjoy rubbing our noses in his arrogance and our elimination from our own country.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372871833144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:17:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872971989-17</Id><Topic><Title>What`s so important about Snowden? Nothing?</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372871833144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently he left the country with a laptop full of additional information that may or may not have anything to do with phone calls. He is basically a traitor if he shares any further secrets with a foreign government. If he felt he was right to do what he did, and didn't do it for money, etc. he could have stayed here and been a hero in the media.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1372872971989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:36:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372873060057-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare to hit low income earners the hardest</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1371226801124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why not, there are more unemployed that when he ran the first time, lets just add unemployed to the increasing list of poor and now sick people under his watch.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1372873060057</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:37:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372873307268-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare to hit low income earners the hardest</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1371226801124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes 'lew' .. for years.(at least 20) when involved in group discussions about insurance complaints .. my question to the group discussion was - what would happen if one day everyone decided to 'cancel ALL insurance', heath, auto, home, etc .. as a solidarity movement - to force companies to fall back into fairness !! I have never complained about any reasonable responsible insurance company. However now .. AND and it started with 'former first lady' Hillary, under the Clinton Administration, with her 'behind the scene' effort to impose a covert National Insurance Plan - but back then Congress stopped it in it's tracks, with much admonishment towards towards Hillary. Now, think about those early political deals between her and Obama, during the Democratic Presidential Campaign when it appeared that Obama was taking the lead .. and to get her to step back !! Oh what nasty deals they came up with for their politiical social agendas What we have today is the need for a nationwide solidarity movement. I still think, particularly today, it's more of us than it is of them !!</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372873307268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:41:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372873342218-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare to hit low income earners the hardest</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1371226801124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't look now Ricky but the ACA is the primary reason the Tea Party got started. It is failing daily. They are now delaying yet another provision of the law because it will cause a lot of local pain and he won't let that happen prior to the mid-term elections. He is running scared now and as more and more of this fiasco is known and found to be too expensive or even in some case unmanageable, he will not survive and neither will the Democrats in 2014.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1372873342218</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372873596504-21</Id><Topic><Title>You got to hand it to old Mr. Slick</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372810076081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 20:07:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"‘They're not ready, we're not ready, and rather than plow ahead, " Not plowing ahead didn't stop them from passing a set of laws they didn't understand or knew how to manage. They are not ready because they didn't know what they were doing and still haven't figured it out. They are delaying this for political reasons and for the fact that they are NOT ready. They don't understand how to be ready because they don't understand the full impact of this law. This was to be Obama's shinning star in the eastern sky that would make him a hero, instead it is making him and his followers look like the incompetent fool they are.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1372873596504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372873644672-22</Id><Topic><Title>You got to hand it to old Mr. Slick</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372810076081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 20:07:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harry probably had to tell him about it and suggest the move to delay because Harry don't want to lose his job.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1372873644672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372873811051-23</Id><Topic><Title>Will Egypt Lead The WAY !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372726911171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shouldn't denounce Sharia Law. He knows it and likes it. He should not denounce any law that the people vote to accept as their law for daily living. The problem is that most that are under Sharia Law didn't make the choice, they were told this is what will rule them. That is the way of Sharia Law.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1372873811051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:50:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372874105051-24</Id><Topic><Title>What have we learned today from our MSM?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1372450034388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:07:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must keep in the mind the new reality...if a white or Hispanic person makes a derogatory comment about a black person, that is racist...the reverse is no longer true.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1372874105051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:55:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372874176739-25</Id><Topic><Title>To all Posters</Title><Username>workhard1966</Username><Timestamp>1372789666261</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 14:27:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good luck with that.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1372874176739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:56:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372874732315-26</Id><Topic><Title>What`s so important about Snowden? Nothing?</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372871833144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well ??? .. It seems that Obama and his "left wing" own most of the media here - I think he had to go abroad. But it still backfired on him !! However .. it has the entire world goverments and their people thinking. My question is .. how did he get such a 'HIGH LEVEL Clearance" with his reported background ?? Nation Security should not be 'farmed out" .. but then again, can we trust our own Goverment ?? Who do we trust anymore .. not Obama, that's for sure !!</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372874732315</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:05:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372877571838-27</Id><Topic><Title>What`s so important about Snowden? Nothing?</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372871833144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"if he shares any further secrets" This directly from the State Department Page "Passport Information for Criminal Law Enforcement Officers", "Denial or revocation of a passport does not prevent the use of outstanding valid passports. . . The physical revocation of a passport is often difficult, and an apparently valid passport can be used for travel until officially taken by an arresting officer or by a court." Snowden is being held captive by Russia, by Russia's own initiative or by US request. Of course the US is requesting extradition so I think you can assume whatever is on his laptop is already shared. I'm sure China got what they wanted too. Snowden is not a diplomat and does not have the protection of his government or international law. I have no idea what he was thinking. He is a traitor and a dumb one at that. If you're upset about government surveillance you don't go to China or Russia, for crying out loud.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1372877571838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:52:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372879918484-28</Id><Topic><Title>What`s so important about Snowden? Nothing?</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372871833144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It does seem strange that a guy that is reported to have a HS education, couldn't make in the military gets a job with a top secret clearance at over $100K per year. Is the reporting incorrect, or is the NSA and its contractors just stupid?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1372879918484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372881988264-29</Id><Topic><Title>What`s so important about Snowden? Nothing?</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372871833144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep .. however one report that I read had reported that he dropped out of H.S. in his sophmore year .... Not a 'fact check' but I was also under the impression that in today's military, you had to be a H.S. graduate to enlist ? This same report stated that his short military career (7 or 8 mos.) ended in a 'General Discharge" ... It seems the NSA shouldn't allow any contractors to do background checks .. if these reports are accurate ?? I'm sure when D.O.D. did their b.g. check on me in 2007 (mid-level security clearance), they saw my 'conceal-carry permit' ??</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372881988264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:06:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372883119463-30</Id><Topic><Title>Will Egypt Lead The WAY !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372726911171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... BUT WAIT ... and Morsi isn't dead ?? But didn't Morsi publicly declared that he would "die" ... rather than be removed from office, for the Egyptian People and to preserve their 'democracy'. Waddaya mean he wasn't able to die as a "martyr" (??) Oh, I guess he was just kidding huh !! Mmm, I guess they just direct others to die, to prove their loyalty .. not the 'brotha-hood' leaders themselves .. it figures !!</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372883119463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:25:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372890537874-31</Id><Topic><Title>Will Egypt Lead The WAY !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372726911171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>,,,“BTW .. has anyone 'ever' heard Obama publicly denounce Sharia Law ??” – jon “He shouldn't denounce Sharia Law. He knows it and likes it.” – winholder Hey, children…if you learned nothing else from your humiliating defeat in the last election, you should have realized that your sophomoric “Birther” nonsense does not resonate well with the vast majority of sane Americans. It continues to make you look like the desperate, simpleton losers that you are with nothing whatsoever to contribute to society other than obstructionism. Yeah, the President of the United States wants to initiate Sharia law…what a childish and buffoonish statement!</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1372890537874</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:28:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372896178556-32</Id><Topic><Title>Will Egypt Lead The WAY !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372726911171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... poor eggo, what repetative buffoonish statements he continues to posts !! But I don't see where either of jon's, or win's post states "Yeah, the president of the United States wants to initiate Sharia Law" .. We only posted that HE (Obama), has NEVER CONDEMED Sharia Law !! Sharia Law is against every principle of our U.S. Constitution &amp; Biblicial upbringing, not to mention it's crimes against humanity, also comdemed by most countries on this earth .. why would anyone want kiss the butts of murders, rapist, and their Sharia Law - If you don't condem it, then you condone it ... they certainly don't mind publicly announcing they want to kill us !! There we have it folks, "echo2165" (the fake Marine) and his childish and buffoonish statements .. and another supporter of the brotha-hood &amp; Sharia Law !! signed - "echo dot 2, lower case L, 65" (echo.2l65)</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372896178556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:02:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372896868402-33</Id><Topic><Title>Will Egypt Lead The WAY !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372726911171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And if one wants the see the REAL news, instead of our U.S. MSM snip-its of spin .. try tunning into PBS 3. They've been running 'France 24' &amp; Algezzera into extended coverage since about 3:00 EST</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1372896868402</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:14:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372904551741-34</Id><Topic><Title>Wow! Negative for the day again</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372790593889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 14:43:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow up again ...when will this ever crash !! another up day after day positive for the day again ...</Msg><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1372904551741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 22:22:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372904594303-35</Id><Topic><Title>What`s so important about Snowden? Nothing?</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1372871833144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So far all he's done is blow the whistle on something I knew was being done back in the 60's. They have spied on anyone that disagreed with "Big Bubba" to varying degrees. You're right about treason though. He told the American people about the spying and "Big Bubba" considers us his enemies.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1372904594303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 22:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>