<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364446068863-1</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Keystone pipeline ever be approved?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1363902082055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No frew frew poodle-wannabe in a widdle skirt .. the yapping chihuahua of the T-board .. none of our group are in need of "mental healthcare" .. unlike you &amp; your group that have nothing to contribute but lots of yap-service !! Go hoover-up somewhere else ...</Msg><Username>coolin_out47</Username><Timestamp>1364446068863</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 00:47:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364452457786-2</Id><Title>Biggest Opportunity for Next Week</Title><Msg>Concurrent (CCUR) could explode next week very low float completely undiscovered yet the company is the world's #1 video on demand (VOD) technology provider to the cable TV industry with clients including 6 of America's top 8 largest cable TV companies. At current price of $7.84 CCUR's enterprise value is only $47.5mm or just 0.76x its revenue. Huge gross margins of 58% compared to CCUR's top rival Seachange (SEAC)'s gross margins of 50% yet SEAC is now trading with enterprise value/revenue ratio of 1.89, which will value CCUR over $15.50 per share! Look for CCUR to break $8 and explode next week - CCUR will likely be hottest play in the entire market! A $23 billion company Virgin Media (VMED) is now deploying CCUR's technology and almost nobody knows yet! CCUR's EPS has been rapidly growing each quarter faster than every other public technology company in existence! Last quarter CCUR's EPS was up 100% from quarter before and 300% from two quarters ago! CCUR's chart looks amazing, double digits should arrive very quickly after CCUR breaks $8!</Msg><Username>jtdmnf533</Username><Timestamp>1364452457786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 02:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364473861073-3</Id><Topic><Title>Not too late for the ride up</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1364395842306</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, jon, et. al. – You’ve bid us all farewell? Is that a promise?...meaning, that when you realize that you are wrong (which is normal)…when you realize that once again you are completely misinformed (which is normal)…when you realize that you have absolutely no idea what you’re talking about (which is normal)…when you have been shown that your standard sources of information are bogus and have no factual basis, whatsoever (which is normal)…when you realize that the finance message boards aren’t going anywhere, and that you have once again embarrassingly made a complete doofus bumpkin out of yourself (which is normal)… …do you PROMISE that you will never return, with any of your aliases? If so, please respond by having wilkes and douch give themselves 47 thumbs up, followed with delusionary self-congratulations on having done so while having fooled absolutely no one but themselves. “Well it's the end of the day and I have 3, so I win” – douch Yeah, you win, alright…pity and ridicule for being so pathetic as to think people are as gullible as you are.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1364473861073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 08:31:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364476052552-4</Id><Topic><Title>Not too late for the ride up</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1364395842306</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do they even bother to read the articles? Clearly not. This is why they're stupid.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1364476052552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 09:07:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364481512704-5</Id><Topic><Title>Organizing for Action (again)</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1364306714081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 10:05:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could this sort of thing be the reason that the media and the FBI report the statistics of murders committed with 'illegal' handguns? Oh, I forgot this justice department and administration doesn't understand the meaning of illegal when it comes to many things. They have this nasty habit of only enforcing laws they like, not necessarily those passed by Congress. A large number and growing of guns shows actually do ask that background checks be part of the rules.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1364481512704</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 10:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364482062423-6</Id><Topic><Title>We are on our way out and Obama is leading the way</Title><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1364321408280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 14:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our problems typically don't start with President's serving eight years; it begins and unfortunately too often doesn't end with 'professional' members of Congress. That is where most of the less than honest relationships with lobbyists are created, nurtured and reinforced. Members of Congress that are more and more often starting to thinks of themselves as some sort of powerful royalty rather and servants and representatives of the people are where most of our problems begin. They consistently create problems that then have to be solved in 'crisis' mode and while they, who created the problems, insist that we believe they are the only people on the planet with the intelligence and experience to solve these self-inflicted problems. The understand that if they keep sharing our treasury in huge displays of generosity toward the weak, helpless and in overabundance with the lazy, stupid and corrupt they will continue to vote for them. They perpetuate the philosophy that no one in their right mind would ever vote against someone willing to give them something for nothing.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1364482062423</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 10:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364482639778-7</Id><Topic><Title>We are on our way out and Obama is leading the way</Title><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1364321408280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 14:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many consider a full-on democracy to be where the majority rules. If the majority votes for an action, idea or law then it should be the law of the land; strange then that the people of California and several other states have voted, in large majorities to ban gay marriage but now it is being forced into court. What happened to majority rule in a democracy? Conveniently many liberals are convinced and will quote that ‘we won; we should get our way because the majority voted us in’. However when the majority votes for something they don’t like, they want the right to force their opinions on others regardless of the majority. I find that the concept of majority rule to be null and void if any minority complains. There was an example in the media this week where an Easter egg hunt was canceled because one family in the school complained. One family! There is no Constitutional right, or any other right to never be offended by something around you or a decision that you can avoid. We in America seem to have forgotten and forsaken many of these thoughts.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1364482639778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 10:57:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364482865619-8</Id><Topic><Title>We are on our way out and Obama is leading the way</Title><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1364321408280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 14:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What gives you the impression that Snopes is an authority or even right all the time? Because you say so? You say a lot, a lot of what is ignored by many or scorned and ridiculed by others. I suggest you jump off the wagon before it picks up too much more speed. Your opinion here is worth exactly the amount we paid to receive it...ZERO!</Msg><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1364482865619</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 11:01:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364487561051-9</Id><Topic><Title>OH .. SAY IT AIN'T SO !!</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1364423228287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 18:27:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“I couldn't resist playing off the headline .. or post it too close to APRIL 1st. (chuckles) !!!!!!!” - jon OH, JON!... you are such a clever scoundrel…and we all thought you were just stupid…but you were only joking with all your farewells. And to make sure we all knew you were only joking, you immediately posted a second message suggesting your ignorance was, in fact, an April Fool’s joke. Sure, jon, everybody makes April Fool’s jokes 4 days in advance. You must look pretty silly shouting “Happy New Year” on December 27th, drinking green beer on March 13th, and trick or treating in your Village People costume on October 27th! Way to take responsibility for your actions, oh ye’ of the moral majority. Way to man up, you pathetic dweeb. That’s as bad as this: “What gives you the impression that Snopes is an authority or even right all the time? Because you say so?” – golf twerp (usganut) No, not because I said so. Because you posted a lie, which Snopes caught you in…because you stated that Joseph Olson said something, to which Joseph Olson, himself, replied denying that he said it. Because the facts were wrong, and they had been altered to fit three different candidates in various right wing blogs and emails over a decade. Because you people are blatant liars, who when exposed, then have the chutzpah to resort to some lame-a#s, blathering trying to deny your intentional efforts to deceive people. And you wonder why America rejects you.? BTW, Happy 4th of July, jon. (chuckles, grins, tee-hee, ;-)</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1364487561051</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:19:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364487587806-10</Id><Topic><Title>Not too late for the ride up</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1364395842306</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At noon today it looks like we are finally starting the run up I was talking about a week ago. Look for a much larger run up next week. AT&amp;T will announce the dividend date and the price should soar above $37. Remember to sell your calls and buy puts the day before the dividend.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1364487587806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364488015651-11</Id><Topic><Title>OH .. SAY IT AIN'T SO !!</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1364423228287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 18:27:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tis great to hear! That leaves investors village as the most prominent site to post investing messages. Spinners like ricky cannot survive there as board members discuss stocks not ricky's spinning BS! Yahoo will lose revenues as people like myself will not be visiting yahoo!!!!!!!!!! Poor ricky and incompetent poster with nowhere to post. So Sad!!!!!</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364488015651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:26:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364488419645-12</Id><Title>they get guns from obama ricky</Title><Msg>poor ricky asked where do people think guns come from - Mexico. Yes, ricky, they come from Mexico via Obama and Holder, or have you forgotten holder's gun sales to Mexican gangs which resulted in the shooting and death of a peace officer in the US. Of course you did not spout outrage at the heinous crime - after all, the action was generated by your worshipped one. that is why your posts are so disingenuous and rated so low. Like your exhalted one, you are a consummate liar! Poor spinning wicky will not longer have a communication vehicle to spew his lies. Poor poor little boy. So sad.</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364488419645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:33:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364488805094-13</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest Opportunity for Next Week</Title><Username>jtdmnf533</Username><Timestamp>1364452457786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 02:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Judging from their Income Statement http://finance.yahoo.com/q/is?s=CCUR+Income+Statement&amp;annual it is not very likely to "explode". It doesn't show the growth you mention and they have a pretty high P/E ratio.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1364488805094</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:40:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364489704419-14</Id><Topic><Title>they get guns from obama ricky</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364488419645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:33:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The gun running was a felony. NO ONE has been arrested. They admit that the derivatives Ponzi operation was a crime too. Again, NO ONE has been arrested.. It only means that criminals now run this government.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1364489704419</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:55:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364489821462-15</Id><Topic><Title>they get guns from obama ricky</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364488419645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:33:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even in the wettest of conservative nights, Holder did not sell guns to Mexican gangs. Not that we need it, but thank you for providing more evidence to judge your complete lack of integrity. What has you so upset are the gunwalking programs. If you'll recall, these programs involved BATF agents observing straw purchases but not intervening in the hopes of catching bigger fish. They did not observe all of the straw purchasers, nor did they succeed in taking down the big fish. Which means the big fish are still using an army of straw purchasers to buy guns legally and transfer or sell them to criminals, or to smuggle them into Mexico. So thank you also for providing more evidence to support my point, not that we need it.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1364489821462</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:57:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364489885839-16</Id><Topic><Title>OH .. SAY IT AIN'T SO !!</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1364423228287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 18:27:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahh, as dumb as you are dishonest.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1364489885839</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:58:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364490014803-17</Id><Title>Yahoo solves the SPAM problem</Title><Msg>Where will the spammers go now to steal free advertising? Where will I go to beat the drum for freedom in America and to warn people about Obama? I hope you can all get along without my financial advice. Yahoo message boards are just one more thing I never thought I would outlive.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1364490014803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 13:00:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364490097770-18</Id><Topic><Title>We are on our way out and Obama is leading the way</Title><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1364321408280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 14:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you aware that extremely rich people have financed most of the leftist groups including "Communism?" Ever wonder why? Lenin and Trotsky were both financed from U.S. and European banks. They would rather run the whole world than a corporation or single country. They will finance any thing that gives them that control and play one brain dead group off against another to retain that control.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1364490097770</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 13:01:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364491587848-19</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo solves the SPAM problem</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1364490014803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 13:00:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For real investment discussions and advice go to investors village. Not much on the t investors village board. Posters are not spinners and tend to focus on investing analysis.</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364491587848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 13:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364491707644-20</Id><Topic><Title>OH .. SAY IT AIN'T SO !!</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1364423228287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 18:27:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>poor little wicky, can't spin on investors village huh! Poor baby. No more of your spinning BS for investors to sift through. Spin away spinner you have a couple days left to your sad and lonely spinning life!</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364491707644</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 13:28:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364491807674-21</Id><Topic><Title>they get guns from obama ricky</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364488419645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:33:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor widdle wicky spinning again, only a couple of days more for your lying spinning ways then you are off to oblivion!!!! Sad! widdle pinner with no one to spin to, sad! (NOT!)</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364491807674</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 13:30:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364491846403-22</Id><Topic><Title>they get guns from obama ricky</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364488419645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:33:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you saying that community organizers are criminals! Oh the surprise and shame!</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364491846403</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 13:30:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364492640949-23</Id><Topic><Title>they get guns from obama ricky</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364488419645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:33:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet you're also disappointed the world didn't end on May 21, 2011. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1364492640949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 13:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364492861689-24</Id><Topic><Title>they get guns from obama ricky</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364488419645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:33:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that the best your lobbyist could come up with for a response. Too much spinning for the leading spinner. So sad! You have my pity! There are places you can go for help. Start off at your local United Way! Wish you the best in your recovery!!!</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364492861689</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 13:47:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364493116113-25</Id><Topic><Title>they get guns from obama ricky</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364488419645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:33:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now it is official: If you are a criminal in one of these three major cities, Chicago, Los Angeles and New York, your chances of facing prosecution for federal gun law crimes is the least in the nation (i.e., of the 90 jurisdictions the districts of Eastern New York, Central California, and Northern Illinois ranked 88th, 89th and 90th, respectively) Is there a pattern here? "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364493116113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 13:51:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364493416574-26</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo solves the SPAM problem</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1364490014803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 13:00:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. I notice the posts about T are years old but I guess we can fix that real quick.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1364493416574</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 13:56:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364494966861-27</Id><Topic><Title>they get guns from obama ricky</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364488419645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:33:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are also the areas with some of the toughest state and local gun laws and sentences. Which means more cases are prosecuted in state courts instead of Federal courts. Federal guns laws are very specific as well. For instance, since gun sales are prohibited in Chicago you simply won't see prosecutions for attempts to buy a gun by a felon. Syracuse-TRAC, which authored the report La Pierre referred to, noted that state and local prosecutions "dwarf" Federal prosecutions. Nice try, though. You can find the report by searching for "TRAC Reports: Federal Weapons Enforcement: A Moving Target"</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1364494966861</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 14:22:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364495061243-28</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo solves the SPAM problem</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1364490014803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 13:00:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to the press release I read (March 1, 2013) the sports and financial message boards will still be supported. Unless things have changed since then, ricky/echo will still be able to spin their propaganda. I guess we will see. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364495061243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 14:24:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364497593927-29</Id><Topic><Title>they get guns from obama ricky</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364488419645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:33:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How does that work? Does ricky cut and paste our posts and e-mail them to some democrap website where they review them, compile a response, e-mail the response back to ricky and ricky posts the response? I just don't think he's that smart! It's gotta be coming from somewhere else. A whole team of people would be my guess. How much do you think he gets paid? By the hour or by the post?</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1364497593927</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 15:06:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364498632378-30</Id><Topic><Title>T is one of top picks like crimson on apex</Title><Username>gibbstyler167</Username><Timestamp>1364482405912</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 10:53:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This looks familiar...</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1364498632378</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 15:23:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364499173402-31</Id><Topic><Title>they get guns from obama ricky</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364488419645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:33:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I just don't think he's that smart!" That smart to do what? Read the article under the headline? Look at the budget tables attached to the budget proposals? Look at the source documents? What exactly do you think I do that is so "smart" that it requires a whole team of people?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1364499173402</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 15:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364501660211-32</Id><Title>financial posters go to investor village</Title><Msg>If you are interested in stock postings, check our investor village as yahoo shuts down message boards. The board is not friendly to posters like the spinner. Posters, though few for t, are more interested in stock data and there are little to no spammers. This will hurt yahoo as I know that it is unlikely that I will be back to yahoo for much.</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364501660211</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 16:14:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364503300003-33</Id><Topic><Title>they get guns from obama ricky</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1364488419645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:33:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Colorado liberals in their infinite wisdom have passed guns laws that the majority of local sheriffs and other police agencies say they won't work to enforce because they are so ambiguous in their language they are practically unenforceable. Kind of like our tax laws. As for the gun walking programs, they knew for past Bush administration experience they didn't work so Obama and crew set out to prove it, succeeded and won't admit to the error's or prosecute anyone responsible for such a fiasco. That gives me great faith and confidence in this group of idiots and crooks.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1364503300003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 16:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364503422115-34</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo solves the SPAM problem</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1364490014803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 13:00:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On a sports message board I used to frequent, the message from Yahoo at the top of the board says they will no longer be available after 3-31 and there currently is not link post anything new or generate a reply.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1364503422115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 16:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364505688435-35</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>adrianosbourne651</Username><Timestamp>1364505688435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 17:21:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364507467226-36</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keylogger site...........</Msg><Username>basherbuste_r</Username><Timestamp>1364507467226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 17:51:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364507828614-37</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo solves the SPAM problem</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1364490014803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 13:00:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...Oh, so you and t.bfine and dale, et. al. will all have to discuss your beloved Texas Rangers elsewhere...bummer. Frogg, too? The Finance boards will still be here, contrary to what jon and wilkes are telling you.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1364507828614</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 17:57:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364508397713-38</Id><Title>T Mobile Smokes T for LAUNCH of BB Z10 ... Just Awesome Phone !!!!</Title><Msg>TM store was great.. friendly KNOWLEDGEABLE Staff re the BB Z10. store in Deerfiled Il could't have been more helpful !! Bought several Z10's. Awesome pricing plan cut bill in almost half. T couldn't provide this kind of service ... or assitance. They have been too busy ripping folks off for years with the most expensive APPLE pricing plans. T Mobile to sell iPhone on the April 12th with great price and great price plan! Now that's more like it .! About time consumers had a real choice.</Msg><Username>capwent</Username><Timestamp>1364508397713</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 18:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364508505105-39</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Keystone pipeline ever be approved?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1363902082055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who cares this is a mesage board for AT&amp;T..</Msg><Username>capwent</Username><Timestamp>1364508505105</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 18:08:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364508637055-40</Id><Title>T-Mobuile is the best .. Thank god merger never happened!</Title><Msg>It's about time its about tech .. three men in crazy race without T !!! YAHOO !!!!</Msg><Username>capwent</Username><Timestamp>1364508637055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 18:10:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364509653256-41</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>jayterrance807</Username><Timestamp>1364509653256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 18:27:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364509849860-42</Id><Title>FLORIDA ATLANTIC UNIVERSITY "Stomp on Jesus"</Title><Msg>If you do not know about this just google "stomp on jesus" and read all about it. Looking around I find a name in the AT&amp;T corporate office who is an alumni of this fabulous sewer! Does AT&amp;T support it? TOP</Msg><Username>topwardbound</Username><Timestamp>1364509849860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 18:30:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364514626347-43</Id><Topic><Title>FLORIDA ATLANTIC UNIVERSITY "Stomp on Jesus"</Title><Username>topwardbound</Username><Timestamp>1364509849860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 18:30:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GET REAL!! ,, AT&amp;T employees about 230,000 people and the diversity of that many people means that the odds are that I went to school with a satanic worshiper but does that mean that AT&amp;T supports worshipping Satan? The answer is going to be no. Don't be stupid.</Msg><Username>whopperkaraoke</Username><Timestamp>1364514626347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 19:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364521677639-44</Id><Title>is this the new T</Title><Msg>regarding jobs there? http://finance.yahoo.com/blogs/daily-ticker/why-quit-job-now-151346969.html?l=1</Msg><Username>zbgb952</Username><Timestamp>1364521677639</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 21:47:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364522583090-45</Id><Topic><Title>FLORIDA ATLANTIC UNIVERSITY "Stomp on Jesus"</Title><Username>topwardbound</Username><Timestamp>1364509849860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 18:30:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have to assume that you made an error in citing the employee populasyone being 230,000. Actually 324,000. Most of the employee universe belongs to a union of some kind where at the end of each working day, they all say "GOD BLESS AMERIKA."</Msg><Username>madam_hillary07</Username><Timestamp>1364522583090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 22:03:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364525030227-46</Id><Topic><Title>FLORIDA ATLANTIC UNIVERSITY "Stomp on Jesus"</Title><Username>topwardbound</Username><Timestamp>1364509849860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 18:30:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry Jesus is going to stamp on them real soon. Read Revelations.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1364525030227</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 22:43:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>