<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-15"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373889000009-1</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman Acquitted</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1373769095727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 22:31:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No! No! No! First we got to get our mad on, and break some windows, burn some cars, disrupt traffic, and let everyone in the United States know just how easy it is for us to take control of the news cycle for a few days. I only wish that our demonstrators had a little more imagination, like the Animalisti Italiani in Europe, who were demonstrating against Jean Paul Gaultier’s use of fur in his fashion show. Wow! half naked demonstrators, now that's what I am talking about. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1373889000009</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 07:50:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373894614367-2</Id><Topic><Title>After Hours Quotes...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1373679027671</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:30:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A great lesson in American politics.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1373894614367</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 09:23:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373894882721-3</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman Acquitted</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1373769095727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 22:31:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The prosecution didn't object to the selection of an all female, mostly white jury because it now gives someone grounds for an appeal that the jury was not a fair representation of his 'peers'.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1373894882721</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 09:28:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373898414853-4</Id><Title>MSM's Responsibility !!</Title><Msg>Now it's Zimm's turn - his attorney's will go after those of the MSM that 're-edited' and comtinued to mis-report the facts from Zimm's 911 call - along with ALL other non-factual reporting .. maliciously intending to mis-lead and incriminate him in the eyes of the public ... YOU GO ZIMM .. hold them accountable &amp; break it off in them !!!</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1373898414853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 10:26:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373899454438-5</Id><Topic><Title>obonga admin files federal charges against Zimmerman</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1373837077241</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:24:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please quote what President Obama said about the outcome. Then proceed to be a nut, it's more effective. Thanks be to God Almighty your kind is dying away.</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1373899454438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 10:44:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373899502156-6</Id><Title>When will the hispanic community realize what just happened?</Title><Msg>When will the Hispanic community realize how easy it was for the left, the democrat party, the MSM, and the administration to throw a law abiding Latino man under their race bating bus of division and hate? Yes my Latino and Latina brothers and sisters you have had a perfect example of what will happen to you if you dare to act in a law abiding manner as a community watch captain, whose only crime was watching and reporting suspicious activities within his community, and after he was attacked and beaten had the nerve to defend himself with his handgun. Yes my Latino and Latina brothers and sisters you have had the perfect example of just where you are in the pecking order of the left and the democrat party. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1373899502156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 10:45:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373900306645-7</Id><Title>AT&amp;T to acquire Leap Wireless in $1.19B transaction</Title><Msg>Search for "SEC Live Filings Digest" to find out more. Filing in Focus: AT&amp;T 8-K, July 12, 2013 AT&amp;T (T) has entered an agreement through which it will acquire Leap Wireless (LEAP) in a $1.19B cash transaction. AT&amp;T will acquire all Leap stock for $15.00 per share, an 88% premium of the company’s closing price of $7.98 on Friday. Wireless providers are in a rush to purchase additional wireless spectrum as bandwidth has become a concern for companies due to the increased bandwidth demand from smartphones and tablets. One of the most recent examples of this is detailed in Filings Digest June 28, 2013, where T-Mobile (TMUS) acquired Advanced Wireless for $308M cash. AT&amp;T will acquire not only the additional spectrum but an additional five million subscribers as well as the Cricket brand that covers approximately 96 million people. AT&amp;T plans to expand its 4G LTE network and leverage Leap’s resources to better compete in the low-cost prepaid service.</Msg><Username>adspatz</Username><Timestamp>1373900306645</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 10:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373901508668-8</Id><Topic><Title>obonga admin files federal charges against Zimmerman</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1373837077241</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:24:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK ghosan .. Obama's quote = "if I had a son, he would look like Treyvon" ... and if you think I might have missed something (??) .. I didn't -- he's still playing the 'race card' .... Nor did I miss the fact that his administration will look to find .... and to re-charge Zimm on a Fed. level. If we were looking for the TRUTH .. why would we care what he or T.M. or Zimm looked like ... that was purely a push towards a favor of an 'ethnic slant" in Obama's favor/color, promoting HIS agenda. The TRUTH did 'over-come" .. and it was done by a diverse panel of women ... not a bunch of Obama brown-nosers - FACT</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1373901508668</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:18:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373902508934-9</Id><Topic><Title>When will the hispanic community realize what just happened?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1373899502156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 10:45:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I watched several "protest" marches on the news. I didn't see one obvious Hispanic in the mob. I did see a bunch of self hating Whites though. Bet many of them are associated with various commie groups. Oh yeah, they're still around and active under many different front names. Guess they never read "The Gulag Archipeligo" by Solzynitsin. Suggest all read this book by a Nobel Prize winner. He has some interesting things to say about those that ran these "Death Camps".</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1373902508934</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373903007402-10</Id><Topic><Title>obonga admin files federal charges against Zimmerman</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1373837077241</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:24:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>talk about injustice on a national level. the Obama admin is frantically looking for something to charge Zimmerman with if they are successful, will lulac, la roacha and the ALCU the protest about one of our Hispanic citizens being railroaded by the DOJ? So far the Hispanic community has been silent.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1373903007402</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 11:43:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373908076922-11</Id><Title>More DRIP shares!!!</Title><Msg>These constant down days are great!!! Let's hope it continues its down trend - the lower the better for more DRIP shares right???!!!! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1373908076922</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 13:07:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373908813106-12</Id><Title>BUY NOW FOR 45 TARGET!!</Title><Msg>ITS CHEAP!!</Msg><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1373908813106</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 13:20:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373908977050-13</Id><Topic><Title>When will the hispanic community realize what just happened?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1373899502156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 10:45:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the administration got around that awkwardness by labeling Zimerman as white, the scourge of the earth, hates every other race, white.</Msg><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1373908977050</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 13:22:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373908994225-14</Id><Topic><Title>MSM's Responsibility !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1373898414853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 10:26:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The kenyan is so PO'ed over the acquittal that he has ordered Holder to find something or invent something to hang Zimm on. He is the most racist person in the USA</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1373908994225</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 13:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373909866208-15</Id><Title>Anyone?</Title><Msg>Why doesn't this stock ever go up? TIA Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1373909866208</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 13:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373910954301-16</Id><Topic><Title>When will the hispanic community realize what just happened?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1373899502156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 10:45:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amen brother, well said. We are heading in the same direction as Cuba after castro took over. Class warfare is the name.</Msg><Username>meneito4</Username><Timestamp>1373910954301</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 13:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373912965904-17</Id><Topic><Title>MSM's Responsibility !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1373898414853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 10:26:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They couldn't even get the acquittal correct. They insisted that he was found not guilty of 'shooting' Martin. He was not, he did shoot him; he was acquitted of murdering him by reason of self-defense.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1373912965904</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:29:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373913099775-18</Id><Topic><Title>obonga admin files federal charges against Zimmerman</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1373837077241</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:24:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was charged by Congress, but the and his fearless leader simply choose to ignore them and their charges. He keeps saying elections have consequences and boy was he correct.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1373913099775</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373913744418-19</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman Acquitted</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1373769095727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 22:31:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>George is not a hero. Being part of a community watch organization does not give you the right to be an idiot. There are many resources he ignored. There were other actions he could have taken that would not have lead to a conflict. Once the conflict was initiated, regardless of by whom, he did have a right to self-defense. The prosecution was wrong in bringing the charges in the first place, but once they did, a trial had to be held. A trial was held and the prosecution did not do their job of proving guilt beyond a reasonable doubt. No matter whom you felt was a fault, this was an avoidable tragedy. This Justice Department with their racist attitude is simply getting even...first they didn't get the verdict they wanted and/or they are simply taking revenge for OJ being tried, acquitted and then tried again and losing. The prosecution, regardless of if you believe OJ or Zimmerman was innocent, didn't do their jobs well enough to get what they wanted. Guilty or innocent, in both the trial was held as prescribed by law and the system did what it was supposed to do.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1373913744418</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:42:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373913896471-20</Id><Topic><Title>NAACP DID NOT APPEAL THE OJ SIMPSON VERDICT-GOLMAN AND NICOLE MURDERED</Title><Username>tomandlia</Username><Timestamp>1373854530544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:15:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There was little or no political gain to be had in appealing the OJ verdict. The President of the U.S. didn't make comments about the guilt or innocence of OJ like this President got involved. Again, Obama tried to create a new crisis out of something that clearly wasn't. It is his game plan.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1373913896471</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:44:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373914028684-21</Id><Topic><Title>Media reshaping who is a minority in America</Title><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1373834476609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:41:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I find it strange that some in the media excused their calling Zimmerman white, because he was of mixed heritage, one parent Hispanic and one white...a condition that they don't use on the President, he is simply black.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1373914028684</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:47:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373914197173-22</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (cont.)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1373679060098</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:31:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A short lesson on American politics. The folks who are getting the free stuff don't like the folks who are paying for the free stuff, because the folks who are paying for the free stuff can no longer afford to pay for both the free stuff and their own stuff. And the folks who are paying for the free stuff want the free stuff to stop. And the folks who are getting the free stuff want even more free stuff on top of the free stuff they are already getting! Now... the people who are forcing the people who pay for the free stuff have told the people who are RECEIVING the free stuff that the people who are PAYING for the free stuff are being mean, prejudiced, and racist. So... the people who are GETTING the free stuff have been convinced they need to hate the people who are paying for the free stuff by the people who are forcing some people to pay for their free stuff and giving them the free stuff in the first place. We have let the free stuff giving go on for so long that there are now more people getting free stuff than paying for the free stuff.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1373914197173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:49:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373914224067-23</Id><Title>Immigrant Gains and Native Losses In the Job Market, 2000 to 2013</Title><Msg>Pert the center for immigration studies, 'While jobs are always being created and lost, and the number of workers rises and falls with the economy, a new analysis of government data shows that all of the net gain in employment over the last 13 years has gone to immigrants (legal and illegal). From the first quarter of 2000 to the first quarter of 2013, the number of natives working actually fell by 1.3 million` The creeps in the Senate voted to legalize the illegal lawbreakers taking legal citizens jobs and to make immigration to this country easier. When in fact they should all be DEPORTED not rewarded.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1373914224067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373914699413-24</Id><Topic><Title>Immigrant Gains and Native Losses In the Job Market, 2000 to 2013</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1373914224067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our immigration process is not broken other that by the fact that we don't enforce the laws on the books. There is a law that required the Congress to appropriate the funds to continue building the fence that was in the law passed in 1986. They have not done so. They are now going to put those who choose to come here in violation of our laws, ahead of those that have worked hard and followed the rules. This administration is constantly speaking of fairness and this is one of the most one-sided acts they have yet taken. We have an illegal immigration issue. We have it because Congress and other branches of our government that are assigned the tasks to reduce and control this issue have not done their jobs, often times not even trying to do their jobs. We have Justice Department and an Executive branch that less than judiciously select which laws they choose to enforce. I beg anyone to find it written in the Constitution or anywhere else that these members of our government have this latitude.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1373914699413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 14:58:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373915042339-25</Id><Topic><Title>PCYC filed for a new cancer drug approval</Title><Username>deal.smart</Username><Timestamp>1373569358528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 15:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After PCYC went up every day last week with a total of 27% gain, it is taking a small break today. If you missed the huge gain in PCYC, you may want to consider loading up PCYC today. PCYC will go a lot higher after shake off some weak hands.</Msg><Username>deal.smart</Username><Timestamp>1373915042339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 15:04:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373915732993-26</Id><Topic><Title>BUY NOW FOR 45 TARGET!!</Title><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1373908813106</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 13:20:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i looked at the charts and see the problem with "T". It is stuck. They need to buy WD40. Seriously, hope you are right. I own "T". I'm either at level or it is down. I would have thought the recent announcement of the company being purchased would have done something! Nope goes down. The only good thing for me is the dividend. Hoping it keeps me level. Again, hope you are right.</Msg><Username>west_seth</Username><Timestamp>1373915732993</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 15:15:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373915733209-27</Id><Topic><Title>When will the hispanic community realize what just happened?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1373899502156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 10:45:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe George got lucky, because according to the National Census Bureau there are only 5 categories of race in this country: o White – A person having origins in any of the original peoples of Europe, the Middle East, or North Africa. o Black or African American – A person having origins in any of the Black racial groups of Africa. o American Indian or Alaska Native – A person having origins in any of the original peoples of North and South America (including Central America) and who maintains tribal affiliation or community attachment. o Asian – A person having origins in any of the original peoples of the Far East, Southeast Asia, or the Indian subcontinent including, for example, Cambodia, China, India, Japan, Korea, Malaysia, Pakistan, the Philippine Islands, Thailand, and Vietnam. o Native Hawaiian or Other Pacific Islander – A person having origins in any of the original peoples of Hawaii, Guam, Samoa, or other Pacific Islands. Further according to the same website: "People who identify their origin as Hispanic, Latino, or Spanish may be of any race. " So for example when our "dear leader" fills out his Census form he by law would mark the "White" category and the "Black or African American" category In the case of Mr. Zimmerman (who identified himself on his Florida driver's license as Hispanic and since the U.S. Census Bureau has no single category for Hispanic or Latino) should have identified himself as "White", "Black or African American" (Mr. Zimmerman's Grandmother is "Black...") and "American Indian or Alaska Native" just to be accurate. I just can't wait for the show trial when a U.S. Attorney gets in front of a Federal Grand Jury and offers these words in summary: "Mr. Zimmerman was so self loathing of his own race and heritage that he stalked and ultimately killed a poor innocent boy, who if he had a son would have looked like him." And the jury said? "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1373915733209</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 15:15:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373916142382-28</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone?</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1373909866208</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 13:37:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have replied twice to this and it shows up and then disappears...</Msg><Username>rdcn100</Username><Timestamp>1373916142382</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 15:22:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373916404922-29</Id><Topic><Title>More DRIP shares!!!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1373908076922</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 13:07:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Strong sell? Based on what? If you really believe that why would you even be concerned about DRIP? Just short it if that's your view. I couldn't imagine this as a strong sell or even a sell. Hold and yes the DRIP is one of the reasons. Also they have a lot of cash and can make a lot of acquisitions or one very big one. Many billions in cash. This isn't VZ with VOD problem after all.</Msg><Username>colorado_dude4u</Username><Timestamp>1373916404922</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 15:26:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373916471333-30</Id><Topic><Title>BUY NOW FOR 45 TARGET!!</Title><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1373908813106</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 13:20:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>45 but not this year ...maybe 2015. This is a crawler.</Msg><Username>colorado_dude4u</Username><Timestamp>1373916471333</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 15:27:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373923556553-31</Id><Topic><Title>When will the hispanic community realize what just happened?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1373899502156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 10:45:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A black man was killed by a Hispanic man and was acquitted by an all woman jury...and it is still the white man's fault !!</Msg><Username>houdini1229</Username><Timestamp>1373923556553</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 17:25:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373931026095-32</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone?</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1373909866208</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 13:37:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just come on the forum now to read what ridiculous sentence you post next. FYI do not know about your at&amp;t stock your talking about but mine is up 20% with solid dividends(around 65 a quarter) dripping into my roth ira. I am 27 and have a 37 year horizon for trading my dividend portfolio consist of: EXC, WM, VLO, HAS, NAT and INTC. Everything was dirt cheap last year where were you?</Msg><Username>nobrainerduh</Username><Timestamp>1373931026095</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 19:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373931125616-33</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone?</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1373909866208</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 13:37:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One more thing I have added a little whenever AT&amp;T is around 33 a share which as worked very well for me.</Msg><Username>nobrainerduh</Username><Timestamp>1373931125616</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 19:32:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373939813242-34</Id><Topic><Title>When will the hispanic community realize what just happened?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1373899502156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 10:45:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In Chicago, that has the highest gun regulations in the country, blacks kill blacks and it's still the white mans fault!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1373939813242</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 21:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373940734885-35</Id><Topic><Title>BUY NOW FOR 45 TARGET!!</Title><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1373908813106</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 13:20:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry west but by your comments can see you understand little about investing(Only reason why I say that is because you back up your answer by saying i looked at the charts lmfao). At&amp;T is known as a income builder if you want something with value you look towards growth stocks then you can short them all day long. This stock is suppose to stay @ a consistent price that stays leveled with the dividend it is paying out. Now other end the dividend will hopefully grow and that will only happen when at&amp;t increases cash flow quarter to quarter in till then we are stuck at this price level.</Msg><Username>nobrainerduh</Username><Timestamp>1373940734885</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 22:12:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373942231804-36</Id><Topic><Title>More DRIP shares!!!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1373908076922</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 13:07:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've done great over the years with my DRIP. I've been using it for over 30 years. I have a lot of profit built in. If it dips I just get more shares at a cheaper price and increase my yield. If you use DRIP you should stay in for no less than five years.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1373942231804</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 22:37:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>