<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363927326654-1</Id><Topic><Title>= = Analyst Predicts Decline to 36.32 =SEE REPORT=</Title><Username>jonesmichael636</Username><Timestamp>1363200233662</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 14:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAM, and the dangerous kind complete with a key logger from India. See the suffix .in? Go there @ your own peril.</Msg><Username>basherbuste_r</Username><Timestamp>1363927326654</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 00:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363934150157-2</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Keystone pipeline ever be approved?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1363902082055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since my last post must have been too intellectually challenging for you to comprehend, I will try to simplify my point with the following facts: o The current occupant of the white house has resisted authorizing the Keystone pipeline because of environmental concerns o The beneficiaries of these delays are companies that transport oil via rail o Burlington Northern is a rail transport company that currently transports oil from Canada to the US o Burlington Norther is owned by Berkshire Hathaway Inc. o The current majority stock holder of Berkshire Hathaway Inc. is a friend and supporter of the current occupant of the white house Bottom line: As long as the Keystone pipeline is not transporting oil, the rail transporters can charge whatever the market will bear. In other words as long as the current occupant of the white house has his job, the owners of rail transport companies (that transport oil from Canada to the US) will have nothing to fear from a competing transport method. Get it? "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1363934150157</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 02:35:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363950380072-3</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Keystone pipeline ever be approved?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1363902082055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“Obviously I don't know what I am talking about…” – wilkes Amen to that, brother (with the exception of that particular statement). And, btw, neither does your gremlin friend.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1363950380072</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 07:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363958014998-4</Id><Topic><Title>Balanced budget in five years.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363874378394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's $36,000 a year for your grandson. The average income in 2010 for a male age 24-35 with a high school diploma was $32,800. With that in mind, what do you suggest is the proper salary for a volunteer solider?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1363958014998</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 09:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363958138859-5</Id><Topic><Title>The Washington Post</Title><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1363890070339</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rush is wrong, wilkes. Idiot dittoheads.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1363958138859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 09:15:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363959435137-6</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Keystone pipeline ever be approved?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1363902082055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The current administration has held up approval of the Keystone pipeline for the stated reason of environmental concerns." No. The stated reason is that Nebraska requested more time to do its own evaluation of alternate routes. There is much local resistance from farmers, ranchers and communities due to the potential impact on their land, water and community development. That is why rail transport is a developing alternative. The Obama administration has not opposed the Keystone pipeline on purely environmental grounds, or in attempt to lower oil production or use. The pipeline simply has little impact on those things. You wackos on the right and the left may try to make this into some huge ideological battle but it is not. It is a practical matter.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1363959435137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 09:37:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363961410696-7</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Keystone pipeline ever be approved?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1363902082055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't they build a new one in the US? Answer, several actually; the EPA and Federal pressure to stop using gas and oil completely.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1363961410696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 10:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363961951362-8</Id><Topic><Title>The Washington Post</Title><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1363890070339</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" I'm smart enough to defer to the experts on things I don't know much about." Yeah, as long as their 'expert' opinions agree with your view of the world as you want it to be. Which experts by the way, there are just about equal numbers of so-called climate experts that will tell you the other is wrong? Kind of like economists, one on every TV or radio show and in every newspaper that insists they’re the ones with the answers. Human nature tells one to accept the version that best fits their beliefs, and you do. I won’t disagree that the climate is changing, the biggest questions around the issues should be are we causing all of it and can we spend enough money to change it? In the US anyway the air quality has improved nearly every year for at least two decades. In Africa, China and India quite the opposite is true, but their governments aren’t demanding we break the bank to save the climate. I wonder why?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1363961951362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363962345156-9</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Keystone pipeline ever be approved?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1363902082055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Why don't they build a new one in the US? Answer, several actually; the EPA and Federal pressure to stop using gas and oil completely." No. It is cheaper and easier to upgrade and expand existing facilities, which the oil and gas industry does regularly. A new refinery in Canada (or the US) would still require a pipeline to move the refined products to market--which basically means attaching to the existing pipeline network and port facilities. IF the keystone pipeline is not built then the tar sands oil will get to market by a pipeline through Canada to ports on the Pacific or by rail. This has nothing to do with oil production. It is a local issue--dealing mainly with resistance in Nebraska-- that wackos on both sides have decided to make into a symbolic event.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1363962345156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 10:25:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363962367498-10</Id><Title>Does the ID "I Golf at Work" Still Post Here?</Title><Msg>The guy who kept claiming he was shorting a huge # of T shares?</Msg><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1363962367498</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 10:26:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363962375647-11</Id><Topic><Title>It looks like Obama wants to bankrupt America</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1362778576708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:36:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Not at all. Obama and I both propose long-term cuts to entitlement spending. " Then where are all these proposals? Is Harry keeping them tied up in committee again? Why isn't he saying he is willing to make changes? Why does he keep saying that if the Republicans won't give him more revenue there is no reason to talk? How is that compromise? You want the 'entitlements' you hate reduced, he doesn't because it was cost him and his Party votes. He only wants more money from higher taxes so he can give away more of our treasury. He doesn't even hide that fact. His ego tells him he won and he can do whatever he desires. He is wrong.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1363962375647</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 10:26:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363964127368-12</Id><Topic><Title>The Washington Post</Title><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1363890070339</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Kind of like economists, one on every TV or radio show" There is no doubt in my mind that any TV or Radio Show can find an economist or scientist to say whatever they pay them to say. If you want to know what real economists or scientist think you read academic journals. You go to conferences. You follow the proceedings and data releases of the FOMC, NBER, BEA, BLS, IMF and other real sources where real economists work. Or the NOAA, IPCC, USGS, the IEA and other real sources where real scientists work. You follow blogs, newsletters and websites run by professionals themselves. These people use the scientific method to overcome the weakness of human nature. You do not turn on the TV or the radio. And you absolutely do not turn on Fox News or Rush Limbaugh (or MSNBC for that matter) where people say and believe what they are paid to say and believe. And what do real scientists and economists say about global warming? Search for the "The Hard Math on Fossil Fuels" by Eduardo Porter. Who does Eduardo Porter cite? The chief economist of the International Energy Agency. The Potsdam Institute for Climate Impact Research. Price Waterhouse Coopers. THAT is were you find out what economists and scientist think. Not Rush Limbaugh.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1363964127368</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 10:55:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363964562587-13</Id><Topic><Title>It looks like Obama wants to bankrupt America</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1362778576708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:36:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Then where are all these proposals?" Obviously not on Fox News or Rush Limbaugh. This is why you are stupid. There are three types of people in the world. People who don't know what's happening, people who know what's happening and people who make things happen. If you don't know what's happening that's your own problem. I've been trying to drop some little bit of knowledge on you for years. It hasn't helped.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1363964562587</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363971758178-14</Id><Title>ITS NOT BB Fault .. they shouldnt have partnered with ATT / New Blackberry Launch / Total Apathy</Title><Msg>AT7T creates the BIG Bummer...... Waited for two years.. Did research .. went into store in Highland Park Il this morning.. No customer service regarding BB launch.. employees stated they were not trained.. to busy to assist.. no phone to play or experience with in your hand.. employees couldnt have cared less.... a unit tethered to the wall with a security bubble pasted over the front screen. ITS ALL ABOUT THE EXPERIENCE ON A SMART PHONE !!!!! Today was supposed to be Blackberry Big return to the US market.. my suggestion BB needs to pull their phones from AT&amp;T and find a vendor that is excited and enthusiastic about new BB products. Looked at web sites for AT&amp;T.. this is a problem not of BB making but a historical coprporate culture issue of AT&amp;T ! This company is really messed up .. the ssues permeate the company at all different levels across all ATT businesses. Senior Management TAke NOTE : The custoer is KING... The customer has the power through the wallet and through the abilty to express themslves to millions of others. There should be no bigger issue for senior management. ATT once was crown jewel in US economy.. today they stink. Senior management has no idea whats going on.. they should go to the stores unannounced and see the excuses and apathy directly. Heads should Roll!</Msg><Username>capwent</Username><Timestamp>1363971758178</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363972315801-15</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Keystone pipeline ever be approved?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1363902082055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your statement: "No. The stated reason is that Nebraska requested more time to do its own evaluation of alternate routes. There is much local resistance from farmers, ranchers and communities due to the potential impact on their land, water and community development." Nice try, and there was some truth to what you pointed out until TransCanada changed the original proposed route to minimize "disturbance of land, water resources and special areas" and the new route was approved by Nebraska Governor Dave Heineman in January 2013. As to your statement: "The Obama administration has not opposed the Keystone pipeline on purely environmental grounds,..." There is probably more truth there than you are willing to admit (i.e., the stated reasons have very little to do with the real reasons which will never be stated publicly). "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1363972315801</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 13:11:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363974128941-16</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Keystone pipeline ever be approved?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1363902082055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the new route was approved by Nebraska Governor Dave Heineman in January 2013." Then I don't understand what your problem is, Froggie. The new plan is undergoing required third-party review and a decision is expected in the next few weeks. I'm sure then we'll hear reasons for the decision. If you simply want to imply that Obama is an environmental wacko who hates oil and has secret alternative motivations for everything he does, you're not without company. You're just useless.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1363974128941</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 13:42:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363974876434-17</Id><Topic><Title>The Washington Post</Title><Username>usganut</Username><Timestamp>1363890070339</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“Yeah, as long as their 'expert' opinions agree with your view of the world as you want it to be. Which experts by the way, there are just about equal numbers of so-called climate experts that will tell you the other is wrong?” – windandale EQUAL NUMBERS? No they’re not, Winnie, not by a long shot. Don’t you ever get tired of spewing the same, repetitive bundle of special interest hogwash?…and don’t you ever get sick of being made a fool of when you can’t backup your Tea Party balderdash with even one substantiated fact? You’ve been called on this at least three times previously, and here you are back again preachin’ the same party-line nonsense, with not one credible source to validate your dimwitted view of a seriously important issue for this planet. After a while, your intentional deception goes from being simply ignorantly silly, to borderline criminal behavior. You really need to grow up. Your “why should we behave if China and India aren’t” selfish attitude should be replaced with a mature concept of “why don’t we take the lead, pioneer the technology, sell it to developing nations and provide a much better world for our children’s children. No, it’s your profits first and screw the planet attitude that continues to leave your kind floundering for acceptance. Well. Let’s revisit a post from last September, with the same invitation for any of you lunatics to show us some scientific data to support your primitive and naïve view on the subject. Governor Perry Blows Hot Air on Global Warming At the first Republican Debate, Rick Perry made the following statements: "The science is not settled on this (global warming). The idea that we would put Americans' economy at jeopardy based on scientific theory that's not settled yet, to me, is just, is nonsense…" …perhaps the real reason that Governor Perry, and like-minded laissez-faire proponents, deny global warming and contend that government regulations hold back business and plea for smaller government and self-regulation is this; Texas, the center of America’s oil and gas industry, also is the number one emitter of the major green house gas – carbon dioxide – in this country today. Is it any wonder, then, why he disavows the findings of the National Academy of Sciences, as well as the overwhelmingly accepted consensus of 18 scientific organizations, whose statement to The Senate concluded: “Observations throughout the world make it clear that climate change is occurring, and rigorous scientific research demonstrates that the greenhouse gases emitted by human activities are the primary driver.” * Let us not let political hot air blow away scientific fact for the sake of short term profit at the expense of long term civilization. Yes, business and the economy are important, but not at the expense of our children and future generations. Here are you “equal numbers” – oh, wait…you haven’t supplied ANY yet. What will be your take on these? I suppose you’ll label them a conspiracy of “Main Stream Scientists” * Letter to the Senate, October 29, 2009 from The Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change and U.S. Global Change Research Program, American Association for the Advancement of Science, American Chemical Society, American Geophysical Union, American Institute of Biological Sciences, American Meteorological Society, American Society of Agronomy, American Society of Plant Biologists, American Statistical Association, Association of Ecosystem Research Centers, Botanical Society of America, Crop Science Society of America, Ecological Society of America, Natural Science Collections Alliance, Organization of Biological Field Stations, Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics, Society of Systematic Biologists, Soil Science Society of America, University Corporation for Atmospheric Research. (BTW, there are even more International Organizations that acknowledge this conclusion, as well. Of course, this is critically and peer-reviewed science, not unsubstantiated propaganda from individuals funded by special interests. I encourage and invite opposing views with accompanying sources, not the usual "there's just as many people who say global warming is marlarkey" - if there are, please show us. If you can't, please stop lying to your fellow citizens for your own gain.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1363974876434</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 13:54:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363978217324-18</Id><Topic><Title>Balanced budget in five years.</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363874378394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Noone wants to look at the actual plan, eh?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1363978217324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:50:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363986146065-19</Id><Topic><Title>Does the ID "I Golf at Work" Still Post Here?</Title><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1363962367498</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 10:26:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1363986146065</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 17:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363990920442-20</Id><Title>district 9 way to go in voting no on your contract</Title><Msg>way to go district 9 in voting down that terrible contract that your union the cwa put forth in your figh with at+t,we here in district 1 in connecticut are still fighting for a fair contract also...let operation jelly bean begin..........</Msg><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1363990920442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 18:22:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>