<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-09"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365481463983-1</Id><Topic><Title>holding up well today...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1365432089558</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 10:41:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What I think isn't important Zon. I was curious because you really watch the price closely. I do too, but I don't concern myself with it that much. Il'll never use any of it. The purpose is to pass it on to my son and not to redeem it unless dire circumstances occur. I converted my stock from taxable IRA's to Roth last year and this. Then I combined them. It's a little complicated. Bottom line, my tax bill this year and next is close to what Wilkie claims he lost. Why do that and pay all the freight? Twofold. To avoid RMD's at 701/2 and to pass it on without my son paying the taxes when my wife and I check out. There's more, but that is essentially what my plan is. It's a keeper. I also considered GE and Altria a while ago. Would have done well with both, but felt T to be the best bet. I spent over 22 years with T and know it quite well. had a great career and would do it all again if I had a choice. Not everybody will say that, but I do. Sounds like your portfolio is solid and well positioned. I'd keep an eye on them and the market as well. If you sniff a problem, it's real easy to go cash and reassess when things settle down. But I wouldn't concern myself with the daily fluctuations. Unless I was Wilkie....</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1365481463983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 00:24:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365482288361-2</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T network outrage in my area. I can't do transaction untill they fix the problem</Title><Username>weirdstock</Username><Timestamp>1365364748148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 15:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Acknowledged Zon. Calling it quits out here on the zany left coast. Michigan/Louisville was a good game. Don't know if you follow basketball. Either team could have won and it wouldn't have mattered. It was good sports entertainment. I'm gearing up for the NBA playoffs. Devout SA Spur fan from the old ABA days. Unfortunately, I'm surrounded by LA Faker fans. Can't stand anything about that franchise. So, I'm a lone wolf of sorts with my loyalty to the truly great scandal-free team from the sovereign state of Texas. Well see how that shakes out. Till the next time, Regards, Dave.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1365482288361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 00:38:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365496489097-3</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't look good for Fisker: o Fisker Automotive, Inc. laid off up to 80% of its employees o Now a class action lawsuit has been filed by Outten &amp; Golden in a California district court o The suit claims that Fisker violated the law by not giving employees a 60-day notice that layoffs were coming o In 2012, Outten &amp; Golden succeeded in getting bankrupted company Solyndra to pay fired employees a hefty $3.5 million settlement in a similar layoff case And "The beat goes on" We can get billions for failed "green energy companies", but we can't get one presidential "OK" for the Keystone pipeline. Thank you Mr. president for all that you do. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1365496489097</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 04:34:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365514184775-4</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why the obsession with Fisker, Froggie? Do you work there? Why not talk about Tesla? Or the Chevy Volt? Or the Nissan Leaf? All success stories. Do you pick and choose your stories Froggie? Why not a full and open account? Got something to hide?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1365514184775</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:29:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365516778626-5</Id><Topic><Title>AT &amp; T = THIEF'S</Title><Username>j.catucci</Username><Timestamp>1365452555540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 16:22:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you noticed that it takes a lot more $ for a tank of gas than it did 5 years ago? The dollar is worth much less than 5 years ago so it will take more of them to buy a share of T. The reason for under $37.50 by Friday is, T will still be beaten down by the dividend that is no longer attached to the shares. It happens almost every time a dividend is paid. T is a great stock for owning and letting dividends and modest stock appreciation work for you over time. I have reconsidered my tactics and found that weekly options provide a greater opportunity for income and lower risk. Try it, you'll like it. You are not as infected with greed as I am so I would recommend that you simply sell far out of the money covered calls every week on Thursday, then just let the options expire worthless. You will find that the gain will exceed the dividend. Even five cents a week will get you 65 cents a quarter (minus commissions). You bring up a great point about other stocks. That is how I lost $340,000. Diversification is great for those who enjoy your type of investing but I found that it was more than I could handle with my excessive concern with the fluctuations in value. Every time a stock dropped in value I lost it because I set stop losses too close to make sure I didn't lose too much. Over 15 years it adds up. Now that I have discovered this price action around dividends I may try other stocks but for now I am sticking with T as it continues the uptrend.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365516778626</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:12:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365517054852-6</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report , thanks !</Msg><Username>mary.grooms</Username><Timestamp>1365517054852</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365517636711-7</Id><Title>Today</Title><Msg>My "bottom" is really..really..really itchy today. I wish coolin_out, dan, jon, bouche and some of my other "friends" were here to help me dig away at it..oh wait, I am here (??) Tee hee..(!!) Maybe "puppy" can help.."Puppy(!!)..Puppy(!!)..grins..</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1365517636711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:27:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365518038959-8</Id><Topic><Title>New sources of information for AT&amp;T, you should see it!</Title><Username>larry_williams64</Username><Timestamp>1364908299493</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 09:11:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this was really helpful</Msg><Username>marywill79</Username><Timestamp>1365518038959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:33:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365518509127-9</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please define "success" as in " All success stories."</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365518509127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:41:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365519935405-10</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As in all three are expanding production in the US. As in costs for all three vehicles are declining--the Nissan Leaf and Tesla are already profitable. As in the technology is here to stay and expanding and will likely be looked at as a major success of the Obama administration. I think in these three cases you'd have to tell me why they wouldn't be considered success stories. You can point to a bump here or a failure there (which is all Froggie does), or argue about whether this or that program was good, but the overall effort has been a success.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1365519935405</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365521263737-11</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one !</Msg><Username>lucille.coffey</Username><Timestamp>1365521263737</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365521671170-12</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you changing the subject from Fisker? Bye the way, that was a good definition of success for those other companies to which you were changing the subject. I'm just not convinced that electric cars are better than cars with internal combustion engines and, if they are, why does it take government to get companies to make them? We had electric cars back in the 30s but they didn't catch on then. Did our tax dollars go to finance the three successful cars you mentioned?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365521671170</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365521788119-13</Id><Topic><Title>AT &amp; T = THIEF'S</Title><Username>j.catucci</Username><Timestamp>1365452555540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 16:22:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanx for the response Wilkie. Way too much for me to respond to, but I understand a lot more by your explanation of 'greed'. I still want an update on the proposed trade you considered that could make you the 5K as you recommended to the poster Catucci who seems to have disappeared.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1365521788119</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365522560023-14</Id><Topic><Title>AT &amp; T = THIEF'S</Title><Username>j.catucci</Username><Timestamp>1365452555540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 16:22:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not going to make that trade because it is beginning to look like it would be a loser. AT&amp;T seems to be making an unusually fast recovery from the dividend. I am planning on buying May and June options now while the price is low. May 39's and June 40's. Both are about 20 cents and should easily double in value at some point before they expire.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365522560023</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:49:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365523275510-15</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you focusing on Fisker? It's one part of a broad effort and industry. Was the computer industry a failure because Digital Equipment Corporation declared bankruptcy? "why does it take government to get companies to make them?" The same reason it always has. R&amp;D is expensive, risky and time consuming. It is often difficult to capture the benefits. From funding Universities and Government Research labs, to patent protection, to regulated monopolies, to loan guarantees, to tax credits to direct subsidies, the government is involved in encouraging R&amp;D in just about any industry you can think of and has been for decades. The ONLY difference between this program and any number of other programs is you Tea Brains don't like environmentally friendly product. You prefer the deadly pollution we see in China. To pretend your objection has something to do with not liking government involvement is ridiculous. "We had electric cars back in the 30s but they didn't catch on then." You also had abundant, cheap, domestically produced oil and a very poor and expensive electric grid. Thanks to massive government involvement in R&amp;D in the electricity generation and transmission industry we now have one of the most advanced electric grids in the world. It can produce power using a variety of fuels, from nuclear to fossil fuels to wind, solar and hydroelectric. It's not 1930 anymore. "Did our tax dollars go to finance the three successful cars you mentioned?" This program provides loan guarantees for private lenders. So no. If a company like Fisker fails taxpayers are on the hook. However, the government collects interest from other loans in the program offsetting or recouping money from loans repaid in other parts of the program.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1365523275510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:01:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365525819931-16</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And "the beat goes on": o Fisker = $193 million loss to American tax payer o Solyndra = $528 million loss to American tax payer o Beacon Power = $39 million loss to American tax payer o Chevy Volt = Per unit cost $75,000, sticker price $39,995, each Volt sold costs GM (a federal government owned automobile company) $49,000, by the end of 2012 GM had sold 13,500 units of a projected 40,000 unit sales o Of the $10 billion invested in green jobs by the current administration $3 billion has been lost so far No you don't need to focus on Fisker to find out how successful the current administration is when it comes to picking winners and losers. Thank you Mr. president for all that you do. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1365525819931</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365526105856-17</Id><Topic><Title>Is FDIC planning to eliminate insured deposits with this plan?</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1365006049779</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:20:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, you're right! It's tough to keep you're money away from both the government and the thieves! And you're right about the police, they don't care! They just want to work their shift, put in their 20 years and get out. I don't bother to report a crime anymore. My brother had his truck stolen, right in front of the store. A tow truck pulled up, hooked it up and wasout of there in less than 2 minutes. They found the truck. It was in the deepest southernmost part of Mexico. They asked him if he wanted to come get it. He said "No thanks."</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1365526105856</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:48:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365527028914-18</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The cotton gin, the automobile, the airplane, electric lights, phonograph, telephone, all invented without government subsidies. You give government far too much credit although it is due some for building the Hoover Dam and TVA and especially for the development of nuclear energy. Westinghouse did more for the grid. There is a place for both government and private development but too much of the government development is pork barrel projects to win votes. I much prefer private development driven by popular demand. " You prefer the deadly pollution we see in China." And China has one of the most intrusive governments in the World; so what is your point?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365527028914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:03:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365527946734-19</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well done</Msg><Username>willian.madrigal</Username><Timestamp>1365527946734</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:19:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365528528652-20</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle and Barack are both hate-filled racists who occasionally slip up in public on open mic’s. It's part of who they are, have been for their entire lives</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364752473909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:54:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when FDR wrote a check for being lazy, and punished hard working people.</Msg><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1365528528652</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365529447526-21</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, there is a place for both government and private development. I prefer loan guarantees which uses government assurances to spur private investment in private research. Much better than the direct subsidies and tax credits sent to companies like Boeing, IBM or Exxon. So what is your gripe? Again, is it just that you don't like green technologies? "And China has one of the most intrusive governments in the World" That's what you Tea Brains think? The problem with China is not that it has an intrusive government? China's economy has been very successful. The problem with China is that it has a totalitarian one-party state. In a democratic state government serves the people. It provides them with clean air, earthquake proof building codes and consumer protections. China has a very intrusive government, but you still can't buy milk without fear it is poisoned. For a group of people who shroud themselves in patriotism, I think you have very little appreciation for what makes this country great.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1365529447526</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:44:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365531303060-22</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you have to be such an insulting #$%$ ricky? Can't you have a conversation without insulting a person because they don't think your way? I didn't think so.</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1365531303060</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 14:15:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365533673532-23</Id><Topic><Title>Optimistic news !</Title><Username>leeconnor743</Username><Timestamp>1365106294330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:11:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice report.</Msg><Username>smithmark374</Username><Timestamp>1365533673532</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 14:54:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365533726277-24</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who did I insult?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1365533726277</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 14:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365534341409-25</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ONLY difference between this program and any number of other programs is you Tea Brains don't like environmentally friendly product. You prefer the deadly pollution we see in China. What a bunch of nonsense! It's stuff like this that is just one of the reasons why you are not taken seriously. Even if you do make a good point!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1365534341409</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:05:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365535459917-26</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well then, you tell me why the Tea Brains are dead against investment in green technologies but not similar investments in other technologies. Look at the Keystone Pipeline. The Motiva Refinery, half owned by Saudi Refineries, is getting over $1 billion in special tax breaks to process the heavy sour crude the pipeline will carry. But Tea Brains insist we have to build the pipeline with no mention of that development investment. What gives?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1365535459917</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:24:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365538125687-27</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great job.</Msg><Username>paulcoleman168</Username><Timestamp>1365538125687</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:08:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365541266729-28</Id><Title>The Gang of Twelve...</Title><Msg>...Hey, wilkes, dan, jon, win, and your other assorted like minded individual(s). Here are the dozen Senators who are threatening to fillibuster any gun control legislation, led by Rand Paul (who's filly on drones went a long way to proving he's a nutball, while accomplishing nothing.) How about you frog folks explain to us all, why the American people, through their elected representatives are not entitled to a vote on this? You won't, because you can't, without revealing that you extremists, who care more about the gun lobby than the 2nd amendment, are afraid that the GOP minority will vote with the Democrats, because that is what America wants. God forbid that reason should prevail and government actually do something for a change. You have no legitimate reason, any more than these twelve pawns of the gun manufacturers do. If these guys proceed, the American public, even in their own supposedly safe gerrymandered districts, will take them out at the polls in the next election. Seriously, just one of you folks, try to explain your position on this (other than "they're comin' for our guns" nonsense.) The Gang of Twelve - remember their names at the polls next time around: "In addition to Paul, Lee, Cruz, Rubio and Moran, the Republican who have signed the second letter are Jim Inhofe of Oklahoma, Richard Burr of North Carolina, Ron Johnson of Wisconsin, Mike Enzi of Wyoming, Jim Risch and Mike Crapo of Idaho, Dan Coats of Indiana and Pat Roberts of Kansas."</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1365541266729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:01:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365541591943-29</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well done.</Msg><Username>andresmith537</Username><Timestamp>1365541591943</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:06:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365551554538-30</Id><Topic><Title>The Gang of Twelve...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1365541266729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:01:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eggo..my "bottom" is still really, really itchy. Do you have a barbevue forkk..I can use(??). Puppy tried nibbling to get off all the peanut butter (teehee) me did put it on earlier..but I am still really..really..itchy. Grins(!!)</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1365551554538</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 19:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365555998317-31</Id><Topic><Title>Is FDIC planning to eliminate insured deposits with this plan?</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1365006049779</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:20:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lovely lavie...Will you prease..prease scritchy scratch my "bottom" for me (??) Me bets..you be "berry berry" good at this whitey hiney scritchy scratchy..(!!) grins :)</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1365555998317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 21:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365556762975-32</Id><Topic><Title>Is FDIC planning to eliminate insured deposits with this plan?</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1365006049779</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:20:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is where I keep all my porn and corn chips (!!) Teehee and extra grins..</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1365556762975</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 21:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365557615308-33</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle and Barack are both hate-filled racists who occasionally slip up in public on open mic’s. It's part of who they are, have been for their entire lives</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364752473909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:54:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My "bottom" still itches..please pretty lavvy come and use your yeast coated cat-like tongue to calm my burning (!!) Happy toes now..teehee(!!)</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1365557615308</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 21:33:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365559974918-34</Id><Topic><Title>How many "green jobs" will $529 million buy?</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1364925284704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HahAHhah..and a beeg teehee too, "figgynuts"...Even "Eggo" with all his "superpowers" cannt #$%$#$%$inate something that isn't there (grins)..you're charac"T"er. chuckles..(??)</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1365559974918</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 22:12:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365563701398-35</Id><Title>I wish</Title><Msg>I wish that I had not been such an idiot with my jon3retired identity. I lays me in my reeking beddy at "nights" and "I"..I am really, really sorry that I such a fool with that ID. It was "really".. my favorite, and I just can't seem to find my.."reel" idem"titty" (heehee.."titty") with all of my other aliases..dan and coolinout and winholder and bouche (I picked this one night when I was really.."really" drunk and I thinked it so funny cuz it sounds like "douche"..teehee). Maybe if alls you will "writes" a nice note to Yahoo sensers..they will give "I" back my "jon3retired..ID..oh, please (??) whines..(??). My "bottom" iches(!!)</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1365563701398</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 23:15:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365564289890-36</Id><Topic><Title>AT &amp; T = THIEF'S</Title><Username>j.catucci</Username><Timestamp>1365452555540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 16:22:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ID thief.</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1365564289890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 23:24:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>