<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367467288862-1</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a sad state of affairs when gun nuts can't change, even to save children. Their opinion is more important to save for them.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367467288862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 00:01:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367467444083-2</Id><Topic><Title>Rubio Can't be that stupid</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1367458387362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 21:33:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that the best story you can tell tonight? It's a good whopper alright, but not the best.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367467444083</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 00:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367468563734-3</Id><Topic><Title>DIST 9 and T finally</Title><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1367460098775</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 22:01:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I certainly hope so. I'm tired of this $hit. Feel sad for those with 15 years or less but they can deal with it. Just tired of being tired.</Msg><Username>pedig4u</Username><Timestamp>1367468563734</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 00:22:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367479076888-4</Id><Title>Credito downgrade is coming.</Title><Msg>Guys, just be patient even if being patient is not virtuoso.</Msg><Username>madam_hillary07</Username><Timestamp>1367479076888</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 03:17:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367486794351-5</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Indeed Echo fails to report the whole story. The gun was bought by the parents for the 5 yr old. They left it loaded in the house accessible to the 5 yr. old. The parents explained they didn't know it was loaded. What version of legislation will solve aboslute stupidity? It seems to me this is a far more perfect example of how not to be a parent.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1367486794351</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 05:26:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367500125945-6</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing like handing out deadly weapons to 5 year olds that look like toys. But hey, if we're going to sell AR-15's en masse to gangs and cartels, they may need them for self-defense on the way to school. After all, if the local bully has a hot pink rifle with a baby blue barrel, your kid has a right to defend himself! These people are touched in the head.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367500125945</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 09:08:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367500338151-7</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm thinking restricting guns made to look like toys may be something we can all agree on, if only to help our law enforcement officers know when they are threatened. And maybe, just maybe, toning down the gun fetish this country has just a little bit. Guns are not the answer to all of your problems.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367500338151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 09:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367501169328-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare key author calls it a train wreck and will quit</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367113843677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 21:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And, when Obamacare is fully implemented in 2014, Aetna will not be able to deny you coverage or charge you more due to pre-existing conditions. That is one of the main problems the health reform law was meant to solve. I feel sorry for you, I really do. You're going to give yourself a heart attack worrying over this only to find out in 2014 that your situation improves with Obamacare. Most Americans won't notice any change at all, and most of the remainder, including you, will experience great benefits. But you, and millions of people like you, are being deluded by con artists whose sole purpose is to get money or political support. And you reject and insult people who are trying to help you, for no gain whatsoever. If you give yourself a heart attack it is your own hateful, ignorant fault.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367501169328</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 09:26:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367501379358-9</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How would I know what you meant? None of what you said makes a bit of sense.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367501379358</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 09:29:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367501926758-10</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fake ricky, you are lying. You proved it by citing a direct quote that did not exist. In my business, that is career ending and I see no reason I should tolerate it from you. I am not playing your game anymore. No matter what I say you will simply change your story or come up with another lie. Anyone can look at the document you posted and come to their own conclusions. And in 2014, even those who do not do so will know you are full of sh**. You've had your whole life to improve yourself as a person. But this is what you are, fake ricky. A message board liar, who can't even use his own alias to hide behind. Pathetic.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367501926758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 09:38:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367502574013-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you replying to me? Winholder want our government "to have the bravery to act" like Russia. Do you know anything about Russian politics? Do you know how Russians treat minorities? Do you know what Putin would do to populist opposition like the Tea Brains? Go live in Russia. Try it on for size. One of the great things about America is its protection of minority rights--political, religious, ethnic and otherwise. You don't like it, you prefer the "bravery" of Russian autocracy, then go to Russia. But there is no place for you and your ilk in a free country.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367502574013</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 09:49:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367504020530-12</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“Indeed Echo fails to report the whole story…It seems to me this is a far more perfect example of how not to be a parent.” – t.bfine There is no question the parents bear some responsibility. The story said that the rifle was sitting in the corner of the room, but they “didn’t know it was loaded.” Sane people don’t store any type of weapon in “the corner of the room”. Sane people also don’t buy .22 caliber rifles for five year olds. Just as importantly, sane people don’t start companies to market pink and blue actual rifles (not those B.B. guns“that’ll put your eye out”), but real small game rifles – to children of any age. Obviously, the entire marketing plan of multiple colors with cartoon-like sounding names is to attract the same market of youth who like Jiminy Crickett and Chip and Dale. And, t.bfine, sane people don’t have the misguided need to have their extremist political opinion necessitate that they defend any company that would design guns for kids, and target (pun intended) that market in another callous example of free market personal greed for profit. You should be ashamed for doing so. What next? And this just in… Coming Soon to a Kid Near You 5/2/13 - Routers, Pilton, MA Due to the overwhelming success of their product line of rifles for children, Keetone Sporting Arms of Pilton, MA has introduced its new line of weapons for children to debut in the fall of 2013, just in time for hunting season. The new products will come in a variety of brilliant colors, with many having names derived from cooperative marketing deals with Disnee*, Loonie Tunes and other cross marketing opportunities The first promotional product is designed to attract youngsters to the new products, with a free miniature switch-blade knife being included with any large box of Cap’n Crunch cereal. McDonalds will follow suit with a line of Ninja throwing knives and nunchucks included with all Kids Meals. The main product line will follow soon after. Being featured in an all-out blitzkrieg of advertisements on Nickleodeon and The Kartune Network will be such kid-friendly staples as Brass Knuckles for Babies, Carbines for Children, Knives for Kids, Grenades for Grandchildren, Thompsons for Toddlers. There will also be a line of fully-automatic weapons entitled Assault Rifles for Adolescents, which will be adorned with famous cartoon characters, including Dopie and Goofy, as a tribute to both the cartoons in which they appeared, as well as the NRA and other fools who encourage, inspire and permit this kind of nonsense to go on. *All companies appearing in this work are fictitious. Any resemblance to real persons, living or dead, is purely coincidental - except one. Oh, and t.bfine.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367504020530</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 10:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367505447649-13</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Recently a young women from our church gave a personal testimonial. In her story she talked about her young daughter Alice Anne. She said that Alice Anne was the love of her life and her daddy's little angel. She talked about the day that she and Alice Anne were home making cookies together. How her big brother Ricky was asked to let the dog out in the back yard. How Ricky had left the sliding back door open just a crack. How she heard the family dog barking and barking in the back yard, which she said she found annoying. How she went to the back door to let the dog in, and saw the dog racing around the swimming pool. How she went out to the swimming pool and found Alice Anne laying face down in the shallow end. How no amount of resuscitation from herself or the EMTs would bring little Alice Anne back to life. How she blamed herself for her moment of inattention and how she and Alice Anne's daddy would never be able to have the same relationship that they had had before the death of little Alice Anne. How she blamed God for taking away her little angel. How she asked God to forgive her for being a bad mother. How only through the grace of God was she able to make it through the day, and continue to live at all. How only through the grace of God was she given a second chance by the birth of her new little angel Sarah Anne. Yes my friends sometimes people make little mistakes that have big consequences, and I am sure that there is a federal law in there somewhere that would have saved little Alice Anne's life. But maybe, just maybe, it is just enough to try and make it through life doing your best to do the right thing, loving one another, forgiving one another when we don't make the mark, and praising God in all that we do. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1367505447649</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 10:37:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367505731318-14</Id><Topic><Title>Rubio Can't be that stupid</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1367458387362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 21:33:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahh, the latest Tea Brain demagogue to fall from grace for not being a complete loon. Maybe the NRA will make a youtube video where Rubio turns into Obama like they did for Cantor? It's interesting to contrast Rubio and Cantor with Bachman &amp; Cain, who fell from Tea Brain grace for being too darned looney and Sarah Palin, who's just the right amount of looney to stay in Tea Brain good graces.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367505731318</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 10:42:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367506282666-15</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile, T is quietly sneaking up on 38...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At the time I posted yesterday, T was almost at 38. That's a buck shy of 39 Beau. To me, the 39 close was artificial. In the final hour or so, it popped from the high 38's to finish at 39. A lot of that last 1/2 point increase was most likely in anticipation of a better than what we got report the following morning. To my way of thinking, the stock was somewhat fairly priced around 38.75. There were buys yesterday at 38. Considering the report was disappointing, we were less than a dollar away from 38.75. Regardless of all the numbers, T held up and recovered decently from the low 36 range where it traded post-report. Today's action does not look as promising as yesterday, but that's the way it goes. But for the the record, i am a long term holder. daily fluctuations don't cause me to lose sleep. Over 30 years of owning it and no regrets. it has served me well. How about sharing your thoughts.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367506282666</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 10:51:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367506533048-16</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile, T is quietly sneaking up on 38...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh now we are going to make things artifcial well lets say it hit 40 than pleasee HOW ABOUT IT HIT 39 DROPPED TO 36 50 AND HAS NOT COME BACK !! YET just please do not candi coat or imagine thiings</Msg><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1367506533048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 10:55:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367506581579-17</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile, T is quietly sneaking up on 38...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I withdrew the Marshal service order after learning you were writing about level 2. I stand or reacted Wilkie. Yeah, that last hour and the couple this morning are hard to figure out. Nothing shaking on the wire services, so it is a mystery. Then again, you know from many years of experience there is sometimes no rhyme or reason to trading activity. This is one if those situations. Just as inexplicable as yesterday's exceptional action was in a down market, so is today's with indexes looking good.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367506581579</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 10:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367506718712-18</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile, T is quietly sneaking up on 38...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typo above: I stand corrected...not 'I or reacted'. Sometimes spell check butchers what I correctly typed in the first place.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367506718712</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 10:58:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367507458280-19</Id><Title>ATTN SHIPLE INSURANCE: HOW COME YOU DON'T HAVE A WEB PAGE?</Title><Msg>After your brilliant responses and disclosure of bottom line income, I was considering throwing some business your way. But all I could find was Shipley Mo-Ped insurance. Is that the same outfit? I'm not in the market for Mo-Ped coverage. If you're going to run a user name of a business, why aren't you on the 'net? Maybe Zonbac is onto something about 'Monopoly' money. Anyway, here's your opportunity to get some great free advertising going by using the Spammers that infest the boards. Think about recruiting some of the Spammers to publicize your business. They'll be happy to flood every board in Yahoo! Finance promoting you 24/7. In the meantime, maybe you would care to inform us why you are not on the Internet?</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367507458280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 11:10:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367507769764-20</Id><Topic><Title>Rubio Can't be that stupid</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1367458387362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 21:33:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans wants you "Barefoot and Pregnant" and ignorant..... that makes up 90% of their voting base</Msg><Username>american_patriot_man</Username><Timestamp>1367507769764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 11:16:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367507965436-21</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea...those millions that were not paying for their healthcare will now have to pay</Msg><Username>american_patriot_man</Username><Timestamp>1367507965436</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 11:19:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367508001052-22</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Frogg, kill your own kids all you want. You can't cure stupid. Nevertheless, there are plenty of laws in plenty of jurisdictions that require fences around pools for that very reason. So we try. But when you start marketing candy colored guns as toys to kids that could kill my kid or someone else's kid, you've crossed a line that I'm simply not willing to let you cross. Manufacture and sell all the swimming pools you want to gangs and drug cartels and stupid parents, I don't really care. But don't give them guns.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367508001052</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 11:20:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367508107302-23</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The WSJ is known to twist the facts when it suits their political agenda(republican)</Msg><Username>formergop_america_n_decline</Username><Timestamp>1367508107302</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 11:21:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367508282364-24</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"misguided need to have their extremist political opinion necessitate that they defend any company that would design guns for kids" Funny, I don't recall defending the manufacturer. I'm pretty sure you made it up. I do believe the parents own the brunt of responsibility for the tragedy. It's too bad we can't come up with legislation that would prevent idiots and folks with zero common sense from buying/owning guns. That would be legislation that would be on point as to this case as well as Sandy Hook.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1367508282364</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 11:24:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367508364260-25</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>----You are right its a liberal disaster...---- No, its nothing like what Obama wanted..but had to compromise with Republicans....its the same program the GOP used in 1994 to counter what they called HillaryCare. They dusted it off in 2009, to counter what Obama wanted.......and Obama pulled a fast one on them by signing it.... better to get something rather than nothing</Msg><Username>american_patriot_man</Username><Timestamp>1367508364260</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 11:26:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367508364360-26</Id><Topic><Title>Rubio Can't be that stupid</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1367458387362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 21:33:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have to agree, If Rubio thinks another 800 page document will fix the problem he is out of his mind, he has been duped by democrat bait and switch and is now trying to sell it to the rest of America. Perhaps there is hope I heard him yesterday and I think he is getting the message conservatives aren't buying the gang of 8 #$%$ he is trying to sell.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367508364360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 11:26:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367509198258-27</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are wrong, you will just have to pay more to make up for those who won't/can't pay. If millions can't afford care now and have chosen to do without it how will Obamacare change that, they still can't afford it especially since under Obamacare healthcare has gotten more expensive. Most have seen at least a 30% increase in cost since it was implemented. How compassionate is it to fine a family for not having healthcare insurance when they choosing to use the money to put food on the table instead? What will happen if they can't afford to pay the fine will Obama put them in jail?</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367509198258</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 11:39:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367509663379-28</Id><Topic><Title>Rubio Can't be that stupid</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1367458387362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 21:33:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You obviously haven't been to liberal states like California or liberal cities like Chicago or Detroit, idiot!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367509663379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 11:47:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367509978139-29</Id><Topic><Title>Rubio Can't be that stupid</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1367458387362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 21:33:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure what you are talking about your list is incomplete, you need to add unemployed, on welfare and food stamps and what you have is a liberal democrat</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367509978139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 11:52:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367510012268-30</Id><Topic><Title>dont miss this, Alerts on stocks that run!!</Title><Username>valdezdominic441</Username><Timestamp>1367504971814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 10:29:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just signed up. hope we make some cash</Msg><Username>gnathan956</Username><Timestamp>1367510012268</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 11:53:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367510209468-31</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This little boy should be placed in foster care for his psychological and physical well being. He will forever be traumatized by this event. The parents, in my opinion, should be prosecuted for their extreme negligence.</Msg><Username>pcaphodge</Username><Timestamp>1367510209468</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 11:56:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367510398446-32</Id><Topic><Title>dont miss this, Alerts on stocks that run!!</Title><Username>valdezdominic441</Username><Timestamp>1367504971814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 10:29:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cool. i just texted in</Msg><Username>buchananjonathan946</Username><Timestamp>1367510398446</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 11:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367510427145-33</Id><Title>Obama: We Will Get Answers in Bombing Case!</Title><Msg>Sorry, no answers today. Tomorrow doesn't look good either.</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367510427145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:00:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367510650384-34</Id><Title>wow, Sick! I just made some huge profits</Title><Msg>If you’re trying to start out trading I highly suggest signing up for their free service. txt “YAHOO” to 5 5 5 8 8 8</Msg><Username>bluke160</Username><Timestamp>1367510650384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:04:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367510745088-35</Id><Title>Cost savings Idea - Eliminate the Border Patrol</Title><Msg>They have become almost useless since Obama is preventing them from doing their jobs</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367510745088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367510854282-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: We Will Get Answers in Bombing Case!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367510427145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:00:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, but now months later they claim that they have pictures of some guys that were around that area that night and are asking the Libyans if anyone knows them. You want to take any bets on the level of response to that request?</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1367510854282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:07:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367510893255-37</Id><Topic><Title>dont miss this, Alerts on stocks that run!!</Title><Username>valdezdominic441</Username><Timestamp>1367504971814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 10:29:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hope these picks r good</Msg><Username>dicksont327</Username><Timestamp>1367510893255</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:08:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367511264196-38</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok, Ok, I give up. Maybe you are correct in your belief that all facets of life should be regulated and controlled by government, and maybe that would lead to a safer world. But maybe, just maybe in a free society there are some risks in life that a responsible person should regulate and control by him or herself without "Big Brother's" oversight. I guess this is just one of those times when neither of us will ever see eye to eye. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1367511264196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367511329043-39</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is his post did he offer investment advice? The question you ignored is still there. You slam someone for something they didn't say. How do you think that might impact your credibility? Oh, I forgot, you don't have any.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1367511329043</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:15:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367511715062-40</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aside from the obvious foolishness of your comments, no I don't wish to live in Russia. I simply want a government that will someday begin to act in the best interests of the citizens of this country and not the minorities that have come here looking for a better life but want to make it like where they just left. I want a government that will do the things necessary to protect the citizens from those that are obvious threats. There are good governments and bad governments that like a squirrel finding an acorn can have at least one good idea occasionally and still not be worshiped or desired as a whole. And speaking of autocracy, that is what Obama pushes toward on a regular basis.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1367511715062</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:21:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367511767744-41</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“Funny, I don't recall defending the manufacturer.” – t.bfine “What version of legislation will solve aboslute (sic) stupidity?” – t.bfine Legislation that would prevent stupid people from manufacturing something intended for killing aimed specifically at children. Legislation that would, thereby, eliminate stupid parents from buying those same weapons manufactured by stupid people, to give to their small children, who, btw, have a very good chance of growing up to be equally as stupid as the parents. And, legislation that would make this argument a moot point. Thus, there would be no need for stupid lobbyists and other stupid people (those of “if the shoe fits, wear it variety”), to defend those stupid manufacturers by suggesting it’s okay to make cartoon rifles for five year olds, but it’s only the parents fault if their kid kills someone. If that’s not defending the gun manufacturers, I don’t know what is. “It's too bad we can't come up with legislation that would prevent idiots and folks with zero common sense from buying/owning guns.” – t. bfine Idiot – n; a person of the lowest order of mental retardation, having a mental age of less than 3 years old and an I.Q. of under 25. Synonyms : Fool, imbecile, half-wit, dolt… …to which I’ll add, any dunce or numbskull with zero common sense who would make the above statement, while being against background checks which would eliminate the mentally ill from buying/owning guns.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367511767744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:22:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367512133660-42</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"…to which I’ll add, any dunce or numbskull with zero common sense who would make the above statement, while being against background checks which would eliminate the mentally ill from buying/owning guns" ...to which I will add, I never said I was against expanded background checks. That is now twice in this string that you made something up in response to my posts. It's come to be expected, however.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1367512133660</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367512269292-43</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Mr. EE Hubcap...man of Peace...answer up.</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366991835062</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:57:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh Dave, I am afraid of the following posts that will be generated by Ricky and Echo about you not paying for your stuff. Saving, investing and collecting on taxes you paid as promised by a mostly liberal government does not qualify as 'paying for your stuff'. Those things are entitlements to this liberal group, unless of course you are poor uneducated and lazy, then you have the right to vote for any Democrat to maintain you status and not be called an 'entitlement' sucker by the libs. I am afraid your post will only serve to tick off the liberal posting Gods herein.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1367512269292</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:31:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367512429743-44</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“Where is his post did he offer investment advice? The question you ignored is still there.” – golf boy Is that all you have, Carl Spackler? I never said a word about him offering investment advice in that particular post. Hell, lately, he’s been offering investment advice on every other post. If you want to take investment advice from a wacked out Birther, good luck. What are you…just filler to get the page to scroll?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367512429743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:33:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367512441339-45</Id><Topic><Title>Cost savings Idea - Eliminate the Border Patrol</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367510745088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Border states need to create their own forces to protect their citizens and stop illegally border crossings then send BO the bill. It is the job of the federal government to protect our borders but BO refuses to do so.</Msg><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1367512441339</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:34:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367512807244-46</Id><Topic><Title>Cost savings Idea - Eliminate the Border Patrol</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367510745088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I knew an ex 101st Airborne man in the Border Patrol 30 years ago. He told me then that the border was lost. Not because of their lack of activity but because the pols wouldn't let them do their job.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1367512807244</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367513058033-47</Id><Topic><Title>Cost savings Idea - Eliminate the Border Patrol</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367510745088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...Right, art. I'm forming the North Coast Navy as we speak to stop those pesky Canucks from the lake invasion of Ohio. We're building a veritable Atlantic Wall just outside the Rock &amp; Roll Hall of Fame. Where do I send the bill? BTW, that's a really smart thing to be doing on a stock message board - advocating for an armed posse of vigilante fools to take the law into their own hands. You guys are absolute clowns.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367513058033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:44:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367513137757-48</Id><Topic><Title>Cost savings Idea - Eliminate the Border Patrol</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367510745088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>None of the pols have enforced the law. I picked cotton in Tahoka, TX in 1949. I got $2.00 per hundred lbs. to start. They flooded the area with Mexicans and the price dropped to .75 cents per hundred. All the Americans left the fields, Black and White. I was lucky, I found a job in power line construction. The price of cotton didn't drop. Obviously the large farmers made more money though.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1367513137757</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:45:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367513346890-49</Id><Topic><Title>Cost savings Idea - Eliminate the Border Patrol</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367510745088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Feds can't be trusted to protect the borders, border states know best how to protect their borders and where weaknesses exist.There would be greater accountability and resposivness if states assumed this role. It has been a problem for many years and has become much bigger under BO.</Msg><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1367513346890</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:49:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367513374279-50</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Mr. EE Hubcap...man of Peace...answer up.</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366991835062</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:57:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Win, I just received my Yahoo notification of your post. Thanx for your support. Thankfully there are more people that recognize the ideals you and I share. I can't speak to the echos, Ricky's and others that are consumed with their political bent. They are on permanent ignore. In fact, I avoid their topics on the board and rarely depart from T commentary. This clown hubcap came on by mouthing off about anti-union krap and I deviated a bit. Even though it was off topic, it did pertain to T inasmuch as they are a union shop, so I couldn't let that slide. Once this jerk revealed himself with all his BS'ing about his personal life accomplishments (in his mind), I had seen enough. Time to leave well enough alone and move on. Thank you for your kind words. We do share the same values. Regards, Dave.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367513374279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:49:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367513560918-51</Id><Topic><Title>Cost savings Idea - Eliminate the Border Patrol</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367510745088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Send the bill to the following address: The White House 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue NW Washington, DC 20500</Msg><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1367513560918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:52:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367513851453-52</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does that resemble, at all, anything I said? No. You just went off on what you think is an anti-"liberal" hyperbole. An image that has nothing to do with reality. This is not a choice between anarchy and totalitarianism. It is attempts to find practical solutions to practical problems in a free and democratic society.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367513851453</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367514091788-53</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I looked up the company on the internet. They literally have hot pink rifles with blue barrels named cricket and chipmunk. In fact, they come in a variety of colors and rainbow designs.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367514091788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 13:01:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367518928284-54</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When I was a kid about 8 my friend next door threw bullets from his dad's army pistol in an incinerator. He was grazed on the side of the head by a bullet. The dad was a WWII decorated vet. Kids find everything and haven't got the sense yet to understand things. Yet the gun nuts think guns and bullets everywhere is just great. Their opinion has to be right at all costs.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367518928284</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 14:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367522430823-55</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When I was a kid about 8 my friend next door threw bullets from his dad's army pistol in an incinerator. He was grazed on the side of the head by a bullet. " I won't call you a liar, clearly you do not understand physics and maybe you were just always gullible. Unconfined bullets don't "shoot" out, they explode. Now you could put an eye out with a piece of flying brass, or get a cut, but it takes a combustion restraining location for a bullet to shoot. I burned many paper shotgun shells because they had swelled from moisture, they would explode.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1367522430823</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 15:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367523449715-56</Id><Topic><Title>Cost savings Idea - Eliminate the Border Patrol</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367510745088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Echo, You're such a Schmuck! How do you live with yourself?</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367523449715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 15:37:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367524334943-57</Id><Title>THIS T BETTER GET BACK TO 39 PLUS SOOOON</Title><Msg>Any takes on this puppy...with stocks u never know</Msg><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1367524334943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 15:52:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367526574719-58</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Mr. EE Hubcap...man of Peace...answer up.</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366991835062</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:57:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No such thing as Obama phones, started under your GWB, and the Pres did not make the decision to cancel tours, the secret service did. The President of the USA isn't a KIng, maybe where you live they have them, not in America. But go ahead keep talking, without the facts, who cares. You're talking trash about Obama to 5 people who aren't changing their minds on what you say, so what good is that doing?</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367526574719</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 16:29:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367526744720-59</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would say that being able to raise your family with a decent standard of living and retiring without being a burden to your kids is a very enviable goal, which unfortunately may not be available to your kids. Today, even if you work for some very large companies, you don't even have a pension.</Msg><Username>gman310</Username><Timestamp>1367526744720</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 16:32:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367529010590-60</Id><Topic><Title>Cost savings Idea - Eliminate the Border Patrol</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367510745088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...OH MY - WHAAAT .. ECHO critical of someone ELSE for posting a NON-STOCK message on a "stock message board" – jon boy Okay, jon, you’ve proven repetitively that you can neither spell nor write. It would now appear that you are hell-bent on proving that you also cannot read. Here’s how it works, son. You are presently at the stage where you are attempting to sound out the words, syllable by syllable. (I might add, you are doing a splendid job.) Next you must learn to string all those syllables together so they flow smoothly. Having mastered the sound of the word, you then must put many of them together to form a cognitive thought – without – and please pay attention, because this gets harder, particularly for you – without pausing inextricably for a useless series or commas, quotation marks, exclamation points and girly emoticons. Assuming that you get that far, (and we all have our doubts), the really difficult part then ensues…reading for comprehension. To simplify all this for you, in response to your comment above, I’ll rephrase my point from this: “BTW, that's a really smart thing to be doing on a stock message board - advocating for an armed posse of vigilante fools to take the law into their own hands.” To this: Same sentence, delete “stock”…meaning it had nothing at all to do with content on any specific message board. Of course you would also have had to interpret “smart” as a facetious knock on fools like you who encourage law-abiding citizens to resort to armed vigilantism when they don’t get their own way…and then decipher on your own, that perhaps that isn’t the brightest thing to do. Got that now, jon? Fortunately for you, there will not be a quiz later. Now I assume you had no difficulty comprehending the sentence that followed that one, did you? “You guys are absolute clowns.”</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367529010590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 17:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367529498616-61</Id><Topic><Title>Cost savings Idea - Eliminate the Border Patrol</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367510745088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The American Indian Counsel has requested that the NFL disassociate itself with all Indian Names. Effective immediately, The Washington Redskins will change their name to the Washington Foreskins in honor of all the pricks in Washington D.C.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367529498616</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 17:18:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367529645734-62</Id><Topic><Title>Cost savings Idea - Eliminate the Border Patrol</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367510745088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...that was cute, even from fake ricky.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367529645734</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 17:20:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367532605787-63</Id><Topic><Title>THIS T BETTER GET BACK TO 39 PLUS SOOOON</Title><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1367524334943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 15:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would September be soon enough? LOL</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1367532605787</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 18:10:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367533688506-64</Id><Topic><Title>THIS T BETTER GET BACK TO 39 PLUS SOOOON</Title><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1367524334943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 15:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey hotshot insurance phony. Where's your web page like I asked you on a previous topic? You don't even have Internet access? You're a fake. Try looking at my topic from about 5 hours ago that you didn't have the balls to respond to.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367533688506</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 18:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367533787033-65</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well Feecesnation, I was standing right next to him when he threw them in, so there go your false accusations, down the drain. Obviously the bullet parts fly everywhere, all of them. You think the casing explodes and leaves the end of the bullet stationary? You think the casing doesn't separate from the bullet? My dad had plenty of guns around too, rifles. It figures your obsession to be right about your opinion, rather than be open minded, led you to believe I don't know gun barrels contain and "point" bullets. We would play with the 45 which was unloaded, maybe, but in time my friend found the loose bullets. As usual you missed the whole point of the post, but focused on something else. You are only interested in standing by your opinion, the lives don't appear to matter.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367533787033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 18:29:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367534030698-66</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not unless provide guidance by educating them as best as possible to prepare them as we have Gman. Then when the time comes, there is always an inheritance. You make a very good point. That's why it is so important for parental involvement every step of the way. Not to be overbearing, but to show them right from wrong as well as what it takes to succede. If that fails, you have done all you can do as a parent. Parenting is a life long responsibility and never really ends. .</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367534030698</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 18:33:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367534080697-67</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I can tell" You're as bad as Feeces, my friend was a wild kid and always was getting in trouble. I was the opposite. I was the tag along friend. You can't tell s...from shinola as they used to say. Maybe you are Feeces, he seems to be omnipresent.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367534080697</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 18:34:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367535987747-68</Id><Topic><Title>Cost savings Idea - Eliminate the Border Patrol</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367510745088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HeeHee...funny old lewcor..(!!).."HIM" pick lint out of wilty belly button..and call IT "picking cotton"..silly..silly..lewcor..(!!)..grins..</Msg><Username>jon3retiree</Username><Timestamp>1367535987747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 19:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367536809209-69</Id><Title>Dang I left .56 on the table selling T</Title><Msg>Loaded on cvi cvrr nuan Iep intc vwehx bwp. Go fer the divis all. Dave last post was dead on. Peace. Sorry for my agitations. Lets make #$%$ loads of $.</Msg><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1367536809209</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 19:20:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367539278726-70</Id><Topic><Title>Ma Bell (T) &amp; Baby Bells (VZ) ??</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1367522825091</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 15:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't understand the "let" part. I'm sure that institutional shareholders discuss with each other before placing their votes. Why would they need anyone to "let" them do that?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367539278726</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 20:01:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367539853252-71</Id><Topic><Title>Today's Volume</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367342969178</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:29:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With all that institutional activity I expected higher than average volume but only about half of the average. I hope it means that there is not much interest in parting with shares at these low prices. The Stochastic looks like it is about to turn up. I hope we get over $38 tomorrow or I am stuck with 40 worthless call contracts.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367539853252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 20:10:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367540022482-72</Id><Topic><Title>THIS T BETTER GET BACK TO 39 PLUS SOOOON</Title><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1367524334943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 15:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, didn't see it. I was making money AGAIN ;-) You just stay long over the next 4 months, and I'll just keep counting the monyy as my put options kick in, ENJOY!</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1367540022482</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 20:13:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367546202597-73</Id><Topic><Title>Ma Bell (T) &amp; Baby Bells (VZ) ??</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1367522825091</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 15:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH NO..(!!) "ME" madde "poor choice of word !" Imagnin "ME" shock..(??) Giggles and Greens..with a cocktail onion sized "She said teehee" (!!)</Msg><Username>jon3retiree</Username><Timestamp>1367546202597</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 21:56:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367546347455-74</Id><Topic><Title>49.1 million A.H. volume?</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1365117157264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 19:12:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even NOT "I" so stoopid to speall "coming" as "comming" in mull-tipple ("ME" likes "tipple") posts.."YOU" is sort of idiot some..(!!) kind or oother..RIGHTS(??)..Geegles and Gins (heehee..I mean "GRINS")..</Msg><Username>jon3retiree</Username><Timestamp>1367546347455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 21:59:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367546459459-75</Id><Topic><Title>Cost savings Idea - Eliminate the Border Patrol</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367510745088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.."THANKS" for too thUMPS UP..silly MISS PanSY LAdY LecWor..(!!) ..Grins..(!!)</Msg><Username>jon3retiree</Username><Timestamp>1367546459459</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 22:00:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367546592464-76</Id><Topic><Title>Rubio Can't be that stupid</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1367458387362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 21:33:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh my..(!!).."ME" will run fst nowing "DISASTER (!!)..is comming..TeeHee..(!!)</Msg><Username>jon3retiree</Username><Timestamp>1367546592464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 22:03:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367546673805-77</Id><Topic><Title>Dang I left .56 on the table selling T</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1367536809209</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 19:20:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't recall my last post, but if you become agitation-free, all is good. I agree that dividends are still the way to go unless circumstances change. Depending on age, goals, income, expenses and a whole slew of other factors, everyone has to tailor their planning accordingly. Financial planning is not a one size fits all as you know. Today was a disappointment compared to yesterday. How can a -100 Dow day result in a decent gain and today a +100 gain produces nothing? No news on anything I have read, so the past 48 hours fades into trading history with nothing to explain it...</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367546673805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 22:04:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367547242929-78</Id><Topic><Title>THIS T BETTER GET BACK TO 39 PLUS SOOOON</Title><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1367524334943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 15:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't want to answer huh? Ill try a third time. WHY DON'T YOU HAVE A WEB PAGE?</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367547242929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 22:14:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367547538388-79</Id><Topic><Title>THIS T BETTER GET BACK TO 39 PLUS SOOOON</Title><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1367524334943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 15:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Patience is a virtue Beau. T is not a high flyer price wise. On occasions, it has run a fast track. More often than not, it will just keep a steady pace. Look at it's history and then take into account the high dividend rate we collect. To expect it to skyrocket? Won't happen.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367547538388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 22:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367547824152-80</Id><Topic><Title>I check in once a month</Title><Username>freakedout35</Username><Timestamp>1367524399082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 15:53:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Name them.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367547824152</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 22:23:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367547991260-81</Id><Topic><Title>ATTN SHIPLE INSURANCE: HOW COME YOU DON'T HAVE A WEB PAGE?</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367507458280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 11:10:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except for your thumb down Shitley, I see your still dodging the question. Try again. WHERE'S YOUR WEB PAGE?</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367547991260</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 22:26:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>