<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-17"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363536172173-1</Id><Topic><Title>Guess Who</Title><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1363296073605</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess plain old fashioned ignorance is the only reason someone could be this bitter about something they know almost nothing about.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1363536172173</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:02:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363536825772-2</Id><Topic><Title>It looks like Obama wants to bankrupt America</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1362778576708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:36:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There is some middle ground between privatizing Medicare &amp; Social Security as Paul Ryan proposes and making Medicare &amp; Social Security untouchable." There is no such middle ground when the Democrats, particularly the President won't discuss such middle ground. Obama has already openly stated that unless he gets the revenue ‘enhancements’ he wants, there will be no budget agreement, and he won't even consider a plan that doesn't meet his requirements. The Democrats created SS and 'The Great Society' plans and they are also the ones that took the locks off the SS lockbox. They expanded Medicare and Medicaid, they expanded welfare programs, and you want to blame the boomers for all their failures. You're almost, not quite, but almost as bad as Obama as never placing responsibility where it in point of fact belongs.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1363536825772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:13:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363537499824-3</Id><Topic><Title>Detailed AT&amp;T Research Report !!!</Title><Username>ashleyjones221</Username><Timestamp>1362156250127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:44:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice one</Msg><Username>jose.delmonte</Username><Timestamp>1363537499824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:24:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363537769095-4</Id><Title>Downsizing Congress - part 1</Title><Msg>A BI-PARTISAN APPEAL: To both Republicans and Democrats. When a company falls on difficult times, one of the things that seems to happen is they reduce their staff and workers. The remaining workers must find ways to continue to do a good job or risk that their job would be eliminated as well. Wall street and the media normally congratulate the CEO for making this type of "tough decision", and the board of directors gives upper corporate management big bonuses Our government should not be immune from similar risks. Therefore: Reduce the House of Representatives from the current 435 members to 218 members. Reduce Senate members from 100 to 50(one per State). Then, reduce their remaining staff by 25%. Accomplish this over the next 8 years (two steps/two elections) this of course would require some redistricting. Some Yearly Monetary Gains Include: $44,108,400 for elimination of base pay for congress. (267 members X $165,200 pay/member/ yr.) $437,100,000 for elimination of their staff. (Estimate $1.3 Million in staff per each member of the House, and $3 Million in staff per each member of the Senate every year) $108,350,000 for the reduction in remaining staff by 25%. $7,500,000,000reduction in pork barrel earmarks each year. (Those members whose jobs are gone. Current estimates for total government pork earmarks are at $15 Billion/yr). The remaining representatives would need to work smarter andimproveefficiencies.It might even be in their best interests to work together for the good of our country! We may also expect that smaller committees might lead to a more efficient resolution of issues as well.It might even be easier to keep track of what your representative is doing. Congress has more tools available to do their jobs than it had back in 1911 when the current number of representatives was established. (Telephone, computers, cell phones to name a few) Note: Congress does not hesitate to head home for extended weekends, holid</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1363537769095</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:29:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363537862473-5</Id><Title>Downsizing Congress - part 2.</Title><Msg>Note: Congress does not hesitate to head home for extended weekends, holidays and recesses, when what the nation needs is a real fix for economic problems. Also, we had 3 senators who were not doing their jobs for the 18+ months (on the campaign trail) and still they all accepted full pay. Minnesota survived very well with only one senator for the first half of this year. These facts alone support a reduction in senators and congress. Summary of opportunity: $44,108,400 reduction of congress members. $282,100,000 for elimination of the reduced house member staff. $150,000,000 for elimination of reduced senate member staff. $70,850,000 for 25% reduction of staff for remaining house members. $37,500,000 for 25% reduction of staff for remaining senate members. $7,500,000,000 reduction in pork added to bills by the reduction of congress members. $8,084,558,400 per year, estimated total savings. (That's 8-BILLION just to start!) Corporate America does these types of cuts all the time. There's even a name for it. "Downsizing."</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1363537862473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:31:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363538033995-6</Id><Title>Congressional Reform Act of 2012</Title><Msg>Congressional Reform Act of 2012 1. Term Limits. 12 years only, one of the possible options below. A. Two Six-year Senate terms B. Six Two-year House terms C.OneSix-year Senate term and threeTwo-Year House terms 2. No Tenure / No Pension. A Congressman collects a salary while in office and receives no pay when they are out of office. 3. Congress (past, present and future) participates in Social Security. All funds in the Congressional retirement fund move to the Social Security system immediately. All future funds flow into the Social Security system, and Congress participates with the American people. 4. Congress can purchase their own retirement plan, just as all Americans do. 5. Congress will no longer get automatic pay raises. Congressional pay will rise by the lower of CPI or 3%. 6. Congress loses their current health care system and participates in the same health care system as the American people. 7. Congress must equally abide by all laws they impose on the American people. 8. All contracts with past and present Congressmen are void effective 1/1/13. The American people did not make this contract with Congressmen. Congressmen made all these contracts for themselves. Serving in Congress is an honor, not a career. The Founding Fathers envisioned citizen legislators, so ours should serve their term(s), then go home and back to work. If each person contacts a minimum of twenty people then it will only take three days for most people (in the U.S. ) to receive the message. Maybe it is time. LET'S FIX CONGRESS!!!!!</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1363538033995</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363547145068-7</Id><Topic><Title>Detailed AT&amp;T Research Report !!!</Title><Username>ashleyjones221</Username><Timestamp>1362156250127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:44:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks.</Msg><Username>haugpaul</Username><Timestamp>1363547145068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363553035996-8</Id><Title>DIST. 9 gonna screw up?</Title><Msg>Will a strike REALLY do anything? How long do ya think anyone in CA can afford to go without pay? T is waiting for union ta screw da pooch on this one. Managers really don't want ya to walk. On both sides, people that you will never see, and could care less about you are telling or watching you #$%$ in the wind. Or, just vote YES. it's as good as you are going to get.</Msg><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1363553035996</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:43:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363553393176-9</Id><Topic><Title>Detailed AT&amp;T Research Report !!!</Title><Username>ashleyjones221</Username><Timestamp>1362156250127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:44:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAMMER !!</Msg><Username>daxwang</Username><Timestamp>1363553393176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:49:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363568205337-10</Id><Topic><Title>DIST. 9 gonna screw up?</Title><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1363553035996</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:43:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have had a year to prepare and save. The cash cow in California will dry up for the over paid milk maidens in Texas. The business plan in 2013 maybe about to hit a snag.</Msg><Username>rhoke9</Username><Timestamp>1363568205337</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363576079741-11</Id><Title>Little things on military bases</Title><Msg>Things closed on week ends and such. Ya know it effects the civilians pay and military moral</Msg><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1363576079741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:07:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>