<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-01"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359710400121-1</Id><Title>OXF - Oversold, Ready to Rally!</Title><Msg>Strong Buy, Enjoy!</Msg><Username>davidgoldberg652</Username><Timestamp>1359710400121</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 04:20:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359720370577-2</Id><Topic><Title>ricky is not the brightest bulb</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1359589333438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dan2003hr...thalidomide baby!</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1359720370577</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:06:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359724165187-3</Id><Title>Pepsi to sign contract with CERP</Title><Msg>HUGE$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>tech.traders994</Username><Timestamp>1359724165187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:09:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359724519550-4</Id><Title>Ed Koch</Title><Msg>Be at peace Mr. Mayor! Shalom!</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1359724519550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:15:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359728617922-5</Id><Topic><Title>ricky is not the brightest bulb</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1359589333438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, all is well according to Ricky. Unemployment is up to 7.9% as of today's report. Not directionally correct, but all is well. The President's job council disbands, so surely all is well.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1359728617922</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:23:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359729269480-6</Id><Title>Just sold</Title><Msg>Got in at 33.92. Sold at 35.38. I might get back in If I see a strong move above 35.40.</Msg><Username>jc18630</Username><Timestamp>1359729269480</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:34:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359730597917-7</Id><Title>Sold Locked in Gain</Title><Msg>Market appears overbought here with the weak economic report today and an increase to 7.9% unemployment.</Msg><Username>thetrdr</Username><Timestamp>1359730597917</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:56:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359734266612-8</Id><Topic><Title>Just sold</Title><Username>jc18630</Username><Timestamp>1359729269480</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:34:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just sold as well. This company sucks... also changed my service provider. AT@T service is antiquated and expensive. My new service provider is one third the cost for similar plan.</Msg><Username>psyc14904</Username><Timestamp>1359734266612</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:57:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359735481682-9</Id><Topic><Title>ricky is not the brightest bulb</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1359589333438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All is getting better, tb, all is getting better. Obviously we are still in recovery--not recovered yet--but the worst is behind us. The hyperbole of the nattering nabobs of negativism is sounding more and more shrill these days. Rather than screaming and whining and stamping our feet we should be working on continuing the progress, right? I am pleased that House Republicans seem to have softened their stances a little bit. We apparently don't have to worry that they'll send us into default if they don't get everything they want right away. That's a good thing--good for the economy and good for our democracy.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1359735481682</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:18:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359735696431-10</Id><Topic><Title>Note to Jon</Title><Username>cloudview92</Username><Timestamp>1359693124238</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 23:32:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like mine, Jon's, some of Frognot and most of us true Americans posts have been removed. But ricky and echo's remain. So ricky and echo did you whine like a little B8t2h to the Yahoo message board to have them removed? Bunch of Sissy LaLa's! You may have noticed I didn't cap your names, thats not an accident, I'm showing a lack of respect for you!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1359735696431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:21:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359735954432-11</Id><Title>IMPORTANT INFO - T</Title><Msg>Check this important info about $T HELPS investor to gain in the market see this thread to see inside! http://finance.yahoo.com/mbview/threadview/?&amp;bn=57696f4c-6d8a-32b1-ab18-308677a59ca2&amp;tid=1359735866799-163814b3-1c95-4a37-90c3-cfb03f80701d</Msg><Username>tressacjb885</Username><Timestamp>1359735954432</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:25:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359736037878-12</Id><Topic><Title>IMPORTANT INFO - T</Title><Username>alenalct6078</Username><Timestamp>1359734980844</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:09:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAM ALERT</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359736037878</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:27:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359736069804-13</Id><Topic><Title>IMPORTANT INFO - T</Title><Username>tressacjb885</Username><Timestamp>1359735954432</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:25:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People I can not to make some revenue with this tips.</Msg><Username>sherrimtl76498</Username><Timestamp>1359736069804</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:27:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359737716016-14</Id><Topic><Title>Note to Jon</Title><Username>cloudview92</Username><Timestamp>1359693124238</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 23:32:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “You may have noticed I didn't cap your names, (sic) thats (sic) not an accident, (sic) I'm showing a lack of respect for you!” – bouch84 And that’s another run-on-sentence with your missed elision contraction sandwiched in the middle. I would like to tell you that I am thoroughly devastated and crushed by your intentional and cruel demonstration of a lack of respect for me…what a brilliant statement you have made! Unfortunately, I can’t really do that, because if you’d check it out, goofy, neither my, nor ricky’s names are capitalized in the first place. Did you put ALL your alphabet flash cards in your bicycle spokes as a child? I will, however, return the favor. You have a great day, douch84. (Would you like to buy a vowel…an “e”, perhaps?)</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1359737716016</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:55:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359741037202-15</Id><Title>OXF - Oversold Value Trade!</Title><Msg>Ready to Rally 100%, Enjoy!</Msg><Username>davidgoldberg652</Username><Timestamp>1359741037202</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:50:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359742807439-16</Id><Topic><Title>OXF - Oversold Value Trade!</Title><Username>davidgoldberg652</Username><Timestamp>1359741037202</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:50:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Palin may move to texass and run for office. You can;t keep a snow/hillbilly down.</Msg><Username>orri1934</Username><Timestamp>1359742807439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:20:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359743902350-17</Id><Topic><Title>How sad what Florida has become</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1359423608733</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 20:40:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I first thought you said, "How sad what Fonda has become." What a traitor to her country!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1359743902350</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:38:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359746590871-18</Id><Title>Get latest Information on PLSB</Title><Msg>PLSB is likely to double short term and be worth $3-5+ mid term. They have revenues, a hot sexy product, great packaging and just everything going for them.</Msg><Username>edwards_katie592</Username><Timestamp>1359746590871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:23:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359747640649-19</Id><Topic><Title>Just sold</Title><Username>jc18630</Username><Timestamp>1359729269480</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:34:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who is the new provider</Msg><Username>sirmidnight</Username><Timestamp>1359747640649</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:40:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359749036779-20</Id><Topic><Title>Ed Koch</Title><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1359724519550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:15:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was a bit like Emperor Nero - asking "How'm I doin'?" while NYC burned, but if you were a civil service worker in NYC in the 1980's you LOVED Ed Koch!!</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1359749036779</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:03:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359750665540-21</Id><Topic><Title>Union Vote</Title><Username>dynnyd</Username><Timestamp>1359593067464</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 19:44:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much of the down trend since 2008 was due to Randell Stephenson being a complete idiot?</Msg><Username>wilson-timothy8303</Username><Timestamp>1359750665540</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:31:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359750668304-22</Id><Topic><Title>2012 Bonus</Title><Username>drank2that</Username><Timestamp>1359222545409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 12:49:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the Bonus rumor is out now...121%</Msg><Username>from_out_of_the_blue</Username><Timestamp>1359750668304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:31:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359753138451-23</Id><Topic><Title>Just sold</Title><Username>jc18630</Username><Timestamp>1359729269480</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:34:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>check out two year chart. higher new lows. I have a sell order of 1/4th my shares at 38</Msg><Username>arsinehghazarian</Username><Timestamp>1359753138451</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:12:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359755693777-24</Id><Topic><Title>2012 Bonus</Title><Username>drank2that</Username><Timestamp>1359222545409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 12:49:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still no confirmation of anything?</Msg><Username>clueless_thought_police</Username><Timestamp>1359755693777</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:54:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359756580653-25</Id><Topic><Title>what a news!</Title><Username>ronbadger80</Username><Timestamp>1359033714046</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 08:21:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful info, thanks</Msg><Username>lawrenceronald13</Username><Timestamp>1359756580653</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:09:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359761704536-26</Id><Topic><Title>Is the AT&amp;T stock a good utility stock to own?</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1359663167643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 15:12:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good analysis! Thanks.</Msg><Username>ordinaryamerican</Username><Timestamp>1359761704536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:35:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359770401230-27</Id><Topic><Title>2012 Bonus</Title><Username>drank2that</Username><Timestamp>1359222545409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 12:49:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>122%</Msg><Username>thomasnoftzger</Username><Timestamp>1359770401230</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:00:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359772467234-28</Id><Title>After Hours Quotes...</Title><Msg>... “One ought, every day at least, to hear a little song, read a good poem, see a fine picture, and, if it were possible, to speak a few reasonable words.” – Johann Wolfgang von Goethe “Any individual entity that pretends to understand the rules that guide this space is under an illusion.” – Ze Frank “The aim of a joke is not to degrade the human being, but to remind him that he is already degraded.” – George Orwell "Already the Obama administration has been rocked by scandal. Beyonce lip-syncing; or at least we think she was lip-synching. Manti Te’o said it sounded very real to him." – Bill Maher “I used to think I was great in bed until I discovered that all my girlfriends suffered from asthma.” – Jerry Sadowitz “This is one time where television really fails to capture the true excitement of a large squirrel predicting the weather…This is pitiful. A thousand people freezing their butts off waiting to worship a rat. What a hype. Groundhog Day used to mean something in this town. They used to pull the hog out, and they used to eat it. You're hypocrites, all of you!.” – Bill Murray as Phil Connors "Yesterday House Speaker John Boehner said that President Obama's focus is to annihilate the Republican Party. Do the Republicans look like they need help from President Obama?" –Jay Leno “Alas! must it ever be so? Do we stand in our own light, wherever we go, And fight our own shadows forever?” – Edward Robert Bulwer Lytton “Whether the weather be fine, Whether the weather be not, Whether the weather be cold, Whether the weather be hot, We'll weather the weather, Whatever the whether, Whether we like it or not.” – John Rushkin</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1359772467234</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:34:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359772476601-29</Id><Title>AHQ (cont.)...</Title><Msg>... “If they can get you asking the wrong questions, they don't have to worry about the answers.” – Thomas Pynchon "President Obama delivered his inaugural address, which set a more liberal tone for his second term, especially the part where he showered the crowd with birth control pills." – Seth Meyers “What do we mean by ‘the public interest?’ Some say the public interest is merely what interests the public. I disagree.” – Newton Minow “Most harm is done by people who are awake.” – Jeremy Hardy “My first wife, I'll never forget her…and I've tried.” – Redd Foxx “Don’t accept your dog's admiration as conclusive evidence that you are wonderful.” – Ann Landers “I’ve come to the conclusion that roughly 50 percent of the adults in this country are simply too ignorant and functionally incompetent to be living in a free society. You might think I'm off base, but every day around half the people in this country go out of their way to prove me right.” - Neal Boortz “I go ‘it wasn't my fault, it was Captain Morgan!’ And my parole officer goes ‘Oh, like when Jose Cuervo made you ride the floor buffer?’, and I said ‘Exactly’!” – jon, explaining his new facial tattoo. “Fall with awareness and acceptance.” – Brian Kest “If you have a choice of selling shoes to ladies or giving birth to a flaming porcupine... look into that second, less painful career.” – Richard Jeni</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1359772476601</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:34:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359772499115-30</Id><Title>Quotes, out...</Title><Msg>... “It is possible to store the mind with a million facts and still be entirely uneducated.” – Alex Bourne “Superfluous wealth can buy superfluities only.” – Henry David Thoreau “If what you have done yesterday still looks big to you, you haven't done much today.” – Mikhail Gorbachev “Earth is but the frozen echo of the silent voice of God.” – Samuel M. Hageman “There is no place in a fanatic's head where reason can enter.” – Napoleon Bonaparte “Lip-synching – let that be a lesson; if you are in Washington DC and you open your mouth and another voice comes out, it better be the NRA, an oil company, or a bank." – Bill Maher “If a man proves too clearly and convincingly to himself . . . that a tiger is an optical illusion--well, he will find out he is wrong. The tiger will himself intervene in the discussion, in a manner which will be in every sense conclusive.” – Lord Bryon “All is mystery; but he is a slave who will not struggle to penetrate the dark veil.” – Benjamin Disraeli “North Korea is the country that the monkeys in The Wizard of Oz came from.” – Lewis Black “Here's a news flash: Today President Lyndon Johnson passed a highway beautification bill. The bill basically said that his daughters could not drive in a convertible on public highways.” – Robin Williams as Adrian Cronauer, Good Morning, Vietnam “Show me a man who lives alone and has a perpetually clean kitchen, and 8 times out of 9 I'll show you a man with detestable spiritual qualities.” – Charles Bukowski “God of the Old Testament is arguably the most unpleasant character in all fiction: jealous and proud of it; a petty, unjust, unforgiving control-freak; a vindictive, bloodthirsty ethnic cleanser; a misogynistic, homophobic, racist, infanticidal, genocidal, filicidal, pestilential, megalomaniacal, sadomasochistic, capriciously malevolent bully.” – Richard Dawkins “If a fetus is a human being, how come the census doesn't count them? If a fetus is a human being, how come when there's a miscarriage they don't have a funeral? If a fetus is a human being, how come people say ‘We have two children and one on the way’ instead of saying ‘We have three children?’ People say life begins at conception. I say life began about a billion years ago and it's a continuous process. Continuous, just keeps rolling along.” – George Carlin “They eat, they drink, and in communion sweet Quaff immortality and joy.” – John Milton “I travel a lot. I hate traveling, mostly because my dad used to beat me with a globe.” Dave Attel “Thank God for Darwin, eh?” – Bill Bailey “Have a good weekend, all.” – echo2165 “O day and night, but this is wondrous strange!” - Hamlet</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1359772499115</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:34:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359778403819-31</Id><Title>Well Egypt agrees with me</Title><Msg>even if ricky doesn't. From Egypt’s Rose El-Youssef magazine, which on Dec. 22 said the six infiltrators turned the White House “from a position hostile to Islamic groups and organizations in the world to the largest and most important supporter of the Muslim Brotherhood.”</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359778403819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 23:13:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359779343591-32</Id><Topic><Title>Well Egypt agrees with me</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359778403819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 23:13:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ricky will challenge me to name the six so I might as well do it now. The article said they are: "Arif Alikhan, assistant secretary of Homeland Security for policy development; Mohammed Elibiary, a member of the Homeland Security Advisory Council; Rashad Hussain, the U.S. special envoy to the Organization of the Islamic Conference; Salam al-Marayati, co-founder of the Muslim Public Affairs Council, or MPAC; Imam Mohamed Magid, president of the Islamic Society of North America, or ISNA; and Eboo Patel, a member of President Obama’s Advisory Council on Faith-Based Neighborhood Partnerships." I was surprised they didn't include Secretary of State Hillary Clinton’s top aide, Huma Abedin who was challenged by Michelle Bachmann. Huma's brother is a leader in the Muslim Brotherhood.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1359779343591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 23:29:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>