<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358592447453-1</Id><Title>So, The Appropriate Managment/Funding of Pensions Should Be @ the Top Of The Performance</Title><Msg>review when doling out salaries, options, and bonuses to the executives committee. Actually, it should take priority as it impacts 1,000's of lives. They JUST figured this out?</Msg><Username>datadoescount</Username><Timestamp>1358592447453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 05:47:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358599512534-2</Id><Title>A must read articulao in today's Barrons</Title><Msg>The confusion between S, Clearwire, T-Mobile and DISH (add to the mix DIRECTO-TV, soon to join the party) is the best thing for T and VZ since it will delay and nullify any competitive pressures in the marketplace.</Msg><Username>madam_hillary07</Username><Timestamp>1358599512534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:45:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358601389179-3</Id><Topic><Title>Economic Lies...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1358345360485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:09:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reich, and his like-thinking communist friend Paul Krugman, are what ails a great capitalistic country like America. They bow to the European model of socialism that has failed miserably. Ponzi schemes don't work, confiscation of other peoples wealth doesn't work, and donkeys don't work.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1358601389179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:16:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358601854310-4</Id><Topic><Title>So, The Appropriate Managment/Funding of Pensions Should Be @ the Top Of The Performance</Title><Username>datadoescount</Username><Timestamp>1358592447453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 05:47:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes and no. They must be factored into the big picture since running a company is no different than a football game where the scrore board tells the most important outcome. Same in running a company where the final profit or loss is what is of outmost important end-result. Surely pensions must be factored in but not to the point of short changing the employees or for that matter the shareholders. Let it be known that it was the former CEO of then AT&amp;T Bob Allen's famous saying that "people are our most important asset." IMO, he was being very dishonest when saying that since immediately thereafter he would turn around and fire tens of thousands of innocent working-class people while giving himself the most generous increases and bonuses he could get away with.</Msg><Username>madam_hillary07</Username><Timestamp>1358601854310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:24:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358608232300-5</Id><Topic><Title>$32.60 AH</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1358469280987</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:34:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did 3X, 35.5, 34.45, 33.45, and will add as/if it goes lower. Had an order in 1 day this week under 33 and it went up so i closed it out. I don't have that many shares, we're talking 100 shares at a time and in an ira. I now :( believe in diversification and never margin :( again. T went to 20 and one time in the last decade and they didn't cut their div, I like 5% div, I am not greedy.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1358608232300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:10:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358618017731-6</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ (cont.)...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1358561592948</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 21:13:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know you live in a country run by idiots... When smoking Pot is legal and widely accepted But smoking Tobacco is treated like a criminal offense. =================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if.... You can get arrested for expired tags on your car but not for Being in the country illegally. =================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if... Your government believes that the best way to eradicate trillions Of dollars of debt is to spend trillions more of our money. ==================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if... A seven year old boy can be thrown out of school for calling his Teacher "cute" but hosting a sexual exploration or diversity class In grade school is perfectly acceptable. ==================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if... The Supreme Court of the United States can rule that lower courts Cannot display the 10 Commandments in their courtroom, while Sitting in front of a display of the 10 Commandments. ==================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if... Children are forcibly removed from parents who appropriately Discipline them while children of "underprivileged" drug addicts Are left to rot in filth infested cesspools. ==================================================== You know you live in Country run by idiots if... Working class Americans pay for their own health care (and the Health care of everyone else) while unmarried women are free to Have child after child on the "State's" dime while never being held Responsible for their own choices. ==================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if... Hard work and success are rewarded with higher taxes and Government intrusion, while slothful, lazy behavior is rewarded With EBT cards, WIC checks, Medicaid and subsidized housing, And free cell phones. ==================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if... The government's plan for getting people back to work is to Provide 99 weeks of unemployment checks (to not work). ==================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if... Being self-sufficient is considered a threat to the government. ==================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if... Politicians think that stripping away the amendments to the Constitution is really protecting the rights of the people. ==================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if... The rights of the Government come before the rights of the Individual. ==================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if... Parents believe the State is responsible for providing for their Children. ==================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if... You can write a post like this just by reading the news headlines. ==================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if... Being stripped of the ability to defend yourself makes you "safe". ==================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if.... You have to have your parents signature to go on a school field Trip but not to get an abortion. ==================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if... An 80 year old woman can be stripped searched by the TSA but a Muslim woman in a burka is only subject to having her neck and Head searched. ==================================================== You know you live in a Country run by idiots if... Using the "N" word is considered "hate speech" but writing and Singing songs about raping women and killing cops is considered "art". =============================================</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358618017731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:53:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358619306451-7</Id><Title>test...test...test</Title><Msg>1234321. test out.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358619306451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:15:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358620015952-8</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ we're being overrun by Saharian sand pirots...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1358561609179</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 21:13:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It just hit me! My dog sleeps about 20 hours a day. He has his food prepared for him. His meals are provided at no cost to him. He visits the Dr. once a year for his checkup, and again during the year, if any medical needs arise. For this he pays nothing, and nothing is required of him. He lives in a nice neighborhood in a house that is much larger than he needs, but he is not required to do any upkeep. If he makes a mess, someone else cleans it up. He has his choice of luxurious places to sleep. He receives these accommodations absolutely free. He is living like a king, and has absolutely no expenses whatsoever. All of his costs are picked up by others who earn a living. I was just thinking about all this, and suddenly it hit me like a brick .......... My dog is a Democrat!!!!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1358620015952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:26:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358621713090-9</Id><Topic><Title>A respectable close</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1358542930816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 16:02:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You related to Wilkes?</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1358621713090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:55:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358622192048-10</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ we're being overrun by Saharian sand pirots...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1358561609179</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 21:13:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your dog is a democrat and you are an idiot. What did you expect?</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1358622192048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:03:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358625399706-11</Id><Topic><Title>AHQ we're being overrun by Saharian sand pirots...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1358561609179</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 21:13:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like he expected something even dumber than his dog to answer. And you obliged him. ROTFL</Msg><Username>dvmb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1358625399706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:56:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358625684792-12</Id><Topic><Title>So, The Appropriate Managment/Funding of Pensions Should Be @ the Top Of The Performance</Title><Username>datadoescount</Username><Timestamp>1358592447453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 05:47:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Factored in??? It's been nearly 5 years of sub-par growth in Pension Obligations due to financial calamity and it's been well-broadcasted to last perhaps a couple more years. Now they take action?</Msg><Username>datadoescount</Username><Timestamp>1358625684792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:01:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358637256159-13</Id><Title>Underfund pensions but gift $4 Billion to T-Mobile</Title><Msg>The $4 B would have gone a long way to filling the pension gap. The elimination of senior management bonuses for at least 5 years would seem to be in order based on just these two examples of management incompetence.</Msg><Username>followthevolume</Username><Timestamp>1358637256159</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:14:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358638196964-14</Id><Title>TIME TO SELL</Title><Msg>28-29 coming very soon. Pension problems ?? SHAREHOLDERS ON THE HOOK ???? THERE GOES ANY DIVY INCREASES . ALREADY SOLD 1275 Sh. FRI MAT GO LOWER ??. Is ATT in Illinois ?? SAME PROBLEMS BK</Msg><Username>missedlow</Username><Timestamp>1358638196964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:29:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358639976141-15</Id><Topic><Title>Picked Up 200 Shares</Title><Username>jjohns8181</Username><Timestamp>1358465247594</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:27:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Loaded 3200 more thru 32.99 up we see 34.40 in two weeks</Msg><Username>jjohns8181</Username><Timestamp>1358639976141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:59:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>