<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360159721819-1</Id><Topic><Title>When, where from, and why did your ancestors move to America?</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1359993883892</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:04:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH...that explains Braica! LOL</Msg><Username>ciscokid_1st</Username><Timestamp>1360159721819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 09:08:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360162921141-2</Id><Topic><Title>(BREAKING NEWS) Analyst Downgrades AT&amp;T</Title><Username>rich_morris</Username><Timestamp>1360161114296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 09:31:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHAT R TALKING ABOUT !!!</Msg><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1360162921141</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:02:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360163004722-3</Id><Topic><Title>(BREAKING NEWS) Analyst Downgrades AT&amp;T</Title><Username>rich_morris</Username><Timestamp>1360161114296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 09:31:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great news!</Msg><Username>michelecook203</Username><Timestamp>1360163004722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:03:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360163005341-4</Id><Topic><Title>(BREAKING NEWS) Analyst Downgrades AT&amp;T</Title><Username>rich_morris</Username><Timestamp>1360161114296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 09:31:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Talking about SPAM</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360163005341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:03:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360163242705-5</Id><Topic><Title>let's keep this simple</Title><Username>doldtko</Username><Timestamp>1360112022150</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 19:53:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not a problem when you have $30 in cash coming in each week. That's the relevant point.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360163242705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:07:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360166480860-6</Id><Topic><Title>DRIPS - Am I the only one that always seems to have my DRIP...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1360010781789</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:46:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think the floor traders are honest? They police themselves with no real oversight. However, many people DRIP so a lot of money is there at the same time competing for the shares. That very well could account for the higher prices.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1360166480860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:01:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360168432409-7</Id><Topic><Title>poster ricky is in Argentina</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1360015909719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 17:11:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem obsessed with Chicago, Froggie. Do you live there?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360168432409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:33:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360169119340-8</Id><Title>CERP tradeing 70 million projected to hit 3-4 dollars</Title><Msg>OMG!!! LOOK FOR YOUR SELF</Msg><Username>stock.brains</Username><Timestamp>1360169119340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:45:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360171862379-9</Id><Topic><Title>poster ricky is in Argentina</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1360015909719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 17:11:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No I don't live there, But I am facinated by the city that our "dear leader" calls home. I am also facinated by the inability of the National media (i.e., ABC, CBS, NBC,, CNN, etc.) to report any news regarding this city's inability to govern and control crime. Remember last month Chicago had the equivalent of two Sandy Hook shooting events whithin the city limits. What did we hear from the National media? crickets How many news conferences has our "dear leader" given where the National media has asked about what his recommendations are for reducing murders in the city of his home. I know you like truth and facts, I do too, but I also like to investigate and point out hypocricy when I find it, because we all know that if the National media finds news that places our "dear leader" in a less than positive light, then the media will spike the story, or pretend that the events never occurred. Can you imagine if the home city of George W. Bush had the reputation that Chicago has? The drum beat for off with his head would be deafening. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1360171862379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:31:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360172152929-10</Id><Topic><Title>let's keep this simple</Title><Username>doldtko</Username><Timestamp>1360112022150</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 19:53:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't you have something better to do with your dildco? We got your point yesterday. You got a problem? Lay it out pal. Enough of the budget lessons #$%$.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1360172152929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:35:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360173379519-11</Id><Topic><Title>New T Analyst Report (MUST SEE)</Title><Username>martincarlos897</Username><Timestamp>1360166832246</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:07:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good information.</Msg><Username>abel_brooks</Username><Timestamp>1360173379519</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:56:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360176632984-12</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY !</Title><Username>william.koening</Username><Timestamp>1359998195453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:16:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice report, thanks !</Msg><Username>myers_james</Username><Timestamp>1360176632984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:50:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360178967893-13</Id><Topic><Title>(BREAKING NEWS) Analyst Downgrades AT&amp;T</Title><Username>rich_morris</Username><Timestamp>1360161114296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 09:31:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>props</Msg><Username>christopherhansen93</Username><Timestamp>1360178967893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:29:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360180012819-14</Id><Topic><Title>DRIPS - Am I the only one that always seems to have my DRIP...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1360010781789</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:46:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My DRIP this quarter was at $35.26, slightly below the median price. The account is with WellsFargo.</Msg><Username>royferg</Username><Timestamp>1360180012819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:46:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360181334497-15</Id><Topic><Title>New T Analyst Report (MUST SEE)</Title><Username>martincarlos897</Username><Timestamp>1360166832246</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:07:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report.</Msg><Username>grayjohn263</Username><Timestamp>1360181334497</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:08:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360181343895-16</Id><Topic><Title>Quotes, out...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1359772499115</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:34:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Echo, do us all a favor. Go into the garage and hang yourself, would you please!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1360181343895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:09:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360181560492-17</Id><Title>Frog Response...</Title><Msg>... “Remember last month Chicago had the equivalent of two Sandy Hook shooting events within (sic) the city limits.” - frog My, oh, my, Frogman, you have a penchant for distorting everything you say to your over-zealously biased view. You have no credibility attempting to discuss the merits of gun control, when your emphasis seems to be on vilifying both our President, (to whom you referred twice in your rant as “dear leader” ala other like-minded birther buffoons), as well as the “National Media”, whom you referenced 4 times with disdain, again like the Tea Party Main Stream Media nonsense. You are a one-trick pony ensconced in extremism Stating that Chicago had “the equivalent of two Sandy Hook shooting events” would seem to infer that there were two mass murder events, totaling 54 deaths caused by assault weapons. Obviously that is not the case. As of January 29th, in Chicago there were 43 total homicides. I don’t have the actual final numbers, but most were individual events, and most were done with handguns. So, your way of discussing a solution to the problem is to criticize the President, the media, and any attempt to actually deal with the situation, all while clamoring for more guns for the patriotic vigilantes. You are a fool. God knows, you don’t want to do anything to jeopardize jon’s ability to sell weapons at gun shows, right, Gomer? And you guys claim Chicago has the most rigorous gun control laws in the country. Not as it relates to bad guys’ ability to easily get guns at random, or the punishment they receive when caught with an illegal weapon. Why don’t you listen to someone who knows the situation – the Superintendent of the Chicago Police Department – who incidentally is a 2nd Amendment advocate in the middle of the chaos, not some wacko demagogue like you. You want to stop gun violence in this country? Then get nutballs like you and the NRA front for the manufacturers to go after the real culprit...the endless supply of illegally obtained HANDGUNS. In my mind, this is a far more important issue than assault weapons. Chicago Police Superintendent: Gun Laws Play Huge Role In Lowering Gun Deaths February 04, 2013 3:00 PM (NPR) Garry McCarthy, the police superintendent of Chicago, favors tougher gun laws. The murder rate rose there last year even as it fell in New York. There were 506 murders in Chicago. New York had 414 with a population roughly three times the size. Superintendent McCarthy says he has a plan to fight gun violence in Chicago. It includes some familiar ideas: banning assault weapons and large capacity magazines, universal background checks as well as three-year mandatory, minimum sentences for illegal gun possession. But he told me, the one thing that would make the most difference, not only in Chicago but in the entire country, is requiring that the government be notified any time a gun is lost, stolen or transferred. SUPERINTENDENT GARRY MCCARTHY: Because in the state of Illinois, somebody who is a legal purchaser of a firearm can go into any gun shop with their FOID card, buy firearms, walk out the door, hand them to whoever they want. There's absolutely no accountability for what happens to that gun. Now, what's the result of that? We had an officer who was shot back in March by the name of Del Pearson. He almost died. He lost three-quarters of the blood in his body. Fortunately, he survived. The gun that was used to shoot Del Pearson, there's one recorded transaction on that firearm. It was bought in Blue Island, Illinois, in 1972 by a 52-year-old woman who died in Little Rock, Arkansas, in 2006. Absolutely no record of that firearm since 1972. Where has that gun been? Was it lost? Was it stolen? Was it a store purchase? We'll never know. SIEGEL: If somebody purchased a gun and did not report it lost or stolen and that gun then were used in a crime, should the person who owned it be held liable in some way for the use of that gun? MCCARTHY: You know, I guess, you're posing a question that says, should I be accountable for the guns that I buy? SIEGEL: Mm-hmm. Yes. MCCARTHY: I would say yes, because it's pretty significant to lose a firearm that can cause the death of another. And the fact is the legal gun owner, the person who is not engaged in straw purchasing, will have an affirmative defense, and at the same time, there will not be a pattern where this person has purchased eight guns over five years and lost all five of them or eight of them. Right now, when we recover a gun at the scene of a crime and I go back to you and I say: Robert, we just recovered your gun. And you say: Oh, thank you. I lost that. And that's the end of the story. That's unconscionable. SIEGEL: Are law-abiding gun owners in Chicago part of the solution to law enforcement or part of the problem that you face? MCCARTHY: I think, you know, the - I'm not ready to make a judgment on that because I support the Second Amendment. But what I am willing to say is the fact that reasonability in these gun laws is recognized by reasonable people, many of whom are gun owners. And if there were no special interests involved in this and it was put to a popular vote in this country today, I believe all of these measures would pass. They would pass muster because they're practical. It's not saying you can't own a gun. It's saying that when you own a gun, there's accountability, and there's responsibility there. And at the same time, when you're not allowed to have a gun and you're illegally in possession of that firearm, there's a certainty of punishment, which is going to have an effect on crime rates. Did you hear that, Froggie? Nobody’s coming after your guns. You just need to show more responsibility with them and tell jon to stop selling them to straw buyers. That’s according to Superindent McCarthy who knows considerably more than you do about the situation in Chicago...and... ...In your heart, you know he’s right.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360181560492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:12:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360183137546-18</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY !</Title><Username>william.koening</Username><Timestamp>1359998195453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:16:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The way to defeat these penny stock free loaders is: use the report abuse blue option at the lower right corner of the post. Yahoo reacts!!!</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360183137546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:38:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360184372611-19</Id><Topic><Title>Frog Response...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360181560492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:12:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>echo2165: You are typical of liberals. If you had the ability to reason you would not be a liberal. When you read: “Remember last month Chicago had the equivalent of two Sandy Hook shooting events within (sic) the city limits.” You interpreted it to mean two 27 fatality events. Any REASONABLE person reading it would understand that it meant the same total fatalities in all events rather than just two events. Your response not only indicates you can't understand what you read but also indicates that you believe all the hog wash in the MSM.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360184372611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:59:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360184926285-20</Id><Topic><Title>let's keep this simple</Title><Username>doldtko</Username><Timestamp>1360112022150</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 19:53:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You lose sight of one very important point. Does AT&amp;T make a profit on borrowed funds over and above the interest cost?? The answer is YES. The shareholders benefit from the debt!!!</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1360184926285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:08:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360186824755-21</Id><Topic><Title>let's keep this simple</Title><Username>doldtko</Username><Timestamp>1360112022150</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 19:53:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There you go complicating things! Remember, he wants to keep it simple. I'll add yet another point beyond simple: In 2012 T returned to shareowners $23B in dividends and share repurchases, which of course, burned cash. I suppose if he isn't an owner he would not appreciate how the company is spending its cash.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360186824755</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:40:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360187711399-22</Id><Topic><Title>Frog Response...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360181560492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:12:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “…you can't understand what you read but also indicates that you believe all the hog wash in the MSM…” - wilkes Why don’t you call Chicago Police Superintendent McCarthy and tell him you consider him a part of the Main Stream Media? I can’t understand what I read? You just read a piece that said essentially that anyone still crying about the Main Stream Media is an ignorant boob, and your response goes a long way to confirming that. Incidentally, skeezix, the issue was handguns. Do you want to discuss the actual point of the story, which you obviously didn’t read, or do you want to simply continue being goofy and making a fool out of yourself? How to Stop the Violence in Chicago by frogwilkes Shut down all media except Fox, do something about the “dear leader”, and arm to the teeth every man, woman and child in Cook County.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360187711399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:55:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360189579350-23</Id><Topic><Title>Frog Response...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360181560492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:12:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obviously that is not the case. As of January 29th, in Chicago there were 43 total homicides. I don’t have the actual final numbers, but most were individual events, and most were done with handguns." I think you just made Frog's point. What difference does it make that there were nearly as many gun related homicides that were not considered 'mass' shootings? 43 is still a large number of dead and to further make his point, you stated most were handgun crimes, not 'assault' weapons. "In my mind, this is a far more important issue than assault weapons." Yes, the number of people killed with illegal weapons by criminals that shouldn't have access and in many cases shouldn't even be on the streets is more important than the semantic argument of the definition of the type of weapon used.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1360189579350</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:26:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360189799860-24</Id><Topic><Title>When, where from, and why did your ancestors move to America?</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1359993883892</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:04:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"and, yes, it tells them she stands as the “great protectors of all” who wish to join us…regardless of race, faith or creed, as it relates to being welcomed to a land of equal opportunities for everyone." If, repeat if, you came here legally!</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1360189799860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:29:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360189890834-25</Id><Title>insiders selling the hell out of this #$%$ gotta go ill be back for a divvy</Title><Msg>maybe</Msg><Username>iveson.larry</Username><Timestamp>1360189890834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:31:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360192602384-26</Id><Topic><Title>DRIPS - Am I the only one that always seems to have my DRIP...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1360010781789</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:46:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the reason is that so many shares are being purchased in DRIP that this constitutes more buying and selling and forces the price per share up. Happens with most DRIP's.</Msg><Username>northvisitor34</Username><Timestamp>1360192602384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 18:16:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360193093943-27</Id><Topic><Title>DRIPS - Am I the only one that always seems to have my DRIP...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1360010781789</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:46:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I paid $35.12 on TD Ameritrade.</Msg><Username>northvisitor34</Username><Timestamp>1360193093943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 18:24:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360195805733-28</Id><Topic><Title>Frog Response...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360181560492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:12:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I wanted too I could get many weapons that are illegal including some quite potent ones. I won't mention where or how for fear some nut case under a psychiatrists care and using druges that cause them to commit these horrific crimes should read this. I have no need of such weapons so won't make any effort to procure them, unless, this government tries taking my freedoms away more than they already have. Funny how they trusted me with them while in service but now try to restrict my rights. The 2nd Amendment was NOT for hunting or personal protection but to stop would be dictators from taking control. "Executive Orders" anyone?</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1360195805733</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:10:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360199302517-29</Id><Title>TOP 20 EMPLOYERS ACCORDING TO YAHOO NEWS</Title><Msg>T ain't one of them</Msg><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1360199302517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:08:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>