<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360240492508-1</Id><Topic><Title>Is the AT&amp;T stock a good utility stock to own?</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1359663167643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 15:12:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The following article from CSCO is extraordinarily noteworthy. Just in case you missed seeing it, here is the link: http://money.cnn.com/2013/02/05/technology/mobile/smartphone-4g/index.html?source=yahoo_quote What are we to infer from this market forecast? To be sure, not all wireless customers are/will be 4G intense data users but nevertheless, the data clearly shows good days are ahead for the AT&amp;T stock.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360240492508</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:34:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360241348827-2</Id><Topic><Title>poster ricky is in Argentina</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1360015909719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 17:11:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's got that fatal malady, Republicanism.</Msg><Username>lv66vette</Username><Timestamp>1360241348827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:49:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360244077588-3</Id><Topic><Title>TOP 20 EMPLOYERS ACCORDING TO YAHOO NEWS</Title><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1360199302517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:08:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, you can always put your cash in a bank. Good luck.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1360244077588</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:34:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360247896269-4</Id><Topic><Title>poster ricky is in Argentina</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1360015909719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 17:11:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But I am facinated by the city that our "dear leader" calls home." Then perhaps you should be thinking more about Rahm than Barack. I understand he is doing a pretty good job of chipping away at the ward system that has so stunted the politics of that city. Perhaps Obama will decide to enter Chicago politics after his term ends. Chicago would be a better place for it. But in the meantime, Obama is not an government official of Chicago and never has been. He is the President of all Americans. Do you think he should spend his days and nights trying to solve the problems of Chicago instead of America? "Can you imagine if the home city of George W. Bush had the reputation that Chicago has? " You mean New Haven CT? Midland TX? Houston TX? Perhaps if he had a Chicago background he would not have so nonchalantly compared the death rate in Iraq to the murder rate in US cities as if that was something to be happy about. But I assure you I am far more interested in what our officials do and what their policy preferences are than where they lived. "What did we hear from the National media? crickets" And this is the most idiotic statement of all. The conservative hack wing of the national media has been harping on everything that has happenned in Chicago since Obama became president. That is how you know to discuss it. All the while they've been telling you "the media" isn't covering the issue, as if they are not the media. Events in Chicago are well covered by the media. The portion of the media concerned with journalistic standards has not covered it because it is unimportant. If the national media only covered what YOU think is important what would we cover? 24-hours of talk about Obama's birth certificate, his skeet shooting ability, his wife's butt, the cost of a bus, lists of the economic indicators that dipped negative this week, and Benghazi. Ad nauseum interrupted only by breaking new alerts everytime crime happens in Chicago. I believe they call that Fox News. Throw in a little religion and you have the 700 club. Both of which just so happen to be a part of the media.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360247896269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:38:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360248035238-5</Id><Topic><Title>Frog Response...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360181560492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:12:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And he's back! So when you wrote in comprehensible English, which alias did you mean to use? Dan? Froggie? Winholde I really am just talking to one or two hacks here, aren't I?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360248035238</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:40:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360248532935-6</Id><Topic><Title>Frog Response...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360181560492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:12:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What difference does it make that there were nearly as many gun related homicides that were not considered 'mass' shootings?" 20 dead six year olds. The particular horror of the crimes is meaningful. That's why we care about terrorism. Terrorists don't kill many people but the horror and pointlessness of the crimes have a pronounced affect on our psyche. Handgun violence is just as important an issue--or more important. But it is also more intractable. Very few Americans want to ban handguns. But taking away guns that allow any lunatic to kill 26+ people in 2 minutes is a no-brainer. Handgun violence is not a reason to keep us from preventing the horrific crimes committed by people with assault rifles.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360248532935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:48:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360248693126-7</Id><Topic><Title>Is the AT&amp;T stock a good utility stock to own?</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1359663167643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 15:12:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanx for taking the time to write some excellent comparative stat's. I'm sure you're going to catch heat by some trolls/posters, etc. that will produce a bunch if obscure #$%$ information. Nice job mate!</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1360248693126</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:51:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360248705133-8</Id><Topic><Title>Frog Response...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360181560492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:12:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Funny how they trusted me with them while in service " What a silly comment. They gave you weapons so you could efficiently kill alot of people. That's why they give servicemembers all kinds of weapons: grenades, F-15s, nukes. Yet we don't "trust" people with them in the civilian world.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360248705133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:51:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360249901192-9</Id><Topic><Title>Scanning Various States Financial News ..</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1360248891589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:54:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Virginia continues to be a laughingstock with McDonnell as Governor &amp; Republicans controlling the GA. And they have that Attorney General who keeps sueing climate scientists. What a shame after Virginia produced Kaine, Warner &amp; Webb over the last decade. Do you think if they keep this up they'll lose their reputation as a great state for business? I think they may. You can't do business in a state run by nutjobs trying to replace the US dollar. Do you think anyone will want to use a currency backed by the full faith and credit of that group of loons? What woman would want to work in that state now? Virginia has been a fast growth state in its urban areas and is now decidely blue. But with Republicans controlling gerrymandered rural districts it has become a microcosm of our national situation. An sophisticated and young urban majority ready to move the country forward with a backward, older, rural minority clinging to institutional power, trying desperately to move the country backwards.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360249901192</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:11:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360250553615-10</Id><Topic><Title>Is the AT&amp;T stock a good utility stock to own?</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1359663167643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 15:12:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks....</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1360250553615</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:22:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360250880608-11</Id><Topic><Title>Scanning Various States Financial News ..</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1360248891589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:54:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “…can anyone shed more light on this 'concept' ?” (Why), yes, jon, I’d be “happy” to “shed” more light (chuckles) on this “concept”…you are an idiot (makes sense) “chuckles, snark.’!*~</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360250880608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:28:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360251021080-12</Id><Topic><Title>Scanning Various States Financial News ..</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1360248891589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:54:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... Yes, by all means…have Virginia develop their own currency…perhaps fashion it after Confederate currency, as it would be about as valuable…then you and Rick Perry down in Texas can proceed with your movements for secession. Neither state will follow you, but you and Rick can secede from mankind and move to Ittoqqortoormiit, Greenland, and comfort each other while waving “Don’t Tread on Me” flags at the (few) other locals.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360251021080</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:30:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360254252053-13</Id><Topic><Title>Is the AT&amp;T stock a good utility stock to own?</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1359663167643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 15:12:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>@C_S. I did look at the chart you referred to. There is no doubt that the future success of this company is based on customers and their data/phone/entertainment usage. Nothing new there. Communications of any kind...present or future...will always be a part of everyday life. I did just about every job at the technician level and retired early from the company. While not perfect, T paid me well and I continue reaping the benefits of my career. I cashed out my pension and invested right back into it because I believe in what they do. After 11+ years, I have benefitted greatly. Those who game play by betting if it goes up or down a few cents every week by option trading or use a similar casino-like strategy #$%$ me off to no end. Especially other retiree's. Investing isn't a game. I hope they get their kicks, but I would prefer they lose their shirts. Same goes for the opinionated bunch that use a lot of flowery terms like "stochastic's, Bollinger Bands" and other krap they toss around to sound like an expert of sorts. All the while gambling away on hopes of the stock going up or down a few cents to make a buck. On the other hand, I put my money where my mouth is. I bought the stock and enjoy the dividends. Any modest price appreciation is a bonus. My ownership will pass to my children and with it the security of a respectable dividend held in Trust for their future. All the gamblers are #$%$ with my children and grandkids by the penny-ante games they play. Is it any wonder I'm not a fan? Your original post was one of the best I've seen in some time. No #$%$, just sound comparison vis-a-vis a quality Utility. I hope viewers take it to heart. You can't argue your post and the thumbs have shown support. My disclosure is as yours. Long. Very long.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1360254252053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:24:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360256428921-14</Id><Topic><Title>Frog Response...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360181560492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:12:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jon, et al., read my post again and see if you can come up with a response that indicates comprehension.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360256428921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:00:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360256571061-15</Id><Title>7 Million to Lose Insurance Under Obamacare</Title><Msg>ouch! Another Obama lie President Obama's health care law will push 7 million people out of their job-based insurance coverage — nearly twice the previous estimate, according to the latest estimates from the Congressional Budget Office released Tuesday. CBO said that this year's tax cuts have changed the incentives for businesses and made it less attractive to pay for insurance, meaning fewer will decide to do so. Instead, they'll choose to pay a penalty to the government, totaling $13 billion in higher fees over the next decade. Our Healthcare under Obama is in serious decline. I Had to make a trip to the emergency room at our local hospital. Has anyone else been to the emergency room since Obama took Office? This place had turned into something like you would expect in a third world free clinic. Bus loads of people being dropped off for free non-emergency care while people with urgent care needs wait in line behind those looking for free healthcare. After waiting for almost 3 hrs without seeing a doctor we just left and took our chances with visiting our doctors office the next day.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1360256571061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:02:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>19</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360257937736-16</Id><Topic><Title>Frog Response...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360181560492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:12:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... “I had to make a trip to the emergency room at our local hospital… Bus loads of people being dropped off for free non-emergency care while people with urgent care needs wait in line behind those looking for free healthcare. After waiting for almost 3 hrs without seeing a doctor we just left and took our chances with visiting our doctors office the next day.” – fake ricky Let me make certain I understand this. You” had to make a trip to the emergency room”, (“HAD TO” being the key phrase) but after waiting for 3 hours, you decided to see your doctor the next day? Doesn’t that make you sound like you were one of those wanting free non-emergency care? I mean, people with what you called “urgent care needs” (i.e. emergencies) don’t wait for 3 hours then decide to leave. Why do you think they call it the Emergency Room? Getting your Johnson caught in your zipper hardly qualifies you for emergency care. So, instead you went to your local doctor the next day for that and a lobotomy, after having Tea at party HQ? I see. (Could those “bus loads” actually have been ambulances by any chance?)</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1360257937736</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:25:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360266203634-17</Id><Topic><Title>7 Million to Lose Insurance Under Obamacare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1360256571061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:02:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when the doctor on call doctor tells you to get to the emergency room you should probaby take his adivce. Yes I have insurance unlike most of the other non-english speaking patients in the emergency room who had brought all their kids to be treated for cold and flu symtoms. When the sun starts to show itself in the morning and you haven't seen a doctor yet after 3 hrs should you continue to wait for who knows how much longer, or make arragements to visit your doctor at his office when it opens?</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1360266203634</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:43:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360266314758-18</Id><Topic><Title>7 Million to Lose Insurance Under Obamacare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1360256571061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:02:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"CBO said that this year's tax cuts have changed the incentives for businesses and made it less attractive to pay for insurance" That's true. But it has nothing to do with Obamacare. The tax break for employer-sponsored health insurance has always been there. The incentives for businesses change whenever the tax code changes. The higher the taxes, the bigger the payoff from any tax loophole, including the health insurance tax break. The CBO's projections for the law never really changed. All of the people who lost employer coverage due to the Bush tax cuts did so in 2002 &amp; 2003. The CBO had projected that when those cuts expired (which was "current law"), more employers would offer health insurance. Since those tax cuts have been made permanent by Obama, those employers will not offer health insurance. You're arguing over projections here, not reality. No additional people are going to lose health insurance. What is really happenning is that people who lost health insurance due to health insurance tax effects of the Bush tax cuts will now have access to insurance on the exchanges or Medicaid. "Bus loads of people being dropped off for free non-emergency care" While I know that you're just lying (you can't even be truthful about an anonymous alias!), you are actually pointing out a problem Obamacare will fix. By law, ERs have to examine patients regardless of their ability to pay, so people without insurance often go to ERs for care. It's really their only choice, but it is actually very, very expensive to treat people for minor ailments in ERs. These visits are covered by taxpayers. But if you provide people with insurance, they go to see a physician, which is much cheaper. Obamacare will reduce the number of uninsured by 34 million people. That is 34 million people with better health at a lower cost to taxpayers. This is, btw, already working in Massachusetts. It is one of the major reasons Romney pushed for Romneycare there. I have to say, he had the right idea on that one.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360266314758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:45:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360266341577-19</Id><Topic><Title>7 Million to Lose Insurance Under Obamacare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1360256571061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:02:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Talking to yourself, Jon, et al.?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1360266341577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:45:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360267479477-20</Id><Title>You Might want to pick up some **YTRV** Feb 19th</Title><Msg>massive news alert yahoo!</Msg><Username>pq.qual</Username><Timestamp>1360267479477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:04:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360279438580-21</Id><Topic><Title>The Art Of Trap ..</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1359902844425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 09:47:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shoots the clay's what?</Msg><Username>rcub5d</Username><Timestamp>1360279438580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:23:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360288408184-22</Id><Topic><Title>Scanning Various States Financial News ..</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1360248891589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:54:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Replace the U.S. dollar? Ever read on a bill. "Federal Reserve Note?" The "fed" is a privately owned banking and money creation system. The bills are printed at cost by the Treasury and used to buy interest bearing government notes. How do you like paying vigorish on "your own" money? There would be NO MONEY in circulation but for coinage. The money is created but not the money to pay the vigorish. It is a gigantic Ponzi scheme that eventually collapses as more and more debt accrues. Do some study and quit being a fool.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1360288408184</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:53:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360295144224-23</Id><Topic><Title>7 Million to Lose Insurance Under Obamacare</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1360256571061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:02:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>quit it with the Fox News C &amp; @ P stuff.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360295144224</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:45:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360295619253-24</Id><Topic><Title>Scanning Various States Financial News ..</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1360248891589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:54:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for this interesting post on ATT. Your never ending need for the attention of strangers seems to be distracting you from the point. Good luck!</Msg><Username>wledigmacsen</Username><Timestamp>1360295619253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:53:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>