<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-06"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370519562294-1</Id><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Msg>The Obama administration is secretly carrying out a domestic surveillance program under which it is collecting business communications records involving Americans under a hotly debated section of the Patriot Act. http://www.cnbc.com/id/100793836</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370521122348-2</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish I could be comfortable they are doing it for the right reasons i.e., our safety and security.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1370521122348</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:18:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370522396934-3</Id><Topic><Title>Land of the free</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369948675101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Commentary from Paul R. Beane on KFYO radio on 1/24/2013: Good afternoon, I'm Paul R. Beane and I'm your right wing gun nut. You know, me and fellow gun owners are responsible for all the carnage in our streets and our schools. Never mind that Ted Kennedy's car has killed more people than my entire collection of firearms-- Most of which I have owned since childhood when I saved my pennies and nickels in order to purchase them and each and everyone is in perfect working order. It is the responsible gun owners of today that are being blamed for all the shootings. Obama calls us the right wing gun nuts, clinging to our guns and to our religion. But lets take a little closer look. The Fort Hood shooter, a Muslim, and a registered Democrat. The Virginia Tech shooter, he wrote hate mail to George Bush and his staff and was a registered Democrat. Aurora Colorado shooter, he was a staff worker on the Obama campaign and took part in Occupy Wall Street. He was a progressive liberal and guess what? A registered Democrat. The Newtown, Conn shooter hated Christians and was a registered Democrat. The Columbine high school shooters were too young to vote, but both of their families were progressive liberals and registered Democrats. And one more thing, not a single one of these killers were members of the National Rifle Association. So I have got it figured out how to make this country much safer; leave the guns alone and lock up all the Democrats. I'm Paul R. Beane and that's the way I see it</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370522396934</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370523258329-4</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Safety &amp; Security ... under this (smoke &amp; mirrors) president ?? Perhaps the only safety &amp; security we have today is a gun behind every bush .. so keep your powder dry boys. His way of circumventing our 2nd. (and 1st.) Amendment</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1370523258329</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370524210386-5</Id><Title>IOGA is looking like it is about to go on a massive run</Title><Msg>I heard there is a massive promo coming into IOGA . Keep an eye on it</Msg><Username>juansweet213</Username><Timestamp>1370524210386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370526447757-6</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well he now has a new "Security Advisor" so that should solve everything. Forget about her Benghazi lies and focus on her education. FOCUS!!!</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370526447757</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:47:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370528057498-7</Id><Topic><Title>Land of the free</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369948675101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So the President gets to raise money for his Party using government tools and you want to blame it all on lobbyists and tax exempt organizations? I don't think any political or lobbying group should be tax exempt ever. Any political 'information' group, fund raisers, special interest group sponsor should be tax exempt. Now back to the original subject that you tried to deflect the attention from, do you think it is fair or any sitting President, from either Parry to use government property in political fund raising efforts? Anything over and above normal SS coverage should be paid for at full cost. Do you disagree with that concept? Yes or no, without the lobbying flack to distract from the subject. Can you accomplish that simple task?</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1370528057498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:14:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370528365447-8</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The debate is over, and I won. That's Obama's line. 'Elections have consequences and we won.' A difference without distinction.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1370528365447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:19:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370528597674-9</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't you really wish that it were that simple. Fox and others are reporting the news about the IRS. The IRS is a leadership shambles and taking Fox off the air won't change that. Get a grip, all that is being done by this administration is not illegal, much of it is politically dishonest and at best stupid, but it leads the general public to questions their motives and to lose confidence. At a point where they administration keeps saying everything is getting better, and it isn't, is not the time to be caught in lies. They have been and are scrambling to get ahead of them before more are found. It really is that simple.</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1370528597674</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:23:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370528796724-10</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This has to be a lie being told by those evil clowns at Fox News. Ricky has already told us that the world would be a much simpler place with bright sunny days for all if only they would go away and folks would stop watching them. Surely his government wouldn't do anything like this?</Msg><Username>winholder</Username><Timestamp>1370528796724</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:26:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370529808013-11</Id><Topic><Title>Wow - another godawful day for T...</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1370442019273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:20:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh... so that's how you lost $400,000? You lose no matter what the stock does right? Cheers. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1370529808013</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:43:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370529884506-12</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sheesh, winholder, grow up. Fox News lies consistently. What do you call someone who tells the truth most of the time, but consistently throws in blatant lies. You call that person a liar. The fact that you people are feeling self-righteous because Fox News has been known to present actual real facts at times is telling. You should demand honesty ALL THE TIME. People who are dishonest or who intentionally set a false impression should be fired. Period. That is the absolute minimum standard. But throwing in some dishonesty and intentionally setting false impressions pretty much describes Fox News and the conservative media these days.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370529884506</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:44:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370530275677-13</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The secret court order was discovered by Britain's Guardian newspaper. It reported the discovery yesterday. Are we calling the Guardian liars?</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1370530275677</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370530542506-14</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How did that reducied embassy security spending work out for you? Did I miss Texas and Oklahoma passing up government disaster money? Do you like your internet fun and PC, cell phone? That was developed by your government spending. The roads you drive on, government spending. The planes you fly on, made possible by your government spending. Didn't Boehner go to brazil on vacation using taxpayer spending? Didn't cantor go to France the same way? Where are the posts of outrage? Or is this reallly all about one thing, the President is not the right color.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1370530542506</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:55:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370530643472-15</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I had hoped that the Obama administration had put a stop to this sort of thing. Clearly we need to repeal or severely curtail the powers granted by the PATRIOT Act. Obama signed an extension to the PATRIOT Act two years ago when attempts to modify it in Congress failed. I'm more prone to trust Obama than I ever was to trust Bush/Cheney, but I think we can agree that granting this kind of power to any president is dangerous. It is a ridiculous breach of individual liberty and it always has been.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370530643472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:57:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370531529954-16</Id><Title>IOGA looks ready to take off. Check it out</Title><Msg>IOGA looks perfect at these levels. Bottomed out and ready for a massive run</Msg><Username>jesusfrazier545</Username><Timestamp>1370531529954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:12:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370531909866-17</Id><Topic><Title>Wow - another godawful day for T...</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1370442019273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:20:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, but then again, you were too stupid to buy under $35, LOL!!!</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1370531909866</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:18:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370532091481-18</Id><Topic><Title>Land of the free</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369948675101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"not automatically mean they are Tea Party members or even wrong" No, they're wrong because they are wrong and they are Tea Brains because they are Tea Brains. I could come up with another term? Fox Brains. Rush Brains. WND Brains. But I think Tea Brains captures it best. Pea brains who may or may not be card carrying members of the Tea Party but may as well be. It fits.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370532091481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:21:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370532105035-19</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very alarming. The Obama Gestapo is taking more of your freedoms and privacy. This goes way beyond the Patriot Act. It is random surveillance without cause. The American Civil Liberties Union said it is "It’s analogous to the FBI stationing an agent outside every home in the country to track who goes in and who comes out,"</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1370532105035</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370532658593-20</Id><Topic><Title>Land of the free</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369948675101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think we need campaign finance reform so that money is less a part of politics in general, precluding the need for or benefit from Presidential fundraising at all. You're worried about trivialities--likely only because you can, at this moment, pin them to Obama. When Romney was campaigning in his taxpayer supported bus I didn't hear a peep from you. The fact is that every President, and his opponent in campaign years, need special security, including special transportation, which is paid for by taxpayers whenever they travel and for whatever reason. If you want to end all this fundraising you complain so loud about, then you need campaign finance reform. If you are not willing to support that then you have no credibility on this issue.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370532658593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370532828360-21</Id><Title>Insider Buying</Title><Msg>Not a lot of money, but still a vote of confidence... Insider Transactions Reported - Last Two Years Date Insider Shares Type Transaction Value* May 30, 2013 STEPHENS JOHN JOSEPH Officer 642 Indirect Acquisition (Non Open Market) at $34.99 per share. 22,463 May 30, 2013 GEISSE ANDREW M Officer 513 Indirect Acquisition (Non Open Market) at $34.99 per share. 17,949 May 30, 2013 WATTS DONALD W Officer 380 Indirect Acquisition (Non Open Market) at $34.99 per share. 13,296 May 30, 2013 BLASE WILLIAM A JR Officer 636 Indirect Acquisition (Non Open Market) at $34.99 per share. 22,253 May 30, 2013 LEE LORI M Officer 75 Indirect Acquisition (Non Open Market) at $34.99 per share. 2,624 May 30, 2013 STEPHENSON RANDALL L Officer 1,603 Indirect Acquisition (Non Open Market) at $34.99 per share. 56,088 May 30, 2013 DONOVAN JOHN Officer 602 Indirect Acquisition (Non Open Market) at $34.99 per share. 21,063 May 30, 2013 DE LA VEGA RAFAEL Officer 849 Indirect Acquisition (Non Open Market) at $34.99 per share. 29,706 May 30, 2013 STANKEY JOHN T Officer 256 Indirect Acquisition (Non Open Market) at $34.99 per share. 8,957 May 30, 2013 COUGHLIN CATHERINE M Officer 114 Indirect Acquisition (Non Open Market) at $34.99 per share. 3,988</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1370532828360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370533115850-22</Id><Topic><Title>man my diamonds got diamonds! over 300% in gains!</Title><Username>goodshahs</Username><Timestamp>1370225127725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 22:05:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i really like this site</Msg><Username>millionairestock</Username><Timestamp>1370533115850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:38:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370534490274-23</Id><Topic><Title>Land of the free</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369948675101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“…it is fair or (sic) any sitting President, from either Parry (sic)” “I don't think any political or lobbying group should be tax exempt ever. Any political 'information' group, fund raisers, special interest group sponsor should be tax exempt.” Well, golfboywinbag, I have absolutely no idea which of your beaucoup conspiracies you are addressing with the above rambling gibberish. First, if you really want to be taken seriously, learn how to construct a basic sentence and get a freakin’ dictionary. Please explain the difference between “any political or lobbying group” (who you don’t think should be tax exempt) and “any political information group, fund raisers, special interest group sponsor” (who you DO believe should be tax exempt?) They’re both political groups by your own definition, aren’t they? Do you have any idea what you’re really trying to say, or did your gerbil just run across your keyboard? And who in the hell do you think you are to be the arbiter of what delineates the travel duties of the President, from what you would like to call “political fund raising.” Are you referring to a specific event? Do you even know what you’re referring to? Do you even know where K Street is? Are you on drugs? It’s also very telling that you bring up the subject of campaign funding…but only as it relates to the President, for some strange reason. If this was anything other than just another of your smear attempts, wouldn’t you be complaining about all politicians, not just the President? Or, in your case, at least all the black politicians? What a joke…suggesting that you guys want to seriously do something about campaign finance reform?? Why don’t you start with overturning Citizens United? And, incidentally, I don’t think churches should be tax exempt, either…particularly the mega-churches who seem more interested in politics than salvation. OH, BLASPHEMY! And, Winnie, the repetitive use of “deflection” gives you away.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1370534490274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:01:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370534510589-24</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee 'icky' ... and Obama's "blame game" lives on thru you !! Did you know I get 40% of my (T.V.) news from the PBS News Hour, about 20% from other PBS programming .. and the rest from MSM !! And why is this you ask (??) - well, I don't have cable or satelite, so I don't get Fox News !! And by the grace of God I had a pretty good GPA in "Common Sense 101 &amp; 2", so I'm able to mentally separate Obama's 'chicken salad' from his 'chicken #$%$' ... oh, but I've never seen anything but 'Chicken S*it comming from 'el presidente' So, as long as you keep accepting Obama's doggie biscuits laced with "whatever" .. as your "payment" for POSTING, you will remain ignorant and down-troddened. You could at least 'try' washing them down with a little Tea instead of drinking from his 'waste water' pipe .. (and you seemed so educated ??) Grow up .. and "THINK" for yourself for once - (you may feel better)</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1370534510589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:01:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370534568611-25</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very strange that you got three thumbs down on your excellent post. Maybe there are some who just look at your name and don't read what you post. The "Patriot" Act was and is overkill and was exactly what Ben Laden was hoping to gain from the 9/11 attack.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370534568611</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370535173310-26</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"icky' .. are you bucking for one of Obama's daughters hand in marraige .. or sumpin ??</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1370535173310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:12:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370535212516-27</Id><Title>If you haven’t checked out IOGA what are you waiting for</Title><Msg>IOGA looks like it is about to run. Do some DD on it. We could see an easy double from these levels</Msg><Username>palmerthomas471</Username><Timestamp>1370535212516</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370535794437-28</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Verizon response; Obama has forbidden Verizon from revealing the order's existence, We are living in tyranny</Msg><Username>art_bell51</Username><Timestamp>1370535794437</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370536912580-29</Id><Topic><Title>If you haven’t checked out IOGA what are you waiting for</Title><Username>palmerthomas471</Username><Timestamp>1370535212516</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:13:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will check it out.</Msg><Username>clucas149</Username><Timestamp>1370536912580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:41:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370537771327-30</Id><Topic><Title>If you haven’t checked out IOGA what are you waiting for</Title><Username>palmerthomas471</Username><Timestamp>1370535212516</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:13:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am buying this now</Msg><Username>jonathanavila624</Username><Timestamp>1370537771327</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:56:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370537884986-31</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How did that reducied embassy security spending work out for you?" Hillary's mistake costs us all, there were billions appropriated but not spent, uninformed moron.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370537884986</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:58:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370538307598-32</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did I say the story was a lie? No, I did not. I said the fact that you people think it is such a big deal that Fox actually told the truth says a lot about you. That is the minimum standard. In most circles "didn't lie" earns you a D at best. In Tea Brain circles it is something that brings you on par with actual respectable journalism and forgives all past and future transgressions.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370538307598</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:05:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370538638072-33</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Until you learn to write comprehensibly you will have a hard time convincing me or anyone else that you are anything but a dimwit. The ability to write reflects an ability to think. Writing well is not optional, especially in this format.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370538638072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:10:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370538654139-34</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Did I say the story was a lie? No, I did not" Great, I was just looking for clarification. Deflection can muddle the point.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1370538654139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:10:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370539069768-35</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. The secret national security court issued the order which included the gag order on the Verizon. It has now done so under two Presidents. The Patriot Act and the secret national security court are the problem. A president, any president, simply shouldn't have that much authority and we should not have secret courts.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370539069768</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370541438445-36</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Rictardo</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1370056426720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 23:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will? Wonderful! Any change in the health marketplace affects my business. The ACA is no different. But repeal of the ACA at this point would also increase business. Believe me, the hack selling "Obamacare Survival Guides" is making far more money off the law than I am. The biggest change for my business is that I will soon be able buy health insurance on the health exchange. I no longer have to rely on my wife's job. Which means she can quit and start her own business if she wants to. That's one of the many reasons I support Obamacare. But I could care less if you like Obamacare or not. Mainly I want you to have the information you need to make an honest assessment, and to allay any unfounded fears you may have about how the law will affect you. Most of the stories you hear are at best worst case scenarios that may affect a few people. Quite a few of them are outright lies.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370541438445</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370543018161-37</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Rictardo</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1370056426720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 23:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting, you don't need Obamacare to buy your own insurance, I know many business owners who insure themselves and their employees. Your statement speaks volumes it means your business makes so little money you can't even afford your own health insurance. I would strongly advise your partner keep his/her job if you can't even afford insurance.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1370543018161</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:23:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370543287013-38</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Rictardo</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1370056426720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 23:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In response to stoopit ricky "The biggest change for my business is that I will soon be able buy health insurance on the health exchange. I no longer have to rely on my wife's job."</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1370543287013</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:28:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370543597196-39</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A president, any president, simply shouldn't have that much authority and we should not have secret courts. " Too late, thanks to you idiots who put Obama in office</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1370543597196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:33:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370544164300-40</Id><Topic><Title>Why was Geithner left out</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1370112645611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What idiocy, winholder. The 157 number was correct. So what? The interpretation of it was completely irresponsible. They may not have lied about the number buy they were so negligent in their duties as journalists as to be equivalent to lying. I cannot make myself more clear. A journalist outfit that lies or irresponsibly jumps to conclusions without investigating has no credibility. If you watch Fox News you are grossly misinformed. Do you think I care what someone so grossly misinformed thinks? Do you think I care if you "lost confidence"? You never had confidence. You've been on a witchhunt from birtherism to Benghazi. You're full of it and you'll always be full of it. You people have cried wolf far to many times now.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370544164300</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370544493991-41</Id><Title>Boston Democrat governor reaction to marathon bombing</Title><Msg>He got drunk and skipped out on bar tab Massachusetts Gov. Deval Patrick says he got "quite drunk" at a restaurant the day after Boston Marathon. Patrick says he was relieved that Dzhokhar Tsarnaev was captured on April 19 because otherwise people would have been complaining about the "shelter in place" order he gave that day, locking down Boston and several suburbs. Patrick said he had no money and couldn't pay his bill.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1370544493991</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370545353855-42</Id><Topic><Title>Boston Democrat governor reaction to marathon bombing</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1370544493991</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:48:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gov. Patrick relayed how he went to a restaurant the day after the bomber was captured, not the day after the marathon. He also knew the owner of the restaurant and arranged to pay his bill the next day, which the restaurant owner said he did. You just can't help lying, can you fake ricky?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370545353855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:02:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370546008522-43</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Rictardo</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1370056426720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 23:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you not say in your post responding to me that you are paid a very handsome salary....if that is true then why does your wife work ? Sounds like your phone isn't ringing off the hook seeking your services ....consulting HAHA more like insulting .Never forget a LIAR has to have a great memory as to keep the story close to the original statement . I'm not calling you a liar rick , but I sure am leaning in that direction .</Msg><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1370546008522</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:13:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370547454610-44</Id><Topic><Title>Boston Democrat governor reaction to marathon bombing</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1370544493991</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:48:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So the wealthy democrat gov. goes to a bar and runs up a big tab getting blasted and says he can't pay expecting someone else to pick up the tab. This behavior stinks of typical democrat policy.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1370547454610</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:37:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370547509984-45</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Rictardo</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1370056426720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 23:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or it means I make rational economic decisions, fake ricky. I could buy my own health insurance but why would I? Group insurance is cheaper. Her employer covers most of the premium. The premium is tax exempt. None of these are true on the individual market today. The health exchanges provides a viable option for people like me and puts small businesses on par with big business. They are especially helpful for new businesses which may not be profitable for years. I don't know what else to tell you. Stop being so hateful and dishonest.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370547509984</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:38:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370547936958-46</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Rictardo</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1370056426720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 23:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I said I get paid, and paid well. I do. But I'm not Mitt Romney. My wife works because it is not 1950.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370547936958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:45:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370548425806-47</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spinning tRicky is the one true liberal poster child!</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370548425806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:53:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370548994224-48</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not the one who brought up Fox News. Or myself for that matter.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370548994224</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 16:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370549088683-49</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. Too late thanks to you idiots who put Bush in office. You do know what the Patriot Act is, don't you?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370549088683</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 16:04:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370549089778-50</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OOPS, nice deflection 'icky' ... but back in the day it was that dang college 'quota" system. There were too many me's enrolling, and you were enrolling as a smar-tass. They said they had enough of those too .. so you went home and changed into your "mule costume". Regardless of your lousy scholastic performance, they pushed you through and you became the first "mule" to graduate the on that "quota system"</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1370549089778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 16:04:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370552951320-51</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a result of over-reacting after 9-11 by Bush and Congress. Then, last year when it could have been dropped, Congress voted to keep it, by a wide margin. Bush? Obama? Congress? politicians in general taking away our rights.</Msg><Username>splicerwannabe</Username><Timestamp>1370552951320</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:09:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370553287239-52</Id><Topic><Title>Insider Buying</Title><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1370532828360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:33:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1370553287239</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:14:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370553718027-53</Id><Title>What does a dead .....</Title><Msg>....cat do when tossed off a roof? BOUNCE!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1370553718027</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:21:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370558591894-54</Id><Topic><Title>Insider Buying</Title><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1370532828360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:33:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry .. it's just their timely (attaboy) acquisitions from their pay packages, not purchases. At $34.99 they'll hold it a little longer this time, maybe till $39 (??) AND they'll dump it again .. it's their pattern</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1370558591894</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370559148814-55</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can you all be so stupid as to give "a thumbs down" to anyone suggesting that Bush jr. started the domestic surveillance program. THIS IS JUST TRUTH.</Msg><Username>freakedout35</Username><Timestamp>1370559148814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:52:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370559310146-56</Id><Topic><Title>Boston Democrat governor reaction to marathon bombing</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1370544493991</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:48:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'icky' .. if we can get rid of YOUR "el presidente" buy the end of the year, I'm going to a bar and get drunk. The only difference is - this poor down-troddened Conservative will find "cash" enough to buy a round for the house !!</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1370559310146</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:55:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370560368005-57</Id><Title>1//2015 call option price</Title><Msg>today stock closed at $35.81 but January 2015 $30 call last trading at $5.80 hmmmmm</Msg><Username>triantew</Username><Timestamp>1370560368005</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 19:12:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370561312699-58</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Rictardo</Title><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1370056426720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 23:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you say your (said) wife is supporting you....yet you are the voice of the internet....posting all day your drivel . You can't be married for the wife would have given you the boot a long time ago .You have no job ,admit it .Your tales of being a consultant is ludicrous , silly folly trying to sell your lies . You are nothing more than a want to be ...keep the faith baby there are a lot of fools out there that may believe you ....but count me out for I am not one of them . You are a joke !!!!</Msg><Username>ltcolhen</Username><Timestamp>1370561312699</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 19:28:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370565890872-59</Id><Topic><Title>Boston Democrat governor reaction to marathon bombing</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1370544493991</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:48:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two things: 1. No matter what Governor Patrick did, it does not excuse you from lying. You are responsible for your own actions and you are a habitual liar. 2. That is why no one trusts you to run a tab.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370565890872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:44:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370566012153-60</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Maybe there are some who just look at your name and don't read what you post." I think you've deduced the pattern.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1370566012153</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:46:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370566541455-61</Id><Title>Sell T</Title><Msg>And buy WIN. You will make money, lots of money and you'll be getting rid of this garbage.</Msg><Username>eluminatlng69</Username><Timestamp>1370566541455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:55:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370566573181-62</Id><Title>Buy WIN</Title><Msg>This co. is nothing but garbage.</Msg><Username>eluminatlng69</Username><Timestamp>1370566573181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:56:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370566612631-63</Id><Title>You're wasting your time</Title><Msg>owning this co. Sell it and buy WIN.</Msg><Username>eluminatlng69</Username><Timestamp>1370566612631</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:56:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370566647014-64</Id><Title>WIN will be a 10</Title><Msg>Bagger. T just doesn't have it.</Msg><Username>eluminatlng69</Username><Timestamp>1370566647014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370566699899-65</Id><Title>Invest in</Title><Msg>WIN and make a lot of money. I'm trying to help you people.</Msg><Username>eluminatlng69</Username><Timestamp>1370566699899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:58:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370566743588-66</Id><Title>I will</Title><Msg>Be here everyday telling you idiots how to make money. Invest in WIN.</Msg><Username>eluminatlng69</Username><Timestamp>1370566743588</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370566781526-67</Id><Title>T is for</Title><Msg>Losers. Invest in WIN.</Msg><Username>eluminatlng69</Username><Timestamp>1370566781526</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:59:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370566836175-68</Id><Title>WIN is</Title><Msg>going to make me a lot of money. You could make money too. If you weren't dumb that is.</Msg><Username>eluminatlng69</Username><Timestamp>1370566836175</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 21:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370566867741-69</Id><Title>T is</Title><Msg>For losers. Buy WIN.</Msg><Username>eluminatlng69</Username><Timestamp>1370566867741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 21:01:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370567216485-70</Id><Title>VZ and T</Title><Msg>Are both losers. Investors in both companies need to invest in WIN.</Msg><Username>eluminatlng69</Username><Timestamp>1370567216485</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 21:06:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370567280705-71</Id><Title>I will be</Title><Msg>Helping shareholders of T and VZ. I will see to it that both Invest in WIN.</Msg><Username>eluminatlng69</Username><Timestamp>1370567280705</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 21:08:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370568007864-72</Id><Title>If you</Title><Msg>Invested $1,000.00 in T 10 years ago you would have $1,010,00 today. WIN is much better.</Msg><Username>eluminatlng69</Username><Timestamp>1370568007864</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 21:20:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370568064371-73</Id><Title>I'm here</Title><Msg>Promoting WIN for one reason. I own shares of the co.</Msg><Username>eluminatlng69</Username><Timestamp>1370568064371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 21:21:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370568175174-74</Id><Title>If everyone</Title><Msg>Here buys WIN, You will make money but more importantly, I'll make money.</Msg><Username>eluminatlng69</Username><Timestamp>1370568175174</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 21:22:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370568297292-75</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you fuss when GW Bush did it after 9/11? Heck, the feds tapped into and re-routed the fiber optics in Calif. and told T to back off!</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1370568297292</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 21:24:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370569061421-76</Id><Topic><Title>US Is Secretly Collecting Records of Verizon Calls</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1370519562294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:52:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obama inherited it from the previous administration which was, um... Obama, but wait he inherited from his previous administration which was Bush, yea that's it , it's Bush's fault, yea, Bush's fault</Msg><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1370569061421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 21:37:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370570228388-77</Id><Title>When will I</Title><Msg>Learn to keep my mouth shut? I should learn to mind my own business.</Msg><Username>eluminatlng69</Username><Timestamp>1370570228388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 21:57:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>