<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367382671152-1</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Terrel Eddy, nobody cares what you think or what you think you did. Nobody. Not Marjorie. Not Robert. Nobody. Get off your wrinkled lazy rump and prune the dead shrub in the front of your ugly little mud colored hut in Gilbert AZ.</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367382671152</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 00:31:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367382937828-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Sorry pepe' .. the media was laughing because they knew he (Obama) was speaking the truth. " Jon, jon, jon...you get stupider by the day. How is it possible?</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367382937828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 00:35:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367383061951-3</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Mr. EE Hubcap...man of Peace...answer up.</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366991835062</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:57:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are an idiot and you wallow in your idiocy. Sow!</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367383061951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 00:37:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367383140088-4</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are killing T</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842470940</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:27:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have thoughts? Are you sure that they are not just gas pains?</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367383140088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 00:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367383334850-5</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiot. Idiot. Idiot. Nathan Kirkpatrick Eddy was born in 1966. Nathan currently lives in San Marcos, California. Before that, Nathan lived in Escondido, CA from 1999 to 2001. Before that, Nathan lived in Escondido, CA in 1999. Nathan Kirkpatrick Eddy is related to Bonnie Wakefield, who is 52 years old and lives in Phoenix, AZ. Nathan Kirkpatrick Eddy is also related to Terrel Eddy, who is 79 years old and lives in Gilbert, AZ.</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367383334850</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 00:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367383448434-6</Id><Topic><Title>Union entitlements are constraining ATT</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366842955734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiot. Idiot. Idiot. Anne E Anderlohr Age 42 Lakeside, CA Relatives: Patricia L Andersoncraven, Raymond Eddy, Eric John Anderlohr, Gregory D Eddy, Colin David Anderlohr, Susanna K Anderlohrpearce, Robert J Eddy, Terrell R Eddy, Emma J Eddy Previous Residences: Poway, CA | Gilbert, AZ | Pine, AZ | Black Diamond, WA | Lynnwood, WA | Escondido, CA | Cardiff By The Sea, CA | Riverside, CA</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367383448434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 00:44:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367405826744-7</Id><Topic><Title>So far, three downgrades and counting</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1367223667252</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 04:21:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, T finished the month up $0.76 even with the ex-dividend adjustment, a miss on top line and at least two downgrades. Looks like it is going to take a bit more to bring the old gal down. If she hits $32 it will be because the overall market takes a dive.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1367405826744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 06:57:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367407388268-8</Id><Topic><Title>So far, three downgrades and counting</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1367223667252</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 04:21:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Insiders are busy selling. Although this can't be generalized as a huge negative, nevertheless, it can't be a positive either.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1367407388268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 07:23:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367410648419-9</Id><Topic><Title>So far, three downgrades and counting</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1367223667252</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 04:21:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"it can't be a positive either." Not necessarily. Because of insider information trading issues, active officers have certain windows of time in which they can sell. Shares are a large part of their annual compensation. In many cases, they are selling only to diversify.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1367410648419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:17:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367414418943-10</Id><Topic><Title>So far, three downgrades and counting</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1367223667252</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 04:21:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Couldn't agree more TB. you may not post as often as you used to, but it always a pleasure to read what you have to say. You're so right to state how a disappointing report...which really wasnt all that bad...didn't tank the stock as the Trollers would lead you to believe. Armageddon came and went with a buck and a half loss. I'll take it. I also agree with you that were the market to take a big hit for whatever reason, T will follow suit along with everything else. Very few companies are immune to market sell-offs. This business has its up's &amp; down's and if investors can't take the volatility, try CD's or a bank savings account.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367414418943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 09:20:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367415711053-11</Id><Topic><Title>So far, three downgrades and counting</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1367223667252</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 04:21:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shorted at $32 and is one of those idiots that thinks he doesn't have a loss until he closes the position.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367415711053</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 09:41:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367415901037-12</Id><Title>All indexes &amp; commodities down T up fractionally...</Title><Msg>It may not hold, but showing resiliency early. Let's hear it from the Troll crowd and all you guys that ran your smack about buying VZ because that was a superior choice.. Ever hear the phrase "long term" traders? Try it, you may like it.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367415901037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 09:45:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367416648879-13</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. Oliver Wyman Consultants estimates that single adults aged 21-29 who are not added to their parent's health insurance (which those age 21-26 can be under Obamacare), who do not have health insurance through an employer, who earn 400% of the FPL (about $46,000), and who choose the best plans in the exchange, may increase by as much as 42% in some states--but you guys just can't help lying, can you? Oliver Wyman also notes that under the ACA, these 21-29 year olds can opt to purchase a catastrophic coverage plan (the plan most often chosen by young, healthy individuals)--which Wyman notes is unaffected by Obamacare, will be much cheaper than other plans on the exchange, and provides a great safety valve for those on the exchange who may experience increases in traditional plans). That's the short criticism of Kessler, who works for the Hoover Institute. Wyman's prediciton for some 21-29 year olds is widely cited by AHIP, without referencing the caveats and alternatives cited by Wyman himself. You can read Wyman's article. Just do a Google search for "Oliver Wyman" and "Contingencies" where the article appeared in January.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367416648879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 09:57:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367416824864-14</Id><Title>BRZV is the next big gainer</Title><Msg>Have you checked out the chart on BRZV. It looks prime to make a huge run to atleast double its current price.</Msg><Username>nashryan855</Username><Timestamp>1367416824864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:00:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367416929378-15</Id><Topic><Title>BRZV is the next big gainer</Title><Username>nashryan855</Username><Timestamp>1367416824864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:00:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could triple. Great tip.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367416929378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:02:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367417259998-16</Id><Topic><Title>All indexes &amp; commodities down T up fractionally...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367415901037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 09:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dave buddy; we have to admit that VZ going up 29% in the past 3.5 months is better than T's 18%. However, right now I wouldn't risk investing in VZ because it has gone up too far too fast. Longer term both VZ and T have a very nice 200 DMA even though VZ has the better 50 DMA. VZ, being a smaller company, has a better chance of growth percentage wise but the whole industry is booming.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367417259998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:07:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367417949526-17</Id><Topic><Title>BRZV is the next big gainer</Title><Username>nashryan855</Username><Timestamp>1367416824864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:00:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't look like it is worth a dime. Never has had any revenue in the 8 years in business. The only way to make money on this one is to find a bigger fool.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367417949526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367418148840-18</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hahahahahahahaha, yeah right, hahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367418148840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:22:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367418357481-19</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But, but hubcap, it wasn't a "liberal" plan, don't you know that? It was a republican idea, now used in MA thanks to Romney. Hubcap, when did the plan turn "liberal?" hahahahahaha</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367418357481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:25:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367418372021-20</Id><Topic><Title>All indexes &amp; commodities down T up fractionally...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367415901037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 09:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wilkie my friend. I wasn't looking for an analysis of which company is a better value. I know that VZ historically runs faster and possibly stronger than T. My point was the chest pounders from another board bragging about why VZ is so much better than T and that we are fools to not follow their path. I have nothing against VZ. it's Trolling krap that aggravates me. You ran off some nice comparative stats. What about PE? What about a potential mountain of debt they may assume if the VOD deal happens? You can make a case for pros and cons for either company on many fundamentals. I'm simply not interested in why someone buys whatever krap they are pumping. I really understand all your Bands, scholastics and all that stuff you study. I just get tired of seeing the Trolls, Spammers and Troublemakers infest the board with drivel. There's a spam post about some two bit company BRZV that a spammer wants us to believe will double, or whatever. They are just as offensive on this board as the idiots that want to convince us they are somehow making a better choice than us. I don't pollute their board with pro-T propaganda, but they seem to think it's open season here. I hope that clarifies my point. I wasn't making any kind of statement about whether one company is better than another. It was directed at the Trollers that can't seem to mind their own business.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367418372021</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:26:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367418605241-21</Id><Topic><Title>BRZV is the next big gainer</Title><Username>nashryan855</Username><Timestamp>1367416824864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:00:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wilkie, you actually took the time to look up this dog? C'mon, I was using the type of a response that Spammers use when they answer their own posts! I'd like to know who thumbed me down for saying it might triple. It was in jest...</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367418605241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:30:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367418662867-22</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama speaking the truth? That is a historic event. I guess it was the shock that made them laugh.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367418662867</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:31:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367420879966-23</Id><Title>I think BRZV is about to go to $1+</Title><Msg>All of the recent developments in BRZV make me think that a big move is about to happen</Msg><Username>tisaiah813</Username><Timestamp>1367420879966</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:07:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367421225269-24</Id><Title>BRZV looks ready to take off. Check it out</Title><Msg>developments I am going to start accumulating some BRZV</Msg><Username>walkerdavid943</Username><Timestamp>1367421225269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:13:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367421462318-25</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what you are saying is the WSJ article is correct. If you want a stripped down bare bones insurance policy that pays for almost nothing than perhaps you can avoid a 42% increase but you will see an increase nonetheless. These stripped down policies are probably not worth the cost since they cover almost none of the normal care you get today. Please don't ignore the CBO findings the Congressional Budget Office estimates that Obamacare will cause 3 million people to lose their insurance completely in 2014. And it expects that 6 million will have to pay the individual-mandate tax penalty in 2016, because they don't want or can’t afford coverage.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367421462318</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:17:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367421668591-26</Id><Topic><Title>I think BRZV is about to go to $1+</Title><Username>tisaiah813</Username><Timestamp>1367420879966</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:07:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tang Xu, President &amp; Director thinks that the Jackson 1 well may be another dry hole but if they keep trying they may find some oil. They have been trying for 8 years to find some oil so their luck should change soon.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367421668591</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:21:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367421946301-27</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, you don't know much about Obama. Obviously you never listen to him. A more patriotic and more American values President there could not be. Obama was born on August 4, 1961, at Kapiʻolani Maternity &amp; Gynecological Hospital (now Kapiʻolani Medical Center for Women and Children) in Honolulu, Hawaii,[2][5][6] and is the first President to have been born in Hawaii.[7] His mother, Stanley Ann Dunham, was born in Wichita, Kansas, and was of mostly English ancestry.[8] His father, Barack Obama, Sr., was a Luo from Nyang’oma Kogelo, Kenya. Obama's parents met in 1960 in a Russian class at the University of Hawaiʻi at Mānoa, where his father was a foreign student on scholarship.[9][10] The couple married in Wailuku on Maui on February 2, 1961,[11][12] and separated when Obama's mother moved with her newborn son to Seattle, Washington, in late August 1961, to attend the University of Washington for one year. In the meantime, Obama, Sr. completed his undergraduate economics degree in Hawaii in June 1962, then left to attend graduate school at Harvard University on a scholarship. Obama's parents divorced in March 1964.[13] Obama Sr. returned to Kenya in 1964 where he remarried; he visited Barack in Hawaii only once, in 1971.[14] He died in an automobile accident in 1982.[15] In 1963, Dunham met Lolo Soetoro, an Indonesian East–West Center graduate student in geography at the University of Hawaii, and the couple were married on Molokai on March 15, 1965.[16] After two one-year extensions of his J-1 visa, Lolo returned to Indonesia in 1966, followed sixteen months later by his wife and stepson in 1967, with the family initially living in a Menteng Dalam neighborhood in the Tebet subdistrict of south Jakarta, then from 1970 in a wealthier neighborhood in the Menteng subdistrict of central Jakarta.[17] From ages six to ten, Obama attended local Indonesian-language schools: St. Francis of Assisi Catholic School for two years and Besuki Public School for one and a half years</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367421946301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:25:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367422311174-28</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So do you now see how ridiculous your false ideas are? His father saw him once in 1971, since he was a baby. He lived in Indonesia only a few years, and attended a catholic school as well as public school. Just garbage from the right wing political machine you spew. There is nothing wrong with the man Obama, and your camp's constant degrading of him with lies is sickening. It comes from something else, not Obama's life, but the left over segregationist mentality.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367422311174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367422680254-29</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"From 10 to 18 he was indoctrinated with Communism under the tutorship of his father who was a highly talented Communist born in Kansas." Let's repeat that.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367422680254</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:38:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367422799535-30</Id><Title>T is the buy now, Cramer....</Title><Msg>VZ is way over priced and loaded with debt. If they buy VOD stake in wireless they will drown in debt. As you all know Cramer is a momentum buyer. He buy's stock at a high. Did you ever see him recommend a stock near its low? NO!</Msg><Username>romannorga</Username><Timestamp>1367422799535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367422861940-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some of what you posted is true but more of it is false which is typical of the BS that Obama publishes about himself. May I suggest you get the facts from a more reliable source. Get the CD "Dreams from My REAL Father". Joel Gilbert has done an exhaustive study of the events in 1960 and 61 and his story sounds much more likely and is backed by much more evidence than Obama's story.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367422861940</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367423018009-32</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats resposible for the bill are pointing their fingers at the administration, saying that the chaotic implementation of the law and its ongoing unpopularity are the fault of the president and his team. And calling the implementation a “train wreck” is kind compared to what Democrats say about the law behind closed doors. . For the overwhelming majority, the only thing they have seen is higher premiums and warnings of increased costs and potentially lost coverage to come.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367423018009</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:43:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367423214821-33</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats own Obamacare not a single republican voted for it.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367423214821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:46:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367423759053-34</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"These stripped down policies are probably not worth the cost since they cover almost none of the normal care you get today." Good point. But Republicans seemed to think they were a better alternative than a public option, so I don't know what to tell you. Many Republicans also argue that we should ALL be on these plans because health insurance should only cover catastrophe (as insurance is generally supposed to do) but we've gotten used to health insurance acting like a benefit that shields buyers from the real cost of healthcare. In other words, we expect to be able to visit the doctor whenever we want for a $15 copay regardless of the costs. Catastrophic insurance doesn't cover doctor's visits, so you would limit visits and choose lower cost providers. This is the essence of many Republican plans to deal with health care costs. "the Congressional Budget Office estimates that Obamacare will cause 3 million people to lose their insurance completely in 2014. And it expects that 6 million will have to pay the individual-mandate tax penalty in 2016, because they don't want or can’t afford coverage." Not at all. The CBO expects 3 million people will find it beneficial to move from their current insurance to the exchanges. They expect that in2016 6 million people will choose to pay the penalty rather than purchase insurance. Many of these will be from Republican states who do not choose to expand Medicaid--leaving a big hole in coverage options for the poor. So, if you have a problem with that, kick Republicans out of state office.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367423759053</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:55:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367423859666-35</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fake Ricky, if you like Putin so much, go live in Russia. See how you like it. As an American you are free to do so. I prefer to live in America where we are free.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367423859666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367423879744-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go live in Russia then.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367423879744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:57:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367424301522-37</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, ricky</Title><Username>dan_mctiernan</Username><Timestamp>1367375624607</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 22:33:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh I'm sure you'll be around.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367424301522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:05:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367424526863-38</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, ricky</Title><Username>dan_mctiernan</Username><Timestamp>1367375624607</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 22:33:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Smooth move getting out before we hit $40. In your tax bracket you would be giving most of the extra income to the IRS anyway.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367424526863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:08:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367424955128-39</Id><Title>BRZV INDICTED FOR FRAUD.</Title><Msg>CEO admits oil wells were dry and he hired paid Spammers to lure suckers to invest. Spams included implied promise of making fortunes. BRZV outlandish promises were made via public message boards on Yahoo! Finance.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367424955128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367424972636-40</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare key author calls it a train wreck and will quit</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367113843677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 21:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The AETNA CARTEL would not even insure me." Under Obamacare, the AETNA Cartel will have to insure you. They will not be able to deny you coverage because of your age or any other pre-existing condition. "YOUR RATES WILL CHANGE" Yes, they will likely go down for someone your age. Insurers will have limits on how much they can increase premiums due to age--and insurers raise premiums alot because of age. This means more of the health cost for you will be born by young people and by taxpayers through the exchange subsidies. Additionally, you may have direct access to subsidies on the exchange, depending on your income. Kaiser is one of the best and most affordable systems out there. If you are having trouble affording them or don't think their coverage is good enough, you should be very much looking forward to 2014. Hopefully then you will realize how much you've been lied to, and change your voting patterns accordingly.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367424972636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:16:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367425166916-41</Id><Title>BRZV looks ready to take off. Check it out</Title><Msg>Don’t miss out on BRZV. From my research</Msg><Username>royb927</Username><Timestamp>1367425166916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:19:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367425592551-42</Id><Topic><Title>BRZV looks ready to take off. Check it out</Title><Username>royb927</Username><Timestamp>1367425166916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:19:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I checked it out and it looks like it is over priced at 5 cents. 8 years and still no revenue. How many dry holes have they drilled?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367425592551</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367425663169-43</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Catastrophic insurance doesn't cover doctor's visits, so you would limit visits and choose lower cost providers." Great drive young families with young children who require frequent dr. visits to a catastrophic plan that pays for nothing. I hope young families remember to good old days before they were forced to Obamacare during in future elections. "The CBO expects 3 million people will find it beneficial to move from their current insurance to the exchanges" BS How can that be? the exchange would be insuruance coverage the CBO is saying 3 million will loose coverage under Obamacare.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367425663169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367425758367-44</Id><Topic><Title>BRZV INDICTED FOR FRAUD.</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367424955128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:15:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope they catch the paid spammers and they pay a hefty fine.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367425758367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:29:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367426599852-45</Id><Topic><Title>BRZV INDICTED FOR FRAUD.</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367424955128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:15:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then draw and quarter them.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426599852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:43:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367426944789-46</Id><Title>Meanwhile, T is quietly sneaking up on 38...</Title><Msg>Indexes still red and last weeks losses almost erased.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367427539559-47</Id><Topic><Title>BRZV INDICTED FOR FRAUD.</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367424955128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:15:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good time for the company to shift from oil exploration to the beauty products industry. Facial and Full Body deep-cleaning mud treatments. I like your thinking. But I pass on your hubcap offer. The T recovery is pretty surprising. I thought it would languish around the low 36 range for a while. 38 is almost on the table again. Wonder how Wilkie's doing with his option thing.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367427539559</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367427924698-48</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile, T is quietly sneaking up on 38...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's right Zon. Both companies operate pretty efficiently as you know by being a stockholder. You like VZ? Fine. Post away to your hearts content on your partisan board. But don't come here woofing about how much better they are than T. Today's action is a real positive in light of last weeks report. I hope both T and VZ keep rising. It is in our best interests.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367427924698</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:05:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367428494732-49</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile, T is quietly sneaking up on 38...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The one minute chart shows that institutional buying is what is pushing the price up. Look at all the 40K, 50K, and 60K minutes. That ain't us little guys. http://finance.yahoo.com/echarts?s=t#symbol=t;range=1d;compare=;indicator=dividend+sma%2850,200%29+bollinger+volume+stochasticslow;charttype=candlestick;crosshair=on;ohlcvalues=1;logscale=off;source=undefined;</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367428494732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:14:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367428901356-50</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile, T is quietly sneaking up on 38...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wilkie. I'm suing you for plagiarism. Be prepared to be served by the Marshal Service. I made that statement yesterday about the trading volume. Only difference, the trades were in the 20-30K range per block. You need to stick to Bollinger and stochastic's and keeping us aware of your latest options games with the resultant ADP.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367428901356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:21:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367428994648-51</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile, T is quietly sneaking up on 38...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is still about T &amp; VZ. Compare the VZ minute chart today with the T minute chart today and it is obvious that institutions are switching from VZ to T. The T chart is in my previous post. Here is the VZ chart. http://finance.yahoo.com/echarts?s=VZ#symbol=vz;range=1d;compare=;indicator=dividend+sma%2850,200%29+bollinger+volume+stochasticslow;charttype=candlestick;crosshair=on;ohlcvalues=1;logscale=off;source=undefined;</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367428994648</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367429007603-52</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But most of the pundits and many Democrats are upset because the exchanges are ready, they will not be ready for a few more years but the law is taking effect anyway??????</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1367429007603</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:23:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367429297636-53</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Cheech and Chong skit is personified in Obama and Biden.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1367429297636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:28:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367429512892-54</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Mr. EE Hubcap...man of Peace...answer up.</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366991835062</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:57:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of Obama phones, while Obama cancelled the WH tours, all the military participation in air shows and put air controllers on leave to save money, did they never think of cutting off some of the free phone service to welfare folks? Nah, that would have been too easy and would have cost him votes. His way he keeps all the Christmas present voters on his side and uses a plan he agreed to and said would never happened and he refused to change to his political advantage. And all you liberals think he is a fair guy! Amazing!</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1367429512892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:31:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367430058829-55</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Mr. EE Hubcap...man of Peace...answer up.</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366991835062</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:57:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Disclaimer here my golfing friend. Please do not associate me...the original poster...with any phone other than the one's I buy and pay for. The numbskull that responded to me has the notion i have a free phone. Nothing could be further from the truth.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367430058829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:40:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367431089277-56</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are upset because they are ready, or because they will not be ready? Most states are operating their own exchanges. The rest (17) will default to the Federal exchange. Setting up the Federal Exchange will take money-- money which the Republican house has withheld. But as I noted in a previous post Republican governors are getting very, very nervous about this. They are worried about how they will look compared to states that have well functioning systems. So Republicans have been loosening the purse strings on this. It is a tight timeline in many cases, but I am confident the exchanges will be ready to go.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367431089277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367431275296-57</Id><Topic><Title>BRZV INDICTED FOR FRAUD.</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367424955128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:15:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Zon, you came up with the mud selling, not me. I give you props for BZRZ going from hydrocarbons to highly purified organic mud. He'll, that's a green industry, much to the likings of those invested in green tech. Now I got to take you to task. First off, I really like Wilkie. Even though he denies it, he is a shorter. But that's ok. He does it with style &amp; charisma and doesn't offend anyone. Even me who doesn't like the shorting community. Continuing. Wilkie sez he lost something like 320K before he 'figured out the market'. What was the result? His newly found technique has shrunk from over 300 a day profit to 35. That is not a good sign. So why would you want to be a student of The Wilkes School of Investing by 'studying &amp; learning by reading his posts?' I don't get that Zon. I bet if Mrs. Wilkie knew about his 'ouija board' option and investing methods financed by the rapidly declining family fortune, she'd become the former Mrs. Wilkes. If I pulled that on my wife, I'd hear about it every second of the day and be banned from ever accessing our bank account. Like I said, I like the guy. In fact, I'd have a beer with him unlike hubcap. But to want to learn his techniques...stick with the tried and true my friend. No disrespect intended to Wilkie. Just a complete difference of opinion regarding how to invest and not lose 1/3rd of a million bucks in a lifetime.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367431275296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:01:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367431760419-58</Id><Title>Officer of At&amp;T - John Stankey</Title><Msg>Hmmm, his last two trades speak volumes, don't they?</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1367431760419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:09:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367431761468-59</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Great drive young families with young children" No, you have that backwards. What is actually occurring is that most of these families will now be able to afford more comprehensive coverage if they want it. Right now, people who don't have employer-sponsored insurance get catastrophic coverage if they can afford coverage at all. After the ACA these people will have expanded access to subsidized comprehensive insurance or Medicaid. "How can that be?" Because that's how the law works. The CBO estimates that 3 million people will lose employer coverage because the coverage on the exchange will be better and cheaper. These will likely be low wage workers who currently only get offered catastrophic coverage from their employers, but will have access to subsidized comprehensive coverage on the exchange.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367431761468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:09:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367432051800-60</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, they do. But Democrats implemented Romneycare. And Romney implemented the Republican-proposed alternative to Hilarycare. Republicans are opposing a policy they drew up solely because it is "owned" by Democrats. And I think that is a very sad thing, a missed opportunity to do good for the American people on a bipartisan basis.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367432051800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:14:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367432146092-61</Id><Topic><Title>Officer of At&amp;T - John Stankey</Title><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1367431760419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:09:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BFD what's the point. The guy gave away his stock to investors that snapped it up at a bargain. We're you his advisor? You get all juiced up over stuff likethis don't you? Go write a home owners policy Troll.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367432146092</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:15:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367432246384-62</Id><Topic><Title>Officer of At&amp;T - John Stankey</Title><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1367431760419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:09:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think it's all too funny that people just realized, today, that the economies of the world are slowing, too funny!</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1367432246384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:17:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367432541067-63</Id><Topic><Title>Officer of At&amp;T - John Stankey</Title><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1367431760419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:09:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stop generalizing about what do or don't know. World economy news is not something new. Stick to peddling insurance if that's really your business. Anybody that has a policy with this Troll, cancel and buy it from someone else.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367432541067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:22:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367432859240-64</Id><Topic><Title>All indexes &amp; commodities down T up fractionally...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367415901037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 09:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Overall market has sunk further and T is one of about a dozen above water. That is impressive. The rebound continues stronger than ever. Maybe we'll find out why soon.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367432859240</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:27:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367433397247-65</Id><Topic><Title>Pink Sheets Penny Stock Runners Alert</Title><Username>green_roland</Username><Timestamp>1367432232648</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:17:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I heard somtin good about this one</Msg><Username>roe_edward</Username><Timestamp>1367433397247</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:36:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367433756571-66</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to Wikipedia, Cheech &amp; Chong were hippie stoners who went on adventures. Just like Scooby-Doo. I have to say, there's a theme to you boomers. A definite theme. Unfortunately it's not the '60's anymore. No more riding around in VW buses getting high and living off "the man". Time to get down to business and pay for your stuff.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367433756571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:42:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367434386771-67</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What is actually occurring is that most of these families will now be able to afford more comprehensive coverage if they want it." More Obama propaganda the CBO tells a different story "the coverage on the exchange will be better and cheaper" Very funny it will be just the opposite as cited by the CBO. what you don't seem to understand is CBO is not saying you will replace your current coverage with exchange coverage, that will cost more and offer less coverage than what you get today, they are saying this "Obamacare will cause 3 million people to lose their insurance completely in 2014." Please again note the CBO's use of the word completely. Try to think about it this way, if you are capable of doing so, under today's plan the employer generally pays a portion of your premium once the employer drops healthcare coverage because they can no longer afford to offer it to employees under Obamacare you will pay the cost of the entire premium if you want health insurance 3 million people will not be able to afford it and therefore go without coverage.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367434386771</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:53:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367434605329-68</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile, T is quietly sneaking up on 38...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Settle down Zon. "You like VZ?" Was meant for the VZ big mouths that came to the T board woofing about VZ. I wrote it in second person...it was not directed at you ok? Re-read it again. It was intended for the VZ intruders on the T board and their obnoxious comments. Maybe I didn't compose it with clarity. I know you own both companies and Frontier as well. The mud stock was pure messing with the Spammers. No need to respond to my getting a life. My comment could be taken the wrong way as you did. Sorry for any misunderstanding.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367434605329</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367435825533-69</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"More Obama propaganda the CBO tells a different story " Winholder will tell you the CBO IS Obama propaganda. Of course, he does so when I cite actual CBO figures. "Obamacare will cause 3 million people to lose their insurance completely in 2014" The CBO never said anything of the sort because it is not true. Please reference the CBO Publication Number and page number of the report where you think the CBO said this. You are full of sh**, fake ricky. There will be a reckoning in the voter booth in 2014.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367435825533</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:17:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367436316277-70</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah, you just dated yourself. You're just some young kid who got a D average in the Obama propaganda school of blogging. I wondered why it took so long for your responses. You have to take our comments, send it off to your sources to get an answer and then post it. You are not that smart! And pay for your own stuff!</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367436316277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:25:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367437476636-71</Id><Title>Faster and Expanded Internet Connections Build Stronger Network Throughout North Carolina</Title><Msg>The technical indicator at helpisland website shows a buy now.</Msg><Username>hradverger</Username><Timestamp>1367437476636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:44:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367437482080-72</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, I'm not young. You're just old. Really, really old.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367437482080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367438015209-73</Id><Title>Splitsville?</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/video/worse-normal-correction-ahead-pro-221400279.html</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1367438015209</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367438038144-74</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Please reference the CBO Publication" Here you are cbo.gov/sites/default/files/cbofiles/attachments/43900_ACAInsuranceCoverageEffects.pdf</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367438038144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367438106772-75</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile, T is quietly sneaking up on 38...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One minute charts? Wow, sorry, but that ain't the big picture!</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1367438106772</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367438419056-76</Id><Topic><Title>Officer of At&amp;T - John Stankey</Title><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1367431760419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:09:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, shoot, someone just cancelled! My yearly commision's total, just fell from $376,153.76, down to $376,149.61, thanks a lot Dave, LOL!!!</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1367438419056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367438716006-77</Id><Title>All I know is that if...</Title><Msg>...Etrade puts my DRIP through right near the hi of the day again ($37.97) - that will be the last straw. I'll be looking for a new on-line broker. They say there's nothing they can do about it but it's always near the hi. I'm suspicious. I know others that get in much lower with different brokers. It may not seem like a big deal but over time it is.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1367438716006</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:05:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367438846414-78</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile, T is quietly sneaking up on 38...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is the big picture when you are talking about institutional buying. That is where it shows up. Go to the URL in my post and you will see what I am talking about because you obviously don't know what you are talking about.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367438846414</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:07:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367440363851-79</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your quote is not in there. Did you think I wouldn't check? In fact, the document points out that there will be 14 million more people with insurance in 2014 and 26 million more people with insurance in 2016 than would have it otherwise, with slight changes in employer coverage more than offset by enrollment in exchanges and expanded Medicaid. That is what the CBO says, and what every other serious health policy analyst I have dealt with says.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367440363851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367440832874-80</Id><Topic><Title>Today's Volume</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367342969178</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:29:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know what to think. This morning it was very clear that Institutions where switching from VZ to T. However at 3 PM institutional trading went way up and T joined VZ in a one hour plunge. Institutional trading is largely computer controlled and it is almost like the computers have gone to day trading. Volume today was below average for T but way above average for VZ. T closed up a dime from yesterday and VZ was down $1.51. I started the week with 10 weekly 38 calls and, when T climbed today, I bought 30 more contracts thinking it would continue up. Now they are only worth a nickel and I paid a dime. I can only hope that T climbs above $38 tomorrow.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367440832874</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367441283556-81</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile, T is quietly sneaking up on 38...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sue away. You were looking at level II trading and I was looking at the one minute chart. I think that will be an adequate defense. What did you think of that wild last hour today? I'm glad I was out to lunch or I would have made some stupid move. Now I am ready for a big run up tomorrow. (I hope)</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367441283556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:48:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367441889016-82</Id><Topic><Title>Officer of At&amp;T - John Stankey</Title><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1367431760419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:09:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You appear to be rather new to stock trading. Keep posting and, as you can see, there are lots of us here ready to criticize what ever you post. You will be amazed at how much you can learn from criticism if you maintain the right attitude.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367441889016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367442290973-83</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile, T is quietly sneaking up on 38...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“I'm glad I was out to lunch…” – wilkes Truer words were never spoken.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367442290973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367443100678-84</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not! It was a typo but of course you knew that and you knew the correct answer, even liberals that listen only to the lame stream media couldn't have missed that.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1367443100678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:18:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367443180485-85</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should be ashamed that this is the best response you could muster.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1367443180485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:19:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367443338956-86</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: "I AM NOT the Strapping Young Muslim Socialist I Use to Be!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367262630171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 15:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's because fewer can afford the gas tor cruise around any longer. The man is now a socialist that many of those in the 60's fought to stop. Scooby-Doo now lives in the White House. Which decade would you prefer?</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1367443338956</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:22:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367444008401-87</Id><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Msg>...“BURKESVILLE, Ky. (AP) — A 5-year-old boy accidentally shot his 2-year-old sister to death in rural southern Kentucky with a rifle he had received as a gift last year, authorities said. The children's mother was home at the time of the shooting Tuesday afternoon but had stepped out to the front porch for a few minutes and ‘she heard the gun go off’…the girl died of a single gunshot wound to the chest area. The company that made the gun, Milton, Pa.-based Keystone Sporting Arms, produced 60,000 Crickett and Chipmunk rifles in 2008, according to its website. It also makes guns for adults, but most of its products are geared toward children….Keystone opened in 1996 with just four employees, producing 4,000 rifles that year. It now employs about 70 people... The smaller guns come in all sorts of colors, including blue and pink…The company's slogan is ‘My First Rifle’…” end So, if 4 employees made 4000 rifles a year, one would suppose that 70 employees could make 70,000 little blue and pink .22 caliber weapons named chipmunk for five year olds. I wonder if the two year old sister had one? Maybe he had Chipmunk and she had Crickett? Only in America.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367444593502-88</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure what number you are looking at. In August 2012—about six months ago—it estimated that 4 million people would lose ESI. It now estimates that 7 million Americans will lose ESI due to Obamacare. Also, employers are now anticipated to pay $13 billion more in penalties compared to the August 2012 baseline, totaling $130 billion over 10 years.</Msg><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367444593502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367445189278-89</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: Prepare for Obamacare Shock</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367360269152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said that right. As soon as they know Obama is for it, the republicans don't vote for it, even their own ideas. It's in the record, and very sad, as you correctly state. In any case the nut jobs small minority opinions don't matter, ObamaCare is law and it is good for the American People.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367445189278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:53:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367447154708-90</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Mr. EE Hubcap...man of Peace...answer up.</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1366991835062</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:57:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now you are boreing me BOY. Too funny. Are your Obama car stickers starting to peel off yet? Use goo-be-gone. My F-250 4wd tag says "Don't Tread On Me".</Msg><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1367447154708</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:25:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367447623765-91</Id><Title>New customer</Title><Msg>Me, and I 'm paying through the nose for unlimited. I still need TV and security. $$$$$ A pull back would be fine with me because I'll get more reinvested shared. This company isn't going to lose money.</Msg><Username>neeljak</Username><Timestamp>1367447623765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:33:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367447807558-92</Id><Topic><Title>5 year old shoots 2 year old sister...</Title><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367444008401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a truly sad and regrettable story. It is sad and regrettable on so many levels that it leaves a compassionate person with both sorrow and dread: o It is sad that a two year old little girl will never know her loving family or the potential of her life o It is sad that her mother will spend the rest of her life in grief and questioning her life choices (i.e., If only I had locked the gun in the gun safe, If only I had not gone out on the porch, If only I had not got the gun for my son, So many if I had not thoughts that they build on themselves) o It is sad that a 5 year-old little boy will spend the rest of his life with the death of his little sister on his hands. There will be so many guilty days and nights that will scar this child and make his life and dreams a mere shadow of what they could have been I admit that it is hard to find any good that could come out of this story, but it does place a big spotlight on the need for gun safety education for both parents and children. Thankfully this has been the primary mission of the NRA over the years, and it makes a case for parents and children enrolling in these classes as soon as possible. I pray for these folks, and hope for the grace of God to comfort them. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1367447807558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:36:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367447919770-93</Id><Topic><Title>Officer of At&amp;T - John Stankey</Title><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1367431760419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:09:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's talk again in 8 weeks, so we can discuss what's "new" at that time, good luck with your long position!</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1367447919770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:38:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367448239605-94</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile, T is quietly sneaking up on 38...</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367426944789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what are u taking about losses erased !!!??? we were at 39 plus went to 36 .50 now 37.55 so still down 1. 5 points to get even up 1 so how are the losses erased ....not even half way back .....hate just plan yaking !!</Msg><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1367448239605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:43:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367449173947-95</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare key author calls it a train wreck and will quit</Title><Username>ricky1820l</Username><Timestamp>1367113843677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 21:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, that is not true. Don't pull it out from where the sun don't shine, Aetna is the biggest monopoly Cartel in the industry, until they are nuked, hopefully soon, if you are over 60 with 10 mg blood pressure meds, they will not even quote you, so stick that where you deserve it ! I have the facts. You have BS.</Msg><Username>cantgthrtondirt</Username><Timestamp>1367449173947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:59:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367450074906-96</Id><Topic><Title>All I know is that if...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1367438716006</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:05:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TDAmeritrade frequently amazes me by getting me options at less than what I bid or selling at more than my ask. I was with E trade until about five years ago when they tied up a stock on some technicality and had no solution for me. I switched the whole account to TDAmeritrade and was hoping they would be easier to deal with. To my amazement, I didn't have to deal with anyone. They fixed the problem without even being asked. If you wnat you can e-mail me at and I will have TDAmeritrade send you some information.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367450074906</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 19:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367457676004-97</Id><Topic><Title>Mass Gov Patrick Seals Records</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1367022719383</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 20:31:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seriously, Fox 45 here in Baltimore has a segement where this poor drug addicted woman have a purse full of Bami phones. This is the most fraudulent entitlement ever. As one Congressman said, If we can't stop this, we are doomed. This should be easy.</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1367457676004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 21:21:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367458387362-98</Id><Title>Rubio Can't be that stupid</Title><Msg>He's selling all of us down the river. Call your Rep ASAP. Not only are we witnessing the Republican Party commit suicide. We are also witnessing the total destruction of our economy. We have 90 MILLION UNEMPLOYED PEOPLE. Small businesses, are closing in record levels due to Obami care. There are no jobs. We have to get rid of these 40 MILLION con men. This bill gives them all of hard earned Social Security benefits, after only 5 years!! TELL RUBIO TO READ THE BILL!</Msg><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1367458387362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 21:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367460098775-99</Id><Title>DIST 9 and T finally</Title><Msg>Get it done. Offers soon?</Msg><Username>bob.beachin</Username><Timestamp>1367460098775</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 22:01:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367464392810-100</Id><Topic><Title>Mass Gov Patrick Seals Records</Title><Username>robfisk</Username><Timestamp>1367022719383</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 20:31:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you never tire of being a big mouthed fool with a shriveled cocktail onion for a willy? YapYapYap...you're a pansy little purse dog.</Msg><Username>wledigmacsen</Username><Timestamp>1367464392810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 23:13:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367464469558-101</Id><Topic><Title>Today's Volume</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367342969178</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:29:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW!! D looks very interesting but I sure wouldn't short it. I will put it on my watch list and buy some puts when it stops going up every day. Thanks for the tip.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367464469558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 23:14:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>