<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369730523121-1</Id><Topic><Title>My Skittles Run !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1369504800335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 14:00:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oer ick`s post: "I really wonder what's behind you and your crowd supporting Zimmer." It's pure racism. You've seen it here and you've seen how they've tried to portray Martin in the conservative press. Huh? They`re both colored.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369730523121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 04:42:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369733717231-2</Id><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Msg>Why do the perpetrators of multiculturalism pick only White countries to eliminate the majority indigenous population and replace it with a multi-racial multicultural society. For example, why isn`t Japan being flooded with tens of millions of Africans and Latinos or China flooded with tens of millions of Indians, Africans and Latinos, or India invaded by tens of millions of Africans, Latinos and Japanese? Why isn`t there an international campaign to racially mix and destroy the cultures of ALL NATIONS, not just White nations? Is it because most non-White races and nations would never allow their races and nations to be destroyed and overrun by people of other races and cultures? Or is it because the perpetrators of multiculturalism have an agenda of genocide against Whites? Using multiculturalism and multi-racial societies as tools, along with other tools, to eliminate and genocide Whties in their own countries? That is what I believe is happening. Why are we Whites allowing our race, cultures and nations to be destroyed and eliminated and seized away from us? At some point in the not so distant future, when we have become a small enough minority, we will have no say so or control, whatsoever, over our lives, cultures or destiny. There are signs that White men are waking up though. There have been huge angry protesst in England by members and supporters of the EDL since the British soldier was chopped to death in the street, many demanding that the invaders go home. I believe the English are a minority in London now. That is sickening. And in a couple of decades the English may be a minority in all of England. That is a CRIME. A GENOCIDE.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369738176549-3</Id><Title>The outlook</Title><Msg>The high yield corporate bonds yield stands at 6.00%, i.e. HYG. Based on that number, the AT&amp;T stock offers a tremendous value at yields of 5.00% with credit ratings far above the corporate high yields level. Working the numbers based on yield alone, never mind the fact that the company has increased the dividends for the last 25 to 30 years and continue to do so, the FV of the stock price is in the $40.00 to 45.00 range.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1369738176549</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369738500913-4</Id><Topic><Title>My Skittles Run !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1369504800335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 14:00:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“I used to park my car after work north of downtown San Diego out of the metered and timed parking areas after work and walk several blocks to a movie in town.” – lewcor You park you car north of the city and walk back into the city to avoid paying a parking meter?????? Wow, that’s impressive information to provide to other like-minded knowledgeable investors. Thanks for sharing that, lew! When you and lavendar went to the Drive-In together, did you hide in the trunk?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1369738500913</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:55:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369742006940-5</Id><Topic><Title>NEW TOPIC..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1369712404287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 23:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...and what, under any proposed gun control law, would have prevented this tragedy?</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1369742006940</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 07:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369742249461-6</Id><Topic><Title>In memory of FDR</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369676204178</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" More lies from the Tea Brains" Beware ricky, there is a "Tea Brain" behind every bush.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1369742249461</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 07:57:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369743199434-7</Id><Topic><Title>NEW TOPIC..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1369712404287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 23:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well 'icky/echo' .. as deranged as you are .. could have done the chivalrous thing and dawned your "super hero costume" and taken those bullets for them. If your 'pretend' super hero costume didn't work .. well, you'd have done us all a favor -</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1369743199434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:13:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369747058123-8</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"For example, why isn`t Japan being flooded with tens of millions of Africans and Latinos or China flooded with tens of millions of Indians, Africans and Latinos, or India invaded by tens of millions of Africans, Latinos and Japanese?" Not for the reason you state. Mostly it is because these countries control their borders and their immigration and if you violate their laws, they jail you and/or deport you.</Msg><Username>ssdependent</Username><Timestamp>1369747058123</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:17:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369747430692-9</Id><Topic><Title>IF I Had A Son !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1369403088396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:44:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How on earth is a kid walking home from the store with a bag of skittles and talking on his cell phone a "suspected criminal"? Because he did so while black? No because he was walking around in the rain, at night, in a neighborhood that had suffered a series of home break in crimes. It had nothing to do with his race, it was his actions and time and place. Being a suspect because of time, place and situation does not make you guilty or innocent, just a suspect. Making those assumptions is no more or less racist than the ones your making about Zimmerman's guilt.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1369747430692</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:23:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369747565367-10</Id><Topic><Title>NEW TOPIC..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1369712404287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 23:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not to worry, in Colorado, they are working hard to start recall campaigns for those politicians that voted for gun control in that state.</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1369747565367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:26:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369748118076-11</Id><Topic><Title>NEW TOPIC..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1369712404287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 23:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing, but the idea that guns save lives is clearly misguided. They may do so in rare instances but guns that are used on people are overwhelming used to shoot or kill people (intentionally or accidentally) who don't deserve to be shot or killed. That especially includes weapons capable of killing 26 people in two minutes.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369748118076</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:35:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369748912213-12</Id><Topic><Title>NEW TOPIC..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1369712404287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 23:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes 'pinhigh' .. I read that this a.m. .. and it's good that it's picking up steam. AND poor little 'icky' is too stupid to realize that one can defend themselves from these crack-pots &amp; criminals .. by arming themselves. However if 'icky' ever needs defending himself from any of these crack-pots or crininals, he can call 'el presidente' and then wait for his assistance.</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1369748912213</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:48:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369749041523-13</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That sounds like a really good idea. Why don't we do that?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369749041523</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:50:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369749424847-14</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. His very perception of reality is wrong. China, for instance, has a large stream of illegal immigration. Search for "China's Immigration Problem" by Gaddy Epstein in Forbes online, dated 7/1/2010. Immigrants go to where the work is. Any other motivation ascribed to overall migrant flows is simply wrong. Japan has been stringent about immigration for centuries, but even there they are beginning to look at reform. As the population there ages they are facing labor shortages and a shortage of workers to pay pensions and maintain tax revenues &amp; infrastructure. It should go without saying that anything Lavendar says is complete BS. Even if he wanted to be honest his viewpoint is so deranged it would not let him.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369749424847</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:57:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369749746556-15</Id><Topic><Title>NEW TOPIC..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1369712404287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 23:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can arm yourself with a shotgun or a handgun, fake echo. You are just the type of deranged nut who should not have any firepower whatsoever.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369749746556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369749968338-16</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lanza Mcveigh, etc etc etc etc, where is your fear of white people? There seems to be a lot more to fear if you start counting color of skin as a measure, from white people. Don't see you pointing them out. If you want to move from a free country, a country made from immigrants, why don't you do that? When did your ancestors immigrate to America? Who was here before them? No doubt they were told to go back to where they came from. When will you come to realize it is the human race, and white people are not any better? Are you old so you will die soon and you can take all that with you to Hell?</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1369749968338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:06:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369750414500-17</Id><Topic><Title>OT-National Review Article</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369429903158</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 17:11:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What? No one wants to comment on some actual (public) honesty from a Republican? Here's an excerpt: "So imagine 2016 in the unlikely but not completely impossible event that a budget surplus does materialize. Republican elevation of the deficit issue will allow the Obama administration and its Democratic allies to declare “mission accomplished,” all without taking the blame for entitlement reform. The House-passed budget that promised a balanced budget within the ten-year budget window by making unrealistically deep cuts in Medicaid and domestic discretionary spending will continue to be hung around the necks of congressional Republicans. One hopes that one or several of the GOP presidential candidates will devise a more compelling economic message and reform agenda. But this will have to be done in a near-vacuum, as conservative lawmakers have been emphasizing deficit reduction above almost everything else." In other words, Obama's agenda worked and the Republican agenda has been "oppose Obama" no matter what he does or what it takes, including completely unrealistic policy proposals. The success of the Obama presidency has left Republicans with no meaningful policy agenda.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369750414500</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369750568953-18</Id><Topic><Title>In memory of FDR</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369676204178</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thankfully Tea Brains are pretty rare. Pesky little cretins, for sure, but rare.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369750568953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369750990004-19</Id><Topic><Title>IF I Had A Son !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1369403088396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:44:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not a jury so your idea that Zimmerman shouldn't go to trial and Martin deserved to die is correct? Just like a Tea Brain. What hypocrisy.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369750990004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:23:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369751569801-20</Id><Topic><Title>NEW TOPIC..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1369712404287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 23:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jon, it's "donned", "donned your super hero costume." "Dawned" has a different meaning. For example, it just "dawned" on me what a shuddering (not "shuttering"...) coward jon is, afraid of his own shadow. Maybe a basic test of reading comprehension and spelling should be part of getting a license for a gun. You wouldn't be able to get a license for a squirt gun, would you?</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1369751569801</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:32:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369751718020-21</Id><Topic><Title>My Skittles Run !!</Title><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1369504800335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 14:00:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you mean "maybe"?</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1369751718020</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:35:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369751798904-22</Id><Title>Never thought this would hold $37....</Title><Msg>Is it being dragged up or legit? I think this will be at $32-$33 very soon.</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369751798904</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369751829729-23</Id><Topic><Title>OT-National Review Article</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369429903158</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 17:11:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah I read it but didn't think it was remarkable. A budget surplus when the president is doing everything possible to destroy our economy is so fanciful that interplanetary travel on a daily schedule by 2016 is more likely. You mention that the writer is a Republican. It might be more accurate to say he is a RINO. It is less relevant that he is Republican than that he is a spaced out Muslim who has left his Muslim roots and thinks of himself as a visitor from another planet.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369751829729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:37:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369751870723-24</Id><Title>sold shares</Title><Msg>i bought 500 shares at 37.00 after the earnings disappointment. does not appear t is going up with the market at this point in time. sold those 500 shares today at 37.07. will wait to see if price drops on market pull-back. if that ever happens?</Msg><Username>vger44</Username><Timestamp>1369751870723</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:37:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369752008889-25</Id><Topic><Title>In memory of FDR</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369676204178</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sitting around the dusty dump in Hesperia listening to Huckabee. God, I want your life!!!</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1369752008889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:40:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369752053801-26</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because it would cost a lot and hurt the economy while providing no discernible benefit. Forget the human implications of going Gestapo on over 10 million people, who do you think is going to pay for this? And your fence? You? Grover Norquist? Mitt Romney? The Koch Brothers? So far they've proven unwilling to pay for the stuff we have. Obama has taken the limited resources he has to handle illegal immigrants and focused on deporting criminals--and has deported more illegal immigrants than all of his predecessors. If you want to do more you will simply have to find a way to pay for it.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369752053801</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:40:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369752330740-27</Id><Topic><Title>OT-National Review Article</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369429903158</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 17:11:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blah, blah, blah...why don't you go bother your wife for a little while? Don't you have grandchildren who will sit rapt at your knee hanging on every word of your empty-headed, demented ramblings? Why are we so blessed with your company, when your family must just be dying for more of your "quality" conversation. No? They avoid you? Like the plague? Really? I wonder why that might be...hmmmmmm....</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1369752330740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:45:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369752924710-28</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finally something we wholeheartedly agree on. "It should go without saying that anything Lavendar says is complete BS. Even if he wanted to be honest his viewpoint is so deranged it would not let him." I feel sorry for him. He probably doesn't even eat Peanut Butter because it was invented by one of the greatest horticulturists of all time, but he was black. George Washington Carver, in my opinion, was as great as the man he was named after and I don't care what color his skin was, he was a man we all (even lavendarsen) should respect highly.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369752924710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:55:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369753590197-29</Id><Title>This is a tough stock to own..</Title><Msg>Never seems to go up much no matter how much the markets are up! Giving back all of todays gains.</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369753590197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:06:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369753618377-30</Id><Topic><Title>OT-National Review Article</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369429903158</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 17:11:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is not so much the fact that the writer is a Republican that interests me, it is the fact that he is a writer for the National Review. Unlike you I don't just swallow any old bu**sh**. Your response is unfortunately all too predictable. Salam is painfully honest in this post and deals with actual reality. You--and most of the Republican base--are intent on keeping your heads in the sand. Obama must be a deranged socialist intent on destroying America. You excoriate anyone who dares to challenge your delusions. Throw in a healthy dose of racism and xenophobia and you have yourself a prototypical Tea Brain. It's a shame. As long as the opposition party is in such a state it will be difficult for our democracy to function.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369753618377</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:06:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369753701022-31</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm glad you mentioned a way to pay for it. My solution: Don't deport illegals; put them to work building a concrete block wall on our Southern border. After seven years hard labor they could apply for citizenship. I think the flow of illegals would cease over night if we were to enforce such a law. My great, great, great, grandfather came to Connecticut from France as an indentured servant with a seven year contract. It sounds like a very good plan that should be reinstated.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369753701022</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:08:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369753985786-32</Id><Topic><Title>sold shares</Title><Username>vger44</Username><Timestamp>1369751870723</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:37:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great move - small proit is better than a loss. This stock never seems to go up anymore - many better choices out there.</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369753985786</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:13:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369754001485-33</Id><Topic><Title>sold shares</Title><Username>vger44</Username><Timestamp>1369751870723</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:37:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"profit"</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369754001485</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369754543223-34</Id><Topic><Title>OT-National Review Article</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369429903158</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 17:11:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You view a surplus by 2016 to be "actual reality". WOW!! you have swallowed the Obama line hook, line, and sinker. I am glad that you are beginning to get what I have been posting. "Obama must be a deranged socialist intent on destroying America." I couldn't have said it any better. I hope the rest of the country wakes up to it before it is too late.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369754543223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369754951137-35</Id><Topic><Title>In memory of FDR</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369676204178</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Thankfully Tea Brains are pretty rare. Pesky little cretins, for sure, but rare" I'll save this one for future reference.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1369754951137</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:29:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369755226257-36</Id><Topic><Title>NEW TOPIC..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..GUNS (!!)..</Title><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1369712404287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 23:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nothing" Probably true because the story didn't give enough detail.</Msg><Username>t.bfine</Username><Timestamp>1369755226257</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:33:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369755392003-37</Id><Topic><Title>OT-National Review Article</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369429903158</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 17:11:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No wilkes. I view the outside possibility of a surplus as actual reality. I view a growing economy, rising revenues and reduced government spending resulting in a rapidly shrinking deficit as actual reality as well. Do you know why I view those things as reality? Because I keep my eyes open and I'm not insane. "You are beginning to get what I have been posting." Yeah, and as myself and Salam have pointed out it is your only message and easily demonstrated to be false. Well, I'll let Salam keep pi**ing in the wind with his attempt to bring some sort of sanity to the GOP. I'm content to stomp you all.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369755392003</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:36:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369755399437-38</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Immigrants go to where the work is." What a a racist you are. Are you saying traditionally white nations are more productive and provide a better life than non-white nations.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1369755399437</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:36:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369755851907-39</Id><Title>LOAD THE TRUCK FOR 45 TARGET!!</Title><Msg>THE BEST MA BELL!!</Msg><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1369755851907</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:44:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369756155148-40</Id><Topic><Title>OT-National Review Article</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369429903158</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 17:11:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"easily demonstrated to be false." On the contrary, Obama's "budget" for 2013 proposed almost a trillion dollar deficit and his 10 year projection proposes another 6 trillion even though it is based on unrealistic economic growth. The increase in the deficit since he took office is further proof of his intentions. Please don't mention Bush in your reply. We know he was not our best president.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369756155148</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369756321279-41</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you read? If you can I suggest you try reading my post again.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369756321279</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:52:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369756733006-42</Id><Topic><Title>LOAD THE TRUCK FOR 45 TARGET!!</Title><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1369755851907</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:44:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stay calm. We are only up 12 cents. Seriously, I like your enthusiasm and agree that before 2016 we will see $45. Unfortunately I loaded my truck too soon and am now down nearly $2,000.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369756733006</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:58:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369757462829-43</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Immigrants go to where the work is." That's why the Europeans came to America. They wanted to get away from their life before, just like now. China, India, and the Arab world were far more developed and productive than the Europeans, who were basically living in caves at the same time. Even your assumption the white skin color is superior is wrong. Most people in the history of the world have been brown. Skin color has come about from needing sun protection, nothing else. Go get that summer tan.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1369757462829</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:11:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369757893720-44</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again, forgetting the human implications (and forgetting the Mytilenian Debate's lessons about the implications of abandoning moral discussion for a democracy) of renewing indentured servitude, I again have to ask who will pay for this? Sure, you have a ready source of (chronologically limited) slave labor. But these slaves must be fed, housed, provided health care (workers compensation or disability?), and guarded. Do you expect the project will be slave run from top to bottom, or will we have to hire skilled engineers, equipment operators and managers? Have you considered the implications of organizing the slaves with slave managers? Not to mention the cost of materials and equipment. We will essentially have taken seven years of these peoples lives and set them to stacking bricks. And then we will make them citizens? Will they have any education or skills? Any savings or retirement? A credit score? Will they have contributed to Soc. Sec., UI, etc? Or will they simply be thrown into the American welfare state, but now with access to full benefits. In addition, indentured servitude has been rejected by every democratic state in the world as morally abhorrent. If the US reinstated it on such a broad scale, to include up to 13 million (chronologically limited) slaves, we would become a pariah and lose any credibility we had as leaders of the free world.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369757893720</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:18:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369758361582-45</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are kind of like me in one respect. You don't always think before you post. For example " Any other motivation ascribed to overall migrant flows is simply wrong." Immigration from North Korea to China is largely hunger and fear. The motivation for the exodus from Syria is terror. Weather is another motivation.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369758361582</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369758469901-46</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Even your assumption the white skin color is superior is wrong." I didn't assume that ricky did. He is implying traditionally white nations are more productive in the modern world and that is why they are becoming less white.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1369758469901</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:27:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369759057379-47</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Living in caves? At the time of the Pilgrims? Your thought processes are screwed up.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369759057379</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:37:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369759448592-48</Id><Topic><Title>OT-National Review Article</Title><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369429903158</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 17:11:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"2013 proposed" Sure it did, in early 2012 when it was proposed. The 2014 budget was released on April 10th. The latest projections from the CBO and OMB take into account the partial rollback of the tax cuts for the wealthy, the payroll tax increase, and the sequester. They also take into account the growing economy and the slowing growth of health care costs. Here's the thing, wilkes. People who are interested in reality notice when it changes. "The increase in the deficit since he took office is further proof of his intentions." The annual deficit has decreased every year since 2009--when Obama took office. In 2009 it was $1.549 trillion. In 2013, just over $1.006 trillion. The OMB baseline estimate for 2016 is $0.524 trillion--lower than it was in 2003. If Republicans hadn't blocked every effort to improve the economy the deficit would probably be even smaller now, and a 2016 surplus a very good possibility.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369759448592</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:44:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369760358033-49</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I implied nothing of the sort. I clearly stated that India and China are as much a draw for immigrants as the US. You can add the Persian Gulf, Russia and Indonesia, and more I don't know about. And the flow goes all over the place. I know more than a few people who have emigrated to Dubai and China. Winholder illegally emigrated to Mexico. Do not project your degenerate worldview onto me, Lav. If you cannot comprehend my posts it is the result of your own sick, sick mind.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369760358033</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:59:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369760898915-50</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think this is a subject that demands its own "Topic". I'll start one.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369760898915</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369760935671-51</Id><Title>Negative today - this stock never goes up anymore even on huge up market days.</Title><Msg>This is probably the most disappointing stock out there. What does it take for this to go up? Might be a LONG time back to $39, Another 5 years maybe. No investor interest whatsoever in T. And why should there be?</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369760935671</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:08:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369761221433-52</Id><Topic><Title>Negative today - this stock never goes up anymore even on huge up market days.</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369760935671</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:08:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is embarassing. How could it be down on a day like today? When you make less $$ than you used to thats what happens - you get whacked. This still has much further to fall. Next earnings could be scary. Why buy T now???????</Msg><Username>smithersj1234</Username><Timestamp>1369761221433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369761332751-53</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I clearly stated that India and China are as much a draw for immigrants as the US. " You never stated that you are changing your tune now that your racism view have been revealed.</Msg><Username>geoff_holt_2001</Username><Timestamp>1369761332751</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:15:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369761625825-54</Id><Title>This is nasty.</Title><Msg>Why does this stock get hammered all the time now? Even on great market days? Is there something wrong with T (besides missing their #'s last quarter)?</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369761625825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:20:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369762126324-55</Id><Title>Immigration solution</Title><Msg>Ricky and I were discussing my idea for solving the Immigration problem and, can you believe it, we disagree. Ricky said that enforcing immigration would "would cost a lot and hurt the economy while providing no discernible benefit." My proposal is that a law be passed to make the penalty for being caught in the United States illegally seven years hard labor building a concrete block wall on the Southern border. I opined that the passage of such a law would reduce immigration and the enforcement of such a law would stop immigration cold and instead cause a panic exodus from the USA. Ricky"s response is: Again, forgetting the human implications (and forgetting the Mytilenian Debate's lessons about the implications of abandoning moral discussion for a democracy) of renewing indentured servitude, I again have to ask who will pay for this? Sure, you have a ready source of (chronologically limited) slave labor. But these slaves must be fed, housed, provided health care (workers compensation or disability?), and guarded. Do you expect the project will be slave run from top to bottom, or will we have to hire skilled engineers, equipment operators and managers? Have you considered the implications of organizing the slaves with slave managers? Not to mention the cost of materials and equipment. We will essentially have taken seven years of these peoples lives and set them to stacking bricks. And then we will make them citizens? Will they have any education or skills? Any savings or retirement? A credit score? Will they have contributed to Soc. Sec., UI, etc? Or will they simply be thrown into the American welfare state, but now with access to full benefits. In addition, indentured servitude has been rejected by every democratic state in the world as morally abhorrent. If the US reinstated it on such a broad scale, to include up to 13 million (chronologically limited) slaves, we would become a pariah and lose any credibility we had as leaders of the free world.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369762126324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369762997274-56</Id><Topic><Title>This is nasty.</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369761625825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:20:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree hope it gains some when divy time arrive bought 1000 shrs at 39 yet long term so may just take 5 per cent for life was not the oring plan ...hope it turns around read next quater will be better ,,,,so they say</Msg><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1369762997274</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:43:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369763524831-57</Id><Topic><Title>This is nasty.</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369761625825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:20:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go back and read my posts. You will find the reasons there. Good Luck</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1369763524831</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:52:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369763599172-58</Id><Topic><Title>LOAD THE TRUCK FOR 45 TARGET!!</Title><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1369755851907</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:44:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry Wilkes71, I hope you still have a small put position. You will be fine, hang in there!</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1369763599172</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:53:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369765012392-59</Id><Topic><Title>LOAD THE TRUCK FOR 45 TARGET!!</Title><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1369755851907</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:44:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very small. Just 10 36 puts that expire Friday. I have 50 longer term calls and have now lost over $2,000.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369765012392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:16:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369766271283-60</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Learn to comprehend an argument. What do you think stating your perception of reality is wrong, citing examples of immigration to Non-Western countries, and then stating immigrants go where the work is means? There's no work outside of the US? No wonder you're so #$%$ dumb. You're a foaming piece of evidence against the notion of white supremacy.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369766271283</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369766900331-61</Id><Topic><Title>Immigration solution</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369762126324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wilkes .. your solution is far simpler and much better for the U.S. .. unless they want to use this as a way to earn their citizenship as 'icky' may imply !!. However the only problem I see .. is the I.R.S. may want to tax them as receiving unreported benefits, thus imprisioning them for tax evasion .. and we'd still have to pay for them. The only way around this delima would be to jail 'icky' and stuff a sock in his mouth .. and then abolish the IRS</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1369766900331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369767270141-62</Id><Topic><Title>Immigration solution</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369762126324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the recap. wilkes. Care to address the questions?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369767270141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:54:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369767550062-63</Id><Topic><Title>Immigration solution</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369762126324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If no one else will reply to ricky, I will. First forget the 13 million figure. It will evaporate when a jury convicts the first one and it is announced on the Spanish channels. Second, I didn't say we would make them citizens at the end of their incarceration. They can apply for citizenship and it will depend a lot on their behavior during their incarceration. As for savings, retirement, and credit score, they will have the same as any other criminal being released from prison. They will, of course, have the option of returning to their native country. As for the administration of the program. It should be turned over to a private company under contract to the government. Of course it will cost something but not nearly as much as a typical government program. The main thing it will do is provide a penalty for entering the USA illegally. Buying them a bus ticket back home is no penalty at all.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369767550062</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:59:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369767782311-64</Id><Topic><Title>Negative today - this stock never goes up anymore even on huge up market days.</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369760935671</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:08:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HAPPY BIRTHDAY 'ossobucco' .. you're only about 5 hours old and you've already made about 20 posts - you're a really smart little 'alias' Can't you find some other stock to b 'ich' about .. (just saying)</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1369767782311</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369768380099-65</Id><Topic><Title>This is nasty.</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369761625825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:20:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're down almost 8% already! Sorry for you. The dividend will never make up for the share price decline. You should probably sell now and cut your losses. This isn't coming back anytime soon.</Msg><Username>smithersj1234</Username><Timestamp>1369768380099</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:13:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369768844184-66</Id><Topic><Title>This is nasty.</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369761625825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:20:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because it is a defensive stock in a bull market.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369768844184</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:20:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369769281112-67</Id><Topic><Title>Immigration solution</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369762126324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Of course it will cost something" All right, we have some factual basis for discussion. There is a direct cost to running a prison labor camp and building a giant concrete block wall on one side of the Rio Grande. Are you willing to pay taxes to cover these costs?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369769281112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:28:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369769412134-68</Id><Title>Down 8% from recent $39 five year high!!!!!!</Title><Msg>$36 nearly history. Almost into official correction territory (should happen in a couple of days). Just shows how nasty things can turn when a company misses its #'s. There is nothing worse in the markets eyes than making less $$$ than you did the previous quarter/year. Next quarter is crucial. Another horrific report and it'll go below $30 - and stay there for a long time. if the markets correct overall - all bets are off. This could go to $25 - $26.</Msg><Username>smithersj1234</Username><Timestamp>1369769412134</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369770641028-69</Id><Title>2 month closing low!</Title><Msg>Markets through the roof last 2 months - this at 2 month low. That last quarter miss was a real turning point for this stock. Dismal performance since. Down $2.75 per share since it hit $39 !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! WOW!!!!!!!!!! A lot of people are down a lot of $$$ since then.</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369770641028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:50:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369770746424-70</Id><Title>Back to a 5% dividend !!!!</Title><Msg>Never thought that would be seen again! Is 6% next? With another rotten quarter the answer is YES!</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369770746424</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:52:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369772755673-71</Id><Topic><Title>Immigration solution</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369762126324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll vote for that. I have been preparing tax returns for 60 years and think it is about time for the USA to replace income tax with a sales tax so individuals no longer need to file tax returns or worry about their charitable donations being tax deductible. And preachers would no longer have to worry about saying something political. The only problem is, who would manage Obama-care?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369772755673</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:25:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369772872795-72</Id><Title>After Hours shows $36.82 0.64 (1.78%) 4:12PM EDT</Title><Msg>After Hours : 36.82 0.64 (1.78%) 4:12PM EDT - Nasdaq Real Time Price Is this real?</Msg><Username>simonofnj888</Username><Timestamp>1369772872795</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:27:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369772919373-73</Id><Topic><Title>Immigration solution</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369762126324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course we would pay taxes to cover the cost. It is much cheaper than paying welfare and food stamps for most of the 13 million illegals.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369772919373</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:28:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369774207502-74</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, so are you saying that they have laws, and that they enforce them?</Msg><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1369774207502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:50:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369777200027-75</Id><Topic><Title>Immigration solution</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369762126324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Illegal immigrants are not eligible for welfare or food stamps. It is absurd to think that most of them are on welfare or food stamps. Most of them come here to work. But if they are working in a forced labor camp we will have to provide them with food, housing, armed guards, health care, etc. It costs the Federal Government about $26,500 to house a prisoner in a medium security establishment. I think that is a reasonable estimate of what it would cost. I would assume you would have to pay at least that much for your time-limited slaves. By contrast, the average annual food stamp benefit is $133 per month or $1,600 annually per recipient. So even if you falsely assume "most" illegal immigrants are on food stamps I am not sure where you find the savings.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1369777200027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:40:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369777461061-76</Id><Topic><Title>2 month closing low!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369770641028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes bought 1000 shrs at 39 sooo yes we r down guess i will have a 5 % income for life till than not my original plan</Msg><Username>beau287</Username><Timestamp>1369777461061</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:44:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369777938099-77</Id><Topic><Title>Immigration solution</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369762126324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“My proposal is that a law be passed to make the penalty for being caught in the United States illegally seven years hard labor building a concrete block wall on the Southern border.” – wilkes, apparently named after the actor from Ford’s Theater in D.C. United Nation General Assembly resolution 217, December, 1948…Article 4, Universal Declaration of Human Rights: “No one shall be held in slavery or servitude; slavery and the slave trade shall be prohibited in all their forms." It would seem logical that “in all their forms” would include your goofy indentured servant scheme, but then again, you view the United Nations as some New World Order conspiracy. But, why concrete blocks??? What are you…some kind of Pharaoh or something? John Wilkes Khufu.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1369777938099</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369778729783-78</Id><Topic><Title>This is a tough stock to own..</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369753590197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It has been a rather easy stock to own for me. I bought in at 27.25 in 9/11 have been collecting the nice juicy dividend since. I prefere this stock stayed around 35 for my reinvested dividends</Msg><Username>acmech13</Username><Timestamp>1369778729783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 18:05:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369779338914-79</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think that America was ever a white nation. The indigenous Native Americans were not white. The world is changing, and people are moving and relocating around the globe. Immigration is a constant factor. White Americans are the descendants of immigrants.</Msg><Username>maramwp</Username><Timestamp>1369779338914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 18:15:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369781556027-80</Id><Topic><Title>This is a tough stock to own..</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369753590197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This im not positive, but I think any signs of inflation or the economy growing faster than expected and there is a chance of a rise in interest rates, stocks that have high yields usually go down...</Msg><Username>dot1996</Username><Timestamp>1369781556027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 18:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369783151568-81</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Or is it because the perpetrators of multiculturalism have an agenda of genocide against Whites? Using multiculturalism and multi-racial societies as tools, along with other tools, to eliminate and genocide Whties in their own countries? That is what I believe is happening." It is that the anti-Christians are intent on destroying Christian societies wherever they are. Why are we Whites allowing our race, cultures and nations to be destroyed and eliminated and seized away from us? At some point in the not so distant future, when we have become a small enough minority, we will have no say so or control, whatsoever, over our lives, cultures or destiny. Whites have allowed themselves to be brainwashed by the anti-Christians in public indoctrination centers (aka, public schools). Do not hesitate to home educate!</Msg><Username>taquinas65</Username><Timestamp>1369783151568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369783820847-82</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just deport the Third-Worlders to their country of origin and make sure they stay there. This country was meant for the progeny of Europeans and not for the progeny of other countries. It says so in the preamble to the constitution: "...for our progeny...</Msg><Username>taquinas65</Username><Timestamp>1369783820847</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:30:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369785636884-83</Id><Topic><Title>This is a tough stock to own..</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369753590197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>even better - it goes down 50% right? moron</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369785636884</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369786372238-84</Id><Topic><Title>2 month closing low!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369770641028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you were the one that bought at $39? LOL</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369786372238</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:12:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369787115139-85</Id><Title>Just keeps getting uglier...</Title><Msg>$35's tomorrow obviously (if not $34's).</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369787115139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:25:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369787594994-86</Id><Topic><Title>2 month closing low!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369770641028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOD!. I'll get shares cheaper with my DRIP plan and keep my DCA cost down. That's how to make money with stocks. You will NEVER out guess the shysters on the floor of the NYSE. Now, if the "Fed" closes the credit window as they did in 1929 you can expect a long term bear market as occurred in the thirties. As long as they keep pumping their fairy tale money out stocks will fluctuate but go up in general. I'll hang on.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369787594994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:33:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369787657670-87</Id><Title>New Dow closing high - this down 1.55%?</Title><Msg>That's #$%$ up. This thing is one damaged stock.</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369787657670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369787800976-88</Id><Topic><Title>2 month closing low!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369770641028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're an idiot.</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369787800976</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:36:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369788174125-89</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>where is that steady stream of illegal Africans, hispanic and arabs into China? or Japan or Korea? Not one single country on this planet that has multi races and languages is without problems because of that. Think I am mistaken? well, list those countries if you can</Msg><Username>fallenangelsthree</Username><Timestamp>1369788174125</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369788249257-90</Id><Topic><Title>Angry protests in England and riots in Sweden</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1369733717231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no. The way to solve the illegal immigrant problem is forced labor or kill them.</Msg><Username>fallenangelsthree</Username><Timestamp>1369788249257</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:44:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369789490177-91</Id><Topic><Title>This is a tough stock to own..</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369753590197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"even better - it goes down 50% right? moron" I think it's time to put your sorry butt on ignore. See ya, moron. Click!.</Msg><Username>ramsdude46</Username><Timestamp>1369789490177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369791490164-92</Id><Topic><Title>Immigration solution</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369762126324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are missing the fact that there would be far fewer than 13 million convicted under this law. Most would leave the country rather than risk arrest. The point is there is no risk involved now. Deportation is the worst that can happen and the chance of being caught is minimal.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1369791490164</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:38:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369792837427-93</Id><Topic><Title>This is a tough stock to own..</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1369753590197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ozzie bucco .. I've been reading your last 1 &amp; 1/2 half hours worth of beechin, you sure do cry alot. Have you taken advantage of this recent buying opportunity - or just the crying &amp; beechin.? Give me your zip and i'll send you some fresh crying towels</Msg><Username>bill.polk79</Username><Timestamp>1369792837427</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 22:00:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369793208082-94</Id><Title>ATT Stock</Title><Msg>At these levels, this stock is a buy. I am also surprised at all the whining on this board...with a strong dividend...if your down, dollar cost down and add to your position....this stock would not go below 36 today...tomorrow is higher and long term is where people will make the most money. Good luck longs. I purchased a small 7.5k position after hours tonite at 36.23/shr</Msg><Username>jk7823</Username><Timestamp>1369793208082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 22:06:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369795883784-95</Id><Topic><Title>ATT Stock</Title><Username>jk7823</Username><Timestamp>1369793208082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 22:06:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somebody wanted in bad. Paid what was it $36.90+ for 1,100,000 shares after hours making th AH trend up. Ot course somone else wanted ot but at a good price.</Msg><Username>aclaydale</Username><Timestamp>1369795883784</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 22:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>