<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367900800445-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's incredible comment</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367699187107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've been drinking again. I'm zoocrack89. You're zoocrack98. You're an idiot.</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367900800445</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:26:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367900928373-2</Id><Topic><Title>Revolution in cell phones coming - Smart glasses by Vuzi - Its breaking out</Title><Username>whattime0000</Username><Timestamp>1367861141317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:25:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You'd have to have finished twelve grades first, and it's clear that did not happen.</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367900928373</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367900973098-3</Id><Topic><Title>Revolution in cell phones coming - Smart glasses by Vuzi - Its breaking out</Title><Username>whattime0000</Username><Timestamp>1367861141317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:25:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Simblance"...HAHAHA...could you be more stupid?</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367900973098</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:29:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367901100735-4</Id><Topic><Title>ANOTHER BAD DAY for "davemartin"</Title><Username>bshipleyinsurance</Username><Timestamp>1367870453108</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:00:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sqwuack..When was the last time you had an original thought, Polly?</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367901100735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:31:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367927793306-5</Id><Title>Cash Balance Pension Plans</Title><Msg>Appears to minimize the risks for the employer and makes the lump sum distribution routine. AT&amp;T and IBM were cited as companies participating in this plan, gradually gaining popularity nationwide. Surely, it is possible to argue the pros and cons of this methodology depending on whether you are the employee or the employer.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1367927793306</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 07:56:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367931503994-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: We will get answers in Bombing Case!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367858327227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:38:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obama only knows how to be a community organizer; he demands that the "man" do things for his people, he is too stupid to realize that now he is da "man"</Msg><Username>emil_chesibilski</Username><Timestamp>1367931503994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:58:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367934405035-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: We will get answers in Bombing Case!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367858327227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:38:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These three men have already given depositions. The transcripts of their depositions are public. The Secretary of Defense, the NATO commander, the State Department's Coordinator for Counterterrorism have already responded to issues raised in the depositions. What do you think is going to happen? You people are ridiculous. You have Froggie &amp; Rush &amp; Glen telling you that after Wednesday the President will have to resign. Why? Because a U.S. deputy chief thinks NATO should have scrambled some planes in Italy? The President will not resign on Wednesday because absolutely nothing will have changed since Tuesday. The ARB report detailed what it described as "systematic failures and leadership and management deficiencies" in the State Department, which Hilary Clinton has taken responsibility for. We know things went wrong in this incident.. But because some media hacks have you Tea Brains in a tizzy you're going to decide it's some big conspiracy that Obama isn't hanged for a traitor on Wed. evening. Nuts! Good Americans are working and pushing to ensure these failures do not happen again. But Congressman Issa and the rest of you Tea Brains are foaming at the mouth to try to pin something on Obama. Issa's selective "leaks" and "sneak previews" to Meet the Press and other media should show you that this hearing is all a media spectacle. A farce produced just for you gullible, old, ridiculous Tea Brains. And, tbfine, the parents of the victims have to endure this farce. And they will continue to have to endure it until you Tea Brains stop being so d***ed ridiculous.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367934405035</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367935557727-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: We will get answers in Bombing Case!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367858327227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:38:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are very well informed. Maybe you could explain what the function of the facility at Benghazi was. The Embassy is in Tripoli.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367935557727</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:05:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936169369-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: We will get answers in Bombing Case!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367858327227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:38:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You people are ridiculous" They don't know anything about any event except what they hear on faux news. They don't read anything, let alone depositions. If their comments are looked at, they usually are saying "Obama knows", "Obama thinks", and their facts and quotes are usually opinions of some other right wing nut, presented as a quote from Obama or the speaker in question.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367936169369</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:16:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936427061-10</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: We will get answers in Bombing Case!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367858327227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:38:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“We could get rid of him Wednesday if the three witnesses to Benghazi Gate are not too intimidated by Obama's Mafia friends. I don't hold out too much hope…” –wilkes So, with no other response from you, I guess that means you won’t be donating $1000 to charity if your current swiftboat “Gate” efforts do not result in the impeachment of the President, eh, wilkie? And the reason will be what again??? Say that one more time…you say if he isn’t impeached you’re going to blame it on The Mafia??? Do you have even a slightly remote idea how irrationally absurd you sound? It’s as though you are intentionally seeking scornful derision for your group on the lunatic fringe…and succeeding quite nicely, I might add.</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367936427061</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:20:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936655903-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's incredible comment</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367699187107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does anyone have a source to the actual Obama incredible comment? The topic was brought up and I wanted to see the original comment, since he was accused of saying something. Otherwise what's the point of saying "Obama's incredible comment" if there is no comment to read?</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367936655903</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:24:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936912491-12</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: We will get answers in Bombing Case!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367858327227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:38:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The attack was on a US Consulate. Do you know what a consulate is? Do I really need to explain the function of a consulate to you?</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367936912491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:28:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367937884843-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: We will get answers in Bombing Case!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367858327227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:38:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google hasn't a link to the depositions you reference. How did you access them? Or is that just another lie you have been instructed to tell.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367937884843</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:44:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367938379533-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's incredible comment</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367699187107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you watched FOX NEWS you would have seen Obama making the statement. But I guess you prefer to be dumb but happy all the way to the internment camp.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367938379533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:52:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367938429782-15</Id><Title>jonny's "postses"</Title><Msg>Tragedy has struck the board. I was hoping to go back and enjoy some of baby jonny's (zonbac98) "wit and wisdom" this morning and his "postses" seem to have disappeared. I cannot find a "simblance" of them anywhere. What a senseless loss for humanity..grins ;) It must be another conspiracy started by Obama and the Mafia..(!!)</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367938429782</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:53:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367938915460-16</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's incredible comment</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367699187107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't even know where to begin. We are arming the drug cartels in Mexico, (and our own gangs) as Obama just discussed with the President of Mexico, but by selling assault rifles to the general public. Why on earth would you think Egypt and Libya were poor judgement? Because they didn't instantly become full-fledged, US supporting Democracies? We are moving from a long period of dictatorship, in countries where we either supported the dictator or engaged in long-term, often violent, confrontation. Do you expect instant success? With little effort, however, we are as far or farther on this process than in Afghanistan or Iraq. We are NOT arming rebels in Syria for exactly the reasons you mentioned. That is what Republicans are upset about now. They have decided, as they always do, that whatever Obama does they should complain about. We are not send "billions" in humanitarian aid to Syria. The current commitment is $385 million. We are not sending humanitarian aid to the Syrian government.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367938915460</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:01:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367938973195-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's incredible comment</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367699187107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok. Except for you Wilkes. You're just nuts.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367938973195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:02:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367939163811-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's incredible comment</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367699187107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or, and call me crazy, they're the Syrian's. It's not like sarin gas is a new technology.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367939163811</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367939447661-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's incredible comment</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367699187107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't watch faux news, but I do want to see the incredible comment. Comments about Obama's incredible comment, are not Obama's incredible comment. Comments about a few words taken out of Obama's incredible comment, are not Obama's incredible comment either. That's one reason I don't watch faux news and why it is called faux news. Somewhere you must have the incredible comment itself to cut and paste here to read. In order to show what you say is true. Or is there no real Obama's incredible comment? Or are you just aimlessly commenting about someone commenting about Obama's incredible comment? Are you saying you got this comment about the incredible comment that accuses Obama of something, off that, so called in my view, news outlet? That makes your post a lie automatically in my view, but let's see the Obama incredible comment they referred to already, OK? Why is it so difficult to produce the Obama's Incredible Comment, all of it? Are you afraid of it?</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367939447661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:10:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367939497672-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: We will get answers in Bombing Case!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367858327227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:38:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently you don't know Ricky, so to help you out ... An Embassy is located in the capitol city, the Counsulate, serving the same function as the Embassy, is located in another city as an extention of the Embassy So the Bengazzi attack IS/WAS an attack on our "EMBASSY" Apparently you nor Hillary were aware .. there is NO difference but for the location !</Msg><Username>redjon_iii</Username><Timestamp>1367939497672</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367940041046-21</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: We will get answers in Bombing Case!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367858327227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:38:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wilkes, the information in the released deposition is the reason Issa is having a hearing. If you don't think it is real, take it up with Issa.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367940041046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:20:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367941649639-22</Id><Topic><Title>Cash Balance Pension Plans</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1367927793306</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 07:56:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't quite understand what it is. Do they give you cash when you retire? If it is enough it would be OK for some as they would invest it wisely. Others would waste it and be without. It's too bad that so many people aren't smart enough to look out for themselves. I always bought all the stoct T would let me have and reinvested the dividends. It has worked well for me in retirement Studebaker paid retirement from current earnings. When they went BK 8,000 people lost their retirement.. A funded retirement is the best way to go.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1367941649639</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:47:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367941711492-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: We will get answers in Bombing Case!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367858327227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:38:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I asked Issa's Office and they said they do have depositions but they have not been made public. So at least your post was a half truth which is far above average for Obama supporters.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367941711492</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:48:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367942532717-24</Id><Topic><Title>Cash Balance Pension Plans</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1367927793306</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 07:56:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A T &amp; T is a pus stain in treatment of employees and especially regarding pensions. But why should I care?</Msg><Username>lucenatraveler</Username><Timestamp>1367942532717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:02:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367942780796-25</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: We will get answers in Bombing Case!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367858327227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:38:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great. Another Tea Brain with a reading comprehension score in the single digits.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367942780796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367943322019-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: We will get answers in Bombing Case!</Title><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1367858327227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:38:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have no desire to quibble with you over the use of the word "public". I write these posts in 10 seconds. If that's all you got out of my post you need to reread it. What you have to deal with is the reality that the information here is already known. What you have to deal with is this is a media spectacle of the worst kind and you may as well have a ring in your nose.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367943322019</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:15:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367948929406-27</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's incredible comment</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367699187107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, it was not. Peppeek was right. Bouche posted comments on the comments. President Obama's actual comment was: "The United States recognizes that we've got responsibilities, that much of the violence in the region is fueled by demand for illegal drugs, including in the United States. We also recognize that most of the guns used to commit violence here in Mexico come from the United States." Which part of the President's comments do you people have a problem with? The part with the facts, or the part where you actually have to take responsibility for the consequences of the policies you support? Because that would be all of it.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367948929406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:48:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367951299607-28</Id><Topic><Title>jonny's "postses"</Title><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367938429782</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:53:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've had my suspicions, but it's clear to me now. They've archived all his posts in his new library.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367951299607</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367953700097-29</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's incredible comment</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367699187107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finally, Obama's incredible comment. Doesn't look anything like the comment about the incredible comment first posted. As usual Obama's comments are right on the mark. Doesn't seem like such an incredible comment, just a regular old comment. Everything was fine with it too. For me, I want the best for America, so I don't try to harm it, just in order to blame it falsely on Obama. The voting for him is done anyway, so what's it all about.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1367953700097</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:08:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367954414543-30</Id><Topic><Title>jonny's "postses"</Title><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367938429782</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:53:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just bought AT&amp;T .. looking for relavent stock related posts .. were are they, did he have any ? oh well ??</Msg><Username>bill.polk79</Username><Timestamp>1367954414543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:20:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367954596493-31</Id><Topic><Title>Cash Balance Pension Plans</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1367927793306</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 07:56:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Must be same as a DUK board troll</Msg><Username>bill.polk79</Username><Timestamp>1367954596493</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:23:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367955091221-32</Id><Title>Imagine these Smart glasses on T network. Vuzi breaking out! Future of cell usage is here</Title><Msg>real run will be amazing... just breaking out now</Msg><Username>whattime0000</Username><Timestamp>1367955091221</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:31:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367955131901-33</Id><Title>ATT should buy Vuzi - the Smart glasses will be Future of Cell usage - Its breaking out, future is here</Title><Msg>Shipping this summer</Msg><Username>whattime0000</Username><Timestamp>1367955131901</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367955150857-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's incredible comment</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367699187107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...Actually, here’s part of wilkes’ original comment: “He will not resign like Nixon did because he has no love for our country.” Right, wilkes. Nixon resigned because he loved our country…well, that and he didn’t want to be impeached and possibly go to jail for criminal deeds far more serious than a #$%$. Gee, wilkes, for a guy that hates his country and is trying to destroy it, Obama has a whole lot more Americans on his side than you obstructionist clowns. The MAFIA??????? $1000 bucks… you in, hotshot?</Msg><Username>echo2165</Username><Timestamp>1367955150857</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:32:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367956070004-35</Id><Topic><Title>Imagine these Smart glasses on T network. Vuzi breaking out! Future of cell usage is here</Title><Username>whattime0000</Username><Timestamp>1367955091221</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure .. as many dummies walking into traffic, light poles, off second floor balconies, into fountains, off of long piers etc - then there would be the operation of motor vehicles. Hey baby, lift up your Vuzi Smart Glasses and watch this big wreck I'm about to have - (dumb spammers)</Msg><Username>bill.polk79</Username><Timestamp>1367956070004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:47:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367956845634-36</Id><Title>AT&amp;T</Title><Msg>T's up on half volume - about 88 bucks the first day ain't bad ..</Msg><Username>bill.polk79</Username><Timestamp>1367956845634</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:00:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367959178605-37</Id><Topic><Title>jonny's "postses"</Title><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367938429782</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:53:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No jon..you know very well that they were never "relavent". If you had ever posted anything relevant, it would be impossible to tell because you are a functionally illiterate nincompoop..sorry about your little "identity crisis"..ouch..lost another ID, did you? Funny thing is, you write so poorly that it is simple (like you) to recognize your new ID..grins (!!)..</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367959178605</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367959314338-38</Id><Topic><Title>Imagine these Smart glasses on T network. Vuzi breaking out! Future of cell usage is here</Title><Username>whattime0000</Username><Timestamp>1367955091221</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb Jon..thinks he's fooling someone. What a pitiful bonehead. Kicked off a message board..AGAIN..(!!)..grins..</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367959314338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367960803984-39</Id><Topic><Title>jonny's "postses"</Title><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367938429782</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:53:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>C'mon, use your real alias, Gdubya43. . .</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367960803984</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 17:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367960972685-40</Id><Topic><Title>Imagine these Smart glasses on T network. Vuzi breaking out! Future of cell usage is here</Title><Username>whattime0000</Username><Timestamp>1367955091221</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They now thumb down posts I see. Those idiot spammers try every trick in the book to look genuine don't they?</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1367960972685</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 17:09:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367962533685-41</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T</Title><Username>bill.polk79</Username><Timestamp>1367956845634</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:00:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jon..it's great you finally bought some T..?? You're kicking butt with those 2.5 shares!! Idiot..grins..</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367962533685</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 17:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367964409976-42</Id><Topic><Title>"What difference, at this point, does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1367862161237</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:42:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The hunt is into which bureaucrats lied. . .in the second debate, told a whopper." Romney. Lie of the Year. Remember? If that is what you are concerned about, you are really mincing hairs. The evidence does show that intelligence reports linked it to violent protests at the embassy in Cairo at first blush. But you are really sticking your nose into a national security issue where it doesn't belong. Even if Obama himself and everyone around him knew it was a terrorist attack and portrayed it differently, you have no idea why. Were they protecting informants or undercover agents? Were they pursuing the attackers and did not want them to know they were on to them? Do you think, in an ongoing national security situation, you have a right to instantaneously know every detail of what happened? Even if releasing that information may put more lives at risk? It was not the only situation occurring at the time--there were violent protests and threats all over the Mideast, so denouncing that video may have been helpful regardless of its real link to the attack. This is the real world, wilkes. Not some kindergarten morality lesson. Obama wasn't starting a war or advocating a policy. He was dealing with a live, ongoing and complex situation in which American lives were in danger. You're upset he *may* have told a fib for a couple of days? You're in a Tea Brain hole. Climb out of it.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367964409976</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 18:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367967092640-43</Id><Topic><Title>"What difference, at this point, does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1367862161237</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:42:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Medical School Exam When I was young my intent was to go to medical school, but I was confused by the entrance exam. The deciding question was, "Re-arrange the letters P-N-E-S-I to spell out an important part of the human body that is more useful when erect." Those who spelled SPINE became doctors. The rest ran for Congress.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1367967092640</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 18:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367967190094-44</Id><Title>DOW 15k</Title><Msg>Wealth distribution works. I have more money now then ever, without having to work. Thank you President Obama.</Msg><Username>freakedout35</Username><Timestamp>1367967190094</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 18:53:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367967504811-45</Id><Topic><Title>jonny's "postses"</Title><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367938429782</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:53:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like jon has loaded up on new IDs since zonbac98 got tossed in the shredder. What a jerkwad.</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367967504811</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 18:58:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367968029189-46</Id><Topic><Title>jonny's "postses"</Title><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367938429782</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:53:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awwww...poor little jonny. Here comes a fun little hissy under whatever his new ID is. Wait for it...wait for it...!</Msg><Username>wledigmacsen</Username><Timestamp>1367968029189</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 19:07:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367970908190-47</Id><Topic><Title>"What difference, at this point, does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1367862161237</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:42:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh my, what an inspired little bit of fiction. The eight months of stone walling, cover up, and disinformation was done for the purposes of protecting the American people and the intelligence gathering ability of various government agencies. And this policy had nothing to do with protecting the campaign mantra of the democrat party as expressed by the president in Las Vegas on September 12, 2012: "A day after 9/11, we are reminded that a new tower rises above the New York skyline, but al Qaeda is on the path to defeat and bin Laden is dead,” Or in New York the day after when he said: We’ve got choices about war and peace,” Obama said. “I ended the war in Iraq, as I promised. We are transitioning out of Afghanistan. We have gone after the terrorists who actually attacked us 9/11 and decimated al Qaeda.” Or on September 21 and 22, 2012 when he said: “al Qaeda is on the path to defeat.” So if “al Qaeda is on the path to defeat.” how in the world could the organized attack on an American embassy with rocket propelled grenades that caused the death of an American ambassador and three other Americans be anything else but a spontaneous demonstration by Libyan citizens who were upset by a so called American YouTube video. Don't you understand the deaths and the attack was America's fault for having that pesky freedom of speech amendment in its Constitution. "In your heart you know he is right." The Frogg</Msg><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1367970908190</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 19:55:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367974976990-48</Id><Topic><Title>"What difference, at this point, does it make?"</Title><Username>froggnot</Username><Timestamp>1367862161237</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:42:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"YOU" is almost as good as = "ME" at cut and pastie..!! Giggles and grins Tadpole foraweenie..(!!)</Msg><Username>jon3retiree</Username><Timestamp>1367974976990</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367975212464-49</Id><Topic><Title>jonny's "postses"</Title><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367938429782</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:53:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh..ho..ho..ho.."somebody" mean to poor "FakeZONBAC" = him mother..!! Greens..</Msg><Username>jon3retiree</Username><Timestamp>1367975212464</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367977261636-50</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's incredible comment</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1367699187107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YAY..!! LOTS OF BIG LETTERS..!! "ME" LOVES BIG LETTERS AND EXCLAMPATION MARKSES..!! YOU "MY" KNEW FAVORITE..!! GRINS..</Msg><Username>jon3retiree</Username><Timestamp>1367977261636</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367982781552-51</Id><Topic><Title>Cash Balance Pension Plans</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1367927793306</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 07:56:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd like a few more thumbs down please.</Msg><Username>lucenatraveler</Username><Timestamp>1367982781552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367983304501-52</Id><Topic><Title>Cash Balance Pension Plans</Title><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1367927793306</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 07:56:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, "A funded retirement is the best way to go.". How many companies offer that now?</Msg><Username>lucenatraveler</Username><Timestamp>1367983304501</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:21:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>