<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365166736298-1</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle and Barack are both hate-filled racists who occasionally slip up in public on open mic’s. It's part of who they are, have been for their entire lives</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364752473909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:54:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I mean that without the black vote, which was higher than normal and all those blacks that voted for him BECAUSE he was black and not necessarily because he was a good candidate, he would not have won the first election and you know it. He charmed the black and all the other voters that will vote for anyone giving away 'government' money to them and they carried the day for him. They did so again in the last election. He was/is the primary choice of blacks, what some call the ‘low information’ voters, and they were the votes that took him over the top. When you add those votes to the blind liberals like yourself, which is why he is President, not because he was qualified or the best candidate. Even Billary would have been a better choice. It isn't that hard to figure out. Why do you keep asking the same question repeatedly?</Msg><Username>pinhighshot</Username><Timestamp>1365166736298</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 08:58:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365167463047-2</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle and Barack are both hate-filled racists who occasionally slip up in public on open mic’s. It's part of who they are, have been for their entire lives</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364752473909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:54:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And what would you have the President do to "stop pretending he is President without his being black"? What steps could he personally take to "stop pretending he is President without his being black"? "Why do you keep asking the same question repeatedly?" Because you keep dodging it. You talk about politicians dodging questions, you Tea Brains have it down to a science. Answer the question and I'll stop asking it.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1365167463047</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 09:11:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365168906474-3</Id><Topic><Title>New sources of information for AT&amp;T, you should see it!</Title><Username>larry_williams64</Username><Timestamp>1364908299493</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 09:11:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome stock!</Msg><Username>morganden77</Username><Timestamp>1365168906474</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 09:35:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365172397885-4</Id><Title>Trading was never so easy</Title><Msg>I texted “stocks” to 555888 and got daily picks sent to my phone. I’ve improved as a trader simply following their picks.</Msg><Username>freemanjuan542</Username><Timestamp>1365172397885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 10:33:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365173376477-5</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT ABOUT THE 10 BILLION DOLLAR PENSION LIABILITY THAT CANNOT BE FIXED?</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1365061879258</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 03:51:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AT&amp;T spent 12 billion last year repurchasing their own stock. Do you really believe that they would do that if it would endanger the pensions?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365173376477</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 10:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365174095953-6</Id><Topic><Title>Hey; what's the matter with T today???</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365004879967</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:01:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like the jobs #'s will be the kick in the gut to keep T from $38 today - in which case it may be a while for $38 with ex-div monday and the usual beatdown that occurs with that.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1365174095953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 11:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365174321716-7</Id><Topic><Title>district 9 contract offer</Title><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1365088599573</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 11:16:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your response is weakens your arguments. The answer is you do not make any decisions for the direction of the company, and you risk no money. Technically specking you are a liability meaning that you cost the company money (overhead cost) that’s ok as long as the overhead cost remains inside the projected figures in their budget. That’s why they have negotiations rather than giving the union whatever they ask for. You are part of the "team and follow directives and procedures--you leave you job do your thing at home and come back the next day. The CEO (may or may not be worth their salary) can make decisions that impact many lives—they have enormous responsibilities. They have no guarantees that they will be able to keep their job year to year. On the other hand, you have a guaranteed job clause in your contract, and have really good benefits." That job of yours pays above market driven wages, so you really have no legitimate grips about your wages. If you want to gripe about your boss' attitude or a co-worker's laziness so be it, but you have no ground to stand on to complain about your wages (the total package). Finally, if you so desire to earn higher and higher wages then work toward becoming management, and work your way up the later, start a company, or change companies. If you don’t want to work that hard then be content in the box you choose to live in. There are bigger problems facing you than the pay check of a CEO. Why are you so angry about CEO pay and not about the government stealing your labor? There are temporary politicians doing permanent damage (by the trillions), and all we hear from you and like types is crickets chirping.</Msg><Username>cureffort</Username><Timestamp>1365174321716</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 11:05:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365175396352-8</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks a lot</Msg><Username>darla_gillispie</Username><Timestamp>1365175396352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 11:23:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365175579926-9</Id><Topic><Title>district 9 contract offer</Title><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1365088599573</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 11:16:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and without at&amp;t employees wouldn't exist --what's the point?</Msg><Username>cureffort</Username><Timestamp>1365175579926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 11:26:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365175826751-10</Id><Topic><Title>district 9 contract offer</Title><Username>ctmuscles</Username><Timestamp>1365088599573</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 11:16:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What will destroy this country is the citizenry’s growing dependency on the federal government.</Msg><Username>cureffort</Username><Timestamp>1365175826751</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 11:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365176053574-11</Id><Topic><Title>Trading was never so easy</Title><Username>freemanjuan542</Username><Timestamp>1365172397885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 10:33:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't have to text anyone or take anyone's picks. I just trade the weekly options for AT&amp;T. When T is down, I buy calls. When T is up I sell the calls and buy puts. When it is down again I sell the puts and buy calls. Pretty simple but I average $100 per day and seldom have more than $4,000 invested. I lose sometimes but this week I have made over $2,500 so that will cover lots of losses. This being Friday I have closed out all my April 5th options and only have $320 invested in 30 next weeks call options. If T reaches $38 today I will buy some put options. I like to go into next week with both calls and puts so I can profit which ever way it goes.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365176053574</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 11:34:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365177566944-12</Id><Topic><Title>Trading was never so easy</Title><Username>freemanjuan542</Username><Timestamp>1365172397885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 10:33:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Wilkie, what happened to $200.00 a day? That's quite a haircut.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1365177566944</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 11:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365177598584-13</Id><Topic><Title>Hey; what's the matter with T today???</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365004879967</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:01:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually ex-dividend is Wednesday but Monday will be too late to buy for the dividend because it takes 3 days after purchase to become a stockholder of record. T came within 4 cents of $38 yesterday and I would not be surprised to see a late surge to $38+ today even with the bad job report. The over all market has already started to recover.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365177598584</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 11:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365177678921-14</Id><Topic><Title>Optimistic news !</Title><Username>leeconnor743</Username><Timestamp>1365106294330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:11:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great update.</Msg><Username>john.white194</Username><Timestamp>1365177678921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:01:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365178765819-15</Id><Topic><Title>Trading was never so easy</Title><Username>freemanjuan542</Username><Timestamp>1365172397885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 10:33:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I calculated the increase in my account since 1/1/2013 and it only averaged $66 per day including the $2,500 that I made this week. So I decided to come clean. Next week I expect to make a killing on the drop after dividend so that will probably bring the average up to $100. I started the year with $2,000 and now have $6,650 so with more to work with and more experience I should get to $200 per day soon. It is those pesky losses that keep me down and I almost always close a position too soon. All fixable with experience.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365178765819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:19:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365178945772-16</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome work!</Msg><Username>miriam.shelton</Username><Timestamp>1365178945772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:22:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365179385510-17</Id><Topic><Title>49.1 million A.H. volume?</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1365117157264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 19:12:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am certainly no expert but my guess is the buyer wants to get in on the dividend and the seller wants to avoid the jobs report drop. Obviously they are very large fund managers. Another guess is that the drop off ex-dividend on Thursday will be large on high volume. I am buying puts today.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365179385510</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:29:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365180072641-18</Id><Topic><Title>Trading was never so easy</Title><Username>freemanjuan542</Username><Timestamp>1365172397885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 10:33:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know Wilky, seeings how you have sunk from 200 a day to a 100 a day and now you're 'coming clean' to 66 bucks a day, I think I may have to text 555888 and 'improve' my chances like the original poster states above. You're slide may be a run of be luck, but I @freemanjuan promises 'trading improvement'. I think it's time to try a new horse. However, before I make that text, I'll wait for my 6K dividend to hit my account on Monday. Then, I'll take the plunge by texting and sign up to make some real $$$$$. Screw those cheesy 5.92% dividends I get every quarter for over 30 years or your 66.00 daily haul...lead me to the promised land @freemanjuan!</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1365180072641</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:41:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365180983275-19</Id><Topic><Title>49.1 million A.H. volume?</Title><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1365117157264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 19:12:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now Wilky, everybody in the investment business knows about the impending dividend payout, jobs report (leaked), ex-dividend, etc. The question is WHY a fund manager, as you suggest, would dump such a huge number of shares with good news abounding for T? You have noticed the increased value recently, havent you? Doesn't track Wilky. By the same token, how wise is your presumable fund manager a buyer at $38.00 of 48M shares? Either things are looking terrific, or something bad is about to happen. Maybe your recently updated $66.00 daily profit will skyrocket, or will it go even lower? Worse case, you may have to re-write your 340K loss to a higher amount next year. Wouldn't want that to happen. Let's hear it.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1365180983275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:56:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365181795907-20</Id><Topic><Title>A Topic For AFTERHOURS (here)</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1365179248706</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing new here Zon. Don't get excited. It's corruption as usual. Stick to T's future and do what YOU have to do to get by. You're wasting your time griping about that sort of thing and its doubtful anyone can or wants to fix it.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1365181795907</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 13:09:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365181892844-21</Id><Topic><Title>Trading was never so easy</Title><Username>freemanjuan542</Username><Timestamp>1365172397885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 10:33:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahh, you are where I would be if only I had known 20 years ago what I know now. I am slow learner and lost over $300,000 before I learned how easy it is to make money in the market. Bye the way, your 6K won't be paid until May 1st.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365181892844</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 13:11:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365182737469-22</Id><Topic><Title>Trading was never so easy</Title><Username>freemanjuan542</Username><Timestamp>1365172397885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 10:33:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I jumped the gun. I knew it was May 1st. My bad. Fidelity wires it to me, so it'll be there 5/1M regardless. Now that you 'learned how easy it is to make money'', how is it you are going down from 200 bucks to 66 per day? Your chart is shaping up like Enron. In fact, I think you once wrote you made 300 a day. Didn't you once claim $300 daily profit? Whatever the case may be, you need to get it together mate. I think you should consider texting 555888 to improve your declining profits. @freemanjuan may be a valuable resource for you. Until you show a reversal, I gotta lower your success rating from B to C. Sorry W. I'll catch you later. Got business to tend to.</Msg><Username>davemartin74575</Username><Timestamp>1365182737469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 13:25:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365183553597-23</Id><Topic><Title>Hey; what's the matter with T today???</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365004879967</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:01:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah...that's what i meant....today is the last day to get in for the div...and yes it has already come back to $37.96 again today</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1365183553597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 13:39:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365189251228-24</Id><Topic><Title>A Topic For AFTERHOURS (here)</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1365179248706</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"and that THEY HAVE have voted (nationally) in multiple states" No they haven't. That is a bald-faced lie that not even your Tea Brain AG is asserting. These are simply duplicate registrations--people who have moved and their registration stayed on the books in their previous state. It's a good idea to remove duplicates from the books but to imply voter fraud is complete BS--which is what we expect from Tea Brains.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1365189251228</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 15:14:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365191694467-25</Id><Topic><Title>The fate of one White Man in FL</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1365009056576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 13:10:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everything in Florida IS about race. You should see all the NON White illegal aliens here. Many of them are brand new intruders, imported recently(and many helping them invade are greedy hateful White), and are taking the jobs that poor Whites would love to have. The politicians in this state and country are eliminating the White MAN from society INTENTIONALLY. That is why they want to reward the illegal invaders with citizenship, to do away with the White majority once and for all. Prepare if you are an ordinary White, man or woman.. You are a target for elimination, imo.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1365191694467</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 15:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365191779924-26</Id><Topic><Title>Hey; what's the matter with T today???</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365004879967</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:01:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What were those censors thinking of grabbing?</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365191779924</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365192183154-27</Id><Topic><Title>A Topic For AFTERHOURS (here)</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1365179248706</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As soon as they make 11 million illegal aliens, democrat voters that's when it's going to be real tough to win the Presidency for the republicans. But to your point, yeah I don't doubt it for a moment. Without voter ID that the republicans are pushing but the democrats are against, voter fraud will become the norm in the future. Then you also have the pesky 47%ers to contend with also.</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1365192183154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:03:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365192358603-28</Id><Topic><Title>Hey; what's the matter with T today???</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365004879967</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:01:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look like you made the $38.00</Msg><Username>quetee2</Username><Timestamp>1365192358603</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:05:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365192483130-29</Id><Topic><Title>Not too shabby.</Title><Username>themightyslug</Username><Timestamp>1365111628790</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 17:40:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$.45 (dividend)/$38.01(current stock price)=.01184. That's an expected 1.184% drop after ex-dividend assuming no other factors (there are always other factors). That would put the stock at $37.56 ($38.01 x 98.816%). Does my math check out?</Msg><Username>themightyslug</Username><Timestamp>1365192483130</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:08:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365193252486-30</Id><Topic><Title>Optimistic news !</Title><Username>leeconnor743</Username><Timestamp>1365106294330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:11:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this report</Msg><Username>juanking780</Username><Timestamp>1365193252486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:20:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365193552982-31</Id><Title>White supremacists or White HATERS in TX?</Title><Msg>The government is beginning to round up the so called White supremacists as a result of the shootings of DA`a in TX with no proof whatsoever that they had anything to do with it. Iit seems Whites have no right to disagree with anything this government does or says when it comes to the elimination of the White majority and possibly our complete elimination. Are these SO CALLED White supremacists responsible for the TX murders? Or are these murders possibly more false flags to stomp out ALL opposition to our elimination, to instill fear in ANYONE who dares speak about our elimination? Could the criminals who have seized control of this country be responsible for the murders? I think it is very possible they are. Just like the CT WI and CO mass killings, were those confused and disorganized young White men really responsible for the mass murders? Or were they possibly patsies in false flags perpetrated in an effort to take away the rights of law abiding WHITES to own guns? You know there are millions of guns in the possessions of criminals(many if not most of them are colored) right now that law enforcement has the right to confiscate. Yet they don`t. It`s interesting, the murdered people are usually also Whites in these made for teevee murders(more hated Whites eliminate?) I never thought I would be in favor of armed police in schools, especially White schools, but I am now. I think we are a target by a hidden criminal elite that runs this country, that may be perpetrating one false flag and then under the pretense of protecting us, they take away our rights to defend ourselves and our right to free speech. The armed police are needed to protect White children from a group of people who may hate them intensely, not from individuasl confused and drugged White patsies. Prepare if you are White, imo, Whites are targeted for elimination, even though it appears we are being protected by the criminal elite.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1365193552982</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365194030049-32</Id><Topic><Title>Hey; what's the matter with T today???</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365004879967</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:01:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bought 40 of the May calls but, as usual, sold them too soon. They were part of the $2,800 profit this week. When T bottoms out later this month I will buy July calls because I think we will hit $40 before the next dividend. Any "followers" that sold their May calls this week made a pretty nice profit.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365194030049</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:33:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365194580388-33</Id><Topic><Title>Not too shabby.</Title><Username>themightyslug</Username><Timestamp>1365111628790</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 17:40:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like you have a great retirement and so do I. I don't think either one of us would last long in New York City.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365194580388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:43:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365195366854-34</Id><Title>Great prophet hits it again!</Title><Msg>Nice job Wilkes, you were slightly off on your prediction, what the heck, an extra 2 cents, nice!</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1365195366854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:56:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365195400677-35</Id><Topic><Title>White supremacists or White HATERS in TX?</Title><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1365193552982</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:25:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here are some of the Whites labeled as skinheads and White supremacists by the SPLC and ADL. The SPLC is part of the U.S. Govt - Dept. of HS. There are many other similar Whites who have been targeted and labeled as White supremacists. Merlin Miller graduated from the United States Military Academy at West Point, NY and served in the U.S. Army, where he commanded two units. Merlin later worked as an industrial engineering manager at Michelin Tire Co. He earned an MFA degree in Cinema/Television from the University of Southern California and worked at Paramount Pictures and later on low-budget features William D. Johnson, J.D., is an international corporate lawyer practicing in Los Angeles, CA. He holds both an undergraduate degree from Brigham Young University, where he majored in Japanese, and a law degree from Columbia University. Kevin B. MacDonald, Ph.D., is a professor of psychology at California State University, Long Beach. MacDonald is the author of seven books on evolutionary psychology and child development and is the author or editor of over thirty academic articles. James Edwards is best known as the creator and primary host of The Political Cesspool Radio Program, an award-winning broadcast Tom Sunic, Ph.D. is a former professor of political science, a scholar, a prolific writer and an accomplished linguist in Croatian, English, French and German. Dr. Virginia Abernethy is a professor emeritus of psychiatry and anthropology at Vanderbilt Medical School. Alexander Carmichal is a solo practicing attorney in the Metro New York area, specializing in civil litigation and constitutional issues.</Msg><Username>lavendarsen</Username><Timestamp>1365195400677</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:56:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365195503551-36</Id><Topic><Title>A Topic For AFTERHOURS (here)</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1365179248706</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>those that are looking for handouts are flocking to the polls and that is what the fool on the hill and his cohorts are delivering. Wait till 2014, then more in 2015. send money to Washington. someone used to post that was it easy frieds?</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1365195503551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:58:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365195642487-37</Id><Topic><Title>Hey; what's the matter with T today???</Title><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365004879967</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:01:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and by the way, are you an immediate gratification required investor? Pull back as healthy for the market. With t buying back shares and the upcoming divi having the usual impact on the divi chasers, look for a slight pull back next week. for a utility transforming this has been a good couple of years.</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1365195642487</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 17:00:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365196207250-38</Id><Title>With no jobs can t maintain?</Title><Msg>With the fool on the hill continuing to destroy the middle class by not creating jobs and continuing to replace a few jobs with much lower paying jobs he has succeeded in destroying the middle class. ricky you have to start paying for your stuff!!</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1365196207250</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 17:10:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365196523267-39</Id><Topic><Title>A Topic For AFTERHOURS (here)</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1365179248706</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Voter ID would do nothing to prevent duplicate registrations, or voting with duplicate registrations. States are doing the right thing to check their rolls for duplicates in the off-election years. The Republicans are out of the presidency for the foreseeable future. It has nothing to do with immigration or voter fraud or whatever excuse helps you sleep at night. It has everything to do with the Republican base being stubborn, ossified, old Tea Brains. Republicans will be competitive for the House for the next several cycles due to gerrymandering in the 2010 redistricting cycle but the Presidency and the Senate are out of reach for the foreseeable future. Or, to put it better, until you fools stop thinking President Obama was elected by some trick or fluke, you're going to continue to lose elections. Some Republicans have seen the writing on the wall and have decided to move in a new direction. Some Republicans have decided permanent opposition ain't so bad and have decided just to stonewall everything. And then there's the Tea Brains on the T message board who, if they saw the writing on the wall at all, prefer to have Rush read it to them.</Msg><Username>ricky18201</Username><Timestamp>1365196523267</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 17:15:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365197075851-40</Id><Topic><Title>A Topic For AFTERHOURS (here)</Title><Username>zonbac98</Username><Timestamp>1365179248706</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should listen to Rush more. You REALLY need the education.</Msg><Username>wilkes71</Username><Timestamp>1365197075851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 17:24:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365198318049-41</Id><Topic><Title>With no jobs can t maintain?</Title><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1365196207250</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 17:10:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zonbac, then ricky should vote for "O". poor widdle wicky can't support himself. ricky needs to step up and start to support others instead of taking from us.</Msg><Username>dan2003hr</Username><Timestamp>1365198318049</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 17:45:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365199030224-42</Id><Topic><Title>Optimistic news !</Title><Username>leeconnor743</Username><Timestamp>1365106294330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:11:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another con artist, this report costs 25 bucks and doesn't tell you anything. What a friggin rip off.</Msg><Username>tealcarver</Username><Timestamp>1365199030224</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 17:57:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365200622719-43</Id><Topic><Title>AT&amp;T Upgraded to STRONG BUY?</Title><Username>miguel.janis</Username><Timestamp>1364394934253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very nice report !</Msg><Username>mohr.eleanor</Username><Timestamp>1365200622719</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 18:23:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365201685335-44</Id><Topic><Title>Closed my ING high interest account</Title><Username>big_stock_pimp</Username><Timestamp>1237309253000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2009-03-17 13:00:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think buying T in March of 2009 was one of the best investments of my life, the stock is up over 70% from where I bought it and the dividend is still over 5%. Have a great weekend everybody!</Msg><Username>big_stock_pimp</Username><Timestamp>1365201685335</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 18:41:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>