<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347289968064-1</Id><Topic><Title>IBM CEO can Acquire RIMM from Chairwomen of the board of RIMM, IBM will regret this golden chance if does not happen</Title><Username>casbah45</Username><Timestamp>1347031981786</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this guy is still stuck with many shares of RIMM and cant get rid if them.</Msg><Username>zer0t0l</Username><Timestamp>1347289968064</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:12:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347293674500-2</Id><Title>Options Expert Anybody?</Title><Msg>What do you think is the opposite of the "covered write". Covered write: Buy a stock - Sell out of the money call. Brings some income. Now, I am short a stock..... Can somebody continue this thought?</Msg><Username>trader537</Username><Timestamp>1347293674500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347296484243-3</Id><Topic><Title>Polled polls 1400 people BIG DEAL</Title><Username>kdurryr7848484</Username><Timestamp>1347202608020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 10:56:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did they say which public housing project they ran the poll in?</Msg><Username>trader537</Username><Timestamp>1347296484243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:01:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347298439159-4</Id><Topic><Title>IBM CEO can Acquire RIMM from Chairwomen of the board of RIMM, IBM will regret this golden chance if does not happen</Title><Username>casbah45</Username><Timestamp>1347031981786</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would be much better for Lenovo group to buy Rimm than IBM. Then Lenovo could outsource the software, servers and the network to IBM global services and Lenovo could just sell the hand sets.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1347298439159</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:33:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347300610137-5</Id><Title>The Euro</Title><Msg>There were some concerns about the Euro affecting the EPS for IBM last quarter. The currency was sitting at multi-year lows last quarter, and it did have a slight negative impact in the IBM quarter. IBM still beat analysts estimates by a nice margin and actually raised guidance for 2012. This quarter the Euro has rebounded 25% off the lows. Will this have a positive impact for the October 16 EPS report? It is logical to assume that the rising Euro can only help this quarter's EPS report.</Msg><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1347300610137</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347300624655-6</Id><Title>How trading？</Title><Msg>Offer value Offer value Offer value what is it? In the past, no one has proposed this idea, but a lot of people in the application, but they will sell the value used in the wrong on the buy. Assessed to the company’s future cash flows, discount rates value, in fact, even at a substantial discount to buy, and still there is no margin of safety. because of the intangible assets of the enterprise in the majority of cases, very unstable, unable to provide investors with a true margin of safety. But offer value for selling a good reference. Following example: Respectively Firm A and B, the total share capital of 100 million shares of the enterprise, A company’s annual net profit of $ 5 million, an annual growth rate of 30% in the next 20 years, the price per share of U.S. $ 5 million, City win was 100 times. B corporate annual net profit was $ 30 billion, 5% in the next 20 years, the annual growth rate of 5%, the price per share of $ 3,000, the market win rate of 10 times So 20 years later, the enterprise’s net profit A $ 950 million, to 8.24 percent as the discount rate, the next 20 years, after a reasonable enterprise value ceiling of $ 11.5 billion, now valued at $ 2.306 billion, the enterprise value per share $ 23.06 20 years later, B Enterprises net profit of $ 79.5 billion, to 8.24 percent as the discount rate, the enterprises of the next 20 years after the reasonable price ceiling of $ 954 billion, the present value of $ 195.8 billion, the enterprise value per share $ 1958. When investors sell operations in A Company of the 100 times City win rate, sold obviously not rational. Room for improvement because there is a great value. B enterprises reached before 10 times City win rate, investors should take to sell the operation. The black spider Fund website</Msg><Username>fengjie583</Username><Timestamp>1347300624655</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347301654496-7</Id><Topic><Title>Polled polls 1400 people BIG DEAL</Title><Username>kdurryr7848484</Username><Timestamp>1347202608020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 10:56:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I found the movie "Obama's 2016" to be very interesting. It's worth seeing.</Msg><Username>yield_of_my_dreams</Username><Timestamp>1347301654496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:27:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347302477440-8</Id><Title>Are H Funds that are short market</Title><Msg>trying to cover with out getting exposed ? Why High flyers are now rising ? What give ?? We staring to feel that we see last min covering before something big !! Smart money closing books ?</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1347302477440</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:41:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347319540730-9</Id><Title>IBM going north of $225</Title><Msg>Buy any pull back.</Msg><Username>billonair49</Username><Timestamp>1347319540730</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347328815455-10</Id><Topic><Title>IBM going north of $225</Title><Username>billonair49</Username><Timestamp>1347319540730</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:25:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doubtful. It's got serious resistance between here and $203. Started buying puts on this today and will add on any strength in the coming days.</Msg><Username>ihopeigetluckyinvesting</Username><Timestamp>1347328815455</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:00:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>