<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-05"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346852079910-1</Id><Title>IBM Upgraded to “Overweight” at Barclays target $240</Title><Msg>hi there</Msg><Username>seafoodsnacks</Username><Timestamp>1346852079910</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346863975769-2</Id><Topic><Title>IBM Upgraded to “Overweight” at Barclays target $240</Title><Username>seafoodsnacks</Username><Timestamp>1346852079910</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gaining market share from HP and Dell. Great!</Msg><Username>win4ster</Username><Timestamp>1346863975769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:52:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346864535841-3</Id><Topic><Title>At age 18, Barack Obama admittedly arrived at Occidental College a committed revolutionary Marxist. What was the source of Obama's foundation in Marxism</Title><Username>kvknkr</Username><Timestamp>1346856511179</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:48:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know, you're not going to change anyone's mind by posting this kind of adolescent nonsense.</Msg><Username>codebuddy</Username><Timestamp>1346864535841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:02:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346865287210-4</Id><Topic><Title>IBM Upgraded to “Overweight” at Barclays target $240</Title><Username>seafoodsnacks</Username><Timestamp>1346852079910</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IBM Upgraded to “Overweight” at Barclays; Several Catalysts Seen Ahead (IBM) September 5th, 2012 I.T. giant International Business Machines Corp. (IBM) on Wednesday caught a big upgrade from analysts at Barclays Capital. The firm boosted its rating on IBM from “Equalweight” to “Overweight” while lifting its price target from $208 to $240. That new target suggests a 23% upside to the stock’s Tuesday closing price of $194.54. A Barclays analyst cited several reasons for the upgrade, including: A new mainframe cycle should help drive EPS upside, Market share gains resulting from outperforming struggling competitors like Hewlett-Packard (HPQ) and Dell (DELL), Higher-margin revenue streams in coming years because of the company’s analytics strategy, and Unlike many companies in its sector, IBM is relatively safe from disruption of its key business components by tech behemoth Apple (AAPL). Accordingly, Barclays also boosted its profit and revenue estimates for the company through 2014. IBM shares were mostly flat in premarket trading Wednesday. The Bottom Line Shares of IBM Corp (IBM) have a 1.75% dividend yield, based on last night’s closing stock price of $194.54. The stock has technical support in the $186-$188 price area. If the shares can firm up, we see overhead resistance around the $200-$201 price levels.</Msg><Username>seafoodsnacks</Username><Timestamp>1346865287210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:14:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346875695986-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to investigate Barney Frank and Chris Dodd</Title><Username>ncsu1979</Username><Timestamp>1344095377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I understand that Obama is going to announce the commencement of this investigation at the DNC in Charlotte tomorrow night. Part of his new and improved commitment to greater government transparency.</Msg><Username>thatgdgreenspan</Username><Timestamp>1346875695986</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346878614474-6</Id><Topic><Title>IBM starting to look like GE Message Board</Title><Username>retiredexaon</Username><Timestamp>1346765263265</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 09:27:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i wouldn't look at the GE board because i cannot stand GE (actually it's Jack Welsh and now his mini me ... destroying an American insitution ... but i do visit the BMY board because i like the company and own the stock , but that board has become useless ... a few cretins , calling for the fall of BMY and the rest is the political cesspool that you mention .... why can't these buffoons post and reply on an appropriate board ????? certainly a bit of political and economic discussion is germaine to any large corporation , but a few posts can cover that ... latter and good luck ... garce</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1346878614474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:56:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346899967993-7</Id><Topic><Title>IBM starting to look like GE Message Board</Title><Username>retiredexaon</Username><Timestamp>1346765263265</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 09:27:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yyyyawwwwn</Msg><Username>johngarcia8181</Username><Timestamp>1346899967993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:52:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>