<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354885482082-1</Id><Topic><Title>So IBM is going f... Employees to meet earnings per share</Title><Username>america_wants_change</Username><Timestamp>1354854184720</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 23:23:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>truly sad, and the end of an era for IBM (U.S. anyway). When shareholders become your top priority at the expense of your employees, it's only a matter of time before both will suffer.</Msg><Username>approval_myass</Username><Timestamp>1354885482082</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 08:04:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354885949770-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: The Dark Side of Special Dividends</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1354733723302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 13:55:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well, I do recall FAR higher tax rates as recently as 1992 (pre-Bush madness), and society was flourishing here in the U.S., and by 2000 we had a surplus. It was the 8 years of spending that followed without income that got us to where we are now, and those that don't see a need for sensible tax increases are beyond reason. (or greedy)</Msg><Username>approval_myass</Username><Timestamp>1354885949770</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 08:12:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354893393568-3</Id><Topic><Title>Major Upgrade for International Business Machines Corporation. Read Now!</Title><Username>louisferland339</Username><Timestamp>1354632990623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:56:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trusting.</Msg><Username>stanleysanchez83</Username><Timestamp>1354893393568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 10:16:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354893393948-4</Id><Topic><Title>Major Upgrade for International Business Machines Corporation. Read Now!</Title><Username>louisferland339</Username><Timestamp>1354632990623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:56:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trusting.</Msg><Username>stanleysanchez83</Username><Timestamp>1354893393948</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 10:16:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354899847683-5</Id><Title>IBM latest pension cut hits older employees hardest.....again.</Title><Msg>This latest cut in the pension hits the people who were hit just 4 years ago especially hard. IBM was putting money into the 401k to soften the cut to the defined plan for those few employees who are still eligible for it. Under the latest change, those employees now lose the entire year of investment income. It could not come at a worse time for them. This hits just as they reach retirement age or are planning retirement. Moving the retirement income target for those employees once again. When the people that brought you success start questioning why it is happening to them, IBM is in trouble. IBM is targeting the only people with legacy knowledge of the inner processes and any kind fo work ethic. It is scary to think that the people who make these decisions are either so insulated from what is being said on the ground floor of IBM or they don't care. Either way, it apperas that they are oblivious to the lower than whale s**t moral that is rampant at almost every level beneath VP.</Msg><Username>louscashcow</Username><Timestamp>1354899847683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 12:04:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354900575981-6</Id><Topic><Title>IBM latest pension cut hits older employees hardest.....again.</Title><Username>louscashcow</Username><Timestamp>1354899847683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 12:04:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"IBM is targeting the only people with legacy knowledge of the inner processes and any kind fo work ethic. " lol no.</Msg><Username>forjunk90</Username><Timestamp>1354900575981</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 12:16:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354901504149-7</Id><Topic><Title>IBM latest pension cut hits older employees hardest.....again.</Title><Username>louscashcow</Username><Timestamp>1354899847683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 12:04:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The development labs in the US are filled with people with 25+ years and that who is hit the hardest each time they cut. When they look back on the last 2 years, they will realize what a huge mistakes they are making. Time will tell.</Msg><Username>louscashcow</Username><Timestamp>1354901504149</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 12:31:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354902186460-8</Id><Topic><Title>Major Upgrade for International Business Machines Corporation. Read Now!</Title><Username>louisferland339</Username><Timestamp>1354632990623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 09:56:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who else is?</Msg><Username>antoniogreen12</Username><Timestamp>1354902186460</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 12:43:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354904863598-9</Id><Title>Seriously. Employees Should B</Title><Msg>Ticked. And All the funds invested in this CO should be TICKED as well. I fyou want to save a few bucks look in the executive suite.</Msg><Username>datadoescount</Username><Timestamp>1354904863598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 13:27:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354905822161-10</Id><Title>Some IBM bigwigs idea to screw fellow employees about 401-K</Title><Msg>Some IBM bigwigs idea to screw fellow employees about 401-K. I can see it now the big wig wants his big bonus while MESSING over their fellow employees while DEMANDING total dedication. I DON'T THINK SO!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>cross_catcher</Username><Timestamp>1354905822161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 13:43:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354906326012-11</Id><Title>FCX Squeeze to 34s</Title><Msg>load up gang</Msg><Username>jjohns8181</Username><Timestamp>1354906326012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 13:52:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354909148330-12</Id><Topic><Title>Deal will be made before Xmas to resolve the cliff</Title><Username>win4ster</Username><Timestamp>1354626683390</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 08:11:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is likely to change the requirement from $250k to $500k, if he makes this offer, a deal can be reached over the weekend.</Msg><Username>win4ster</Username><Timestamp>1354909148330</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 14:39:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354910733988-13</Id><Title>All employess should sell</Title><Msg>thier ibm stk they are holding in their 401Ks. That's what I would do if I worked there.</Msg><Username>divisgood</Username><Timestamp>1354910733988</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:05:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354912081018-14</Id><Title>Good Ole IBM. Better Believe Largest Layoffs will Always Happen Before Dec. 15th.</Title><Msg>Some brown nosing fast track wannabe derived this plan in the belly of Mount Doom while conspiring with satan himself. Bend over again faithful IBM'ers.</Msg><Username>octopus1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1354912081018</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:28:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354912205073-15</Id><Title>Hmm… leaving IBM is starting to seem more likely for me…</Title><Msg>This 401k idea has really made me think about whether to stay or move on. I am currently working on a project where I work 60 to 80 hours per week and only charging 40 hours because the project was sold with a super tight budget. I start at 4:00am in the morning to get the status report from the offshore teams due to the time difference. Then I work with the team and the client until 7:00pm or 8:00 pm. I leave work to have a fast food dinner after that I have to catch up with all administrative tasks IBM asks you do such as getting professional certifications that IBM requires to keep your job but they don’t provide any free training. It comes out of your own pocket. Before I go to bed at 11p, I have a quick conference call with the offshore team that is waking up to dicuss tasks they need to do before I wake up at 4am. Then I repeat this cycle all over again the next day. Sometimes on the weekends as well. Now, I have nothing against the offshore team. They are a great group of people. Their schedule sucks just as bad. They have to stay up until 2am for me. Not only that, they also work on multiple projects at that the same time. Now with reduced benefits, it really doesn't make any sense for me to ruin my health and personal life to keep benefits that are really worthless. I met this great lady who told woke me up to the craziness of working so hard that it negatively affects my health only to have company provided health insurance.</Msg><Username>putesputes</Username><Timestamp>1354912205073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:30:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354913813315-16</Id><Topic><Title>Some IBM bigwigs idea to screw fellow employees about 401-K</Title><Username>cross_catcher</Username><Timestamp>1354905822161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 13:43:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what a laugh riot .. the powers that be can get the populous to think in any manner that they so desire ... just how does this 401k thing apply to anyone ???? yes , IBM gets to retain $$$ for a few more months and allow it to work for them , like banks kiting checks ... this changes almost nothing for the employees .. yes , if you get let go prior to 12/15/any year ... you don't get the match , but what about someone hired on 12/1 or maybe 12/14 .. they get the match (on no dollars .. lol ) .. up until the vacation plan was rejiggered in the 90's .. the same thing applied .. get hired on 12/31 and start off with 2 weeks vacation .. get hired in March and receive 3 days .... in the long run , it evens out .. but if you are going to get all lathered up because you might lose a little bit of matching dollars (it would only be 1 year's worth at worst) then i feel sorry for you ... your vision should be a little borader and a little longer ..... NOT ONLY THAT .. just look at the posts who are blaming IBM mgmt for this awful thing .. consider those levels of mgmt who make these rules ... like the person who is making 200K + and pumping thier 401K .. they have a lot more lose with the new plan than anyone posting on this board .. it's nit ... get over and move on .....</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1354913813315</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:56:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354918813637-17</Id><Topic><Title>Hmm… leaving IBM is starting to seem more likely for me…</Title><Username>putesputes</Username><Timestamp>1354912205073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:30:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, we all did those things one time or another. I think you will be rewarded for your time. Believe me. IBM is a great company.</Msg><Username>ulutasd</Username><Timestamp>1354918813637</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 17:20:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354920240532-18</Id><Topic><Title>Hmm… leaving IBM is starting to seem more likely for me…</Title><Username>putesputes</Username><Timestamp>1354912205073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:30:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leave as fast as you can. IBM is a house of cards. They have been screwing their employees since 2001. This is just another brick in the wall. I left IBM a couple years ago and couldn't be happier. Making 140% of what I was making at IBM. Most companies won't tell you this but IBM global services is a joke in the business I have come across several instances of project failures on their part. Get out and be happy. No one deserves to not be paid for 20 to 30 hours of work a week.</Msg><Username>farboo1316</Username><Timestamp>1354920240532</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 17:44:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354920307850-19</Id><Topic><Title>Some IBM bigwigs idea to screw fellow employees about 401-K</Title><Username>cross_catcher</Username><Timestamp>1354905822161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 13:43:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The big wigs get a BIG BONUS on kicking down their fellow employees while DEMANDING total dedication. RED FLAG HERE for IBM. SELL!</Msg><Username>cross_catcher</Username><Timestamp>1354920307850</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 17:45:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354924585251-20</Id><Title>IBM 401K Debacle | Farce | Disaster | Fiasco | Calamity | Incompetence</Title><Msg>92,000 angry US employees, leading most of the company and most of the projects (with GRs)... but we're getting some good new acronyms at least. IBM stands for... Idiots Become Managers Indians Badly Managed Anyway, this is a direct #$%$" statement for US employees. How is IBM changing any retirement programs for the rest of the employees across the world... yes, that is the question... Post your new acronyms as responses to this post. Fight the power, but at least find the humor in it.</Msg><Username>washsale</Username><Timestamp>1354924585251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 18:56:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354925193847-21</Id><Topic><Title>IBM 401K Debacle | Farce | Disaster | Fiasco | Calamity | Incompetence</Title><Username>washsale</Username><Timestamp>1354924585251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 18:56:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It does seem like all the press releases and TV programs are focusing on employees leaving vs. getting laid off before Dec 15. Why is no one focusing on the fact that IBM schedules huge layoffs, and now they have more power to do it right before Dec 15 to save a buck? This is total #$%$.</Msg><Username>washsale</Username><Timestamp>1354925193847</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 19:06:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354925380839-22</Id><Topic><Title>Hmm… leaving IBM is starting to seem more likely for me…</Title><Username>putesputes</Username><Timestamp>1354912205073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:30:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Billing only 40 hours and providing 60-80 of work is actually illegal in the US. The US government should look into this. IBM is cooking the books on both sides of the ledger, and now they are screwing the employees directly too. What a great company. American business at its finest.</Msg><Username>washsale</Username><Timestamp>1354925380839</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 19:09:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354925908051-23</Id><Topic><Title>Hmm… leaving IBM is starting to seem more likely for me…</Title><Username>putesputes</Username><Timestamp>1354912205073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:30:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, you'll be rewarded with a heart attack or other medical problem and IBM will drop you like a stone.</Msg><Username>darthvadermentor</Username><Timestamp>1354925908051</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 19:18:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354932706490-24</Id><Topic><Title>Hmm… leaving IBM is starting to seem more likely for me…</Title><Username>putesputes</Username><Timestamp>1354912205073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:30:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This 401K idea is just the latest in benefit pullbacks. I think this one affects morale in the lower ranks across the company. The way it was announced was the oddest thing I've seen. Management has cut costs to the bone to where it is difficult just to get a pencil and notepad issued. Management's tunnel vision on the road-map needs to be adjusted. Where are the Watson type managers? No more freebies for the company.</Msg><Username>jayseenc</Username><Timestamp>1354932706490</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 21:11:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354940592753-25</Id><Topic><Title>Hmm… leaving IBM is starting to seem more likely for me…</Title><Username>putesputes</Username><Timestamp>1354912205073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:30:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are being used and probably the rest of your team. Billing 40 hours and using staff for 60 to 80 is a shell game. Your stress level has to be through the roof and I wound up in a hospital two years ago for that reason. Prep your departure, find something else first and GET OUT ASAP. Good luck to you. And to the shill a few posters down, no, IBM will not reward you.</Msg><Username>retiredexaon</Username><Timestamp>1354940592753</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 23:23:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354940637926-26</Id><Topic><Title>Hmm… leaving IBM is starting to seem more likely for me…</Title><Username>putesputes</Username><Timestamp>1354912205073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:30:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WAS a great company, when Watson ran it. Everybody else since then has been downhill for the emps, great for those shareholders though.</Msg><Username>retiredexaon</Username><Timestamp>1354940637926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 23:23:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>