<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-05"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349443395641-1</Id><Title>ST JOKE OF THE DAY : 7.8 EMINPOLYMENT hahahahahahahahaha,,, is the game rigged Mr. President</Title><Msg>do you believe this guy in the white-house, and these numbers /????????????????????????============== not-------me =====================</Msg><Username>flashywildwest</Username><Timestamp>1349443395641</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:23:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349443886366-2</Id><Topic><Title>How are the memories on this board</Title><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1349362241130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am sooo happy to hear from you again. I think the others posts also very good. I sleep well every night. Have a great day.</Msg><Username>ulutasd</Username><Timestamp>1349443886366</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:31:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349443977998-3</Id><Topic><Title>How are the memories on this board</Title><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1349362241130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>O only go back to the 407s.</Msg><Username>ulutasd</Username><Timestamp>1349443977998</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:32:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349452730231-4</Id><Topic><Title>How are the memories on this board</Title><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1349362241130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think about all the bozo's, present company excepted of course, all the bozo's who have come and gone over the years like dr fungcool, dellpickle, m.rowe56, and a string of other bad actors who have gone up in smoke over the years. The one common thread was the bitterness and crippling fetish about old Blue common to all now. Sadly, some who got smart and got out when Mr. Buffett was loading up in 2011 are no doubt still specter's lurking about, looking into Big Blue's progress. To the rest of you men (and members of Augusta) I say to you: Stay the Course!</Msg><Username>yield_of_my_dreams</Username><Timestamp>1349452730231</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 11:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349454015249-5</Id><Title>Under invested, performed Hedge Funds manipulating the market today</Title><Msg>Its very disturbing how they get away with it Very depressing They underestimated this country and people. First they shorted US in 2008 to death thinking that this country will never recover and now they watching recovery and getting angry at us</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1349454015249</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 12:20:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349458624297-6</Id><Topic><Title>IBM Earnings</Title><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1349203194082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fun fact.... It took IBM 12 years to buy back the 2 for 1 split in May 1999. They still need about 30 billion dollars to buy back the 114 milion remaining shares. As for the 2015 date IBM will do whatever is necessary to achieve that goal.. That will mean Layoffs. So If you here that IBM is "downsizing again" this will mean that they are not doing it in revenue but by getting rid of more workers. Just some fun facts.</Msg><Username>dailytrader512</Username><Timestamp>1349458624297</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 13:37:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349459250748-7</Id><Title>New all time high</Title><Msg>Wkth this new time high I hope that the stock does not split. The high price seems to be keeping day traders away and investors are taking charge. Evidence is the reduced daily volumn.</Msg><Username>bob787m</Username><Timestamp>1349459250748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 13:47:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349460021598-8</Id><Title>Chinese Facebook RENN RUMORS BELOW 3 to 4 bagger in OCT</Title><Msg>VERY easy and long overdue move bouncing off a manipulated price to begin with Options seem to be backing these rumors up. 1.Same exact market makers pushing around everyone else in renn just like they did in bidu pre explosion! 2.Same exact underwriters! 3.Same extreme manipulation, 28-4 after RENN IPO, they slammed bidu down 1st 2 years straight also 4. Same pattern of you go against these guys at all and you lose guaranteed! Now they are starting to go higher with RENN, soon they all pounce on prey at once! 5. Rumors, big names, and Billionaire chatter and competition between at least 3 parties regarding RENN 6. The richest man in the entire country of China on your board of directors does not hurt. 7. Lastly 3 rumors 1. Ken Fischer taking a possible 5 million share position 2. At a live dinner event, CEO CHEN and the richest man in China gave a toast and said they will not rest or be happy till RENN has a mnimum of a 100 billion dollar marketcap! 3. At a seperate event a caterer to the TRIAD CHINESE MAFIA said they will run RENN to at least 60 themselves! The fireworks are suppose to start in Oct with a triple or 4 times the stock price! Options have been being bought as if this will indeed happen! I have a broker at Raymond James I went to college with, he says something is up with RENN because much of the trading is being hidden, they appear to be either making it look like it is coming from many different places or the buys really are. I would get 100,000 shares if I could honestly</Msg><Username>namfong43</Username><Timestamp>1349460021598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 14:00:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349460146078-9</Id><Topic><Title>IBM Earnings</Title><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1349203194082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IBM will not be splitting the stock any time soon. IBM has 450,000 employees throughout the world. Nobody said they will be laying anyone off. The firm said $50 billion in buybacks and $20 billion in dividends. You bet they will make their stated goal.</Msg><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1349460146078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 14:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349465014502-10</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's very first act as president, makes him look like someone with something to hide, not the person that swore that if elected, his administration would be the most OPEN presidential administration ever, you decide!</Title><Username>first_act_yd</Username><Timestamp>1348929996224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:46:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure, keep the idiot/liar in the White House for another 4 years.</Msg><Username>joeyvt</Username><Timestamp>1349465014502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 15:23:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349465193645-11</Id><Topic><Title>Under invested, performed Hedge Funds manipulating the market today</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1349454015249</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 12:20:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They will bring market and stocks down to a level where they acan enter and finish strong for the year. The SEC will look the other way.</Msg><Username>ozzie232</Username><Timestamp>1349465193645</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 15:26:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>