<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-18"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353215208336-1</Id><Topic><Title>IMPEACH OBAMA</Title><Username>p1sorell</Username><Timestamp>1353092926172</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:08:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is the smartest president this country has seen so far. After all, he is cleaning up the mess the previous president left behind.</Msg><Username>cash_is_king_now</Username><Timestamp>1353215208336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 00:06:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353217851988-2</Id><Topic><Title>If the world wondered why Iran needs nukes, look at the brutal massacre taking place in Gaza.</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1353130866781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 00:41:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ clown!!!! .</Msg><Username>irvadelman</Username><Timestamp>1353217851988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 00:50:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353257396004-3</Id><Topic><Title>IMPEACH OBAMA</Title><Username>p1sorell</Username><Timestamp>1353092926172</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:08:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>None of the above. He is making things worse and refuses to investigate two of his own, Democrats Barney Frank and Chris Dodd, who were running Freddie and Fannie and who encouraged banks and lending institutions to lend to the uncreditworthy. Don't be a simpleton. Know the facts. Bush tried several times to reign those two knuckleheads in but loudmouth Frank would have it no other way. Frank is the person most responsible for the mess we're in.</Msg><Username>thatgdgreenspan</Username><Timestamp>1353257396004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 11:49:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353272603924-4</Id><Topic><Title>IMPEACH OBAMA</Title><Username>p1sorell</Username><Timestamp>1353092926172</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:08:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who care if the news is heard this way or another because it does not change what was happened in Libya. However, when GOP change the facts to attack Iraq, that was serious. If American follow GOP strategy then this country was poorer than Bangladesh while a few rich flee to other countries.</Msg><Username>cash_is_king_now</Username><Timestamp>1353272603924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 16:03:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353273096188-5</Id><Title>Bottom line, GOP lost big and it will lose more when it acts badly this way</Title><Msg>Romney and most of GOP have their heads in the sand and ignoring the most basic facts.</Msg><Username>cash_is_king_now</Username><Timestamp>1353273096188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 16:11:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353273727133-6</Id><Title>IBM has bought over 300 million shares since 2007</Title><Msg>IBM continues to buyback shares 50 to 80 million shares per year. This is a huge advantage for new investors. While most or even all large caps like MSFt adding shares, IBM constantly reduces the number of its shares. There are 2 points: 1- IBM has confidence in its technology and progress. 2- IBM returns money to investors in a huge way and they may see their money doubled or tripled in coming years.</Msg><Username>cash_is_king_now</Username><Timestamp>1353273727133</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 16:22:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353274853626-7</Id><Topic><Title>See it at $220 in a few months</Title><Username>help4all1332</Username><Timestamp>1353099304678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:55:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you're right on, February or March. And heck yeah now is a great time to jump in or hold what you have.</Msg><Username>dino2hootie</Username><Timestamp>1353274853626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 16:40:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353280991906-8</Id><Title>My Bet -- We GO Over the Cliff &amp; Senate Democrats Pass a Bill Changing Provisions of Sequester Cuts</Title><Msg>They can amend it if they can't get enough Republicans to cross over and vote for it. The proposed legislation will cut taxes below $250k -- probably not back to the old Qualified Dividend &amp; Cap gains rates -- maybe progressively lower as you go down the taxable income ladder. The Republicans will hate it but if they are voting on a tax cut it will probably get passed -- it may well restore some of the cuts to Defense and probably raise the debt ceiling by a big amount. Obama is holding the cards. I think we are looking at slowing international demand based on numerous Q3 reports from the likes of 3M, DOW &amp; DuPont. The tax hikes won't help here. The US has been in recovery for a long time with the Fed as accommodative as possible. I think we could see a slowdown here in Q1, some layoffs and anemic employment reports. There could be a lot of selling before YE.</Msg><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1353280991906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 18:23:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353287404380-9</Id><Title>IBM is looking at the big picture</Title><Msg>IBM sold its PC division in 2005. It knew that most hardware companies like DELL, HPQ and INTC will see the hardship and business loss in future. However, this is just the beginning of losses for hardware companies and there will get much h worse. AAPL is not immune and it will join DELL and HPQ soon. One main reason for IBM change of strategy is the nanotube technology. IBM is developing the technology that can reduce the chip size by factor of 10 or more while INTC, ARM and other companies already reached to a point that can not reduce the chip size anymore. No wonder that IBM has switched to software while developing a new technology for hardware. This will revolutionize the hardware, the same effect when the technology changed from tube to transistor. As an investor, one should put money in this kind of technology, something that can not be copied easily. AAPL did well for a while but AAPL technology was not something that is hard to copy. That is why AAPL may drop much more while IBM will rise steady and firmly in near and far future.</Msg><Username>veqasfletch2001</Username><Timestamp>1353287404380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 20:10:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353288855062-10</Id><Topic><Title>My Bet -- We GO Over the Cliff &amp; Senate Democrats Pass a Bill Changing Provisions of Sequester Cuts</Title><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1353280991906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 18:23:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Semiconductor companies are trading at prices very close to early 2009. Other sectors are not that far while the economy is not as weak as 2009. Can we say that fiscal cliff is already priced in? Fiscal cliff is something that media has created since one way or another, there will some agreements between two parties. Now, hedge funds that have been behind the curve are purring gasoline on the fire to bring the stocks down so they can get the chip shares. Even if taxes go up by a few percent then investors don't want to pass profits. They may sell but they also buyback. The small cap may not cover soon but big cap and the company with good record like IBM will be in demand. The big guys are after companies like IBM and CAT and they see this as the best opportunity to grab the shares cheap. IBM is also buying back its shares at these cheap prices. No wonder the smart ones like Buffets have loaded and probably are loading now while there is opportunity to buy those 10% or more below fair value.</Msg><Username>veqasfletch2001</Username><Timestamp>1353288855062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 20:34:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>