<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349184436239-1</Id><Topic><Title>Will IBM jump on the Bernanke "Free Unlimited Crack for TBTF Banks" market with OCN assets buy?</Title><Username>jjjinglehimersmith</Username><Timestamp>1349147902021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 23:18:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Jumping on the Bernanke Bandwagon. Tax-avoiding growth has peaked. No growth remaining without Bernack's windfall free money for his finance owners." It's and old story. You try to be in the right investments for the future, and that means flowing in the direction of market forces. IBM recently issued 10 year debt for par at 1.875%. IBM can't load up on debt but it can add and replace maturing notes &amp; bonds with cheap money that will benefit EPS for years. When IBM invests new money in capital assets, including acquisitions, IBM's Return on Invested Capital (ROIC) is north of 25%. In addition, IBM's alternative use for cash flow, share buybacks, have called in about 1/3 of the stock since 2002. The perpetual investment dollars traded for IBM stock are up in the ROIC range as well -- like the $18.8 bil invested in IBM buybacks in 2007 at about $106. Strong multinationals with pricing power should be able to absorb currency fluctuations. I'd have a chunk in domestic heavy debtors like T &amp; VZ who also have pricing power -- a Federal Judge blocked the current FCC from regulating wireless under the old wire line regs. Holding paper currency on the sidelines looks like a strategy that will cost the holder purchasing power. Commodities, real estate REITS, or high quality stocks like IBM, T, VZ and a string of others who increase productivity giving them pricing power looks more attractive now than bonds, especially high yield bonds, and debt like callable preferred stock. The US and Europe are going to dilute paper currency to circulate more of it to fend off deflation. That why they call Bernanke "Helicopter Ben" because he said in a speech a long time ago that if he were faced with deflation he would drop money on the USA from helicopter's. Go with the flow -- but watch very carefully.</Msg><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1349184436239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 09:27:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349189395095-2</Id><Topic><Title>Buy $182</Title><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1338496083000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-05-31 16:28:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sorry to inform you that day traders have an annual income of around 14K USD. You are like a smack addict in that you are foreced to "chase the dragon".</Msg><Username>lucenatraveler</Username><Timestamp>1349189395095</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 10:49:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349191966409-3</Id><Topic><Title>Buy $182</Title><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1338496083000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-05-31 16:28:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are not paying attention...</Msg><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1349191966409</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 11:32:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349192533915-4</Id><Title>Time to start buying soon the market</Title><Msg>HFT just went crazy!!!!They punching retail in the stomach</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1349192533915</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 11:42:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349201645657-5</Id><Topic><Title>It is about time for IBM to announce a 3 for 1 STOCK SPLIT !</Title><Username>fstephens</Username><Timestamp>1349105213837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't let the price be your indicator. IBM will split its stock 2 for 1 when the number of shares outstanding hits 1.1 billion. They have about 1.13 billion shares outstanding now so at the present course and speed of their share buyback problem i would say you can expect an announcement at the April BoD meeting and subsequent shareholder meeting. Two tens for a twenty but perhaps more affordable for more investors.</Msg><Username>ned_digger</Username><Timestamp>1349201645657</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:14:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349203194082-6</Id><Title>IBM Earnings</Title><Msg>IBM has delivered double digit earnings growth for more than a decade. That is a nice track record for Big Blue. In 2010, IBM generated $11.67 in earnings. In 2011, IBM generated $13.44 in earnings, and that is a 15% YOY earnings growth. IBM has guided the street to about $15.10 for fiscal 2012. However, the 15% earnings growth which they achieved last year, would mean IBM reports earnings of $15.45 for this fiscal year. If you look at their road map it is quite possible they reach this number. IBM is ahead of schedule in delivering their $20 of earnings by 2015. They plan on returning value to shareholders in the way of $50 billion share repurchase and $20 billion in dividends. It is no wonder why Warren Buffett bought into Big Blue.</Msg><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1349203194082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:39:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349203487067-7</Id><Topic><Title>IBM Earnings</Title><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1349203194082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hello</Msg><Username>lvchgo5</Username><Timestamp>1349203487067</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349203932432-8</Id><Title>We doing a study how Hedge Funds fallow Id names</Title><Msg>How they jump and short stocks that people post on message boards this is why we always wait to short or go long because we know that the attack will come with in seconds from angry hedge funds. Well I have message for you !!!!!Fk you!!!!!!!!!!!! you guys think you smarter then the world ?? LOL!!!!</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1349203932432</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:52:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349219589115-9</Id><Topic><Title>Ninty Six Year High Today</Title><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1349101317593</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 10:21:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I knew the company when they sold scales.</Msg><Username>zer0t0l</Username><Timestamp>1349219589115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 19:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349219798164-10</Id><Topic><Title>It is about time for IBM to announce a 3 for 1 STOCK SPLIT !</Title><Username>fstephens</Username><Timestamp>1349105213837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thats right. If it splits two for one, then I can buy two shares instead of my usual purchase of one share.</Msg><Username>zer0t0l</Username><Timestamp>1349219798164</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 19:16:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349227816433-11</Id><Topic><Title>Ninty Six Year High Today</Title><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1349101317593</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 10:21:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When the big boys statr pumping it's time to take profits and get out of the way, then buy back in much cheaper for the next run to new highs.</Msg><Username>pmaly1</Username><Timestamp>1349227816433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 21:30:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349228434457-12</Id><Topic><Title>Buy $182</Title><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1338496083000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-05-31 16:28:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This last run is exhausted. The big boys are pumping and taking profits. Time to do the same and get back in low 200s. The market has made substantial gains in the past 6 weeks on low volumne. The upward movement can not be sustained without consolidation. Currently commiting new $ at $210.79 would be foolish and not the best entry point.</Msg><Username>pmaly1</Username><Timestamp>1349228434457</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 21:40:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349228575944-13</Id><Topic><Title>Breakout Soon?</Title><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1349060440194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:00:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You will be able to get in much lower then $210.79.</Msg><Username>pmaly1</Username><Timestamp>1349228575944</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 21:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>