<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-29"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348920411554-1</Id><Topic><Title>Three Weeks Tight</Title><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1348587840707</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:44:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How To Spot A Fine Chart: Savvy investors know there's no such thing as a sure winner. But they boost their chances of success by looking for stocks in proper bases that show tight price action. Weekly closing prices that vary 1% to 2% from the prior week in a period lasting a of couple weeks or more indicate that the stock may be getting ready to break out. The logic goes as follows: Tight trading over a period of time is a sign that the stock is being supported by institutional investors — banks, mutual funds, pension funds and so on. These funds typically buy shares over time, rather than all at once, to avoid running up the share price and to keep a low profile. As interest in the stock builds, the "supply" of shares that investors are eager to sell dwindles. As demand strengthens, the price rises. So it pays to figure out where the big funds are putting their money. Sustained institutional demand typically shows up in patterns marked by low volatility. These include flat bases, handles in cup bases and three-weeks-tight patterns, in which one week's closing price is within 1% to 1.5% of the prior week's close. In addition, the stock's intraday or weekly trading range may narrow and volume will be subdued, indicating high investor conviction as the stock builds its base.</Msg><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1348920411554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:06:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348929996224-2</Id><Title>Obama's very first act as president, makes him look like someone with something to hide, not the person that swore that if elected, his administration would be the most OPEN presidential administration ever, you decide!</Title><Msg>Obama's very first act as president, makes him look like someone with something to hide, not the person that swore that if elected, his administration would be the most OPEN presidential administration ever, you decide! Obama's very first act as president was: To unequivocally SEAL EVERY RECORD ABOUT HIS PAST, from his birth, to schools he attended, to residences addresses he lived at, to colleges he attended, to grades he received, to degrees he received, to jobs he held, to affiliations in the Chicago area, to his political affiliations, yes Obama SEALED his entire past, as his very first act as president! Along with sealing his total past, Obama made it a 100% Firing Offense, for any government employee to dig into any record from his past! And the cover-ups continue, with Obama's administration being the most secret administration ever, dam shame that his perpetual lies &amp; #$%$. convince many of the folks out there to give him a second chance for another four years... to destroy the Good Old U.S.A! One of Obama's latest is to give the new Muslim Brotherhood, that took over the Egyptian Government, $1 Billion In Aid That Obama Pledged to them, shortly after they gained control of the Egyptian Government! A short list of Obama Pledges, Prior to his election as President: 1) I will cut the Budget deficit in half in four years... ~ Result ~ Obama has added nearly $ 4 Trillion in New Debt, Yes, More Debt added in 4 Years than the First 41 Presidents Of the U.S.A. added, &amp; yes, all piled on future generations... 2) I will make it easier to grow jobs... ~ Result ~ The Obama administration has implemented 2,000 NEW REGULATIONS that U.S. Industry must deal with, while world wide businesses coast onward, without such massive constraints on their operations, significantly reducing their ability to compete worldwide! 3) I will protect the environment... ~ Result ~ In the past 4 years, the Obama Administration has Closed or converted to natural gas 83 U.S. Coal Fired Power Plants, cutting thousands of jobs, raising the cost of Electricity &amp; placing Millions of U.S. citizens in danger of electricity shortages in the near future... ~ Meanwhile, China Continues its relentless march onward, Opening ONE NEW COAL FIRED Power PLANT Each &amp; EVERY WEEK, For the past two years, Yes in China alone... ~ Ask, how can U.S. Industry Compete, answer they ABSOLUTELY CANNOT, resulting in strangulation on U.S. growth &amp; employment! 4) I will work to make the U.S. Energy Independent... ~ Vetoed the Keystone Pipeline From Canada, which would bring in Millions of Barrels of cheap Canadian Oil... ~ Refused to open &amp; issue permits for U.S. Coastal Oil drilling, while Foreign Oil Companies encroach the U.S. Coastline, drilling away... ~ Placed massive restrictions on Mining &amp; Use of Coal in the U.S.A., directing the Closure or conversion to natural gas of 83 U.S. Coal Fired Power Plants, cutting thousands of jobs, raising the cost of Electricity &amp; placing Millions of U.S. citizens in danger of electricity shortages in the near future... ~ Funded a Billion $ for Renewable Energy, much of which has gone Bankrupt in the past several years... 5) I will implement stimulus programs, that will control unemployment to 8%... ~ Reported unemployment continues way above 8%, with unreported unemployment reported to be as high as 19%... 6) Added Two Million Federal Employees to the U.S. payroll, to over regulate U.S. Businesses &amp; Citizens, all these NEW JOBS contributing ZERO Productivity to the U.S. economy, but adding to the mounting $ deficit... 6) Forced Obama Care Through, consisting of some 2,000 pages of which No Democrat that Voted for it, ever read it in it's entirety... Obama Care if not repealed, will Bankrupt The U.S.A. within several years of it's full enactment... 7) 45 Million U.S. Citizens on Food Stamps, documents the failure of the Obama administration to help the poor in the U.S.A., despite the massive Billions of $$$ being spent on social programs. Only significant job growth can resolve the U.S.'s economic problems &amp; Obama cannot comprehend! 8) Look at Obama's background... Look at Obama's past &amp; current associates... Look at Obama's accomplishments to date??? Now, you decide just what Obama has accomplished in his 4 year term &amp; just what was he attempting to hide with his very First ACT As President? Then Get Out &amp; Vote Obama OUT!!!</Msg><Username>first_act_yd</Username><Timestamp>1348929996224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348953574870-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's very first act as president, makes him look like someone with something to hide, not the person that swore that if elected, his administration would be the most OPEN presidential administration ever, you decide!</Title><Username>first_act_yd</Username><Timestamp>1348929996224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:46:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please everybody vote Obama out and save our country.</Msg><Username>thruston</Username><Timestamp>1348953574870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 17:19:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348968863662-4</Id><Title>Earnings Date?</Title><Msg>Have they set date? I see Yahoo says the 16th. but they are not always right. TIA</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1348968863662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:34:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>