<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-21"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350795444606-1</Id><Topic><Title>Why this is bottom price</Title><Username>cash_is_king_now</Username><Timestamp>1350774638814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Out of 25 analysts, one crazy one lowered to hold. Most analysts were bullish. IBM income was better by one penny. Hardware drown since customers are waiting for new hardware in Q4. IBM will be $ 210 in a short time.</Msg><Username>zapmaster_the_kinq</Username><Timestamp>1350795444606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 00:57:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350817765590-2</Id><Topic><Title>I'm on the sidelines</Title><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1350676065453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:47:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A Romney or Obama victory will not move the markets much either way. Are you reading too much into the political aspect of the markets?" I'm concerned about a worldwide slowdown. In the US, as of 1/1/13 the Bush Tax cuts will expire and Obamacare will begin to be implemented and that won't change if Romney is elected -- the Senate will probably stay Democrat. It looks like the US could print another negative GDP number for an upcoming quarter as the recovery of 2010 is clearly trending down even while the Fed buys T Bonds and mortgage backed securities like there is no tomorrow. I believe that as far as GDP goes 2008 was about (.4%), 2009 was (3.5%), 2010 was 3%, and 2011 - 1.7% I believe an Obama win will prompt a knee-jerk reaction in the form of a stock sell-off in the US. We could also see a prolonged period of sluggish capital investments in the US. We may also see further bail out cash transfers from the Fed gov't to states dry up which will mean more municipal bk's and that could hurt USA investor confidence. Given the backdrop, I'm worried generally and when IBM started to sink after saying deals were deferred I decided to go to cash to try and avoid a slide of my capital account. I sold IBM shares in 2008, then I started accumulating and bought all my shares back in 2009 but I have gone to cash twice since then so I've already paid the tax. I'll be back in IBM for the long term but buy &amp; hold is not something I'm going to be caught doing if we're drifting into another world recession. United States GDP 2008 -(0.4) 2009 -(3.5) 2010 - 3.0 2011 - 1.7</Msg><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1350817765590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 07:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350827554313-3</Id><Topic><Title>Latest Methods Of Trading International Bus ...</Title><Username>gwendolynmcneil282</Username><Timestamp>1350738713662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 09:11:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAM SITE MALWARE ALERT</Msg><Username>rr4ever</Username><Timestamp>1350827554313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 09:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350830911603-4</Id><Title>Check out the new film: 'HONEY I SHRUNK THE OBAMA CAMPAIGN'</Title><Msg>Check out the new film: 'HONEY I SHRUNK THE OBAMA CAMPAIGN' Starring David "Shapeshifter" Axlrod, Stephanie "Bomb-thrower" Cutter, Hillary "The Fall-guy" Clinton, Jabba the Wasserman-Schultz along with Nancy Pill-popping Pelosi and Dirty Harry Reid</Msg><Username>demedici</Username><Timestamp>1350830911603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 10:48:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350842809060-5</Id><Topic><Title>$183.60 is the critical bottom.</Title><Username>cmegladon</Username><Timestamp>1350587262557</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 15:07:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Friday was either a form of market capitulation or the beginning of another round of volatility with extreme downside bias. Interestingly, techs are leading this down. Pne side says Benny and the jets won't allow. Anything to interfere with the wealth effect. But wll find next wek. Gl all.</Msg><Username>cmegladon</Username><Timestamp>1350842809060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 14:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350850568675-6</Id><Title>If oboma wins</Title><Msg>IBM can take away all IBM health benifits and make all employes pay fot it themselves or else employes will get a fine for not haveing insurance. Be careful who you vote for</Msg><Username>onbell2004</Username><Timestamp>1350850568675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 16:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350852306303-7</Id><Topic><Title>If oboma wins</Title><Username>onbell2004</Username><Timestamp>1350850568675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 16:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who you trying to scare? If Obama wins, IBM will continue health benefits in order to attract good employees. Costs of those benefits will go DOWN in the long run, as insurance companies will have to keep costs down or give rebates. If Obama wins, America wins.l</Msg><Username>newly_retired</Username><Timestamp>1350852306303</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 16:45:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350852455939-8</Id><Topic><Title>If oboma wins</Title><Username>onbell2004</Username><Timestamp>1350850568675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 16:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If oboma wins IBM will have huge layoffs</Msg><Username>onbell2004</Username><Timestamp>1350852455939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 16:47:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350852664712-9</Id><Topic><Title>A Serious View on IBM</Title><Username>francisfrancis63</Username><Timestamp>1350650259992</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Sees Middle Class Tax Increase as a Victory read this and vote for Obama if you like it. –Obamacare law contains 20 new or higher taxes on American families and small businesses– The Largest Tax Hike in US History has just been upheld by the Supreme Court of the United States and President Obama sees this assault on the middle class as a victory. The already unpopular 2010 health care reform law has been converted by the court into a $1.76 trillion tax increase funded by escalating taxes to be paid the vast majority of taxpayers. The high court’s ruling leaves in place 20 tax increases in the health-care law, of those, 12 tax hikes would affect families earning less than $250,000 per year, including a “Cadillac tax” on high-cost insurance plans, a tax on insurance providers, and an excise tax on medical device manufacturers. By formally converting ‘Obamacare’ into ‘Obamatax,’ the court allows Obama to raise taxes on the middle-class. The decision is a distressing blow to taxpayers and represents the single largest tax increase on young people in the nation’s history. When it takes full effect, the Internal Revenue Service will have immense new power and authority to persecute and prosecute a whole new group of taxpayers. If the law takes full effect, it will devastate small businesses and destroy any chance for a sustainable economic recovery. It will add trillions of dollars to the national debt and push the country toward bankruptcy even faster than current projections. Any individual who believes that this decision must be overturned must do everything possible to undo the damage that has been done, especially at the ballot box on November 6.</Msg><Username>obama_tax_secrets</Username><Timestamp>1350852664712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 16:51:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350859098890-10</Id><Topic><Title>A Serious View on IBM</Title><Username>francisfrancis63</Username><Timestamp>1350650259992</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First, political junkies should not post here. Second, IBM is the most secure stock in the market, better than toy maker AAPl and better than GOOG, MSFt, ORCL, CSCO and others. In addition, IBM has a lot of room to increase its margin since it has a high revenue and it is 82% software.</Msg><Username>zapmaster_the_kinq</Username><Timestamp>1350859098890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:38:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350860637197-11</Id><Title>IBM did not miss the income</Title><Msg>IBM was little low on revenue but income was ok. The low for revenue was mostly from hardware where customers were waiting for new ones. Currency exchange was another reason. So, IBM is ok and does not deserve this kind of punishment. IBM is on track for income of $20 per share by 2015.</Msg><Username>zapmaster_the_kinq</Username><Timestamp>1350860637197</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 19:03:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350860784624-12</Id><Title>$20 per share for IBM</Title><Msg>This is analysts target.</Msg><Username>zapmaster_the_kinq</Username><Timestamp>1350860784624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 19:06:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350864202914-13</Id><Title>Insider</Title><Msg>"Inside Bain's Chinese Sensata Factories, Where Workers Put in 12-Hour Days for $.99 - $1.35 an Hour. Bain didn't build that new factory -- the Chinese Government Did October 20, 2012 | Mitt romney has made Obama's out-of-context “you didn't build that” quote a central theme of his campaign. It's ironic, as Mitt Romney is going to profit just before the election when Bain-owned Sensata Technologies moves 170 high-tech jobs from Freeport, Illinois, to a plant in China built for the firm by the Chinese government. Sensata enjoyed record revenues last year – this isn't about making the “hard choices” necessary to save a failing enterprise. The workers in Freeport have been working 24 hours a day, in three shifts. They make $14-17 per hour, with benefits. According to a report by the Institute for Global Labour and Human Rights, one of Bain's first actions after buying Sensata was to set up “12 Sensata/Bain capital funds 'organized under the laws of the Cayman Islands' so as to avoid paying taxes.” They'll get a small tax break for relocating the plant – the one Mitt Romney insisted did not exist during the first debate – and then use those offshore funds to defer taxes on some of the income the company generates. American tax-payers, on the other hand, have paid $780,000 to retrain some of Sensata's laid off workers in Illinois, according to the New York Times . One would be hard pressed to come up with a clearer example of capturing private gains while socializing the costs. Mitt Romney is not directly involved in Bain Capital, but he did build its business model. In 1998, when he was actively running Bain, he personally visited the Global-Tech Appliances plant in Dongguan, China. He witnessed, personally, the horrific conditions the plant's workers were toiling in for .24 cents an hour, and didn't hesitate to invest millions in the firm." -Alternet dot org. "Romney's Bain Capital Is Sending a Bunch of High-Tech Jobs to China on the Day Before the Election. The story of Sensata Technologies is about the hollowing out of America's economy by a rapacious 1 percent. October 16, 2012 | On the day before an election that's supposed to hinge on jobs, taxes and the middle class, Bain Capital, the company Mitt Romney founded, will close the doors of a factory in Freeport, Illinois, and ship 170 good, high-tech jobs to China. The employees of Sensata Technologies were forced to train their Chinese replacements, and the American flag that long flew over the factory was reportedly removed while the Chinese engineers were visiting the site. A group of workers have set up camp across from the factory -- calling it “Bainport” -- and some supporters have tried to block the trucks hauling equipment out of the plant. According to Dave Johnson , there have been several arrests. Sensata workers have asked to meet with Mitt Romney and hoped to enlist his help keeping their jobs in the United States, but he has refused, instead remaining on the campaign trail where he speaks often about “getting tough” with China. The most important part of the story is that Sensata Technologies is profitable operating in Illinois. Net income last year was $355 million, up 16 percent from 2010. The company reported total revenues of $1.8 billion in 2011, up almost 19 percent from the year before. According to a company financial statement , “both 2011 net revenue and adjusted net income represent record levels for the company.” So this has nothing to do with “making hard choices” in the process of turning around a failing business, which is how the Romney campaign describes Bain's corporate raiding. Bain's partners are looking for a modest boost in profits by locating the plant closer to the booming Asian automotive market (Sensata makes high-tech automotive parts). They'll get a small tax break for relocating the plant – the one Mitt Romney insisted did not exist during the first debate – and possibly defer taxes on some of the income the company generates. It takes both capital and labor to make a successful business like Sensata Technologies. In order to make a few more bucks, 170 of the people who helped make the company thrive will be cast aside like so much trash. The layoffs will surely have a ripple-effect in Freeport – a town of 25,000 with a declining population and a poverty rate well above the national average. The move is the epitome of corporate America's lack of patriotism – it's capital unmoored from any sense of responsibility for the people that make the profits or the communities where they live. The city passed a resolution Monday asking Romney to intervene. But the Sensata story has, so far, had little impact on the presidential race, mostly because Mitt Romney has no direct involvement in the operations of the company he established (despite continuing to make millions as a “passive retired partner”). But this is reading the story of Bain Capital too narrowly. Mitt Romney is directly responsible for its business model. As Tom Gaulrapp -- a lifelong resident of Freeport and 33-year employee of Sensata – told the Huffington Post's Amanda Terkel, “They're still using his business model. He's the one who taught them how to do this. These guys were put there by him. So you can say he doesn't run the day-to-day operations, but he's still at blame for the way they do business." Mitt Romney started the firm, and built it up on a strategy of buying firms with little money down, loading them with debt, raiding their pension funds and breaking their unions and then “harvesting them” – in his words – for a profit. Romney is the only person to ever serve as Bain's CEO – since his departure, the firm has been run by a managing committee. The story is bigger than Sensata, and bigger than Bain. The issue is the turn America's corporate culture has taken, and what the consequences of its model are for our economy and, indeed, our society. And it is Mitt Romney's embrace of that model – ravage capitalism that is loyal to no nation-state and blind to every human virtue but profit – that should be disqualifying. In the New York Times , Chrystia Freeland, author of “Plutocrats: The Rise of the New Global Super-Rich and the Fall of Everyone Else,” wrote about the historical tendency of elites to self-destruct by extracting wealth from the broader community to such a degree that the society becomes dysfunctional and mired by social problems. She recalls how the Venetians became the most prosperous society in the world during the 14th century by opening their economy to a broad swath of the population. Then, at the height of its golden age, “the upper class acted to lock in its privileges, putting a formal stop to social mobility with the publication of the Libro d’Oro, or Book of Gold, an official register of the nobility. If you weren’t on it, you couldn’t join the ruling oligarchy.” She then notes parallels to the United States, which featured one of the most egalitarian economies through much of the last century, but is now plagued by rising inequality and decreasing economic mobility. She writes: The 1 percent cannot evade its share of responsibility for the growing gulf in American society. Economic forces may be behind the rising inequality, but as Peter R. Orszag, President Obama’s former budget chief, told me, public policy has exacerbated rather than mitigated these trends. Even as the winner-take-all economy has enriched those at the very top, their tax burden has lightened. Tolerance for high executive compensation has increased, even as the legal powers of unions have been weakened and an intellectual case against them has been relentlessly advanced by plutocrat-financed think tanks. In the 1950s, the marginal income tax rate for those at the top of the distribution soared above 90 percent, a figure that today makes even Democrats flinch. Meanwhile, of the 400 richest taxpayers in 2009, 6 paid no federal income tax at all, and 27 paid 10 percent or less. None paid more than 35 percent... Educational attainment, which created the American middle class, is no longer rising. The super-elite lavishes unlimited resources on its children, while public schools are starved of funding. This is the new [Venice]. An elite education is increasingly available only to those already at the top. Bill Clinton and Barack Obama enrolled their daughters in an exclusive private school; I’ve done the same with mine. Much of this is the result of the 30-year assault on organized labor. It's worth noting that Sensata Technologies is a non-union shop, which is a big reason the firm can move profitable operations abroad without much resistance. Employment, in raw jobs numbers, should not be the defining issue of this election viewed in isolation. We also need to consider what kinds of jobs are being created. A recent study conducted by the National Employment Law Project (NELP) found that while only 21 percent of the jobs lost during the recession were low-paying (with median hourly wages from $7.69 to $13.83), a majority of those created during the recovery – 58 percent – have come with such low wages. These trends are not Mitt Romney's doing, but he is the walking, talking personification of what's been happening in the American economy. Mitt Romney was an innovator in offshoring. He and his family will make a few more dollars as a result of shipping those jobs to China, at the expense of the workers who “built that” in the first place. That's why the story of Sensata Technologies should have an impact in this race. -Endquote. -Alternet dot org</Msg><Username>sunnsailor</Username><Timestamp>1350864202914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 20:03:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350877688077-14</Id><Title>two words "Fiscal Cliff"</Title><Msg>timing is key, and beating the big players, make your move before them</Msg><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1350877688077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 23:48:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350877768525-15</Id><Topic><Title>$183.60 is the critical bottom.</Title><Username>cmegladon</Username><Timestamp>1350587262557</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 15:07:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no correction yet, just playing with markets, to propel it at EOY, but the real correction will be to make the next ADMIN suffer and they will definitely suffer, along with all of us</Msg><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1350877768525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 23:49:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>