<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344089159000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Today's Jobs Report</Title><Username>dopytrader</Username><Timestamp>1343995944000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 08:12:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next 3 jobs reports before election will be weak.</Msg><Username>dopytrader</Username><Timestamp>1344089159000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:05:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344095377000-2</Id><Title>Obama to investigate Barney Frank and Chris Dodd</Title><Msg>for their gross mismanagement of Freddie and Fannie during the Bush years and come clean on a charade that allowed an ACORN community activist, with no governing experience, to become president of the U.S.. I commend Obama for finally putting truth ahead of politics, as was promised repeatedly. History, and members of his own party, may yet judge him as something more than an "amateur". God bless America.</Msg><Username>ncsu1979</Username><Timestamp>1344095377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344110582000-3</Id><Title>blackjack, the blind hog found an acorn!!</Title><Msg>Thurs morning I had $1700. in the account I play options in.. Bought puts on IBM and CVX.. They tanked.. Doubled that money.. But turned around and bought 40 $195. calls on IBM at about .55 ($2200.) on those calls that were expiring the next day... I sold them yesterday morning at $2.50($10K).. If I weren't so broke or had bigger balls.. I could have held on and got $16K... But I ain't complaining.. You hardly ever turn $1700. into $10.5K in 2 days.. In fact last Fri, I turned over $8k into that $1700...BTW: I am going to play the mkt next wk to do the same thing it did this wk... There is a lot of money to be made off those wkly options.. If you can just figure out what those manipulators are doing!!! Anyway, I got a little money to play with!!! If you got a few chips and a chair.. You are still in the game!!!</Msg><Username>jrmills0014</Username><Timestamp>1344110582000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344113197000-4</Id><Topic><Title>blackjack, the blind hog found an acorn!!</Title><Username>jrmills0014</Username><Timestamp>1344110582000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:03:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW: Since 07 I lost a fortune playing options.. Had quit.. Decided a couple of mths ago to take $5K and see if I could beat the manipulators at their game.. Had that $5k up to $8k Last fri. By days end it was down to that $1700. But do you realize.. If you can figure out what they are going to do?? You could actually run $5k into $1M in short time, playing those wkly options!!! BTW: I placed $7500. of that $10K, yesterday on what I think they will do this coming week!!! If I am wrong.. I will still have more money, than I started with Thurs morning... If I am right.. That $1700. could turn into $25K, by Tues. And $50K by Fri!!! Bottom line: I got into the game with $5K.. I know I got the worst of this game... But, if I start getting it right!!! Not only will I try to win all the money.. I will try to win the table cloth!!! The only thing we really got to figure out is what the manipulators are going to do next.. These stks will trade at what is beneficial to them!!!</Msg><Username>jrmills0014</Username><Timestamp>1344113197000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:46:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>