<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-04"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349347010908-1</Id><Title>India's Services Sector Grows at Fastest Pace in 7 Months</Title><Msg>India's services sector expanded at its fastest pace in seven months as a spurt in new business encouraged firms to hire more staff, a survey showed on Thursday, suggesting the worst of the economic slump may be over. The HSBC purchasing manager's index for the services sector, which gauges the activity of hundreds of Indian companies, rose to 55.8 in September from August's 55.0. A reading of 50 and above separates growth from contraction and the index has held above the break-even mark since November last year. India's services sector makes up for over 60 percent of the country's gross domestic product and a strong reading in HSBC's survey augurs well for the economy, where growth has faltered in recent months against the backdrop of political upheaval. "Service sector activity grew at a faster clip in September led by firm demand, underscoring (its) resilience," said Leif Eskesen, an economist at HSBC. "This further lifted employment, which helped businesses keep up with orders." The new business sub-index surged to its highest since February allowing firms to hire more workers, and employment touched a 15-month high. But survey participants are now less optimistic about the future. The sub-index measuring business expectations, a gauge of what firms think conditions will be like in a year's time, fell to 67.2 from 74.0 in August. Policy measures taken by the U.S. Federal Reserve and the European central bank to shore up their respective economies have led to an increase in demand for Indian services. Still, the fragile recovery in the U.S. and a dire euro zone economy pose a threat to India's export dependant services sector. Growth in Asia's third-largest economy languished near its slowest in three years at 5.5 percent in the quarter ended June, as the lack of reforms by New Delhi and high interest rates hurt investment. Determined to regain investor confidence and bring the economy back on track, the government launched a slew of reforms last month by slashing fuel subsidies and inviting foreign investments in retail, aviation and broadcasting. Rising Prices Prices also rose at a faster pace in September from the previous month, the survey showed. That could further fuel wider inflation in the economy where the wholesale price index rose to 7.55 percent in August after a temporary slip in July to a three-year low. That could pose a complication for the Reserve Bank of India which, although determined to fight inflation, may find the task difficult. "The RBI has limited room for policy rate cuts given the persistence of inflation, although further progress on fiscal consolidation and structural reforms may eventually pave the way for some easing," Eskesen said. A similar survey on Monday showed factory activity expanded at a steady pace in September as new orders and output rose.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1349347010908</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 06:36:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349356139674-2</Id><Title>VOTE FOR OBOMBA ???..... WERE WHY ?????</Title><Msg>BLACK MALE UNINPLOYED UNDER BUSH WAS 27% --- WITH OBOMBA ITS NOW 48% --- By flashywildwest.11 seconds ago.Permalink . 50% OF THE KIDS COMING OUT OF COLLAGE THIS YEAR WILL NOT GET A JOB TILL AFTER JAN/2013 AT BEST............................................................WHY IS THAT MR. PRESIDENT ????........................................................................................WHO DO YOU BLAME THIS ON ???, WE ALL KNOW ITS NOT ===========YOU================ AND HE'S LOOOOOOOOOOOOOKING OUT FOR WHO ???????????????????????......................ANSWER: NO ONE BUT HIMSELF..........BROTHERS.....................</Msg><Username>flashywildwest</Username><Timestamp>1349356139674</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:08:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349358345032-3</Id><Topic><Title>India's Services Sector Grows at Fastest Pace in 7 Months</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1349347010908</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 06:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks! nice article</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1349358345032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:45:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349362241130-4</Id><Title>How are the memories on this board</Title><Msg>anyone remember how SUN , Oracle , HP , Dell , and others were going to eat IBM 's lunch ???? HP going strong , eh ??? Larry Ellison continues to tread water ... What ever happened to CRAY ??? stick with a winner , you won't get rich over night , but you will sleep well every night .... garce</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1349362241130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:50:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349365843557-5</Id><Title>Right from the horses mouth .........</Title><Msg>Today we announced a significant expansion of our enterprise systems portfolio with offerings including new Power systems based on the POWER7+ architecture and new Storage systems such as the DS8870. These announcements build upon the recent release of our new mainframe, the zEnterprise EC12. Together, these offerings bolster our Smarter Computing approach, bringing enhanced levels of value to clients by addressing their evolving requirements in a new era of IT. This includes their need for IT that delivers business insight from big data, is cloud-ready to increase efficiency and improve the economics of IT, and ensures the security of their critical information. With these announcements we have an opportunity to build on a breadth of offerings that our competitors cannot match. Our new Power, Storage and zEnterprise solutions will be key to delivering on our 4Q financial commitments and will help give us the fast start we need as we head into 2013.</Msg><Username>wtxing</Username><Timestamp>1349365843557</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349372553293-6</Id><Title>HPQ?</Title><Msg>HPQ is one of the stalwarts of Silicon Valley, and is getting destroyed by the competition. Meg Whitman has no answers for their demise. IBM is taking market share from HPQ, and their are many others as well. They want to get into the tablet market with the WebOS that was purchased from PALM. They cannot compete with IBM, and moving into AAPL's domain seems like the once powerful HPQ is heading towards the gauntlet. AAPL owns the consumer tablet market, and there is no way HPQ makes any headway with that project.</Msg><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1349372553293</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:42:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349388236764-7</Id><Topic><Title>HPQ?</Title><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1349372553293</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:42:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why don't you go on HPQ's board and impart your knowledge upon them. HPQ is awaiting advice like yours.</Msg><Username>zer0t0l</Username><Timestamp>1349388236764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 18:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349388514737-8</Id><Topic><Title>How are the memories on this board</Title><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1349362241130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've been sleeping well since IBM (tabulating co.) sold theik first meat scale.</Msg><Username>zer0t0l</Username><Timestamp>1349388514737</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 18:08:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349388725263-9</Id><Topic><Title>How are the memories on this board</Title><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1349362241130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how about Burroughs, RCA, DEC,, STC, NCR</Msg><Username>zer0t0l</Username><Timestamp>1349388725263</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 18:12:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349392098670-10</Id><Topic><Title>How are the memories on this board</Title><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1349362241130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sleeping Well also. Good to see you are still here and posting. Always a welcome sight to see your posts of substance.</Msg><Username>dino2hootie</Username><Timestamp>1349392098670</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>