<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-14"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371211567957-1</Id><Title>NetSol Technologies, Inc. (NTWK) !!! They keep hiring</Title><Msg>watch it</Msg><Username>i_love_ntwk</Username><Timestamp>1371211567957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 08:06:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371216491730-2</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and layoffs</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1370366399824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:19:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think IBM management is in a much better position to manage its staff compared to anonymous pundits on a message board. The fact is that IBM has been a very stable employeer compared to many others -- no 30k layoff at IBM like HPQ. The alternative to staff rebalancing is to keep people on the payroll when projects are finished or cancelled or demand simply isn't there.</Msg><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1371216491730</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371220727927-3</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and layoffs</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1370366399824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:19:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...And when you and others oversees ever going to understand that companies can only be successful only - and only - because of its people.. People are the great assets any company has. People react in the same manner in which they are reacted to. It is like a mirror. You stand before a mirror and you see a reflection of how you behave: You smile, you get a smile back, You show anger you get an anger back. The essence of any successful business relies on: Loyalty, competency and sound business direction. You lose any of these 3 factors and you will find mediocrity. The difference between Apple, and GM (the old GM which went bankrupt) were in : Loyalty of the employees, their competency, and the sound business direction. At this point in time IBM is somewhere between Apple and the old GM (but though it has distanced itself from Apple, it is still far from the old GM).</Msg><Username>ajpb</Username><Timestamp>1371220727927</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:38:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371224133821-4</Id><Topic><Title>Reverse split coming....</Title><Username>ninht88</Username><Timestamp>1371070979902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:02:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$195 is coming for you next week...watch N win!!</Msg><Username>pple64</Username><Timestamp>1371224133821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 11:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371226222373-5</Id><Topic><Title>Expert picks for free</Title><Username>bowenelijah701</Username><Timestamp>1371130055073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 09:27:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am buying this now</Msg><Username>mossalex731</Username><Timestamp>1371226222373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:10:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371226530723-6</Id><Topic><Title>Woah! what a good pick. Up 400%</Title><Username>carterkey303</Username><Timestamp>1371054944468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:35:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. So in theory.</Msg><Username>mossalex731</Username><Timestamp>1371226530723</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371227520026-7</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and layoffs</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1370366399824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:19:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IBM has been laying off and retiring workers for 50 years (approx) this is how IBM stays in business. unlike govenment bringing accountability to new lows, corporations must sink or swim on their own. if sectors of their business cannot do business without incurring losses they cannot be rewarded. worldwide and USA there is COMPETITION that WILL obliterate the company. government has no such problems, cash is thrown overboard so long as taxpayers are around to fund cash trashing.....FOR NOW.</Msg><Username>ma012c</Username><Timestamp>1371227520026</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:32:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371233606880-8</Id><Title>Scrutiny of IBM's Corporate Citizenship</Title><Msg>IBM issued a statement, true to form, that does not talk about employee cuts, as a matter of its corporate policy. However, given that the corporation receives huge amounts of revenue in federal and state government contracts, it must demonstrate with a very high level of verifiable public taxpayer and governmental confidence that it does indeed abide by all national and state-level Equal Opportunity laws and regulations in making cutbacks in the United States. If the corporation has nothing to hide, it should have an "open kimono" disclosure strategy release demographic data on what specific types of employees were let go, and why in relation to IBM's corporate strategy, in order to instill confidence that the cuts were done entirely by "by the book". In the absence of voluntarily disclosed data from IBM, recently laid-off employees could report to their Alliance on the demographics of who exactly they are, so that a fair measure can be taken on whether age, seniority level, sex, race or any other federal Equal Opportunity-related parameter factor statistically significantly played any possible role on the layoffs, in relation to the corresponding percentages expected to be present in the general company employee base. Also, the statistics of previous layoffs by the company could be looked at carefully and relatively easily by investigators from both federal agencies and state employment agencies, using information on age, gender, race, etc. from unemployment claim information filed by ex-IBM-ers in states with historically large IBM layoffs in the past such as NY, NC , CA or TX. This would quickly tell if any trends in EO-non-compliance are statistically discernible. If there is any cause for concern, a wider investigation could then be instituted. by the government. If there is no cause for concern, that could be publicly disclosed as well, to make the IBM corporate lay-off actions, and the lack of details pertaining to them smell at least a little rosier.</Msg><Username>medchemlead</Username><Timestamp>1371233606880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 14:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371234543216-9</Id><Topic><Title>Scrutiny of IBM's Corporate Citizenship</Title><Username>medchemlead</Username><Timestamp>1371233606880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 14:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, anyone with an IBM fetish is not allowed to sit on any municipal, state, Federal or in your case a fantasy jury. So no investigation into IBM slashing up to 2% of world wide staff of 434k. Analysts point out that the $1 bil IBM has estimated for staff RIF would be under 2%. IBM is always hiring because of total per annum attrition including layoffs, retirements and voluntary resignations. If you cut down on the length of your rants you would get more of your audience reading past the first sentence. But then it wouldn't be a Big Blue fetish.</Msg><Username>yield_of_my_dreams</Username><Timestamp>1371234543216</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 14:29:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371236328445-10</Id><Topic><Title>Reverse split coming....</Title><Username>ninht88</Username><Timestamp>1371070979902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:02:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your dream cimes true!!!</Msg><Username>bigk95133</Username><Timestamp>1371236328445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 14:58:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371238634905-11</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and layoffs</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1370366399824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:19:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Loads of jobs? What planet are you on, not Earth. Oh, Burger King is hiring and YES Ginny is canning the 50s crowd big time. IBM is already lean and mean which explains all those profitable service accounts that LEAVE IBM for somebody else. Frankly, you are an idiot.</Msg><Username>cheekynewyorkgirl</Username><Timestamp>1371238634905</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 15:37:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371238681215-12</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and layoffs</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1370366399824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:19:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, and what about salary? India has a working wage of $4 per hour. That MATTERS to IBM moron.</Msg><Username>cheekynewyorkgirl</Username><Timestamp>1371238681215</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 15:38:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371239301321-13</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and layoffs</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1370366399824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:19:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you want the truth but you can't handle the truth. LOL</Msg><Username>realgrit</Username><Timestamp>1371239301321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 15:48:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371240151534-14</Id><Title>Workforce Reductions: 1300?</Title><Msg>Try 2,286. Almost double</Msg><Username>cheekynewyorkgirl</Username><Timestamp>1371240151534</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 16:02:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371242194176-15</Id><Title>From the Hudson valley Patch</Title><Msg>From the White Plains patch website (White Plains is Ginny's home city) "IBM is slashing its workforce around the world, according to media and employee reports. "IBM’s decision to drop the ax on hundreds of employees — 697 in Dutchess County alone — was part of a global cutback based on a shortfall in first-quarter results," wrote reporter Roberto Cruz in the Poughkeepsie Journal. The news infuriated NY State Senator Greg Ball (R-Putnam) who said he had been raising alarms about IBM's poor corporate citizenship since 2009. Media reports said IBM issued a statement that did not talk about the cuts, rather citing change as a constant in the technology industry. Alliance@IBM, website of the IBM Employees' Union, is keeping a running tally of the layoffs, department by department. They totalled 2,286 as of the morning of June 13. WRAL TechWire quotes an analyst speculating that up to 8,000 jobs will go overall. This simply confirms what we have know about IBM’s tendency to accept taxpayer dollars, lay folks off and shift responsibility,” Ball said in a press statement. “We’ve asked Governor Cuomo to get solid commitments from IBM in writing, in return for taxpayer subsidies, yet he has refused to do so. If anyone needs a case study in poorly managed corporate welfare, in a state set to unveil billions more, this is it.” According to Ball, he demanded in 2009 an investigation into IBM’s offshore practices after they received over $100 million from New York State. In December of 2008, IBM also accepted $45 million from the Empire State Development Corporation in return for not cutting jobs at its East Fishkill facility. Just two weeks later, the company laid off 274 workers.</Msg><Username>medchemlead</Username><Timestamp>1371242194176</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 16:36:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371246989537-16</Id><Topic><Title>Scrutiny of IBM's Corporate Citizenship</Title><Username>medchemlead</Username><Timestamp>1371233606880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 14:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>medchemlead - you said "However, given that the corporation receives huge amounts of revenue in federal and state government contracts," IBM's revenues from all US govt. contract generally stays below 2% of total revenues. That's about $2 billion if you are wondering.</Msg><Username>alreadyhaveauser</Username><Timestamp>1371246989537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 17:56:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371247047704-17</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and layoffs</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1370366399824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:19:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ma012c - not 50 years, 20 years. First layoff was in 1993. Prior to that it was all incentive based to retire.</Msg><Username>alreadyhaveauser</Username><Timestamp>1371247047704</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 17:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371247497140-18</Id><Topic><Title>Scrutiny of IBM's Corporate Citizenship</Title><Username>medchemlead</Username><Timestamp>1371233606880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 14:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AND, if you don't think that they have to report their information to the Feds or States they are laying off people in, you are naive. They just don't make it public. The alliance guys want it to be public because they have a vested interest in trying to organize the company, get it?.</Msg><Username>alreadyhaveauser</Username><Timestamp>1371247497140</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 18:04:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371265805735-19</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and layoffs</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1370366399824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:19:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To wiwi17wkxks, Typical content-free answer from a typical American worker. No facts. No analysis. No new information. Just "you really don't have a clue..." And your grammar is also horrible. One who DOESN'T have a clue would be correct not "One who don't have a clue." I purposely removed the extra words so that you would understand the correction. You are a typical overpaid, under skilled, illiterate product of the American school system, with an opinion on everything. Always waving that big foam "we are #1" finger in the air. Well guess what? You're not #1. You're not even in the top 10. The world knows it; IBM knows it; every corporation in America knows it; only the American worker doesn't seem to know it (or as you would say - "American worker don't know it"). Case closed...</Msg><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1371265805735</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 23:10:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371266926222-20</Id><Topic><Title>IBM's biggest problem</Title><Username>me_hoping_for_hun</Username><Timestamp>1371152651987</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 15:44:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3,000 executives (bands D,C,B,A) in a company with 450K employees is not a large number. It's around 0.6%. It also means the average executive has 150 employees. So the average executive in IBM should be paid as much as a CEO of a small company - and they are not. And since the compensation is heavily weighted in terms of stock and options, IBM executives are decidedly underpaid compared to most other corporate executives. I know at least a dozen who have left for significantly larger compensation packages. In fact, executive retention is one of IBM's biggest concerns. When the stock stops rising they flood out the door because the base salary and bonus is a snap to match anywhere else. A Vice President at a large investment bank could hire an IBM Vice president to mow their lawn and never notice the expense.</Msg><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1371266926222</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 23:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371268273726-21</Id><Title>When the "Cloud" evaporates in the Big Blue sky</Title><Msg>When a "Cloud " evaporates or moves over to the "Amazon", there is nothing left in the Big Blue sky for hopes of a rainy day when it will rain down money; so hold no stock if you want to stay above water. I be em-pty.</Msg><Username>medchemlead</Username><Timestamp>1371268273726</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 23:51:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371268558767-22</Id><Title>Amazon- A Cloud over IBM</Title><Msg>"The CIA picked Amazon over IBM for a lucrative government contract not because of price, but because of the company's "superior technical solution" – a view that contrasts with IBM's vision of itself as the go-to tech organization for governments. The revelation came to light on Friday when the US Government Accountability Office released a partially-redacted report that outlined the reasons for why the spooks plumped for Amazon over IBM for a $600m private cloud contract, and why IBM protested this decision. The GAO report partially upheld two of IBM's complaints relating to percieved pricing and technological differences between it and Amazon, and the CIA's subsequent relaxing of a solicitation term for Amazon, and rejected the rest. Now, the CIA has 60 days to decide to either take the GAO's recommendations and reevaluate the two companies, or stay with Amazon. Although Amazon came in with an evaluated annual price of $148 million per year versus IBM's $94 million, the CIA chose Amazon for its technical sophistication, the report says. "While IBM's proposal offered an evaluated [deleted] price advantage over 5 years, the [source selection authority] concluded that this advantage was offset by Amazon’s superior technical solution," the report says. IBM's price did appear to have some provisions attached to it which freaked out the procurement body, which "found 'serious cost risk' associated with IBM's proposed contract clause which indicated that the contractor would [deleted]." We don't know what the [deleted] bit could say, but speculate that it's typical for major enterprise contracts to contain provisions relating to cost-overruns that can trigger additional fees."</Msg><Username>medchemlead</Username><Timestamp>1371268558767</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 23:55:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>