<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358331827869-1</Id><Topic><Title>this is all temporary</Title><Username>lezamaharold</Username><Timestamp>1358264943582</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:49:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report!</Msg><Username>chanjames660</Username><Timestamp>1358331827869</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 05:23:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358343364876-2</Id><Topic><Title>this is all temporary</Title><Username>lezamaharold</Username><Timestamp>1358264943582</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:49:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well written report, thanks</Msg><Username>jamesclement302</Username><Timestamp>1358343364876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:36:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358353346517-3</Id><Topic><Title>IBM downgraded by JP Morgan $215 to $197</Title><Username>thseeker1</Username><Timestamp>1358194198113</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 15:09:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>save your cash.. losing it takes years to regain. why should any stock be a buy in economies that are growing slowly if at all. cash is being hoarded.</Msg><Username>briarspratt</Username><Timestamp>1358353346517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:22:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358354135896-4</Id><Title>Will the analysts miss their target again?</Title><Msg>I have to laugh when "the street" announces that a certain company 'missed' the earnings prediction. Its the analysts who 'missed'. The company does not predict, They might give a 'ballpark' figure. The analysts churn data from a company and set a revenue target price. Setting it higher than it should be leads to a 'miss'.</Msg><Username>zer0t0l</Username><Timestamp>1358354135896</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:35:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358365331602-5</Id><Topic><Title>2 Things We All Know Obama Hates: "Colonialism"... and "Capitalism".</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1357675426366</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:03:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... but when it's too progressive, then "incentives" are supressed, the society becomes unproductive and internationally un-competitive and succumbs to general economic decline. This has been true of all progressively socialist countries prior to the one Obama is attempting to promote here in the U.S. The problem is, the top 1% in America contribute about 42% of all federal income taxes but only have 1% of the vote. The bottom 47% of americans pay no taxes but have 47% of the vote. Such a situation perpetuates the interests of those who feed off the system and marginalizes the influence of those who pay into the system. The result is a "socialist vortex" that is similar to what is dragging many european countries into bankruptcy and depression. The U.S. will not escape economic collapse. There is no will to cut out of control spending amongst the dominant left in american politics and tax increases can only address a small percentage of the huge deficits. Meanwhile, Rampant Deficit spending and massive money printing at the federal reserve are rapidly sending our economy to the brink as credit rating companies increasingly threaten to further downgrade the credit quality of U.S. Treasuries. Alreadyhaveauser... you're getting the America that you and Obama want... and we're rapidly moving toward the bankruptcy that your vision for America will produce. S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1358365331602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:42:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358365371331-6</Id><Topic><Title>this is all temporary</Title><Username>lezamaharold</Username><Timestamp>1358264943582</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:49:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big thanks !</Msg><Username>malik_david</Username><Timestamp>1358365371331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:42:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358389123291-7</Id><Title>Will they make the $29.15 billion for the quarter</Title><Msg>The accountants will make the EPS, but you can not fake the Rev. Q3 was a free pass will they give another free pass for Q4 if Rev is below $29 I think #$%$ around with Employee 401K to save Rev for 2013 as they #$%$ those employees that get laid off before end of year and push off all payments to end of year might be a tell about future Rev They are digging down deep, Next they will go after Benefits again</Msg><Username>cvs9yt</Username><Timestamp>1358389123291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 21:18:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>