<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373723715542-1</Id><Topic><Title>Stop Whining... Stop Complaining... Get back to Work...</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1371677629786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 17:33:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The latest resource action will cost IBM $1 Billion in extra expense. The cuts were deep, with a high percentage of America's technical leaders being kicked to the curb... most of which were leading and running all the projects, staffed by 90% low cost, GR bodies. And IBM shareholders should be happy for that? When IBM starts simply focusing on a single quarter... the company is in big trouble. After 2015, I guess the CEO will be a GR from Indonesia.</Msg><Username>rosemariesanchez</Username><Timestamp>1373723715542</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 09:55:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373729733080-2</Id><Topic><Title>Bummer .. Holding 190 calls bought for 3.5 .. Dump of hold till Fri?</Title><Username>rob1reddy</Username><Timestamp>1373390863018</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 13:27:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got rid off it on Thurs. for nickle and dime profit !</Msg><Username>rbaddam</Username><Timestamp>1373729733080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 11:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373732465351-3</Id><Topic><Title>Stop Whining... Stop Complaining... Get back to Work...</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1371677629786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 17:33:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>except that IBM has a long tradition of complaining employees ... i worked there for 32 years and did very well ... but there were always complainers .. it was very obvious that they went from cradle to IBM with no idea how the rest of the world operates ....</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1373732465351</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 12:21:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373732588668-4</Id><Topic><Title>Stop Whining... Stop Complaining... Get back to Work...</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1371677629786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 17:33:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Problem is they can't afford it. Revenue per employee at places like Google is 5X greater than IBM why do you think that IBM continuously lays off people ??? IBM is also so rich , that they can afford to carry the extra and most likely will leverage them for new deployment ...... IBM still needs to shed some lower margin operations and bring that ratio back from the stratosphere ... g</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1373732588668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 12:23:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373732750285-5</Id><Topic><Title>Stop Whining... Stop Complaining... Get back to Work...</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1371677629786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 17:33:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yup ... LG got IBM down to just over 200k employees ... time to do some trimming .. and they will ... IBM has been the penultimate corporate camelion .... probably THE most adaptable company ever on this planet .. .there are cycles and the current one has seen the population grow larger than need be , no urgency , but programs need to be put in place and probably already are .... g</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1373732750285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 12:25:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373732856663-6</Id><Topic><Title>Stop Whining... Stop Complaining... Get back to Work...</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1371677629786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 17:33:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem is that IBM no longer values some employees as they once did. fair enough and it would be an item of concern IF there were other companies who value their employees , but those days have passed ... as far as concern for employees</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1373732856663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 12:27:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373732961747-7</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer</Title><Username>zer0t0l</Username><Timestamp>1373673045152</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 19:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes , but from his standpoint, IBM doesn't pay enough div and the next double of share price will be far longer than the last one ... he often speaks as though he is still running a hedge fund ... IBM is still a great place for retail investors ... little risk , little downside ... some div and expect cap appreciation ... garce</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1373732961747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 12:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373734055907-8</Id><Title>On American Employees, i.e. Deadwood</Title><Msg>With over 3,000 cut thus far, and so many posters here insisting that only shareholder value counts for anything at all, WHY have any overpaid American workers AT ALL. Hey, if Ginny can reduce US headcount to perhaps 30 - inclusive of her and Board of Directors - she can fire everybody else and move the whole lot over to Bangalore where everything is cheaper-faster-better and god knows closer to those all important customer support and programming centers.</Msg><Username>retiredexaon</Username><Timestamp>1373734055907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 12:47:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373743900012-9</Id><Topic><Title>Stop Whining... Stop Complaining... Get back to Work...</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1371677629786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 17:33:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I might not have made myself clear, but I didn't literally suggest "lavish" spending, hence my quotes. Suffice it to say, IBM can afford meals, team building events, and occasional off sites. It doesn't have to be 1st class plane tickets &amp; IBM can get excellent hotel deals. Moreover, not all 450,000 employees need this kind of spending. Development and sales do. Again, many companies with offices in Silicon Valley shell out the money to do so. SAP has a major office in Palo Alto, with free meals. You don't need rock bands, but you need compelling culture. IBM can figure it out. They did it once before. They can do it again. Something tells me they will need to.</Msg><Username>banmate7</Username><Timestamp>1373743900012</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 15:31:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>