<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-08"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357623929080-1</Id><Title>Revenue Numbers?</Title><Msg>IBM reports earnings in two weeks, and the number that mainly concerns me is their revenue number. IBM has shown decelerating revenue the past two reports. This is a trend that needs to be reversed or the stock will take a big hit. The CFO claimed at the last report that contracts from the 3rd quarter were to be pushed back into the 4th quarter. If this is true, then IBM should be in great shape. If not...</Msg><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1357623929080</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:45:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357659184045-2</Id><Topic><Title>Revenue Numbers?</Title><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1357623929080</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:45:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Revenue is the issue. I heard Cramer respond to a question about IBM revenue last night and the reply wasn't reassuring -- the question from the guy calling in was pretty long and Cramer just said if it went to $180 he would buy more for his charitable trust. So it sounds like he is concerned about the tings that will hurt big tech revenue -- weak economies in Europe &amp; Asia and a strengthening dollar. We will see soon!</Msg><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1357659184045</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:33:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357662755958-3</Id><Title>If you watched CNBC would you want to invest in this market ??</Title><Msg>no way !! only negative out of their mouths!! Simon I think he is the worst ! I think socialists send him to this country with one mission !!!LOL!!!LOL!!</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357662755958</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:32:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357668648299-4</Id><Topic><Title>If you watched CNBC would you want to invest in this market ??</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357662755958</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:32:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CNBC is the new comedy central. The market is fake, the news contrived and you live in a play. CNBC just pulling strings so you do not cash out of the system.</Msg><Username>againscammed</Username><Timestamp>1357668648299</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:10:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357670354262-5</Id><Topic><Title>Revenue Numbers?</Title><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1357623929080</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:45:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typically this is the strongest of all quarters as contracts and the majority of the business is closed during this quarter. I have IBM clients who keep emphasizing they have had a very busy quarter. That is vague as I realize the words themselves. If the CFO's comments translate to 4th qtr contracts, we should be in great shape if revenues are back to where we need them to be. I think a 200 handle should be achieved after closing even approaching the 202 203 mark. I feel this stock although it is considered a growth trades a little better than that but not quite to what a value stock would trade it. I feel strongly that the quarter will be another January hit and we should fly to and past 200.</Msg><Username>anuandamit</Username><Timestamp>1357670354262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:39:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357670373888-6</Id><Topic><Title>If you watched CNBC would you want to invest in this market ??</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357662755958</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:32:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CNBC speaks the truth the whole truth and nothing but the truth ... just ask Jim Cramer ... he would never stear you wrong!</Msg><Username>nperillo</Username><Timestamp>1357670373888</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:39:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357673165641-7</Id><Title>time to buy...CTIC</Title><Msg>STRONG BUY</Msg><Username>dave.attal</Username><Timestamp>1357673165641</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:26:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357675426366-8</Id><Title>2 Things We All Know Obama Hates: "Colonialism"... and "Capitalism".</Title><Msg>The United States has historically been a bastian of both Colonialism and Capitalism. That is why Michelle Obama said, following Obama's 2008 campaign, that she hated what America was until Mr. Obama became president. That comment proved to be very, very insightful. Because it explains Mr. Obama's obsession with jacking up taxes on those American's with the most investment capital (eg: the top 2%) even though taxing that segment of american taxpayer produces the least tax revenue per dollar taxed and discourages the most job creation... 2 things that America desparately needs. Mr. Obama's insistence that congress relinquish it's custody of the "debt limit" is very much due to his consistently huge, $Trillion dollar federal deficits and his opposition to any spending cuts that might reduce those deficits. He is essentially seeking to make these deficits perpetual despite the liklihood that they will bankrupt America.... what better way to engineer a government takeover of America. We MUST remember that Mr. Obama is the sworn enemy of a "free-enterprise" america. His hatred for colonialism was fostered at an early age by his father, and his hatred for the free-enterprise capitalism that made America great was cultivated by his step-father, Frank Davis, an outspoken, card-carrying communist, and his college advisor, who is an outspoken, socialist ideologue. We are now learning that for Mr. Obama, a "balanced approach" to the budget means that now that taxes have been raised without any corresponding spending cuts... ... that it's now time to begin considering, you guessed it, MORE tax hikes... under the guise of "closing loopholes and tax reform". Call it what you want to, but it all adds up to a steady march toward european-style socialism. Spokanimal</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1357675426366</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:03:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357676155071-9</Id><Topic><Title>If you watched CNBC would you want to invest in this market ??</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357662755958</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:32:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL!!! those guys keep bringing bears soon there will be no retail investor left to invest Keep up the good work Wall Street volume is down huge last few years and they don't #$%$....</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357676155071</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:15:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357676456675-10</Id><Topic><Title>2 Things We All Know Obama Hates: "Colonialism"... and "Capitalism".</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1357675426366</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:03:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"discourages the most job creation" What a hoot you are!</Msg><Username>alreadyhaveauser</Username><Timestamp>1357676456675</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:20:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357678304392-11</Id><Topic><Title>2 Things We All Know Obama Hates: "Colonialism"... and "Capitalism".</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1357675426366</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:03:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Generally, a wealthier person has more invested... either in stocks and bonds, or in a directly-owned business. Since most jobs are created by businesses, then it follows that the owners of those businesses are responsible for job creation. The wealthiest Americans own the most businesses. Similarly, the wealthiest americans invest the most money in stocks. Investing in stocks raises the price of those stocks which, in turn, makes IPOs more fruitful for the issuing corporations and provides them with more capital to expand and hire americans. Alreadyhaveauser, you are probably the only person on this board that doesn't have an understanding of these basic concepts of capitalism... ... so, the more appropriate characterization is.... what a hoot YOU are. S.</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1357678304392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:51:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357679387556-12</Id><Topic><Title>2 Things We All Know Obama Hates: "Colonialism"... and "Capitalism".</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1357675426366</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:03:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ummm, yeah right. That's why there has been so much job creation while the Bush tax cuts have been in effect. A study from the Congressional Research Service -- the non-partisan research office for Congress -- shows that "there is little evidence over the past 65 years that tax cuts for the highest earners are associated with savings, investment or productivity growth." In fact, the study found that higher tax rates for the wealthy are statistically associated with higher levels of growth. Quit thinking and read something willya?</Msg><Username>alreadyhaveauser</Username><Timestamp>1357679387556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:09:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357679984165-13</Id><Topic><Title>2 Things We All Know Obama Hates: "Colonialism"... and "Capitalism".</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1357675426366</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:03:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... if tax cuts are directed at Americans with no investment capital... people who don't invest in the stock of companies and who don't own businesses... rather than americans who DO invest in stocks and DO own businesses... ... that you would like us to believe that those tax cuts would result in more job creation? You can cite all the mumbo-jumbo you want to... and blame Bush, Clinton, or even Dwight Eisenhower if you want to... ... but a spade is still a spade no matter how somebody like you wants to characterize it.</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1357679984165</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:19:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357681272848-14</Id><Topic><Title>2 Things We All Know Obama Hates: "Colonialism"... and "Capitalism".</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1357675426366</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:03:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said "Generally, a wealthier person has more invested... either in stocks and bonds, or in a directly-owned business. Since most jobs are created by businesses, then it follows that the owners of those businesses are responsible for job creation. The wealthiest Americans own the most businesses." Q: Did THEY, or did THEY not (THEY = top 2%) just have approx. 10 years of lower taxes than before? WUT HAPPENED BUB?</Msg><Username>alreadyhaveauser</Username><Timestamp>1357681272848</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:41:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357684923922-15</Id><Topic><Title>Revenue Numbers?</Title><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1357623929080</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:45:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is normally a good quater lets see and good luck</Msg><Username>bestplayer371</Username><Timestamp>1357684923922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:42:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357699974458-16</Id><Title>Time to buy</Title><Msg>It will fill the gap at the $210 area. Set to break and trend above the 200ma. Great support on the 50ma. And look who is the largest holder $14billion</Msg><Username>jcoppola9</Username><Timestamp>1357699974458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 21:52:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357703090803-17</Id><Topic><Title>Time to buy</Title><Username>jcoppola9</Username><Timestamp>1357699974458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 21:52:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bought 100 shares today. It has done well even in the recession and business is now improving. I suspect they'll be doing really well (better than the estimates) once the economy is stronger. IBM is a business service company.</Msg><Username>ephyfe</Username><Timestamp>1357703090803</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:44:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>