<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372571597063-1</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and layoffs</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1370366399824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:19:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am writing a book about my 30 years of cover-ups and very bad management,,stay tuned, drunks rule the roost, this is not an honest co.</Msg><Username>bobbybee01</Username><Timestamp>1372571597063</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 01:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372580927847-2</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and layoffs</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1370366399824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:19:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I assume this incredible piece of literature will be in English. First, of course, you'll need to learn the language. So let's begin with your earlier post: granted not "grantet" protection of our troops not "protection on our troops" their sweat shops not "there sweat shops" sweat shops around the world not "sweat shops in the world" And you managed all those mistakes in just two sentences. You're just another worthless product of the American public school system.</Msg><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1372580927847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 04:28:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372592404697-3</Id><Topic><Title>And now a message from one of my heros - David Stockman (The Great Deformation)</Title><Username>ib_millionaire</Username><Timestamp>1372537431255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 16:23:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"During the last 5 years IBM spent less on capital investment than its depreciation and amortization charges, and also shrank its constant dollar spending for R/D by nearly 2% annually. Neither of these trends is compatible with staying on top of the fiercely competitive tech industry." During the last 3 years from 2012 IBM spent $6.3 bil, $6.258, $6.026 bil and the % of revenue has been 6.03%, 5.85%, 6.03%. IBM has also filed the most patents for the last 3 years. The above quote suggests that IBM has reduced its R&amp;D by 10% during the last 5 years and that it is losing ground because it doesn't do enough R&amp;D. Mostly, its people who sold the stock in 2011 at $170 who post this kind of baloney. Not to worry, the truth detector is on the job.</Msg><Username>yield_of_my_dreams</Username><Timestamp>1372592404697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 07:40:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372602447749-4</Id><Title>Over 3,000 jobs cut Ginny and ...</Title><Msg>The shareholder value has not improved. Article on Yahoo finance indicates that IBM and Accenture have been hit hard. Hmmmm, I would rather focus on client support than cutting jobs for clients, maybe if you actually KEPT some of your clients, you would have better revenue numbers. But, then again, all management knows here is reduce expenses and you can reduce your way to profit, right????</Msg><Username>retiredexaon</Username><Timestamp>1372602447749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:27:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372602509395-5</Id><Topic><Title>video message from CEO blaming the employees is a sign of trouble</Title><Username>frombadtoworse</Username><Timestamp>1372431826070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:03:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anybody remember old John Akers in 1991 blasting employees for hanging around the water cooler???</Msg><Username>retiredexaon</Username><Timestamp>1372602509395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:28:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372616866333-6</Id><Topic><Title>And now a message from one of my heros - David Stockman (The Great Deformation)</Title><Username>ib_millionaire</Username><Timestamp>1372537431255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 16:23:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Truth-detector ?? You are a JOKE! How is that buy and hold working for you?? Yea I sold at 170. And a few times at 120 and last year at 198. Of course I bought at 180 the day before Jan eanings and made a quick 10%. I wont be buying the day be_FORE earnings this time.. I will be looking FORE you after earnings next month TRUTHY!! My guess you will be hiding. Anyone LONG and STRONG in these markets is an IDIOT! David Stockman rules! See you after EARNINGS FOOL! .</Msg><Username>ib_millionaire</Username><Timestamp>1372616866333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 14:27:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372618972838-7</Id><Topic><Title>Over 3,000 jobs cut Ginny and ...</Title><Username>retiredexaon</Username><Timestamp>1372602447749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:27:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you cut jobs of the actual employees who have the client contacts and client relationships, and keep their higher-ups who don't know a thing (but have their underlings do the grunt work) ensconced in their comfy positions, the corporation loses out big time. Such cutbacks cut back on employee morale and employee productivity and do nothing to help the corporation other than to show minimal short term gains to the Street and preserve upper management bonuses. It provides zero benefit to shareholders looking for a hold or long term position and does not auger well for the corporation's future. Wake up, BoD, or the shareholders will be quite vociferous at the next Annual Meeting about the corporate leadership, or the lack thereof.</Msg><Username>medchemlead</Username><Timestamp>1372618972838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:02:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372635474079-8</Id><Topic><Title>And now a message from one of my heros - David Stockman (The Great Deformation)</Title><Username>ib_millionaire</Username><Timestamp>1372537431255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 16:23:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hilarious!! Consider the source of this nonsense. David Stockman's record as an investor is dismal and most of his major projects as a private business man went bankrupt. I'm not surprised he is bearish on IBM and everything else having to do with American business. In a March 2012 interview, David Stockman says we're facing a financial crisis, and he holds no stocks, only short-term Treasurys, saying, "I'm just in short-term, yeah. Call it cash. I have some gold. I'm not going to take any risk." Ouch!!! He missed one of the greatest bull runs in US history and has...wait for it.... GOLD?? = double ouch. "In 2010, Stockman agreed to pay $7.2 million to settle a lawsuit with the Securities and Exchange Commission that claimed he had misled investors as chief executive officer of Collins &amp; Aikman Corp., a maker of auto parts. " This guy is a piece of work who throws around numbers and gloom and doom stories every time he wants to sell a book. If this guy is your hero, my condolences for your losses.</Msg><Username>gamalataki</Username><Timestamp>1372635474079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:37:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>