<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-09"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370794282851-1</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer see IBM drop $10</Title><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370577602894</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 00:00:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"IBM could trade down $10 on negative news. and that would be a little less than a 5% move down ... considered to be a very healthy correction by everyone's take .... that statement certainly applies to the over 5000 listed stocks .... but even IF such action occurs , IBM is still on track for 300 ... g Cramer's format is not unlike a woman's .... DRAMA , URGENCY , his inflections telegraph an "act now" mind set ... for the novice and intermediate investor .. Cramer is excellent with demonstrating analysis ... forget his specific calls , do your own DD .. he's teaching you how .... next time you watch him , sit back with rock glass of your favorite scotch , with no more than 1 cube .... g</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1370794282851</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:11:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370794335327-2</Id><Topic><Title>Dow......turning lower</Title><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370629941923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:32:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thank you much .. i missed that one .... btw , once the sun sets tonight , it will be dark outside .... g</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1370794335327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:12:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370794508950-3</Id><Topic><Title>Dear Ms Rometty</Title><Username>medchemlead</Username><Timestamp>1370571478797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 22:17:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>true</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1370794508950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:15:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370800882016-4</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and layoffs.. and US corporations</Title><Username>fraudhasnofriends</Username><Timestamp>1370374936998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:42:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eh, get your history right. Watson was under indictment in 1914 for unethical business practices when he was with THE CASH. IBM founder and old school date for a few decades after that. But of course that is immaterial in this world of Bangalore help desks.</Msg><Username>retiredexaon</Username><Timestamp>1370800882016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 14:01:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370804974064-5</Id><Title>IBM Validates BIO-key's Fingerprint Technology for IBM Security Access Manager for Web</Title><Msg>Great opportunity in the FP market. Several major fortune 100 Co's partnering with BIO-key, (BKYI), like GE, MSFT, ORCL, AT&amp;T. Worth a look http://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-validates-bio-keys-fingerprint-121200893.html</Msg><Username>jonqpublic9999</Username><Timestamp>1370804974064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:09:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370808201611-6</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer see IBM drop $10</Title><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370577602894</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 00:00:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is making the point that dividend paying stocks are over valued! All of them! PCG has 5% EPS growth and a multiple of 25! MCD has single digit EPS growth and a multiple of 20! IBM is growing earnings at about 10% with a multiple of 15, and that is too rich. Investors pulled money out of the bond market and put them in safe, dividend paying stocks. Look for the growth stocks to take off in the second half of 2013, and the blue chips take a breather.</Msg><Username>qofaslave69</Username><Timestamp>1370808201611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370821396160-7</Id><Topic><Title>made 60k on IBM puts!!!!</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1366434222044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 01:03:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MDEG</Msg><Username>millyherr</Username><Timestamp>1370821396160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:43:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370825482799-8</Id><Title>Cry the beloved company, IBM</Title><Msg>Cry the beloved company, IBM Cry the beloved company for what you once were, and what you have become. Cry for the misguided, who have led the way to where the company is and continue to lead the way to oblivion. Cry for them because they do not recognize the damage they cause the company in the long term seeking to save their own hides and compensation packages in the short term. Cry for the management who appear to care only for stakeholders breathing down their necks. Cry for them myopically watching only the next quarter’s financial statement, not the long term survival and growth of the corporation. Cry about “Project Mercury”. Cry for the total erosion of employee commitment and loyalty by your creating an atmosphere of uncertainty, job insecurity and fear in your global workforce, which are devastating to a corporation’s well-being, killing any productivity or future hope. Cry, Ginny for what you have allowed to happen on your watch. Cry Sam, for what you saw happening, and did nothing to stall. Cry for the captain on the bridge who now pilots the ship to ????? . Cry, Mr. Gerstner, for the erosion of the foundations you laid for the company’s rising like a proud Phoenix again. Cry, the beloved company for the world changing technologies that will likely be lost to mankind by the stifling of productive creativity in the workforce, with the advent corporation’s short-sighted near-term fiscal policies. Cry for the shame of management continuing to receive fat paychecks and benefits, when rank-and-file employees are forced to get less and less, and continual demands are made for more and more given up by them. Cry foul for the failures of company leadership that have brought upon this situation. Cry in shame, Board of Directors, for allowing what has happen with eyes wide open. Cry, the shareholders, who put your trust in them. Cry, Mr. Watson, for what little remains of your dream and vision for your dreamchild, IBM. Cry, the beloved company, IBM.</Msg><Username>medchemlead</Username><Timestamp>1370825482799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:51:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370831440226-9</Id><Topic><Title>Cry the beloved company, IBM</Title><Username>medchemlead</Username><Timestamp>1370825482799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:51:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Opinions vary. Sometimes chemestry does not work out. Griping on a message board will probably not improve your skill set. Good luck to you son.</Msg><Username>eye_be_m</Username><Timestamp>1370831440226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 22:30:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>