<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365765950189-1</Id><Topic><Title>RED tomorrow 4 sure...</Title><Username>issi2668</Username><Timestamp>1365710176584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:56:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IBM a Pig? You need your head examined.</Msg><Username>lucenatraveler</Username><Timestamp>1365765950189</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 07:25:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365766097248-2</Id><Title>Infosys Shares Dive 20% After Revenue Forecast Disappoints</Title><Msg>http://www.cnbc.com/id/100636387</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1365766097248</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 07:28:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365770946515-3</Id><Title>Open as low as $211</Title><Msg>With today's low as $208.50 Big red on its way...</Msg><Username>nt2668</Username><Timestamp>1365770946515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 08:49:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365771459390-4</Id><Title>IBM Invests $1 Billion in Flash Technology</Title><Msg>The first of IBM's big divestitures was disk drive manufacturing in 2002. Followed by PC's in 2005. IBM's R&amp;D makes it a 9' tall quarterback to see down field. Tough times back then though...July, 2002 "Following the $2.05 billion agreement to sell the money-losing hard disk drive (HDD) operations to Hitachi , Armonk, N.Y.-based IBM on Tuesday announced it would lay off 1,500 employees from its Microelectronics Division, a move aimed at increasing operational efficiencies. The layoffs, which accounts for about 7.5 percent of the unit's work force, follows an earlier announcement that Hitachi would shell out $2.05 billion for the bulk of IBM's HDD-related assets. Initially, the Japanese electronics behemoth would own 70 percent of the new company and make a series of fixed payments to IBM before taking full ownership after three years. As a result of all of the staff cuts, Big Blue said it would take a pre-tax charge of approximately $2 billion to $2.5 billion, primarily in the second quarter. "These include charges associated with the company's exit from the hard disk drive business, write-offs of assets in the Microelectronics business, and charges related to productivity initiatives, principally workforce reduction," IBM said in a statement."</Msg><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1365771459390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 08:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365775287007-5</Id><Topic><Title>Is April 18th confirmed as the earnings date?</Title><Username>manu_le_parisien</Username><Timestamp>1365709177955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:39:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Shortly after that they will have their board meeting and set and announce the dividend rate for the next year, which will start with the next payment. I am hoping they bump it up to a buck. I also think their is a small possibility that they split the shares (if not now, it will come after they move up through $220 - DJ doesn't want any share price so high it gets a totally unbalanced weighting - that's why Google isn't there) . So how about a 2:1 split and 50 cents a share starting with the next payment" The IBM stockholders meeting is set for April, 30. There's usually a BOD meeting during the IBM Annual Meeting and a new dividend hike and share buyback capital allocation will probably be announced the first day of the stockholders meeting. I'd love to see IBM take the divvy up to $4 but it would be out of character with its history. I think it will go to $3.85. I don't believe IBM will split its stock before 2016. DJ doesn't have the standing to ask IBM to split its stock. DJ has no say in what IBM does. I think IBM is going to get past the $20 per share boggy set for 2015 before it splits the stock -- they are not going to have to play with the math -- there is no reason to split IBM. The old idea that it makes a stock more buy-able by small investors became meaningless after on-line trading and $10 commissions became ubiquitous.</Msg><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1365775287007</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 10:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365791198581-6</Id><Title>money has to go to stockslike ibm etc</Title><Msg>no where to go</Msg><Username>jamestanit</Username><Timestamp>1365791198581</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 14:26:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365802110691-7</Id><Topic><Title>Is April 18th confirmed as the earnings date?</Title><Username>manu_le_parisien</Username><Timestamp>1365709177955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:39:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>after 18th of April, I believe it will sink below $200 this time. Sell N run away...</Msg><Username>chidragon38</Username><Timestamp>1365802110691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 17:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365820928573-8</Id><Topic><Title>IBM Invests $1 Billion in Flash Technology</Title><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1365771459390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 08:57:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and don't forget the selloff of the tape drive business (forgot to whom) and the printer busines to RICOH, both of which were labor intensive and a minimum return on the dollar. IBM doesn't need the "brick and mortar" any longer.</Msg><Username>zer0t0l</Username><Timestamp>1365820928573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 22:42:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>