<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-23"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371998525946-1</Id><Topic><Title>Business Insider Article- Laid Off IBM Employee Says The Company Is Blowing It By Cutting The Wrong People- Julie Bort</Title><Username>medchemlead</Username><Timestamp>1371345283585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 21:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So the best timing is to sell at "EPS to $20 by 2015", and not affected by "Road Kill".</Msg><Username>maoxie</Username><Timestamp>1371998525946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-23 10:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372014157667-2</Id><Title>Monthly Unique Visitors of Local Corp (market-cap only 38 million) will increase after my estimate to about 120 million in Q2/2013 - an increase of more than 10%against the about 106 million in Q1/2013.</Title><Msg>The math is very simple, because we know the monthly unique visitors of two from three months of Q2/2013: 04/2013: 23,785,928 Monthly Unique Visitors 05/2013: 27,804,187 Monthly Unique Visitors If we now take the averarge of this two months in June 06/2013: 25,800,000 Monthly Unique Vistors (very conserative estimate) That are together 77.4 million Monthly Unique Visitors from the Flagship-Site of Local Corp in Q2/2013. In Q1/2013 had Local Corp reported about more than 12 million every month - and Local Corp has expanded the network strong in last time and my estimate for Q2/2013 is 13 million from the network ervery month = 39 million from the network in Q2/2013 (very conserative estimate). If we now add the 77,4 million from the flagshipsite and the 39 million from the network = 116.4 million Monthly Unique Visitors of Local Corp in Q2/2013 by a very conserative estimate and a reach of near 120 million by a more optimistic view (for example by an estimate of same Monthly Unique Visitors on the flagshipsite in June like in May).</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372014157667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-23 15:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372014739337-3</Id><Topic><Title>Monthly Unique Visitors of Local Corp (market-cap only 38 million) will increase after my estimate to about 120 million in Q2/2013 - an increase of more than 10%against the about 106 million in Q1/2013.</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372014157667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-23 15:02:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why the valuation of Local Corp with lower than 40 million is one of the biggest jokes the Nasdaq had ever seen The Inflection Point of Local Corp is Now • Five material challenges in 24 months withstood »Significant cost to the company in revenue and earnings • Highest revenue per employee ever »Projected growth to about $900k per employee EOY »Running lean! • Returning to profit »Significant cost savings starting 1Q13 »Achieved 1Q13 Positive Adjusted EBITDA »Achieved positive cash from operations from 1Q13 Reuters: Local Corp Issues FY 2013 Guidance; Revenue Guidance In Line With Analysts' Estimates Local Corp Issues FY 2013 Guidance; Revenue Guidance In Line With Analysts' Estimates Thursday, 9 May 2013 04:15pm EDT Local Corp announced that for fiscal 2013, it expects revenue of between $93 million and $95 million and adjusted EBITDA to be at least $5 million. According to I/B/E/S Estimates, analysts are expecting the Company to report revenue of $95 million and EBITDA of $5.80 million for fiscal 2013.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372014739337</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-23 15:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372032579328-4</Id><Topic><Title>made 60k on IBM puts!!!!</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1366434222044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 01:03:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TCCTT</Msg><Username>stockfater</Username><Timestamp>1372032579328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-23 20:09:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>