<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-29"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372488581192-1</Id><Topic><Title>layoffs are a sign of trouble</Title><Username>frombadtoworse</Username><Timestamp>1372431608619</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:00:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder if an amoral company can survive. You can only cut US jobs for so long. I don't know, maybe management should learn how to make what the customers want and maybe they should learn how to sell said product instead of destroying the lives of the people that are actually doing their jobs and doing them well. What a joke</Msg><Username>ohnonotagainenoughallready</Username><Timestamp>1372488581192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 02:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372502092443-2</Id><Topic><Title>layoffs are a sign of trouble</Title><Username>frombadtoworse</Username><Timestamp>1372431608619</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:00:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The days of the ugly American international carpet baggers are over. If you do biz in China you need Chinese employees -- same is true in Japan or just about any industrialized country including India. If IBM employees were distributed by revenue, than about 30% would be North American. It looks like it's less than that by design. What makes you think your view is superior to IBM management?</Msg><Username>man_the_ramparts</Username><Timestamp>1372502092443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 06:34:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372510277074-3</Id><Topic><Title>layoffs are a sign of trouble</Title><Username>frombadtoworse</Username><Timestamp>1372431608619</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:00:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>be damned? Really? When the layoffs have been going on for 20 years and flat revenue, yeah, go ahead, load up. LMAO</Msg><Username>teamb562</Username><Timestamp>1372510277074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 08:51:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372510591323-4</Id><Topic><Title>the cycle of down is here</Title><Username>sell_quickly</Username><Timestamp>1372447188975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:19:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well, when a pig gets fat and lazy and blames the piglets for everything, it can do nothing but sink</Msg><Username>teamb562</Username><Timestamp>1372510591323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 08:56:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372510984458-5</Id><Topic><Title>look for ~185-182 ......</Title><Username>txtrader77</Username><Timestamp>1372440406888</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>price will recover?? Really? What do you base this on...mass layoffs or is Genie going to pull a rabbit out of her trick hat at a board meeting before she gets fired? Maybe she will pull out 90,000 US RA's to show a profit.</Msg><Username>teamb562</Username><Timestamp>1372510984458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:03:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372513944008-6</Id><Title>strong sell</Title><Msg>ibm is absolutely bearish just now just like orcl and aapl</Msg><Username>simulpaolo68</Username><Timestamp>1372513944008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:52:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372519636098-7</Id><Topic><Title>look for ~185-182 ......</Title><Username>txtrader77</Username><Timestamp>1372440406888</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>history ... history ... history .. coupled with the fact the IBM has one of the most astute mgmt teams anywhere ... study the markets , study history , study IBM ... the company is still running on Sam's programs , which are fine ... BTW did you notice that Oracle and Accenture also got beaten up ... Friday's swoon was not IBM related .... g</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1372519636098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:27:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372519674817-8</Id><Topic><Title>Can someone ...</Title><Username>cangelosi_g</Username><Timestamp>1372364918651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 16:28:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>calm down and look to buy more ...</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1372519674817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:27:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372519761893-9</Id><Topic><Title>Can someone ...</Title><Username>cangelosi_g</Username><Timestamp>1372364918651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 16:28:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i would also posit that the Russell indexes being rejiggered on Friday had some effect also ... as Cramer would say .... "exogenous event" .. perfect time to reload the winners ... g</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1372519761893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372519828443-10</Id><Topic><Title>IBM looks bad here</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1372429154398</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:19:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good thing that opinions are personal ...</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1372519828443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:30:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372519899571-11</Id><Topic><Title>Traders Sell Now !</Title><Username>p1sorell</Username><Timestamp>1372354889886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 13:41:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes , the absolute best time to close the barn door , is when the horse is galloping down the lane .... dropping from 215 to 191 ??? that move is over ...</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1372519899571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372527608338-12</Id><Topic><Title>video message from CEO blaming the employees is a sign of trouble</Title><Username>frombadtoworse</Username><Timestamp>1372431826070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:03:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As if you think they are to blame? What an unctuous load of #$%$. No they are not to blame. Tthe average rank and file IBM employee works 20% overtime and still that isn't enough to please the execs and a-holes like you.</Msg><Username>nyse_marketmaker</Username><Timestamp>1372527608338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:40:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372531880978-13</Id><Topic><Title>video message from CEO blaming the employees is a sign of trouble</Title><Username>frombadtoworse</Username><Timestamp>1372431826070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:03:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To say that" The average rank and file IBM employee" is who Ginny blamed for the soft revenue is a complete canard. She blamed the IBM sales staff for not closing deals in process. And the IBM sales staff is compensated above the average IBM employee to close sales. That's exactly what the IBM CFO said during the conference call and at a 5/24/13 Barkley's investor conference. Below is an excerpt from Business Insider summary of her video: "IBM CEO Ginny Rometty After last week's poor earnings, IBM CEO Virginia Rometty "delivered a rare companywide reprimand" in the form of a five-minute long video memo, Spencer Ante of the Wall Street Journal reports. Rometty said, "Where we haven't transformed rapidly enough, we struggled. We have to step up with that and deal with that, and that is on all levels." During IBM's earnings call, executives blamed IBM's sales team for the worse-than-expected quarter. Rometty revisited this theme in her video. "We were too slow to understand the value and then engage on the approval and the sign-off process," she said. "The result? It didn't get done." She said that from now on, IBM will respond to all client contact within 24 hour"</Msg><Username>mr_dinky_dot_bomb</Username><Timestamp>1372531880978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:51:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372537431255-14</Id><Title>And now a message from one of my heros - David Stockman (The Great Deformation)</Title><Msg>BIG BLUE: STOCK BUYBACK CONTRAPTION ON STEROIDS IBM’s huge buyback program shows financial engineering helped by the Fed’s “”bubble”” finance regime enables companies to literally “”BUY”” themselves a higher stock price. During the 5 years ending in fiscal 2011, the company spent a staggering 67 BILLION repurchasing its own shares, a figure that was equal to 100 percent of its NET income. The buy-back program brought approximately 550 million or 36% of the 1.5.billion shares outstanding into its treasury. Nearly 40% of these shares reentered the float, mainly to refresh the management stock option kitty. Former CEO Sam Palmisano cashed out 110 million of stock options a few weeks after his retirement party. The problem remains that IBM’s earnings – like nearly all big cap global companies – could not be flattered permanently by the Fed’s BUBBLE finance. And now the weakening Euro will take its toll on the company’s reported results. With nearly two_thirds of its sales outside the United States, the company’s sales are now falling in dollar terms and will likely continue. During the last 5 years IBM spent less on capital investment than its depreciation and amortization charges, and also shrank its constant dollar spending for R/D by nearly 2% annually. Neither of these trends is compatible with staying on top of the fiercely competitive tech industry. I don't own IBM stock anymore nor have any Short interest - its just a little info for you to ponder - I don’t care what you do.</Msg><Username>ib_millionaire</Username><Timestamp>1372537431255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 16:23:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372543825832-15</Id><Title>Lots of insider was selling</Title><Msg>The sales must be very bad. IBM is too big. It seems that it is in a business of trading people. Is it really the corporate model you want of US - shipping high pay job offshar? As India salary is rising, it is not as profitable as before, Firing will Euro business is still down, China - slow, US may be the same as last year. So, it cannot grow either. P/E for a non-growth stock should be around 10. Just good enough to beat inflation + the premium for risk. It falls into the utility category.and P/E should be around 10 in my view. I will wait till the correction of this stock finish before jumping in. .</Msg><Username>topinvestgun1</Username><Timestamp>1372543825832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 18:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372564433990-16</Id><Title>Will become a cheaper price soon</Title><Msg>I expect to see IBM at $155 or less by end of July.</Msg><Username>shoathai</Username><Timestamp>1372564433990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 23:53:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>