<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370098261976-1</Id><Topic><Title>Bought at $10.00</Title><Username>zer0t0l</Username><Timestamp>1369971489413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 23:38:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 1966 the stock traded around $350 until May when it split 3:2 and traded around $550. So you are claiming to have purchased the stock at a pre-split price in the $350 or $550 range 47 years ago. And because you are the greatest genius who ever lived or the biggest idiot (no way to tell from here) you had the foresight to keep it through the Akers collapse and the internet collapse and the 2008 housing bubble collapse. But if you really invest that way then why didn't you just buy the S&amp;P at 72 (it's 1630 right now). Or - even better - 30 treasuries at 18% in the early '80s. Or gold in 2004 at $325. Or Apple 10 years ago at $7 (it went to $700), or GOOG at $98 in 2005 (it's 900 just 7 years later). So you missed all of those AAPL, GOOG, gold, 30 treas, S&amp;P, but you picked IBM and that is the one you held onto for 47 years. And let's not forget Berkshire - $2600 to $171,000 since 1987 (65X in27 years) versus IBM (20X in 47 years).</Msg><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1370098261976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370131281602-2</Id><Topic><Title>Bought at $10.00</Title><Username>zer0t0l</Username><Timestamp>1369971489413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 23:38:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I worked for the company and they had a great stock options plan. Your purchase price was at 85% and if the stock was down, you never bought for less than the price you optioned in on that day. The stock would rocket up to and beyond 200 for example but your option date/price was based on 100. You payed 85% of 100 for the year for a stock that was listed at 200.</Msg><Username>zer0t0l</Username><Timestamp>1370131281602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 20:01:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>