<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371650167816-1</Id><Title>Bernanke - -Greenspan Clone</Title><Msg>Today's WSJ lead editorial: "In 2003 Alan Greenspan and a certain new governor named Ben Bernanke cited deflation risks to justify holding the fed funds rate at 1% for an entire yeareven though as the economy was accelerating. This was the original sin that did so much to produce the housing bubble and financial bubble." Deja vu</Msg><Username>p1sorell</Username><Timestamp>1371650167816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 09:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371653760472-2</Id><Title>SANTALLI !!!!!!! ?????</Title><Msg>LOL!!!!LOL!!!!!! too much coffee this AM ??? LOL!!!! that was good</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1371653760472</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 10:56:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371656329201-3</Id><Title>Sale of servers to Leveno</Title><Msg>Is IBM going to divest the server division</Msg><Username>oppsforegoodnews</Username><Timestamp>1371656329201</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 11:38:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371676585036-4</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and layoffs</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1370366399824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:19:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. The subject of that sentence was "one of those really smart people" so the correct English sentence is: "One of those really smart people who doesn't have a clue." The key is the word "One." "One who doesn't." Get it??? You are both excellent examples of our nation's public school system.</Msg><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1371676585036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 17:16:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371677629786-5</Id><Title>Stop Whining... Stop Complaining... Get back to Work...</Title><Msg>If IBM is such a terrible place to work then why not just go somewhere else. That's what shareholders do. If we don't like an investment we dump it and move on. If it loses money and our confidence falls we cut our losses. Everyone will say how difficult it is to find another job in this economy - but some employees have hung on for a decade while they complain what a #$%$ place IBM is. There's no excuse for that. If you can't find another job in a few years then the problem is you not the company. If the shareholders are happy - and they are - then who cares what the employees think. And to those who point to stock buybacks and financial engineering; that is exactly what IBM should be doing. I would say they represent their shareholders' interests better than almost any other company. Employees are just like wrenches and hammers. There's a Home Depot every few miles and they have tons of wrenches and hammers. So stop complaining and plan your own future instead of counting on IBM.</Msg><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1371677629786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 17:33:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371680238185-6</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and layoffs</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1370366399824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:19:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Per an article in a Chicago regional paper this AM (Daily Herald) there are roughly 30K manufacturing jobs going begging in northern Illinois right now. Part of that is undoubtedly due to the state's lousy financial condition, but much of it is due to the fact that when high school grads hear "manufacturing" they think of 1940s and 1950s foundry conditions--hot, dirty, dangerous, physically exhausting. and with low wages. That isn't necessarily the case any more, but the high school guidance counsellors are still pushing "get a college degree--ANY college degree--to get higher salaries." Bachelors's degrees in history, english lit., and political science no longer result in good jobs with big paychecks.</Msg><Username>sq_rigger</Username><Timestamp>1371680238185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 18:17:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371685625143-7</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and layoffs</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1370366399824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:19:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yup .. and the American worker (and nonworkers) don't take anything for granted , right ??? LOL .. i guess that they just feel entitled .... life , and it's components, are what you make it/them .... a long time ago , I complained that i had no shoes , then i met a man who had no feet .... if you still have your feet .. get out there and do it .... g</Msg><Username>iamgarce</Username><Timestamp>1371685625143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 19:47:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371689380760-8</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes Aricle- Peter Cohan "As It Shrinks In A Growing Market, Does IBM Have A Strategy?"</Title><Username>medchemlead</Username><Timestamp>1371440098107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 23:34:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Restructuring charges doubled over the past year. So it's a big fat gamble - like everything else. We'll find out soon enough. Investing is always a gamble.</Msg><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1371689380760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 20:49:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371689683808-9</Id><Topic><Title>Sale of servers to Leveno</Title><Username>oppsforegoodnews</Username><Timestamp>1371656329201</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 11:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're back with the same drivel ? I thought you were annoying other boards but NOoo ! You're back here !</Msg><Username>zer0t0l</Username><Timestamp>1371689683808</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 20:54:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371693435463-10</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and layoffs</Title><Username>jand2357</Username><Timestamp>1370366399824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:19:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes - I get it. You are clueless. I suggest writing James Kilpatrick and let him help you see the light. I have little time for debating someone with limited intellect.</Msg><Username>copywrites</Username><Timestamp>1371693435463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 21:57:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>