<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-06"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370522817494-1</Id><Title>Looks like I have found another winner. Check out IOGA</Title><Msg>Do some DD on IOGA . I think with the right momentum we could soar past $1</Msg><Username>matthewsbrody230</Username><Timestamp>1370522817494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:46:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370546850580-2</Id><Topic><Title>#1 championship diving...</Title><Username>bigk95133</Username><Timestamp>1370459954332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:19:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>look like it...</Msg><Username>shoathai</Username><Timestamp>1370546850580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370571478797-3</Id><Title>Dear Ms Rometty</Title><Msg>Dear Ms Rometty -a piece of advice : it is YOU who must step up to the plate, like you told your employees to do in April. The buck does indeed stop with you. If the quarter prior to your "pep talk" to employees was not that great, it is YOU who are ultimately accountable. True leaders say "We must step up to the plate", not chide employees and say "You must step up to the plate". As long as you don't include top management in the great blue milieu that is IBM, and isolate yourselves in an Armonk ivory tower, you create a great divide that is not in the best interest of the corporation, and which perpetuates the stagnation and diminished productivity. Lead by example. Take a pay cut. Take a $1 annual salary for a year to offset the circa 16 million you got in a previous year, and still be okay. You can pay over 160 rank and file employees with the corporate savings that would entail. Do not demoralize your employees. Inspire them. Empower them. Walk the halls of the different units of the corporation around the nation and the world, speak to the rank and file employee, get to know your people; those in the trenches for corporation who give of themselves, and not the sycophants in the top management vying for favors and selfish attention. "Walk with kings, but don't lose the common touch". To lead well requires a modicum of humility and a great deal of selflessness. To lead you must command respect. To command respect, you must earn it. To earn it you must know your people. Really get to know your people. As an engineer understand how all the cogs fit together to make Big Blue work to find out where the machinery can be better oiled or tuned. Corporate success is not written in a Business School "How to" manual, looking at only the next quarter's profits by implementing cutbacks and layoffs. That has oft been done, and fails as a strategy in the long term because it creates a disloyal and edgy workforce always uncertain of their future. Big Blue deserves better.</Msg><Username>medchemlead</Username><Timestamp>1370571478797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 22:17:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370572979826-4</Id><Topic><Title>Dear Ms Rometty</Title><Username>medchemlead</Username><Timestamp>1370571478797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 22:17:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great speech medcem but if Gini took a pay cut it would scare me. I would have to sell my shares since the pay cut would indicate that the company is indeed losing money. However, by the time a CEO takes a cut the bad news was baked into the stock price and that price was reduced big time.</Msg><Username>zer0t0l</Username><Timestamp>1370572979826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 22:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>