<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-18"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345263173000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Moves Into the Mobile Market</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345211669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The single core Medfield has hyperthreading. For the phone/tablet applications it seems to scale nicely so performance is somewhere between a one and two core CPU. I think it is about 1.6x a single core. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hyper_threading A number of the issues of the CISC vs RISC PC wars will repeat themselves again. Unless things have changed dramatically, ARM code size will be about 40% larger than the same Atom version. That leads to a lower code cache miss rate and fewer memory operations. More of the combined LLC will be available for data. That leads to fewer data cache misses. The buffers driving the buses to the memory consume lots of power. It is very hard to distill the argument down to a frequency vs frequency comparison. There are a number of issues on both sides that muddy the comparison. I would probably look at the operation and standby times of systems built on both chips. There is a lot of discussion about process benefits. Those who say that processes are equal are in the minority. With 22nm Ivy Bridge hitting 50% of Intel CPU shipments this quarter, it shows how fast Intel can convert and ramp. It seems to be several times as fast as TSMC is doing.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1345263173000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:12:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345264431000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Moves Into the Mobile Market</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345211669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Medfield based Lava Xolo has half the normalized battery life of an A5 based IPhone4s on web browsing workloads.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1345264431000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:33:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345268425000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Moves Into the Mobile Market</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345211669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep. Lava web browsing on 3g net is only about half. Battery life while talking, performance loads and many of the other test results, however, are in the same range. Not the best but not the universal half. Page 6 Battery Life Lava Xolo X900 Review - The First Intel Medfield Phone by Brian Klug on 4/25/2012 http://www.anandtech.com/print/5770</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1345268425000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 01:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345277283000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Moves Into the Mobile Market</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345211669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Other ARM chips can't match the A5 performance either which suggests it is not the application processor that is causing this difference. Intel will reduce the power/core by having a new Atom design built with all the experience of the first generation and by having very specialized LP version of the already very low leakage 22nm process. Since Pentium 4 Intel have been exemplary in producing great new designs and I expect Silvermont to be no different. Medfield was just a toe in the water but Silvermont will show what Intel can really do on a very advanced mobile chip as if their future depended on it and in effect their future large growth does. If you expect only incremental progress you will probably be very disappointed, I expect new bar raising on both performance and power usage.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1345277283000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 04:08:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345278588000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Moves Into the Mobile Market</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345211669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The point I'm making is Intel is not uniquely positioned to make greater progress than competitors on either architecture or process. Both camps will make about the same amount of progress if you buy the law of averages. I would tilt the balance in favor of the ARM camp because they have much more momentum in low power. Medfield is not a first generation design. They've been pitching "low-power IA" for some time now.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1345278588000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 04:29:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345281873000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Moves Into the Mobile Market</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345211669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ARMH stock price always climbs above Intc until earnings reporting.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1345281873000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 05:24:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345292807000-7</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Tablets to cost 300 bucks less than Intel Tablets</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1345160386000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:39:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>irrelevant... _______________ The perfect word for ARM 64.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1345292807000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:26:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345294128000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Moves Into the Mobile Market</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345211669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Medfield is not a first generation design.' Its architectural core is even if the chip energy management has evolved over different SoC generations. That us why you can pick any Atom from any series (N,D,Z) and rely on very similar performance characteristics. ' Both camps will make about the same amount of progress if you buy the law of averages. I would tilt the balance in favor of the ARM camp because they have much more momentum in low power.' The law of averages has not helped AMD much ;-). The fact that ARM has had that momentum for so long does not imply there is much low hanging fruit left for them whereas Atom was Intel's first serious attempt at a low power architecture. I would put more credence on Intel's architects making progress than any architectural team in the ARM world which is split up amongst ARMH, QCOM, AAPL, NVDA etc.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1345294128000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345295147000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Moves Into the Mobile Market</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345211669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARMH, QCOM, AAPL, NVDA are all building the next generation of chips that have been validated in the market by high volume sales. You couldn't say that of Medfield. Intel is shooting at a moving target. Raw architecture and process optimization don't necessarily translate into chips that your customers could fly with. I suspect Motorola was arm-twisted into building Medfield based phones and even they are not exclusive Intel.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1345295147000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:05:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345296384000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Moves Into the Mobile Market</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345211669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It comes down to a question of will at some point. How badly does Intel want to join in the smartphone/tablet market? Intel is focusing billions of dollars of resources into CAPEX just to get them to a point of not only producing 14nm smart phone chips but in numbers that are mind blowing. Had ARM successfully transitioned into 28nm this year to the point that most of the cutting edge phones on the market would currently be using them I would have agreed with your statement of ARM momentum. They are having problems ramping up production of sub-30nm. Intel can afford to make better products for a cheaper price. Then they can afford to get sales people out to get design wins of new products using Intel. Unlike the PC industry the phone industry can be dominated by the right contracts with a few key suppliers. But, let's just imagine that Intel is locked out of Samsung and Apple. Let's just say they would be exclusively ARM until their last day in business. Intel can make design reference phones for all the large mobile carriers. They can go to AT&amp;T and tell them how to get a $150 Intel phone. AT&amp;T can be in charge of pushing out updates on their schedule. They can offer it for less (free with contract). Intel can help pay for co-branded advertising. There are so many things that Intel can do that ARM cannot do. It's no longer a question of "if" Intel wants in at the table, it's more of a question of how many seats it will take. If you are betting on ARM you are backing the wrong team.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345296384000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:26:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345296706000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Windows RT tablets will be $300 cheaper than Windows 8 devices</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345216522000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:15:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"According to Schmoock, Windows 8 tablets will cost between $600 and $700, meaning that Windows RT devices should tip up for aroud $400, in the same ballpark as most Android tablets." That's bad news for RT. In order to gain traction it needs to come in a half of an Android tablet. Looks like it will be another ARM shelf warmer. Hey thanks for the good news. RT is worse off than I thought! BTW, who is anxiously waiting for any Windows 8 devices?</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345296706000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:31:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345297228000-12</Id><Title>Just A Weekend Thought</Title><Msg>With summer vacation continuing next week, expect volume to stay very thin. Both the DJIA and the S&amp;P 500 are now only a hair under their multiyear highs. The magnet from those highs is likely to bring the indexes to their new multiyear highs. Should the breakout happen in a decisive fashion, expect bears to capitulate. Complacency is on the rise. But with the central bankers having their hands out ready to stop any fall, downside is limited. The melt-up could go a little further. have a nice weekend</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1345297228000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345297288000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Moves Into the Mobile Market</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345211669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel wants to join and bring IA along. They need to leave IA at the door and bring only their process advantage to the table, but they are having trouble swallowing this pill.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1345297288000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:41:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345297407000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Just a Few Thoughts for You Folks-</Title><Username>stewpidstewie</Username><Timestamp>1345220148000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 12:15:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have a great sense of humor. This was hilarious. have a nice weekend.</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1345297407000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:43:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345297861000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Moves Into the Mobile Market</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345211669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the advantages of x86 is they won't have to be vendor specific. Everyone will have the same chip and are free to program them to their own specs.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1345297861000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345298266000-16</Id><Title>still waiting for the tablet fad to cool down</Title><Msg>I tried to use the tablet, but it's too uncomfortable having to hunch your neck all the time. I find the netbook much more comfortble.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1345298266000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:57:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345302554000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Windows RT tablets will be $300 cheaper than Windows 8 devices</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345216522000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:15:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Windows RT devices should tip up for aroud $400" http://www.forbes.com/sites/netapp/2012/08/14/windows-rt-tablet-price-release-date-otoh/</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345302554000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:09:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345302737000-18</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Tablets to cost 300 bucks less than Intel Tablets</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1345160386000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:39:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>irrelevant... "The perfect word for ARM 64." ------------------------------------------ Then provide one shred of info about it... Or in reality... you have NO CLUE... NONE !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345302737000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:12:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345306693000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 3 issues?</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345233168000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 15:52:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't change the fact that Tegra3 is having battery life issues and may heat up considerably. It's what's to be expected when you do more complicated computing.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345306693000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:18:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345306837000-20</Id><Topic><Title>A Brief History of Semiconductors Edit</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1345215164000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:52:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you skip ahead to chapter titled "Sub 30nm, and other fiascos?"</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345306837000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:20:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345308629000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 3 issues?</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345233168000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 15:52:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fair enough, when INtel gets their tablets out... we can compare them to the future ARM teblets that will be available at that time...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345308629000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:50:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345309052000-22</Id><Title>Rombo dropped 4 pts in Raspukin poll. Down 2 now.</Title><Msg>VP pick is a death blow.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1345309052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:57:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345314061000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Extreme Caution!</Title><Username>cyruskkg073</Username><Timestamp>1345294285000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:51:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the free video</Msg><Username>diannwfa254</Username><Timestamp>1345314061000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:21:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>45</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345315703000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 3 issues?</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345233168000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 15:52:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with your comments regarding Tegra 3 issues. Google sales 2 version 199$ and 249$ versions of Nexus 7. Both are sold for a loss, google is trying to compete with Amazon low end kindle and to give some answer to iPads. I played with the Nexus 7, it doess look nice but other than that it looks like enlarged smartphone. imo, the Thinkpad tablet with windows 8 will take the stage and will leave other tablets including ipad in the dust.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345315703000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:48:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345320179000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Tegra 3 issues?</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345233168000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 15:52:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with your comments regarding Tegra 3 issues. Google sales 2 version 199$ and 249$ versions of Nexus 7. Both are sold for a loss, google is trying to compete with Amazon low end kindle and to give some answer to iPads. ----- Not quite: When additional costs are considered, IHS estimates that Google will at least break even on sales of the 8GByte model, priced at $199—and will make a modest profit on the 16Gbyte version, which is priced at $249. http://www.isuppli.com/Teardowns/News/pages/Low-End-Google-Nexus-7-Carries-$157-BOM-Teardown-Reveals.aspx</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1345320179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 16:02:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345323557000-26</Id><Title>Company on the line at IDF &amp; no Paul O.?</Title><Msg>He's not even going to be there?? Intel needs to impress at IDF by blowing the doors off with Haswell performance details. Intel is losing too much mindshare.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1345323557000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 16:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345327441000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Company on the line at IDF &amp; no Paul O.?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1345323557000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 16:59:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I heard he's not going just to tick you off. No kidding, that's what I heard!</Msg><Username>backstreetboy_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1345327441000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:04:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345328702000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Rombo dropped 4 pts in Raspukin poll. Down 2 now.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1345309052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:57:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This may have something to do with it: http://www.dailyfinance.com/2012/08/17/romney-bain-closes-us-plant-workers-train-chinese-replacements/ Way to go Bain Capital.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1345328702000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345329131000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Rombo dropped 4 pts in Raspukin poll. Down 2 now.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1345309052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:57:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RED ALERT</Msg><Username>wallisweavergayalias_alert</Username><Timestamp>1345329131000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345331485000-30</Id><Title>INtel Xeon Phi</Title><Msg>http://vr-zone.com/articles/intel-s-mic-xeon-phi-die-has-62-cores-and-was-aimed-for-clocks-much-higher-than-1ghz-to-fight-nvidia-gk110/17019.html</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345331485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345331629000-31</Id><Title>Powered by HONDA</Title><Msg>Powered by HONDA Spirit by Senna</Msg><Username>bilng_sinte</Username><Timestamp>1345331629000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:13:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345331963000-32</Id><Title>Warren Buffett Dumps All Shares of Intel</Title><Msg>"Unfortunately for Intel, this also doesn't change the fact that they are now seeing pressure from companies like NVIDIA and Qualcomm from both the consumer and enterprise business segments that once held so strongly." http://www.brightsideofnews.com/news/2012/8/17/investment-oracle-of-omaha-warren-buffett-dumps-all-shares-of-intel.aspx</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345331963000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:19:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345332235000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffett Dumps All Shares of Intel</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345331963000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:19:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then again, GETANID61 DETESTS Intel and fails to post the FACT that the shares of Intel were sold by someone, NOT NAMED WARREN BUFFETT within Warren Buffet's company. He also fails to mention that Intel bought back an infinite amount MORE shares this year than Buffet's company sold. Again, the original poster is an Intel hater looking for ANYTHING to feed his horny fantasies of Intel collapsing. PS, ARMH has lost 30% since he started pumping it here last year....Intel up 30%.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1345332235000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:23:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345332478000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffett Dumps All Shares of Intel</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345331963000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:19:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>psssssstt. He also fails to mention that Buffet has openly stated that he doesn't understand Tech. Furthermore, he fails to mention that Intel was sold at a PROFIT, unlike his other Tech holdings AND that Buffet's company bought GM earlier this year after selling some Intel and GM promptly tanked. Buffet = Gambling old coot. Getanid61 = paid Intel basher.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1345332478000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:27:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345332827000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffett Dumps All Shares of Intel</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345331963000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:19:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks like more NVDA pipe dream than anything else.. imo, another NVDA drop is coming</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345332827000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345333149000-36</Id><Title>POWERED by HONDA</Title><Msg>POWERED by HONDA</Msg><Username>bilng_sinte</Username><Timestamp>1345333149000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:39:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345334041000-37</Id><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Msg>http://www.electronista.com/articles/12/08/14/similar.amount.subsidized.by.microsoft.for.xbox.360.at.launch/</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345334424000-38</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And subsequent articles saying no way the price will be that low. Unless they price it at what might really sell and absorb the huge losses...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345334424000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 20:00:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345334584000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Rombo dropped 4 pts in Raspukin poll. Down 2 now.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1345309052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:57:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney's VP pick has cost him my vote. Anyone who represents himself as an uber budget guy and votes for two unfunded wars and an unfunded prescription drug bill is a total fraud in my world. And there is the issue of every single republican in congress signing the no new tax pledge of Grover Norquist. Didn't we elect these guys to represent us good, bad or ugly? I don't remember voting for Grover Norquist.</Msg><Username>semiwiz2002</Username><Timestamp>1345334584000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 20:03:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345336021000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is he posting this over and over again? Unless it's close to free it won't have a lot of traction. I think RT stands for "Released Too-Late."</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345336021000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 20:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345336537000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>199$ price is what's it's worth to be fair</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345336537000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 20:35:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345337098000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Rombo dropped 4 pts in Raspukin poll. Down 2 now.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1345309052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:57:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder how much $ Slick Willard will pocket as a result of this very anti-American deal?</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1345337098000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 20:44:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345339578000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Rombo dropped 4 pts in Raspukin poll. Down 2 now.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1345309052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:57:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you notice, it is already too late. take that.</Msg><Username>qubic_ytile</Username><Timestamp>1345339578000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 21:26:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345339688000-44</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is he posting this over and over again? ____________________________________________ Because he's a Euro-TRASH Hypocrite who in one breath crucifies people for posting old articles and in the next breath.......he posts old articles over and over. One of the scummiest posters to ever touch this board.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1345339688000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 21:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345339781000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffett Dumps All Shares of Intel</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345331963000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:19:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this the same Nvidia who's CEO begged Intel to Fab its chips? lol....</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1345339781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 21:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345339939000-46</Id><Title>Nvidia begging Intel to make its chips...</Title><Msg>......lol http://www.forbes.com/sites/briancaulfield/2012/03/22/nvidia-intel-should-let-us-build-chips-in-its-factories/</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1345339939000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 21:32:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345341031000-47</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffett Dumps All Shares of Intel</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345331963000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:19:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Understanding why Warren Buffett is clueless: http://seekingalpha.com/article/815271-understanding-why-warren-buffett-sold-intel?source=yahoo</Msg><Username>golf_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1345341031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 21:50:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345342332000-48</Id><Topic><Title>What a great find!</Title><Username>rochjbt724</Username><Timestamp>1345302361000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:06:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent commentary!</Msg><Username>kathyeuav891</Username><Timestamp>1345342332000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 22:12:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345343439000-49</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they do, the 4 remaining OEM RT partners will basically bail on Win8 ARM devices. HP already got the message and has bailed on ARM altogether. RT at $199 is basically useless. You need to get to upgrade to around $400 to get something useful for the user. RT will go down as a failed attempt by Microsoft to try to create an "ecosystem" to compete with established Apple &amp; Android.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1345343439000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 22:30:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345344770000-50</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" HP already got the message and has bailed on ARM altogether." LIES !!! Partner Qualcomm ain't ready... "RT at $199 is basically useless" Any info ?? or you have NO CLUE... NONE !!!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345344770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 22:52:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345345226000-51</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LIES !!! Partner Qualcomm ain't ready... Any links to document your statement? Any info ?? or you have NO CLUE... NONE !!!!!! No LINKS? I guess everyone will have to just trust you. Noone lies on an anonymous message board.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1345345226000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 23:00:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345345755000-52</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LIES !!! Partner Qualcomm ain't ready... Any links to document your statement? --------------------------- you can google it, here's the first from a search... "The company had reportedly partnered with Qualcomm to build a Windows RT tablet, and Qualcomm's CES presentation last January made it clear that the company was very serious about breaking into the tablet/netbook market. With its major partner gone AWOL" http://hothardware.com/News/DisARMED--HP-Kills-ARMbased-Windows-Tablet-Likely-Thanks-To-Microsofts-Surface/ ------------------------------ Any info ?? or you have NO CLUE... NONE !!!!!! No LINKS? I guess everyone will have to just trust you. Noone lies on an anonymous message board. ---------------- I posted a link on the first post !!!! The rest are your claims !!!!!!!!!!!!!! Where are your links ??? Or rather you have NO CLUE... NONE !!!! to your claim</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345345755000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 23:09:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345348524000-53</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rule of thumb: you get what you pay for. If you pay $199 for a tablet you got yourself a $199 POS</Msg><Username>sanjitkumar23</Username><Timestamp>1345348524000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 23:55:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>