<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347251987896-1</Id><Topic><Title>Dissapointed to see Wally posting meaningless non-Intel stuff.......Here's a Q and A with Otellini</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347240229836</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 21:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bbb, Lets face it ..... it is "better to keep your mouth closed and be thought a fool than to open it and remove all doubt". Of course, noone thought you a fool until you started this baloney Paul O. stuff. Since Paul O. will retire in 4 years, he will be at the Intel helm until retirement. There is no chance of Intel changing CEO. Otellini is highly respected both inside and outside Intel. If that "really" bothers you and you believe your story, then I recommend that you take all your funds and short Intel back down to $20. I will applaud you for following your opinion 100%. However, I believe you will very unhappy for that decision.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1347251987896</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 00:39:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347272297688-2</Id><Title>Intel free to form a strong bottom here</Title><Msg>All is mostly upside from here i think. The risk is priced in and declared and you know the worse case and its over. So now we start the game of building to go higher. Maybe it takes time but who cares. Sell out of the money puts and dare it to go lower and buy a ton of call leaps then or deep in the money 1-2 months out calls at -2sd. But selling puts here is the safer option. I like to sell jan 2014 22s every time they go higher than 2.4 and close them at 2 or less and then wait for repeat later. I was out of sep calls due to getting close to expiration when we went over 25 so rapidly last week and hoped to use the money to go long November ones but the market closed a bit higher than my 25 exit and i waited one day for a possible better price and got lucky that it tanked big on the news without having entered the continuation October or November position. That was a close one but i ll take luck any day. I wont buy them yet unless we go even lower. If we dont go lower i will wait 1-2 days to see what they want to do with intel and then enter some calls for later months. I think the damage is done and its over now and therefore i am not afraid that much. However they may not let it run up big either so calls may be a hard play here until the case for bottom is safer and volatility goes a bit down again, hence the wait now. Selling puts in small numbers is the safer way to play any intel stabilization and if it drops more they are so easy to defend anyway. We will see 30 eventually this year or early next. Dont even worry about it. Its a very safe proposition. Obama will get reelected and then you start a new bull market after tax rates for the rich go higher finally and stupid republicans realize that they cant waste another 4 years trying to trash the economy to get the presidency. What punks! . You just dont know when they will stop the trashing on intel but it ought to be close.(same aholes that hate America hate also intel probably republican so#$%$ that love to short markets.) They may even start this week. At some point Friday intel was feeling like going all the way to 24.7 after first going to 24.01. It will obviously look a lot like a bargain sooner or later. Because well of course it bloody is one! And all this doom and gloom is just the set up for another round of earning beats and upgrades. Wait it out by selling puts after multiple bad days. Then watch them expire worthless or roll to lower strike or even let them be exercised and sell calls of same strike or one higher on these shares right away or on rallies. Easy money. Not as sexy as buying calls directly on buy signals for 100% runs but it has to be for now until they have had it with their #$%$ trashing.</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1347272297688</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 06:18:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347276846012-3</Id><Topic><Title>U know, why WB sold out INTC...insider info?</Title><Username>shares245</Username><Timestamp>1347238869354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 21:01:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WB will lose too if dow goes under 10k. He is mostly going long. He didn't make his fortune being short. Going short is like gambling. You lose more often in a bull market.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1347276846012</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 07:34:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347281053526-4</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>With the exception of the DJ Transportation index which is still lagging, all other major indexes are at or near their multiyear highs. Bulls clearly have the momentum while the low volume suggests that there is still plenty of skepticism out there that the uptrend started in June will last. Such skepticism could work in the bulls' favor, sending stocks melting up. If the market movements after the Fed's QE at the height of the subprime crisis in 2009 could provide guidance, stocks are heading higher now that the ECB is due to follow the Fed's path. With that said, the ECB's move still needs blessings from Germany and the market can be vulnerable to negative comments out of Germany on the ECB's decision. In addition, economic fundamentals will need to improve to support gains in stock prices on a longer term basis. On a short term basis, downside is likely contained. Buy dips and stay cautious and nimble.</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1347281053526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 08:44:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347282394497-5</Id><Title>IDF Tomorrow</Title><Msg>IDF starts tomorrow but today the board is again flooded with the big Wall Street firm affirming shills with the messages of doom and gloom. Wall Street doesn't care about US economic recovery. But you should. Send the letters...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347282394497</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347282607506-6</Id><Title>Barron's Says Housing Recovery is Real</Title><Msg>After an ugly six-year decline, home prices are starting to look up. Why the rebound is for real. Plus: What's next for the top 50 U.S. housing markets.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347282607506</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:10:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347282723120-7</Id><Title>Intel Sets The Bar At 10 Watts, Haswell Details Leak Ahead of IDF</Title><Msg>From HotHardware: Ahead of this week's IDF, Intel's annual Developer's Forum, the company let an interesting number slip through the cracks: 10W. With all of the leaks we've seen so far, along with information Intel itself has revealed, it's clear that the company has been focusing like never before on power efficiency with its Haswell microarchitecture. "10W" highlights that well. As Intel's TDP ratings include the GPU, that number becomes all the more impressive.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347282723120</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:12:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347282877310-8</Id><Title>The PC Isn't Dying: Don't Sell Into The Sensationalism</Title><Msg>In the recent article, "Dead Money Walking: Sell PC Players And Buy Apple Before It's Too Late" by David Alton Clark, the author suggests that investors sell their PC-oriented players and jump into buying shares of Apple (AAPL) as quickly as possible. I have to respectfully disagree with Mr. Clark and urge the prudent investor to not follow the herd by selling the temporarily beaten down PC stocks. [That would be the big Wall Street firm self-serving sensationalism...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347282877310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:14:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347283366346-9</Id><Topic><Title>The PC Isn't Dying: Don't Sell Into The Sensationalism</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347282877310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:14:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Although I like INTC, you can't fight the slow down in PC sales. It is real. They are not dead, just decreasing in demand which will squeeze INTC's sales and margins. On the positive side, INTC is cheap. Look at the earnings and dividend. They have the ability to make acquisitions and branch out. But it is not a strong buy. A hold at best.</Msg><Username>binnybozo</Username><Timestamp>1347283366346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:22:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347284002082-10</Id><Title>INTC getting crushed again...</Title><Msg>typical for the Paul O. era. He's almost as bad a CEO as Bryant was.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1347284002082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:33:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347284217850-11</Id><Title>Wallis</Title><Msg>I do like one thing about Intel. They create a lot of jobs in America. It's unfortunate that Andy Grove created a culture of mean-ness and winner take all. That worked for a while (or did it?) It's hard to tell whether Intel was just another company swept up in the internet bubble. Oh, their fabs are second to none also. Great fabs. The CPUs are still basically 386's. Thirty year old designs now, can you believe it?</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347284217850</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:36:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347284295369-12</Id><Title>OBAMA ECONOMY GOING WOBBLY...</Title><Msg>...and the Wall Street insiders - mostly Democrat - have been propping up the Chief by low volume selling back and forth. Just like other great Leftist fiascos - think U.S.S.R. of yesteryear or China's cooked books today - the rule of natural economic law will out.</Msg><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1347284295369</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:38:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347284354910-13</Id><Title>INTC in trouble 3Q</Title><Msg>Next earning, INTC will deeply slide below $21. Good time for a short on this stock CSCO &amp; JNPR will advance to $25. Watch N learn.</Msg><Username>chidragon38</Username><Timestamp>1347284354910</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:39:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347284695716-14</Id><Topic><Title>INTC in trouble 3Q</Title><Username>chidragon38</Username><Timestamp>1347284354910</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:39:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, with the Q3 results already locked in there is going to be a slide. Sorry, Butkus (I mean Lucy). But with Intel's pre-preemptive strike, the only thing that can happen on the Q3 announcement is a bump for Intel. You know they put some slack into the estimate. Who else in the world would post up a Intel bash/Cisco pump other than Lucy? The cockroaches are out, the bottom is in...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347284695716</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:44:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347284732750-15</Id><Title>Wow, 23's and market hasn't even corrected yet !</Title><Msg>This could go lower than last summer, and I thought that was unthinkable.</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1347284732750</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347284803945-16</Id><Topic><Title>The PC Isn't Dying: Don't Sell Into The Sensationalism</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347282877310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:14:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No matter how you cut it the stock is a pig.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1347284803945</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:46:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347284827249-17</Id><Title>Intel P/E is 10</Title><Msg>Yet Wall Street's biggest firms are in full-on attack mode. Send the letters...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347284827249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:47:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347285147700-18</Id><Topic><Title>Intel P/E is 10</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347284827249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Send the letter to whom ? Your daddy?</Msg><Username>nj_maverick</Username><Timestamp>1347285147700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347285265442-19</Id><Topic><Title>How many trading days left until ...</Title><Username>jimbo_homegamed_u</Username><Timestamp>1302902388000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2011-04-15 17:19:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis Weaver Day? President Barry Obama has declared May 21 Wallis Weaver Day, a national day of remembrance: "In six months those who bought Intel at 24 will look just fine." Wallis Weaver, May 21, 2010 ====================================================================== WALLUS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! YO MAMA BE CALLIN' YOU!</Msg><Username>myle_der_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1347285265442</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347285824982-20</Id><Title>New investing App</Title><Msg>I have just created a new android app that keeps an updated record of all the important FDA dates. Its called "Drugdates" and you can check it in the Google Play Marketplace. Regarding Intel, it isn't currently part of my portfolio, however i will keep an eye on it. The portfolio has a current gain above 82%.</Msg><Username>lusitanae</Username><Timestamp>1347285824982</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:03:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347286537445-21</Id><Title>Perfect Buying Opportunity</Title><Msg>This is the stuff that fortunes are made of. A herd following the advice of people like Cramer with a mythology "PC is dead" that is so obviously bone-headed wrong, you just know in a year or two they'll be drinking the Kool-Aid.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347286537445</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:15:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347287004408-22</Id><Title>As my daddy was wont to say, "Ya know ...</Title><Msg>Harlum, Wallis Weaver means well, but ya just cain't repair stupid."</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1347287004408</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347287016863-23</Id><Topic><Title>Intel P/E is 10</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347284827249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis, what do you think their P/E should be? They are a no growth company. I think 10 is fair, maybe 12, but with HPQ and Dell dead in the water, no higher.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347287016863</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:23:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347287555724-24</Id><Title>Typical analysts, kicking it while it is down.</Title><Msg>I'm buying.....................................</Msg><Username>lincoln_knight</Username><Timestamp>1347287555724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:32:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347287569114-25</Id><Topic><Title>Perfect Buying Opportunity</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347286537445</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:15:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cramer is absolute bald headed ulgy #$%$ He said the same thing about PG when it was trading at 59 and see where PG is now. Anybody who looks Cramer's advice for investing are definitely naive.</Msg><Username>nj_maverick</Username><Timestamp>1347287569114</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:32:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347287715637-26</Id><Title>Maybe it's time for Mux Prob to 'splain to 'em about ...</Title><Msg>Juhhny Bowl Un Jour and his Merry Bands of Men in Tights?</Msg><Username>myle_der_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1347287715637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:35:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347288042765-27</Id><Topic><Title>Perfect Buying Opportunity</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347286537445</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:15:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It might be a good swing trade. This thing will be trading in a band for a long, long time. They have nothing new in the pipeline.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347288042765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:40:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347288121681-28</Id><Topic><Title>This Is Gonna Be Fun</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1336573582000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-05-09 10:26:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WallDUH! What FUN, FUN, FUN you must be having today! Wheeeeeeeeeeeee!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1347288121681</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:42:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>49</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347288148112-29</Id><Title>No buyers are stepping up..now $23.47</Title><Msg>Way to go Intel for defensing your share price.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1347288148112</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347288167646-30</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, 23's and market hasn't even corrected yet !</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1347284732750</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:45:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This POS is nothing if not a real disappointment.</Msg><Username>bridgecrew</Username><Timestamp>1347288167646</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:42:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347288410328-31</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, 23's and market hasn't even corrected yet !</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1347284732750</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:45:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This stock will stop its slide at the 600 MA, currently 22.13. That moving average was the ultimate support in 2011.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347288410328</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:46:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347288439435-32</Id><Topic><Title>The PC Isn't Dying: Don't Sell Into The Sensationalism</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347282877310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:14:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No matter how you cut it the bashers are the pigs INTC will kill the ARM before this war is over and the IPAD will get killed too- by the Windows 8 tablets which will be mostly INTC tablets and the Droid tablets which will be using more and more INTC innards. ARM is in a war- they will lose it or become marginalized by INTC's power</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347288439435</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:47:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347288650959-33</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, 23's and market hasn't even corrected yet !</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1347284732750</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:45:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being 20% off its high and a tech leader I dont swallow this overpriced market......its a corrected market, with AAPL and GOOG pushing the market to New highs.</Msg><Username>chcknlittle</Username><Timestamp>1347288650959</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:50:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347288668076-34</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, 23's and market hasn't even corrected yet !</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1347284732750</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:45:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>then sell it and move on you big baby!</Msg><Username>lincoln_knight</Username><Timestamp>1347288668076</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:51:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347288727334-35</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, 23's and market hasn't even corrected yet !</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1347284732750</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:45:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interested in owning Intel shares under 23......sold $23 Oct put for .60</Msg><Username>rmed64</Username><Timestamp>1347288727334</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:52:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347289490467-36</Id><Title>INTC needs to get into mobile fast. Time to innovate!</Title><Msg>This stock is lagging the market bigtime. Time to buyback shares also.</Msg><Username>jdr52683</Username><Timestamp>1347289490467</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347289826558-37</Id><Title>DINOSAUR RACE! INTC VS. HPQ!!!</Title><Msg>The two former bellwethers have been reduced to SMELLWETHERS. Anyway, the RACE TO THE BOTTOM IS ON! Like the guy said, THE WORLD CHANGED BUT INTEL DIDN'T! TOOO FUNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347289826558</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:10:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347290609010-38</Id><Topic><Title>The PC Isn't Dying: Don't Sell Into The Sensationalism</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347282877310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:14:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis, you're fired. Your incessant pumping of this stock, which is now down 20% from its high - where you recommended buying - is a pox on this forum. Ultrabook was a flop, and now everyone long the on the stock like you recommended is paying for it. Go away.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1347290609010</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:23:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347291196855-39</Id><Topic><Title>The PC Isn't Dying: Don't Sell Into The Sensationalism</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347282877310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:14:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Ultrabook makes the most sense with touch screens, W8 and aggressive prices - all which has yet to occur. It is far too early to predict the demand for Ultrabook or near-Ultrabook devices.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1347291196855</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:33:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347291722685-40</Id><Title>Intel and mobile phone</Title><Msg>Intel want to do design mobile phone long time ago, but they don't know how to do, because CEO is bad.</Msg><Username>vinhxle</Username><Timestamp>1347291722685</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:42:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347292114045-41</Id><Topic><Title>Intel and mobile phone</Title><Username>vinhxle</Username><Timestamp>1347291722685</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:42:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CEO is just fine, your Engrish is bad.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1347292114045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:48:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347292114601-42</Id><Title>NTWK $5.3 UP 33c....BREAKING OUT!! NEW TARGET $16...GUIDES FOR 40% 2013 REVENUE GROWTH &amp; $1/SHARE NET INCOME. NEW CLOUD DIVISION ANNOUNCEMENT IS HUGE!!..September 6, 2012. NTWK created a new division, NetSolCloudVM, that will offer infrastructure-as-a-service (IaaS), initially targeting the North American market. Set to launch in September as a division of NetSol North America, NetSolCloudVM will provide clients with IT infrastructure on a monthly tiered subscription basis</Title><Msg>SHORT TERM TARGET $10+ .......2013 GUIDANCE: 40% GROWTH AND $1/SHARE NET INCOME NTWK'S OTHER CLOUD DIVISION VROOZI ALREADY EXPLODED IN REVENUES IN Q4 2012.....POTENTIAL ACQUISITION TARGET WITH CLOSE TIES TO SAP 3M SHARE FLOAT......AFTER EARNINGS PROFIT TAKING OVER.....MAGNIFICENT CHART In its updated public cloud forecast in June, Gartner estimated that IaaS was the fastest growing cloud segment with a projected GAGR of 41.7%, and exceeding a $20 billion global market by 2016. "We made a calculated decision to enter this growing market given our years of experience as a software developer, the minimal investment required, and the revenue potential given just the breadth of our current relationships," said Najeeb Ghauri, chairman and CEO of NetSol. "I am fully confident in our highly capable team, reinforced by our talented group of IT professionals, to scale the business quickly and capture a portion of this burgeoning industry, creating an additional revenue driver and further diversifying our revenue mix by geography." "What we are offering, in essence, is private cloud performance at an elastic cloud price -- giving potential customers in our target market segment the performance, flexibility, reliability, and a no-nonsense fixed pricing model that they have long desired," added Imran Haider, COO of NetSol North America and head of NetSolCloudVM. "As a growing software company ourselves, we have critical insights into the efficiency and productivity needs of NetSolCloudVM's target customer base and look forward to unveiling our new services in the coming months." ===== 4Q and FY 2012 EARNINGS SUMMARY......9/4/2012 NetSol Technologies Reported RECORD Fiscal Fourth Quarter and Year-End Results - 9/4/2012 - Fourth Quarter 2012 Revenue Surges to an all-time quarterly record of $14.3 Million on Increased License Revenues and associated maintenance and service agreements going forward - Fourth Quarter 2012 Earnings Advance Significantly to $0.25 per Diluted Share - Full Year 2012 revenues a record $38M - Full Year 2012 Earnings of $0.39/share - Company Expects Record Fiscal 2013 Annual Revenue Growing over 30% to $46 million to $49 million, With Earnings per Diluted Share Advancing to $0.80 to $1.00 - Per the CC, Company anticipates doubling revenues and net income by 2015 NTWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Only 3 million share float - Fast growing profitable US-based global cloud and license-based software company with 8 offices worldwide (US, China, Australia, UK, Pakistan, Singapore, Thailand, Saudi Arabia) – - Trading at 5 PE and 1 times sales – This is about 25% of sector average - Revenues are increasing at double digit rates, - Guidance calls for 30% revenue growth in 2013 - 3 consecutive quarters of profitability, - Guidance calls for $1/share net income in 2013!!! - Global alliances with Mercedes Benz and SANY Corp of China. - No. 1 in China and the APAC region in its niche market of leasing and financing software - It’s Vroozi Division is a fast growing Cloud Computing Play with strong relations with SAP, ORCL, MSFT. - Vroozi’s SAP-approved smartOCI procurement search catalog software built on SaaS is being adopted rapidly. Revenues exploded in 4Q 2012 and are expected to multiply in 2013 and a big reason for the 30%+ 2013 projected revenue increase - Vroozi has been created as independent entity to potentially IPO it or sell it to a cloud-acquiring giant like SAP and others - Strong balance sheet with $1/share Cash - With every license they sell a lucrative 5-year service and maintenance agreement building strong recurrent revenues - Huge and consistent insider buying. Insiders bought over 5% of the outstanding shares since 2010 - Strong institutional investor support grew to almost 20% from 11% last year - NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc.process of testing our new message boards. Please provide your feedback so that we can optimize the user experience.</Msg><Username>nick.jr40</Username><Timestamp>1347292114601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:48:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347292128303-43</Id><Topic><Title>The PC Isn't Dying: Don't Sell Into The Sensationalism</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347282877310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:14:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, stay invested... positive surprise in next month's earning</Msg><Username>sanju6e</Username><Timestamp>1347292128303</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347292225787-44</Id><Topic><Title>INTC needs to get into mobile fast. Time to innovate!</Title><Username>jdr52683</Username><Timestamp>1347289490467</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:04:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Announcements coming from IDF starting tomorrow!</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1347292225787</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:50:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347292472006-45</Id><Title>Insane</Title><Msg>Look how INTC stacks up against others on their field. 9/10/2012 PE PE -For Div. Cash INTC 9.99 8.91 3.70% 13.65B AAPL 15.86 12.82 1.60% 27.65B GOOG 20.9 14.26 0% 41.72B QCOM 18.33 15.21 1.60% 13.4B MSFT 11.29 11.14 2.70% 62.04B ARMH 53.74 31.29 0.50% 585M</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1347292472006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:54:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347292524681-46</Id><Title>HAA HAAA I trash Rombo and you clowns cry. I simply use another name.</Title><Msg>Yahoo--blocks my other account 24 hours and so what. Are you that upset that Romney is now down 5% in the Raspukin poll? Or are you upset that Romney now says on Meet the Press Yesterday that he WILL NOT repeal all of Obama care. The flip flopper in chief ROMBO Romney is laughing at you rightwing teabagging Republicans. He hates you and he hates your tastes in food and your Race cars too. In fact, he is a LIB and you idiots lost the election no matter who wins. Two Libs running and you are pathetic losers who just figured it out. WAHHH WAHHH I want my country back cry you puossssys. Grwo some nuggets and quit your crying. If you are a true Libertarian, you should have voted for Ron paul you jackoffs. Now Obummer wins and you are the idiots who re-elected him by backing Rombo the rich boy with a LIB record of governing.</Msg><Username>gopmeltdown2012</Username><Timestamp>1347292524681</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:55:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347293078219-47</Id><Topic><Title>The PC Isn't Dying: Don't Sell Into The Sensationalism</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347282877310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:14:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm a huge Intel bull, but this statement is false, Intel just warned on Q3 profits and Q3 is nearly over, so they already know what the numbers will be. Still, INTC is a great investment at today's prices, I expect something big out of IDF!</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1347293078219</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347293853740-48</Id><Topic><Title>Insane</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1347292472006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, but PC's are dead, havent you heard? And, INTC will never ever grow again. Thats what most believe as Intel's brand has been reduced to trash.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1347293853740</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347294577416-49</Id><Title>NTWK $5.3 UP 33c....BREAKING OUT!! NEW TARGET $16...GUIDES FOR 40% 2013 REVENUE GROWTH &amp; $1/SHARE NET INCOME. NEW CLOUD DIVISION ANNOUNCEMENT IS HUGE!!..September 6, 2012. NTWK created a new division, NetSolCloudVM, that will offer infrastructure-as-a-service (IaaS), initially targeting the North American market. Set to launch in September as a division of NetSol North America, NetSolCloudVM will provide clients with IT infrastructure on a monthly tiered subscription basis</Title><Msg>SHORT TERM TARGET $10+ .......2013 GUIDANCE: 40% GROWTH AND $1/SHARE NET INCOME NTWK'S OTHER CLOUD DIVISION VROOZI ALREADY EXPLODED IN REVENUES IN Q4 2012.....POTENTIAL ACQUISITION TARGET WITH CLOSE TIES TO SAP 3M SHARE FLOAT......AFTER EARNINGS PROFIT TAKING OVER.....MAGNIFICENT CHART In its updated public cloud forecast in June, Gartner estimated that IaaS was the fastest growing cloud segment with a projected GAGR of 41.7%, and exceeding a $20 billion global market by 2016. "We made a calculated decision to enter this growing market given our years of experience as a software developer, the minimal investment required, and the revenue potential given just the breadth of our current relationships," said Najeeb Ghauri, chairman and CEO of NetSol. "I am fully confident in our highly capable team, reinforced by our talented group of IT professionals, to scale the business quickly and capture a portion of this burgeoning industry, creating an additional revenue driver and further diversifying our revenue mix by geography." "What we are offering, in essence, is private cloud performance at an elastic cloud price -- giving potential customers in our target market segment the performance, flexibility, reliability, and a no-nonsense fixed pricing model that they have long desired," added Imran Haider, COO of NetSol North America and head of NetSolCloudVM. "As a growing software company ourselves, we have critical insights into the efficiency and productivity needs of NetSolCloudVM's target customer base and look forward to unveiling our new services in the coming months." ===== 4Q and FY 2012 EARNINGS SUMMARY......9/4/2012 NetSol Technologies Reported RECORD Fiscal Fourth Quarter and Year-End Results - 9/4/2012 - Fourth Quarter 2012 Revenue Surges to an all-time quarterly record of $14.3 Million on Increased License Revenues and associated maintenance and service agreements going forward - Fourth Quarter 2012 Earnings Advance Significantly to $0.25 per Diluted Share - Full Year 2012 revenues a record $38M - Full Year 2012 Earnings of $0.39/share - Company Expects Record Fiscal 2013 Annual Revenue Growing over 30% to $46 million to $49 million, With Earnings per Diluted Share Advancing to $0.80 to $1.00 - Per the CC, Company anticipates doubling revenues and net income by 2015 NTWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Only 3 million share float - Fast growing profitable US-based global cloud and license-based software company with 8 offices worldwide (US, China, Australia, UK, Pakistan, Singapore, Thailand, Saudi Arabia) – - Trading at 5 PE and 1 times sales – This is about 25% of sector average - Revenues are increasing at double digit rates, - Guidance calls for 30% revenue growth in 2013 - 3 consecutive quarters of profitability, - Guidance calls for $1/share net income in 2013!!! - Global alliances with Mercedes Benz and SANY Corp of China. - No. 1 in China and the APAC region in its niche market of leasing and financing software - It’s Vroozi Division is a fast growing Cloud Computing Play with strong relations with SAP, ORCL, MSFT. - Vroozi’s SAP-approved smartOCI procurement search catalog software built on SaaS is being adopted rapidly. Revenues exploded in 4Q 2012 and are expected to multiply in 2013 and a big reason for the 30%+ 2013 projected revenue increase - Vroozi has been created as independent entity to potentially IPO it or sell it to a cloud-acquiring giant like SAP and others - Strong balance sheet with $1/share Cash - With every license they sell a lucrative 5-year service and maintenance agreement building strong recurrent revenues - Huge and consistent insider buying. Insiders bought over 5% of the outstanding shares since 2010 - Strong institutional investor support grew to almost 20% from 11% last year - NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc</Msg><Username>nick.jr40</Username><Timestamp>1347294577416</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:29:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347294753183-50</Id><Title>OINTC ONCE A DIG ALWAYS BE A DOG FOR THE LAST 15 YEARS</Title><Msg>,MUST BE PUT TO SLEEP BY THE ASPCA</Msg><Username>dexter.galileo</Username><Timestamp>1347294753183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347294842512-51</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend has made $26 a concrete floor</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1338408959000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-05-30 16:15:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I said it 2 months ago, and I'll repeat it now. The floor for Intel is $22.50 (a 4% dividend yield), and obviously not $26 nor $25 nor even $24.</Msg><Username>merenkov</Username><Timestamp>1347294842512</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:34:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347294953864-52</Id><Title>Intel is horrendous this past week.</Title><Msg>Huge short play it is and the longs are upset. Things look grim. Could be worse though--we could be Romney backers. But back to Intel. Intel needs to make the deal with Apple. Apple wants one of the new to come Intel super fabs making the vast majority of Apple chips at 22 nm and then 14 nm. Apple hates Samsung and so Intel can do this deal. The shorts, if this deal is signed, will be in a massive panic and be ripped to shreds as Intel breaks out to 35. Intel will make massive net profits with or without Apple in the years to come but Apple would explode Intel share price up NOW! The two giants are in talks. The talks have been on going for over 6 months. Likely, the Google -Motorola move to Intel chips will be a wake up call for Apple who needs to be seen as having the top end performance in the Iphone area in order to keep the High end pricing. The Intel share price now is insanely low and just shows how much money is tied into the other than Intel chip areas in the stock market. The Apple share price will go higher and many of the owners of the Apple stock are shorting Intel but that will quickly change as soon as paul O signs the deal with Apple to make the CHIPS for the Iphone and Ipad using the Intel X86 chip. Funny thing is Apple will go much higher on the report and Intel will too. Time for this? Any time now but certainly before Intel opens the 14 nm super fab. Apple wants it and Apple wants to knew Samsung in the nuggets. Paul O just need to drink some more wine and to be there at the table using an IPHONE and IPAD as he meets with the Apple executives--and he need to show the benchmarks simulated with Intel inside the same. Never has there been a better time to buy Intel in the last 12 years.</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1347294953864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:35:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347295569087-53</Id><Topic><Title>Insane</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1347292472006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is cheap and under appreciated. I'm going to start buying for my Roth-IRA if the div gets much better. I'm thinking at 4%+.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1347295569087</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:46:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347295821323-54</Id><Topic><Title>Insane</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1347292472006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pretty close now, isnt it?</Msg><Username>d186282mps</Username><Timestamp>1347295821323</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:50:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347295919469-55</Id><Title>Arms race? On eve of Intel’s developer event, ARM argues that it is winning the mobile race</Title><Msg>Arms race? On eve of Intel’s developer event, ARM argues that it is winning the mobile race Intel is about to talk up its progress in making chips for smartphones and tablets at its Intel Developer Forum this week. But its arch rival ARM has preemptively argued that it continues to dominate the market for processors for mobile devices, based on the strength of its partner ecosystem. ARM has had the inside track on mobile devices because it started with a chip architecture that was designed for low power from the start, compared to Intel’s approach of trying to redesign computer chips so that they can operate on a lower amount of power, said James Bruce, lead mobile strategist, in an interview with VentureBeat. As the market shifts from low-performance, low-power mobile devices to smartphones and tablets — which feature high performance and low power — ARM and its partners continues to win the bulk of designs, Bruce said. ARM is a designer of chip architecture, and its partners take those blueprints, modify them to their own needs, and fabricate chips for use in mobile devices. Now even the entry-level devices in both phones and tablets are requiring better processing capabilities and faster connectivity. Intel, which is banking on getting chips into at least 20 upcoming Windows 8 tablets, argues that this change in the market will favor its own heritage of high-performance computing. But ARM says chips based on its technology are still undercutting Intel on power usage and are hitting the lowest price points in the market at the same time. For instance, a new Lenovo phone with a high-end ARM Cortex A9 processor with Mali 3D graphics now sells for just $75. Samsung recently introduced a digital camera with the Android operating system and connectivity. ARM partners have launched a number of system-on-chip solutions to do battle with Intel. Those partners include Spreadtrum, Qualcomm, Broadcom, Mediatek, Samsung, Nvidia, and Texas Instruments. If you count Apple as well — another ARM licensee — those chip makers have the mobile market covered from top to bottom, from single-core to quad-core solutions. Chip manufacturers such as Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co., Samsung and Global Foundries are investing heavily to keep up with Intel in manufacturing chips that can deliver on both performance and low power. Mobile operating systems, meanwhile, are advancing quickly with a one-year innovation cycle and are driving improvements in software efficiency and distribution. ARM believes that tablets could be shipping about 400 million units a year by 2015, compared with just 17 million units in 2010. By comparison, the number of smartphones shipping in 2015 is expected to top 1 billion units, compared to 300 million in 2010. Smartphones are now outselling feature phones in many markets, and they are the prime generators of internet connections. “Your smartphone is now your primary compute device,” Bruce said. “It gives you access to your digital life in places where you don’t want to carry your laptop.” In the past five years, Bruce said that mobile computing has seen huge technical advances. He said screen resolution has improved six-fold during that time, while data connectivity has increased 15-fold. Video resolution has improved 14 times, graphics performance has improved 10 times, main memory has increased four times, and processor performance is up 15-fold. By comparison, advances in personal computing technology are much more gradual. During the past five years, the user experience has improved with the rise of app stores, connectivity to the cloud (rather than the PC), the introduction of full web support, and multitasking. Mobile devices are becoming hubs for your digital content. They’re contextually aware, offering information on your surroundings. They’re becoming platforms for digital identity and payments. Smartphones are getting connected to different devices around the home, such as computer displays and TVs. By 2013, ARM-based solutions for entry-level smartphones will cross over 1-gigahertz in performance, Bruce said, while the high-end ARM chips will top 1.5 gigahertiz with multiple cores. New Arm Cortex A15-based chips are coming out in the next year. Texas Instruments and Samsung have announced A15 devices on their roadmaps. “You’ll see a doubling in performance over the next couple of years,” Bruce said. Applied Micro Circuits Corp. (AMCC) is developing a high-end 64-bit ARM-based X-Gene server microprocessor. The chip has been under way for some time and it packs energy-efficient dual cores. AMCC hopes to launch the chip in the second half of 2012. If it delivers on that product, then it will challenge Intel’s multibillion-dollar stronghold in data center computing. The question is whether it can keep pace with Intel’s own server chip schedule. But a chip like this shows that ARM can cover everything in the computing spectrum. “There’s a massive ecosystem around ARM devices,” Bruce said.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347295919469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:51:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347295972714-56</Id><Title>TSMC spends $10 billion on expansion</Title><Msg>TSMC is expected to spend $10 billion next year in capital works as Apple plans to contract the outfit to build its next-generation processors. According to the Chinese-language Economic Daily News TSMC has informed the equipment suppliers of its decision to hike capital expenditure for 2013 to US$10 billion. This indicates that TSMC has overcome technical problem with 20nm process, which Apple’s next-generation processors are said to use. It also suggests that Jobs' Mob is speeding up its reduction of work it gives Samsung. Apple has reportedly sent around 200 design engineers to help TSMC get familiar with the company’s next-generation processor designs at TSMC’s facility in Central Taiwan Science Park. Pilot production of the processors at TSMC will start in the first half of next year and general production will start in the second half.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347295972714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347297373201-57</Id><Title>INTC = POS</Title><Msg>Piece of A S.T This garbage is going to follow AMD steps in few years heading straight into bankruptcy. Hope it does and RIP INTC</Msg><Username>nj_maverick</Username><Timestamp>1347297373201</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:16:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347297938755-58</Id><Title>I see $22 soon!</Title><Msg>Volume and price action says 22 to 22.50 next level down!</Msg><Username>buythetrend</Username><Timestamp>1347297938755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:25:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347298228482-59</Id><Topic><Title>I see $22 soon!</Title><Username>buythetrend</Username><Timestamp>1347297938755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:25:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see $19 soon. This garbage should file for Bankruptcy in few years when a full blown recession is there. POS..POS..POS.............................RIP INTC</Msg><Username>nj_maverick</Username><Timestamp>1347298228482</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:30:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347298775483-60</Id><Topic><Title>INTC = POS</Title><Username>nj_maverick</Username><Timestamp>1347297373201</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jeeeez man didnt you take advantage of thos covered calls again you can do it at least every year if not more often and bring home some good money- you can usually go deep in the money and make more- and you git divys too- the 28 buck peak earlier this year was a pretty good gain-and it will happen again in the coming year and INTC is going thru this cycle just about every year</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347298775483</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:39:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347299176439-61</Id><Topic><Title>INTC = POS</Title><Username>nj_maverick</Username><Timestamp>1347297373201</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup. I own Oct $26 calls. Will wait till earnings I think but should make good money by then. The hit I wasn't expecting when I bought few weeks ago.. Though I am not worried.. Should be good by Oct.</Msg><Username>verioinc</Username><Timestamp>1347299176439</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:46:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347299259944-62</Id><Topic><Title>I see $22 soon!</Title><Username>buythetrend</Username><Timestamp>1347297938755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:25:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You either lost money on INTC or your a short. This is too strong of a company to go out of business. I don't know why I respond to blind shorters. Easy to jump on bandwagon.</Msg><Username>verioinc</Username><Timestamp>1347299259944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:47:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347299314145-63</Id><Title>P/E Now Below 10</Title><Msg>As the market gets really stupid. I encourage all shorts to hang in there. I'm sure there's more to go. At least that's what every cockroach posting shill seems to be saying. But go ahead - hang in for IDF. Hang in for the smartphone announcements. Hang in for the Windows 8 release. Hang in for earnings where we now know there won't be any miss. After all, what could go wrong? Lucy was right all the way from 17.67 to 29+, right? Lucy was never right for more than a short period of time. But that was then and this is now. I'm sure Lucy being wrong for several years was just a fluke. The PC is dead. The internet is fading out of use. Big Data is in decline. The Internet of Things is a myth. Other than Lava, Orange, Motorola, Lenovo, MegaFon, ZTE and Karbonn, Intel has no presence in mobility. The ARM world needs nothing more than 90nm production because of their advanced micro-architecture. Go with Lucy. You'll be fine. LOL</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347299314145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:48:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347300187195-64</Id><Title>This is painful!!!!</Title><Msg>No cruel joke here. I'm bleeding bad. When will this sell complete and the stock start picking up. Pulling back from mid$27. This is over sell. I'm surprise that it keep dropping even though this was known all along. Shouldn't it be mostly priced in? Should have gotten out at $25 last Thursday. It hurts bad.....</Msg><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347300187195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347300441332-65</Id><Topic><Title>This is painful!!!!</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347300187195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Owning this company stock is for someone who is a brain dead. This company is a utter garbage and i hope like other fraudulent companies this company goes belly up and become bankrupt. One of the most disgusting company who sucked in all the investors ripping off their investments.</Msg><Username>nj_maverick</Username><Timestamp>1347300441332</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347300724880-66</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC spends $10 billion on expansion</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347295972714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Wall Street Cheat Sheet reports that apple will introduce the new imac on the 12th along with the Iphone. (Why create noise at the big Iphone annoucement with a pc that is in a dying market). I am betting that Paul O. will be there to introduce the new imac and annouce that apple will be using Intel chips next year. Apple making the switch is too big of news to keep secret months in advance. There has been a saying that Apple suppliers will not talk of future projects because of fear a losing Apples business. If they lose that business, that would be leaked. So that why I believe it will be annouced now and give the Apple community time to prepare. Apple stock price is supported by high margins and the phones/tablets with arm chips are quickly becoming a commodity. Apple margins will be hurt by low margin, high volume competitors. Apple needs to seperate itself from the others. Intel chips will be ahead of arm chips by next fall.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1347300724880</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:12:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347300753287-67</Id><Title>How Intel’s Medfield will dismantle ARM</Title><Msg>don't underestimate INTEL In short, ARM &amp; Co. are in a very unenviable position. Intel now has a beachhead and its terrifying, industry-clobbering, 60%-gross-margin wehrmacht will surely follow. You might only see a few Medfield-powered scouts in 2012, but by the time the 22nm Silvermont tanks roll around in 2013 and x86 is better than ARM across the board, expect to see dozens of Santa Clara design wins. Unless TSMC, IBM, GloFo, or Samsung uncover some kind of ancient scroll that details the magic of 14nm, come 2014 and the Airmont core, I wouldn’t be surprised if Intel completely dominates the Android smartphone market. Following the Motorola partnership, I would also be very surprised if Microsoft and Apple aren’t working on x86 versions of their mobile operating systems, too.</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1347300753287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:12:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347301051215-68</Id><Title>ARM Holdings Still Eating Intel's Lunch at Seeking Alpha 02:04pm EDT</Title><Msg>This can't be good. I hate to admit it but Lucy was right.</Msg><Username>wallisweiner</Username><Timestamp>1347301051215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:17:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347301152697-69</Id><Topic><Title>This is painful!!!!</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347300187195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I already told you, no cruel joke. Or should I add no insult, too? Like you have never made any bad buy in your hold life?</Msg><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347301152697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347301256022-70</Id><Topic><Title>This is painful!!!!</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347300187195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For a record, I am holding this POS garbage.</Msg><Username>nj_maverick</Username><Timestamp>1347301256022</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:20:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347301512930-71</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC spends $10 billion on expansion</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347295972714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"arm chips are quickly becoming a commodity." more capabale too... gonna bring those CPU ASPs down... that's what commodities do... "Apple needs to seperate itself from the others." That's why they build their own SOCs, and NOT use INtel...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347301512930</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347301627373-72</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC spends $10 billion on expansion</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347295972714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? Wow, this is interesting. It's interesting that a company that has failed so badly at getting 28nm out this year is going to have 20nm up and running by next year. And Apple is going to bet the farm on this? Oh I can see the delays now. When you look at Apple's track record they haven't really been pushing for cutting edge technology. The A5X is 40nm and only recently have they moved to 32nm with the iPad2. Why the sudden push for cutting edge technology that doesn't exist yet? This just looks like some disinformation that comes out now and then. Actually, this seems like #$%$ that ARMH puts out or Morris Chang to make them look interesting again.</Msg><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1347301627373</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:27:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347301959539-73</Id><Title>22s nice entry 3.6% div 18 months out back in high 20s low 30s</Title><Msg>might buy uncle ben keeping rates zilch</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1347301959539</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:32:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347302311367-74</Id><Topic><Title>I see $22 soon!</Title><Username>buythetrend</Username><Timestamp>1347297938755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:25:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am looking to enter. I've found most people are looking at 22 as an entry point. The market gets exaggerated so actually high 19's will likely be the best point to get. I will wait.</Msg><Username>smathan75</Username><Timestamp>1347302311367</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:38:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347302412150-75</Id><Title>The world changed overnight</Title><Msg>There is a worldwide recession for everybody and every corporation but Intel. When sales are bad it means that the company is a dinosaur that is about to become extinct. It means that "nobody" wants to buy a PC and "Everybody" wants an iPad even though PC's outsell iPads 10 to 1. There just must be a lot of nobody's out there. Perhaps the worldwide economic downturn has caught up to Intel as well. Show me any other company in the world that sells $12B of anything in a quarter that is considered going instinct. The professional bashers love to paint an ugly future for Intel. Only one thing, even they know it's not true. The stock is now under 10X P/E. It's a great time to buy, and if you're long, it's just a down cycle. Intel has plenty of up cycles. Or you can take business advice from so called experts who say it's a great time to sell Intel at a low and buy Apple at nearly $700 a share when it was trading for $85 a few years ago. The low for Intel was in the high twelves about four years ago. I'll put it to you another way, what is more likely in your opinion? Intel at $46 a share or Apple at $1400 a share? BTW, what new product since the iPad has Apple introduced to boost sales? Remember Apple TV and all the subscriptions services, how are they doing? Sure the new iPhone will be out soon and sales will rocket, but it will be to existing customers. The iPhone is losing market share to Android quarter by quarter. A 20nm TSMC ARM processor won't draw people in. And that is realistically end of 2014 if not pure #$%$ vaporware.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1347302412150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:40:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347302475187-76</Id><Topic><Title>This is painful!!!!</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347300187195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The big guys are running in fear of the death of the PC market. This is likely overblown and Intel is pushing hard to get into the mobile market. The multiple is suggesting that they think Intel will do poorly. If they start doing well, the stock will probably skyrocket... again.I find it hard to pass up a near 4% div. on a growth company like this. I'm considering buying more. Not saying it wont go down more though. I think it will be 25+ again.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1347302475187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:41:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347302593074-77</Id><Topic><Title>This is painful!!!!</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347300187195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>small correction: They are doing pretty well already, meant that more for the mobile side.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1347302593074</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347302811159-78</Id><Title>Hey, Paul...you suck as CEO!</Title><Msg>Thanks for the 20% drop in share price over the last 4 months.</Msg><Username>cray3040</Username><Timestamp>1347302811159</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:46:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347302921676-79</Id><Topic><Title>This is painful!!!!</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347300187195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude, you make no sense...seriously.</Msg><Username>cray3040</Username><Timestamp>1347302921676</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:48:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347303548266-80</Id><Topic><Title>This is painful!!!!</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347300187195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lucy, I mean Maverick, you are a class A idiot. The ECB just announced bond buying program, EU will start to stabilize, and you can almost guarantee that Bernanke will introduce QE3 this week, it is an election year after all, and he needs his boss to get re-elected.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1347303548266</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:59:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347303643913-81</Id><Topic><Title>This is painful!!!!</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347300187195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who makes no sense? moi? no way!!!</Msg><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347303643913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:00:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347303651365-82</Id><Topic><Title>This is painful!!!!</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347300187195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My point being, the Q3 slowdown is due to several reasons, mostly people waiting for Win 8 touchscreen laptop/ultrabooks, but also due to macro issues etc. which are going away.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1347303651365</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:00:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347303762005-83</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>lidiaenu5630</Username><Timestamp>1347302715666</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm looking for great articles. Nice to be here.</Msg><Username>jeantzz775</Username><Timestamp>1347303762005</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:02:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347303822009-84</Id><Topic><Title>I see $22 soon!</Title><Username>buythetrend</Username><Timestamp>1347297938755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:25:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>veroinc your right on the button-i dont own yet 22s i buy.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1347303822009</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:03:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347304211335-85</Id><Topic><Title>The world changed overnight</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1347302412150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My neighbor has an iPad, I asked how she likes it, she told me she never uses it. In fact, nobody in their house has touched it in months, not even their 16 year old daughter. The "PC is dead" crowd are complete idiots, iPad is and always will be a companion device until they replace the ARM chip with a x86 one and switch out iOS for OSX.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1347304211335</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:10:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347304464984-86</Id><Topic><Title>This is painful!!!!</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347300187195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If so then hold my hand, we are going to pray!!!! God damn it, get it back to the $25 range!!!!</Msg><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347304464984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347304622487-87</Id><Topic><Title>This is painful!!!!</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347300187195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As a matter of fact, I know that one group in Austin, TX is building mobile product, not mobile PC, it's phone/consumer application. I wonder when they will start releasing their products. Sometime, being HW engineer, we got sucked in too early once we see a good design in the pipe..... I hope the market see this and everyone will be hype!</Msg><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347304622487</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:17:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347305332357-88</Id><Title>Anybody excited to see what announcements are made at IDF</Title><Msg>Day 1 of IDF is tomorrow, 9/11/12...</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1347305332357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347305640691-89</Id><Topic><Title>I see $22 soon!</Title><Username>buythetrend</Username><Timestamp>1347297938755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:25:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have Oct $26 calls and I am tripling down today to bring my avg down. Technically speaking lots of upside.. I did it with BMY and it paid off huge. You can't always find bottom but avg down and when it goes up you make money faster. Follow charts they don't lie. This is oversold big time..</Msg><Username>verioinc</Username><Timestamp>1347305640691</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:34:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347305760779-90</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is horrendous this past week.</Title><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1347294953864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:35:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder if this is the week when we find out that Apple will be making the switch. I'm sure they haven't yet, otherwise Intel would not have needed to warn for Q3.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1347305760779</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:36:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347305789162-91</Id><Title>NASDAQ</Title><Msg>NASDAQ is down hugely over the DOW - thanks to the big Wall Street firms who use their money and leverage to manipulate the small investors out of their equity. Write the letters. Copy the SEC. In the meantime, it's good for a laugh when the market gets this stupid. There is no company the market understands less than Intel. Having totally over-reacted I now want to see the shorts try to make a case for more downside. Of course, the big boys will get out and leave the #$%$ on this board to holler "Reddddddddddddddddddddddd" as Intel moves back up. If those cretins never had the light come on during the entire time Intel moved from 17.67 to 29+, they aren't going to grow a brain now. IDF tomorrow, then QE3. Let's see how well the shorts are doing at the end of the week...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347305789162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:36:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347305960828-92</Id><Topic><Title>I see $22 soon!</Title><Username>buythetrend</Username><Timestamp>1347297938755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:25:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maverick probably used to work for AMD or something, his hate for Intel is so irrational that it goes way beyond having lost some money or just bashing while shorting. Reminds me of Dnenni.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1347305960828</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:39:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347306672091-93</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC spends $10 billion on expansion</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347295972714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not a peep from Wally on this thread? This news isn't sitting well with him. Rest assured he'll say something sarcastic, but it won't hold any water. This news DESTROYS Intel. Just destroys them !!</Msg><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1347306672091</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:51:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347306792007-94</Id><Topic><Title>I see $22 soon!</Title><Username>buythetrend</Username><Timestamp>1347297938755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:25:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$23.02 is a certainty. DID YOU LISTEN TO LUCY? or DID YOU LISTEN TO PUMPWAD? or ARE YOU ANOTHER OF PUMPWAD'S ALIASES? LUCY WAS RIGHT AND THAT'S A FACT!!! TOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347306792007</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:53:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347306793759-95</Id><Topic><Title>I see $22 soon!</Title><Username>buythetrend</Username><Timestamp>1347297938755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:25:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As we speak, the garbage INTC is still going down. LOL Keep shorting this B.ch all the way to $12. This company sucks more than AMD because AMD is within a trading range. RIP INTC,. Soon you're going to head into Bankruptcy.</Msg><Username>nj_maverick</Username><Timestamp>1347306793759</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:53:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347306863446-96</Id><Title>uncle uncle. ok already enough is enough</Title><Msg>will fell good when this over correction turns around.</Msg><Username>hd_lowrider_stormy</Username><Timestamp>1347306863446</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:54:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347307127902-97</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>lidiaenu5630</Username><Timestamp>1347302715666</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job. Informational article.</Msg><Username>vivanjnq977411</Username><Timestamp>1347307127902</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:58:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347307468344-98</Id><Title>Garbage down with MASSIVE volume</Title><Msg>$19 we come..............$12.......................imminent BK.</Msg><Username>nj_maverick</Username><Timestamp>1347307468344</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:04:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347307474926-99</Id><Topic><Title>I see $22 soon!</Title><Username>buythetrend</Username><Timestamp>1347297938755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:25:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well I just triple downed on my Oct $26 calls. I remember people calling Ford done when the stock hit $8. Well I bought $9.00 points and tripled my money. BMY after the big charge back I doubled. You can't make money without risk. I was early on my BMY calls but loaded up on dips. Once it took off I was making money quick. All you shorts dream. INTC is way oversold. Look at the charts. It will bounce back just be ready.</Msg><Username>verioinc</Username><Timestamp>1347307474926</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:04:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347307770683-100</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC spends $10 billion on expansion</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347295972714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>' The A5X is 40nm and only recently have they moved to 32nm with the iPad2.' A5X is 45nm.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347307770683</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:09:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347308078053-101</Id><Topic><Title>Garbage down with MASSIVE volume</Title><Username>nj_maverick</Username><Timestamp>1347307468344</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:04:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fess up.how many shares (r) u holding?</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1347308078053</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:14:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347308564355-102</Id><Topic><Title>Apple made the ipad to be a reader, (plus) to compete with amazon who made their reader first and apple played catch up to amazon</Title><Username>fmsg35</Username><Timestamp>1347211650351</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:27:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First kindle 2007 First Ipad 2010 Apple copied amazons Idea</Msg><Username>fmsg35</Username><Timestamp>1347308564355</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:22:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347309626030-103</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is horrendous this past week.</Title><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1347294953864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:35:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed, but remember, once upon a time this thing was $12 bucks....Buy just a little on the way down, and buy just a little more on the way back up...</Msg><Username>batmensch</Username><Timestamp>1347309626030</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:40:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347311062240-104</Id><Title>If Intel needs to make a deal with Apple, then they are doomed</Title><Msg>An Apple deal is NOT happening this year. PS, they don't need a deal with Apple!!!</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347311062240</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 17:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347311161838-105</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is horrendous this past week.</Title><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1347294953864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:35:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can hear the Beach Boys singin' "Wouldn't it be Nice."</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347311161838</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 17:06:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347311760943-106</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>lidiaenu5630</Username><Timestamp>1347302715666</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have entered my email address. Waiting for the update.</Msg><Username>shantayxyt208</Username><Timestamp>1347311760943</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 17:16:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347311943299-107</Id><Topic><Title>How Intel’s Medfield will dismantle ARM</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1347300753287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:12:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too little, too late. TSMC has invested 10 billion and will have 20nm next year, surpassing Intel. Airmont was pushed back to 2015 that was announced in July, making it a huge speculative play at this point.</Msg><Username>bchen2400</Username><Timestamp>1347311943299</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 17:19:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347312117463-108</Id><Topic><Title>Anybody excited to see what announcements are made at IDF</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1347305332357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. The only thing that matters this week is iPhone 5 on Wednesday.</Msg><Username>merenkov</Username><Timestamp>1347312117463</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 17:21:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347313288460-109</Id><Topic><Title>I see $22 soon!</Title><Username>buythetrend</Username><Timestamp>1347297938755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:25:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well, it is back at rsi 30, albeit with a lower low by 1.00 than the last time. If one had the smarts to sell way up there above 26.30 as it started falling, again,buys here at a 3.00 discount for a possible oversold bounce, though it may be nothing more than that, a bounce, given that the prior lows were taken out. sure not gonna short at rsi 30 Poor Waldo, rides it from 24.00 in May 2010 to the 17's same year, then rides it to 29.40, and now back down below 24.00. sure not gonna get rich with INTC that way.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1347313288460</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 17:41:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347313445220-110</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>lidiaenu5630</Username><Timestamp>1347302715666</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one. I will subscribe now.</Msg><Username>maureenpmm946736</Username><Timestamp>1347313445220</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 17:44:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347313961928-111</Id><Title>If it keeps doing this...</Title><Msg>I may commit suicide!!!!! Come on, bottom out at $23 and go up please.</Msg><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347313961928</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 17:52:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347314576020-112</Id><Topic><Title>I see $22 soon!</Title><Username>buythetrend</Username><Timestamp>1347297938755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:25:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC leading PC chip maker, likely will become a top three mobile chip maker with its cheap silicon and foundry/commodity/engineering expertise. Cash flow could pay off debt in a year-ish. ~$7.5 B for buybacks and ~4% dividend cushions downside. Daily, weekly charts oversold. Monthly chart approaching oversold and shows support at ~22. Two consecutive high volume days with buyers piling up at the close around 23.19 today. I sold puts , will buy on further weakness to 22</Msg><Username>yelyacs</Username><Timestamp>1347314576020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347315120529-113</Id><Title>INTC- BEST CPU and CHIP MAKER</Title><Msg>Intc- best cpu and chip maker no matter what device we use today or future, processors are needed no end for cpu's , its universal product</Msg><Username>galsrayny</Username><Timestamp>1347315120529</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:12:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347315124216-114</Id><Title>LOL at the Insane Clown Posse around here</Title><Msg>I'm in at 20 and will hold for 20 years at which time I'll have at MINIMUM doubled my money (probably triple) off of the Dividend itself. At that time, if the stock is worth just 20 bucks, I'll have my original investment back PLUS triple my money..........that' sif the stock never moves a penny! Idiots.</Msg><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1347315124216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:12:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347316009329-115</Id><Topic><Title>The world changed overnight</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1347302412150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, the goal is to have one OS. Which is why that going to 20nm ARM processors only means a faster and more efficient version of the exact same thing. It's good for ARMH, good for TSMC, not so good for Apple.</Msg><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1347316009329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347316009346-116</Id><Topic><Title>The world changed overnight</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1347302412150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, the goal is to have one OS. Which is why that going to 20nm ARM processors only means a faster and more efficient version of the exact same thing. It's good for ARMH, good for TSMC, not so good for Apple.</Msg><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1347316009346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347316009351-117</Id><Topic><Title>The world changed overnight</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1347302412150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, the goal is to have one OS. Which is why that going to 20nm ARM processors only means a faster and more efficient version of the exact same thing. It's good for ARMH, good for TSMC, not so good for Apple.</Msg><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1347316009351</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347316009357-118</Id><Topic><Title>The world changed overnight</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1347302412150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, the goal is to have one OS. Which is why that going to 20nm ARM processors only means a faster and more efficient version of the exact same thing. It's good for ARMH, good for TSMC, not so good for Apple.</Msg><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1347316009357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347316009548-119</Id><Topic><Title>The world changed overnight</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1347302412150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, the goal is to have one OS. Which is why that going to 20nm ARM processors only means a faster and more efficient version of the exact same thing. It's good for ARMH, good for TSMC, not so good for Apple.</Msg><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1347316009548</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347317837599-120</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>lidiaenu5630</Username><Timestamp>1347302715666</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am from Chicago. I love your article.</Msg><Username>jaimeeswu8847</Username><Timestamp>1347317837599</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:57:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347318114379-121</Id><Topic><Title>Anybody excited to see what announcements are made at IDF</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1347305332357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wouldn't it be great if Apple released the iPhone 5 with a x86 processor?</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1347318114379</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347318236007-122</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is horrendous this past week.</Title><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1347294953864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:35:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i've never seen it yield 5%... would be surprised if I ever do... thats $ 18</Msg><Username>darkrai468</Username><Timestamp>1347318236007</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347318407683-123</Id><Topic><Title>If Intel needs to make a deal with Apple, then they are doomed</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347311062240</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 17:04:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will be Apple who needs Intel, that's when they will make the switch. I believe it will happen before it becomes necessary, in order to get ahead of the competition.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1347318407683</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:06:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347318523483-124</Id><Title>3.9 % Dividend Yield...</Title><Msg>Opportune time to buy for income.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1347318523483</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:08:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347319029365-125</Id><Topic><Title>3.9 % Dividend Yield...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1347318523483</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:08:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if they announces something mobile this week or INTC is will be under $24 for a few day.</Msg><Username>tollsname10</Username><Timestamp>1347319029365</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347319669530-126</Id><Topic><Title>3.9 % Dividend Yield...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1347318523483</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:08:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>still too early looking for 22.50 or below</Msg><Username>bylo19</Username><Timestamp>1347319669530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:27:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347319736192-127</Id><Topic><Title>Anybody excited to see what announcements are made at IDF</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1347305332357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ain't going to happen</Msg><Username>bylo19</Username><Timestamp>1347319736192</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347320549673-128</Id><Topic><Title>3.9 % Dividend Yield...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1347318523483</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:08:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then you get yield close to 5%..... no way!</Msg><Username>tollsname10</Username><Timestamp>1347320549673</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:42:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347322259836-129</Id><Topic><Title>If it keeps doing this...</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1347313961928</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 17:52:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't blame you. I'd do myself in also, but can't afford the bullet.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1347322259836</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 20:10:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347322523812-130</Id><Topic><Title>The world changed overnight</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1347302412150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two problems with this amateur analysis. One: No customers on the hook. Two: ARM implementation has about eight bridges between the CPU and the memory. The performance is absolutely horrible. Intel is basically duct-taping crappy parts together. They are in damage control mode, big time. Next desperation question.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347322523812</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 20:15:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347323912547-131</Id><Title>I believe INTC will beat on earnings</Title><Msg>The warning reduces the expectations of the idiots on WS. INTC will beat, thus rewarding the good guys and #$%^ing on the Lucy's.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347323912547</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 20:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347325839722-132</Id><Topic><Title>The world changed overnight</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1347302412150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell us how they duct taped 12 billion together in 3 MONTHS, Vinnardo. LOL, you aren't scaring anyone other than maybe a little old lady or two...The new Fab 42 that's soon to come online, you know....the most advanced Manufacturing facility in the world just laughed at you.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347325839722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:10:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347326230613-133</Id><Title>Anonymous coward Vinnie, or 12 Billion in 3 months?</Title><Msg>This #$%$ wants to buy as low as possible, no more no less. Spit in his face.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347326230613</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:17:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347326621759-134</Id><Topic><Title>Anonymous coward Vinnie, or 12 Billion in 3 months?</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347326230613</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:17:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, are there only two choices? What about Walis Weaver. Hasn't he been beating the drum for INTC for two and half years while the stock has made the round trip to back under $24? Shouldn't we all just buy and hold based on all those laudatory articles he has posted over the years about Intel and the global economy? Remember when it was first announced that Windows 8 would run on ARM processors? Didn't at least someone say at that time that WINTEL was dead? Yes, I believe someone said that. But I guess Wallis was right about that one too, eh?</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1347326621759</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:23:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347327103806-135</Id><Topic><Title>Anonymous coward Vinnie, or 12 Billion in 3 months?</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347326230613</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:17:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lucy heard the word "coward" and stood immediately to attention. Tooooo Funnny.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347327103806</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:31:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347327568006-136</Id><Title>Intel shows off technologies of the future</Title><Msg>From PCPro: LED data encoding The first project to catch my eye was headed “Line-of-Sight Marketing”, though in fact I’m sure the idea has worthier applications than advertising. The project, demonstrated by Intel research scientist Rick Roberts, encodes digital data into LED lights. To the eye, the lights appear to shine constantly, but in reality each one flickers in a programmed, very high frequency pattern. A smartphone app can be used to observe and decode the information in less than a second. Fundamentally it’s a similar idea to QR codes, but less intrusive. Information can be embedded into ambient light or dual-purpose displays, such as the advertising hoardings envisaged by Intel. A 30fps camera (as found on a typical smartphone) can decode 15 bytes of information per second from each LED, so a display comprising a few dozen lights could in theory convey a decent paragraph of information – or a link to richer online resources, such as Augmented Reality overlays. As Roberts admits, though, there’s as yet no standard in place to specify how such information might be encoded, nor how to tell smartphone users to scan the light in the first place – both issues that will clearly need to be addressed before the technology can go mainstream.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347327568006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:39:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347327686804-137</Id><Title>Intel shows off technologies of the future-II</Title><Msg>From: PCPro Any-surface displays One of Intel’s more touchy-feely projects is a social networking concept that invites you to categorise images according to emotional responses and “energy levels”, with a view to finding friends who share your responses. Frankly I’m not sure the idea appeals, but what did excite me was the technology used by Intel research scientist Margie Morris to showcase it: Using nothing more than a domestic projector and a regular Microsoft Kinect motion sensor (as pictured at the top of this post), an entire wall was turned into a photo browsing interface that could be dragged and interacted with by “touch” – or, in reality, by tracking the user’s hands and triggering actions based on their movements. Admittedly, the concept merely builds on previous ideas – including Intel’s earlier “Oasis” project, showcased back in 2010 – and it’s not perfectly smooth or flawless. Nevertheless, the fact that it’s possible to get get this far with mainstream hardware raises intriguing possibilities for future entertainment systems. Not for nothing does Intel call it “display without boundaries”.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347327686804</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347327822308-138</Id><Title>Intel shows off technologies of the future-III</Title><Msg>From PCPro Micro digital signage On its face, Intel’s micro digital signage project is a very simple idea: replace the traditional paper pricing information on supermarket shelves with a network of small LCD screens. When prices or product details change, all the signage can be updated instantly via a single data update at the back-end. Over time, and across all the many products stocked by a large supermarket, the idea could save considerable manual labour. The prototype on display was built from smartphones running Android, and product director Tom Birch showed how using smartphone-style touchscreens additionally allowed customers to find more information about products. I’m not personally convinced there’s much demand for extended information about groceries, but using smartphone technology also brings you something much more interesting – a camera attached to each digital sign. With cameras on board, micro digital signs can be not merely a way to communicate pricing information, but a way to monitor everything that’s going on in the store. Birch described work already underway on algorithms to detect when items on facing shelves were out of stock, further reducing the need for manual stock-taking. He suggested it might even be possible for the cameras to identify the products opposite them and pass that information across to the relevant signs – enabling each sign always to automatically show the correct information and price for whichever product was placed next to it. And when no one’s around, the screens could go to sleep, saving energy. At present the prototype hardware is, in Birch’s own words, “really expensive”, and certainly not a viable investment for retailers. With further development and economies of scale, however, it’s easy to imagine how micro digital signage could eliminate enough drudge-work to make an attractive investment for large retailers.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347327822308</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347327902334-139</Id><Title>Intel shows off technologies of the future-Intro</Title><Msg>From PC Pro: The Intel Developer Forum starts tomorrow in San Francisco, hopefully with some good news about the processors and chipsets we’ll be drooling over in the coming Spring. As an appetiser, however, the company has today been looking further ahead with one of its occasional “technology showcases”, introducing a few projects from its labs that are currently mere prototypes, but which could change our everyday lives in years to come – the most striking of which you’ll find below.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347327902334</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:45:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347328209041-140</Id><Title>IDF 2012: Intel outlines a future of ubiquitous computing</Title><Msg>A future also filled with sensors and advanced algorithms to guide us, with example concepts from Intel Labs For the media day at Intel's Developer Forum (IDF) in San Francisco, Intel researchers and scientists put away the transistor tech talk briefly and formed a panel with science fiction authors to discuss in creative detail some of the things that the company has been researching. Primarily, the focus was on the relationship between people and their computers in the future, which Intel says will be shaped by ubiquitous computing and new methods of interaction as chips get small enough to be installed in anything. The sci-fi authors were originally paired up with Intel researchers to get an idea of the future technologies that they are working on, and to incorporate those technologies into their own stories for an IDF book titled The Tomorrow Project Anthology (the third in the series). Among the authors on the panel was Karl Schroeder, who said that Intel's lab experiments were "used as tools" to write the stories. Some real world examples from Intel's labs session followed, and showcased what the future might hold for the way we use processing power and computer interfaces. All of the concepts rely on heavy data collection and analysis in order to try and enrich the way we work and play. We also saw a working demo of Intel's Display without Boundaries project, which essentially allows any object to become an interactive screen. The example we saw projected images onto a curved bowl, and you could spin those images as if they were on a roulette wheel. Feedback from your hand gestures and position was given to the computer through an Xbox 360 Kinect sensor. Another example was a wall of photos that could be moved around — great for interactive galleries perhaps. Microsoft has long been involved in surface touch and object detection technology (through PixelSense), and Intel itself first highlighted its Oasis object detection technology back in 2010, but Display without Boundaries isn't confined to one partocilar surface or shape and it highlights the fact that Intel is thinking well beyond the square PCs of today as far as how we will physically use computers in ten or 20 years from now. Not only that though, the future will also have a heavy focus on sensors and advanced algorithms to crunch all the data collected by those always-on sensors in real-time. Some working examples of future concepts were shown off by their respective scientists and researchers during Intel's Labs session. These are technology concepts catering to both personal usage and business environments, building on some of the features that are already available to us in smartphones and laptops. We saw a system that is designed to be a recommendation engine, based on various data streams from a person and their group of friends. The concept is to use location sensors, services like Foursquare, and other data, to help aid decision making in various circumstances. In one example we were given, this system would be able to analyse the data from a group of friends and make an informed decision on where the group should eat, not necessarily based on common interests or averages. Intel wants to make the technology think more naturally. In the real world, you might want to go to a place because you know a particular friend likes it (but not necessarily all of them), or you might want to go somewhere you've never been before based on how many times you've been to other places. For business users, one very specific example we saw was a solution based on sensors that can detect who is close by in order to automate things such as meeting and collaboration software. Computers can be detected via Blutooth, and audio sensors can analyse vocal patterns, all in order to ascertain if certain users are in range, and allowing those users to start collaborating immediately. Hassle-free Meeting. To tackle the problem of deciding which communication method to use when you want to contact someone, a group of researchers is working on a system that analyses location and accelerometer sensors, as well as other things such as computer activity and calendar information, to find out if a person is busy working, if they are in a meeting, or if they are currently on the move. It will suggest the best way to contact them based on the data collected by the sensors so as not to disturb them. Situational Communication. Finally, interactive shopping shelves were on display, sporting a collection of sensors and touchscreens to aid both the shopper and the staff. The touchscreens could be used to display pertinent information about products, such as allergy warnings, for example, as well as live pricing (which could allow store workers to more efficiently change product pricing). Furthermore, customers could leave feedback, such as a rating, for products, and even view Twitter streams about products right there on the shelf. The shelves would also be able to detect when stocks need replenishing. Interactive Shopping. All of these concepts are in the works by researchers and we were shown very raw examples of what can be accomplished. With the amount of data collection that's possible, and with very smart people creating algorithms to organise it all, the future of computing will be equal parts scary and exciting and perhaps a lot more hands on (and voice on) than the tablets and smartphones of today allow.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347328209041</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:50:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347328707071-141</Id><Title>Twisting ARMs</Title><Msg>From: Hot Hardware IDF ARM: ARM is in an awkward position. It doesn't directly compete against Intel, but it's the face of a successful mobile architecture that's increasingly threatened by Intel's Atom. With Intel talking up Clover Trail tablets and Atom going out-of-order at 22nm, ARM is going to focus on the Cortex-A15. ARM may or may not spend much bandwidth discussing its next-generation 64-bit architecture, ARMv8. The company's focus will be on painting Intel as a would-be competitor saddled with an x86 architecture that's too hamstrung by legacy issues to compete effectively. It's worth noting in advance that this simply isn't true. Intel's goal for smartphones in 2012 was to launch a platform that could compete with other midrange Android phones. It did so. Even if Intel's 22nm Atom slips to later in 2013, as is currently rumored, the company can afford the delay.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347328707071</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:58:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347329136642-142</Id><Title>Is QE3 Coming this Thursday?</Title><Msg>People have been clamoring for QE3 for more than a year. Now it seems the noise has reached a fever pitch. UBS ( UBS ) joined the list of market forecasters predicting that the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) will announce a third round of quantitative easing at its monthly meeting this Thursday. JPMorgan Chase ( JPM ) and Goldman Sachs ( GS ) had previously predicted that the Fed would take action this week. Many are viewing last Friday's jobs report as the tipping point.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347329136642</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347331309773-143</Id><Title>Intel and better cloud Server chips or a Coward named Vinnie?</Title><Msg>Intel tying server chips to fabric for cloud computing, HPC By Agam Shah, IDG News Sep 10, 2012 10:20 am ntel on Monday said it is developing high-performance server chips that in the future will serve up faster results from cloud services or data-intensive applications like analytics, all while cutting electricity bills in data centers. The chip maker will integrate a converged fabric controller inside future server chips, which will make server communication faster while helping data centers operate at peak efficiency, said Raj Hazra, vice president of the Intel Architecture Group. Fabric virtualizes I/O and ties together storage and networking in data centers, and an integrated controller will provide a wider pipe to scale performance across distributed computing environments. The integrated fabric controller will appear in the company's Xeon server chips in a few years, Hazra said. He declined to provide a specific date, but said the company has the manufacturing capability in place to bring the controller to the transistor layer. The controller will offer bandwidth of more than 100 gigabytes per second, which will be significantly faster than the speed offered by today's networking and I/O interfaces. The chips have enough transistors to accommodate the controllers, which will only add a few watts of power draw, Hazra said. Companies with huge Web-serving needs like Google, Facebook and Amazon buy servers in large volumes and are looking to lower energy costs while scaling performance. Fabrics connect and facilitate low-latency data movement between processors, memory, servers and endpoints like storage and appliances. Depending on the server implementation and system topology, fabrics are flexible and can organize traffic patterns in an energy-efficient way, Hazra said. For example, analytics and databases demand in-memory processing, and cloud services rely on a congregation of low-power processors and shared components in dense servers. An integrated controller will help fabrics intelligently reroute or pre-fetch data and software packets so shared endpoints work together to serve up faster results. HPC or high-end server environments may use a fabric with a mix of InfiniBand, Ethernet networking and proprietary interconnect technologies, while a cloud implementation may have microservers with fabric based on standard Ethernet and PCI-Express technologies. Fabric controllers currently sit outside the processor, but integration at the transistor level also reduces the amount of energy burned in fetching data from the processor and memory, Hazra said. The integrated controller in the CPU will be directly connected to the fabric, and will also make servers denser with fewer boards, cables and power supplies, which could help cut power bills, Hazra said. Intel for decades has been integrating computing elements at the transistor level to eke out significant power savings and better performance from processors. Intel has integrated the memory controller and graphics processor, and the fabric controller is next, Hazra said. "That's the path we're on with fabrics," Hazra said. "Integration is a must." Intel's processor business is weakening partly due to a slowdown in PC sales, and the company's profits are now being driven by the higher-margin data center business. Intel's server processors already dominate data centers, and integration of the fabric controller is a key development in the company's attempts to bring networking and storage closer to servers. Intel has quietly been integrating the fabric controller on chips and made a series of acquisitions to boost its interconnect and networking portfolio, Hazra said. Intel bought privately held networking company Fulcrum for an undisclosed price in July last year, acquired InfiniBand assets from Qlogic $125 million in January this year, and then purchased interconnect assets from Cray $140 million in April. Intel's rival Advanced Micro Devices has its own fabric technology acquired from SeaMicro, a server company it purchased for $334 million [M] this year. Prior to the acquisition, SeaMicro previously developed microservers with Intel and was subject to rumors of acquisition by the chip maker. But soon after AMD acquired SeaMicro, Intel said it was working on its own fabric and had no interest in the SeaMicro's fabric technology. AMD is now selling SeaMicro-branded servers technology and has plans to put the fabric, called Freedom Fabric, in products ranging from dense servers to supercomputers. AMD executives have hinted they will integrate the fabric controller inside chips. AMD is expected to make an announcement around its SeaMicro products on Monday. Server chip maker Calxeda also has a system-on-chip called EnergyCore that packs ARM processor cores with a fabric switch.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347331309773</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:41:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347331805492-144</Id><Topic><Title>Intel and better cloud Server chips or a Coward named Vinnie?</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347331309773</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:41:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ummm, AAPL stock up 30x (3,000%) while INTC talks about optimized FORTRAN code? You decide. I already said INTC fabs are second to none. So use that for mobile stuff, where 99.999999999999% of the action is. INTC is stuck on super I/O chips, USB, Win 98 (SE) and rotating disk drives.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347331805492</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347331936614-145</Id><Title>Yes, INTC dominates the server market. Crushes the competition.</Title><Msg>So, they have locked up about .0000000001% of the market. Hands down. No competition. Done deal. Dead to rights. Signed, sealed, delivered. Good job. Meanwhile, stupid little AAPL steals the entire consumer marketplace.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347331936614</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:52:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347332117704-146</Id><Topic><Title>Intel and better cloud Server chips or a Coward named Vinnie?</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347331309773</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:41:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vinnie, please don't attempt to obscure the facts by pointing out the performance of INTC over the last decade. That is the past. So Wallis was wrong about the past. So what? Wallis is nothing if not forward looking. It's all about the rosy future of FORTRAN optimization and McAfee ripping off witless consumers to slow down their computers. That's the future, Vinnie.</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1347332117704</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:55:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347332303364-147</Id><Topic><Title>Intel and better cloud Server chips or a Coward named Vinnie?</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347331309773</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:41:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>12 Billion dollars in 3 months in a crappy economy says Vinnie is an idiot.</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1347332303364</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:58:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347332667580-148</Id><Topic><Title>Intel and better cloud Server chips or a Coward named Vinnie?</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347331309773</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:41:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem with your assessment is that Vinnie has been right about the stock for the last decade while the optimists have been dead wrong and have been treated to dead money as a result.</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1347332667580</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 23:04:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347332786555-149</Id><Topic><Title>Is QE3 Coming this Thursday?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347329136642</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's say it is coming, Wallus. Is that going to turn INTC from a dog into a darling?</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1347332786555</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 23:06:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347332812944-150</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, INTC dominates the server market. Crushes the competition.</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347331936614</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are a little low on the Intel server market share aren't you? I thought it was about 80%? Apple is the largest player in the consumer marketplace. They have a lot of room to grow. Apple PC market share is below 20%. Apple smartphone market shares is now 17% they have room to take market share back. Apple tablet market share is 70%. "Entire consumer marketplace" you are talking about is the tablet market?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347332812944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 23:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347333042065-151</Id><Title>Psss, Vinny (Lucy)..hate to blow your cover but INTEL profits heavily when Apple phones are sold</Title><Msg>Apple phones sold = more servers (servers chips are the highest margin chips) Intel sells. Again, to recap, Apple sells phones and Intel profits as a result.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347333042065</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 23:10:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347333141369-152</Id><Topic><Title>Psss, Vinny (Lucy)..hate to blow your cover but INTEL profits heavily when Apple phones are sold</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347333042065</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 23:10:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When do Intel shareholders make money?</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1347333141369</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 23:12:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347333281112-153</Id><Topic><Title>Intel and better cloud Server chips or a Coward named Vinnie?</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347331309773</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:41:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem with your assessment is that Vinnie has been right about the stock for the last decade while the optimists have been dead wrong and have been treated to dead money as a result. ++++++++++++++++++++ Tell that garbage to the people that bought at 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23 and even higher since they got paid the Dividend the whole time. Lucy/Vinny (same loser), you are so dumb that's it's not even fun to kick you around.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347333281112</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 23:14:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347335450532-154</Id><Topic><Title>Psss, Vinny (Lucy)..hate to blow your cover but INTEL profits heavily when Apple phones are sold</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347333042065</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 23:10:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When do INTEL share holders make money? Just like many did today. Options. Learn the game.</Msg><Username>makahasnow692</Username><Timestamp>1347335450532</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 23:50:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>