<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351140630563-1</Id><Topic><Title>it's Windows on Surface RT that's the greatest letdown of all...</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351106394061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is just what I was thinking. The Surface is not capable of being a work computer. It is also too large and expensive to function as a cheap, portable tablet. I have a 23" HP Touchsmart as my main home computer. I just bought a HP 14" laptop with an Intel i5 processor and 8GB of ram for just over $500 as my portable work computer. I am planning on buying the new Nook HD 7" tablet for $199 which I will probably just leave in my car for use as a portable tablet.</Msg><Username>tlee22202</Username><Timestamp>1351140630563</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 00:50:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351141305217-2</Id><Topic><Title>Options: SELLING JAN $21 CALLS</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351103682462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think the action is overt and an attempt to push the stock price either up or down. I think the process is only designed by someone to take a large option position with a prepaid entry/exit cost that is less than the dividend. As a side effect, the process encourages the option market maker (OMM) to take action. When he is pressured to short, it is like swimming laps with a 1 pound weight on your back. The stock does not sink to the bottom but as you swim, it takes more effort to stay up. When the OMM is encouraged to buy, there is buoyancy and floats up the price. Like Tuesday when INTC was strong in a down market. Last NOV, there was 1.6million contracts traded on the day before ex-dividend. That translated 160mil shares. I am watching and gathering data.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351141305217</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 01:01:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351145664223-3</Id><Topic><Title>Young Women Voting Early Coast to Coast for Mitt Romney</Title><Username>political_gangsters</Username><Timestamp>1351120370532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:12:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Voting for romney is voting for america. If you love our beautiful country you should vote for a president who cares, protects and promotes america. That is not obama. Obama is not for america. Obama is for himself and muslim countries.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351145664223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 02:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351148352369-4</Id><Title>Rumor has it, boom boom Rumor has it</Title><Msg>Rumor has it Intels the one I'm leaving you 44444444444444444444444444444444444. Pay that Divyy, beeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeethces !</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351148352369</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 02:59:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351152751653-5</Id><Topic><Title>Intel CEO: ARM, QCOM &amp; NVDA are threats.</Title><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351098256290</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:04:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>allthingsdDOTcom/20121024/exclusive-intel-ceo-paul-otellini-on-windows-8-the-tablet-market-and-competing-with-arm/ Intel CEO Paul Otellini on Windows 8, the Tablet Market and Competing With ARM 'Windows 8 represents a new kind of Windows release for Intel both in terms of the opportunities to expand into new markets as well as the threats posed to the chipmaker’s core PC processor business. On the one hand, the chipmaker sees the new Microsoft operating system as a way to both drive traditional PC sales as well as crack the tablet market today dominated by Apple’s iPad. “It’s a watershed event,” Otellini told AllThingsD in a telephone interview Wednesday. “The fact it spans form traditional PCs and tablets and then in all the hybrid devices in between is really very powerful. it allows the hardware side to really exercise creativity in a way that we haven’t been able to do for quite some time.” However, the release also presents new challenges and comes at a time when PC sales are under pressure from both a weak economy and as consumers are opting to spend their electronics budget on other purchases, including tablets. Intel has already warned that it expects slower-than-traditional PC growth in the fourth quarter, though Otellini said it is hard to say how much Windows 8's move into tablets might help things. “That particular element won’t be known until January when you count the numbers and see how well Windows 8 tablets did versus Android versus iPad,” Otellini said. Even on the PC side, Intel will have to deal with greater competition. Though used to competing against smaller rival Advanced Micro Devices, Intel now finds itself in competition also with ARM-based chipmakers such as Qualcomm and Nvidia now that Microsoft has a flavor of Windows — Windows RT — that runs on those chips. Otellini noted that Intel has seen other rivals come and go in the PC market before, including chipmakers such as Via and Transmeta. “I happen to be around long enough to remember those guys,” he siad. “People come and go and we’ve never had an exclusive, if you will, and overall the best chip has won.” While Windows RT machines can boast strong battery life, Otellini said that Intel-based machines will be able to offer compatibility the ARM-based companies won’t, noting Intel-based Windows 8 machines will run all the software and Web sites written for past versions of Windows. “That will not be as true on the RT (machines),” Otellini said. “I’m not sure that iTunes runs. I’m not sure that Quicken runs.” As for whether Windows 8 is ready for prime time, Otellini says the PC industry is ready. “It’s in perfect shape,” Otellini said. The company also found itself with some explaining to do after Bloomberg reported earlier this month that Otellini questioned Windows 8's readiness at an internal meeting. The company has since been trying to reaffirm its hopes for the release, including at an event in San Francisco. Otellini says he is quite excited about the opportunity with Windows 8. “We’ve been anxiously awaiting it,” Otellini said. “I’ve been doing this for a long time and I haven’t seen this level of excitement and creativity within the joint Intel-Microsoft customer base in a long time.” Otellini won’t be in New York for the big launch, though. He and other top Intel executives are at an internal meeting in San Diego for much of this week. But Windows 8 represents an opportunity for the PC to continue to evolve and change. Touch machines in particular, Otellini said, are poised to become a mainstay throughout the PC market. “A year from now I think selling a PC without touch will be very difficult, at least (for consumers). Enterprises are slower to change.” Otellini said he has personally been using a touchscreen Acer machine. “It’s pretty compelling,” he said. “I never thought that I would … touch my screen much, but it works out pretty well.” That said, Otellini isn’t convinced everyone will shift to tablets. “I happen to believe that the standalone tablet is not the form factor people will (move) to,” Otellini said. “The fact everybody is now fitting tablets with keyboards suggests that real buyers have come to the same conclusion.”'</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351152751653</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 04:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351153731899-6</Id><Topic><Title>NYK2OH gets his tail kicked by Marsavian, part 1</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350649302914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:21:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>theblueredmonk: 'We will see what Clovertrail can do in reality.' The reality matches my analysis and proves MSFT have released a major lemon with their Tegra 3 Surface tablet which is not quick and has no meaningful apps and which should bomb within months ..... anandtechDOTcom/show/6385/microsoft-surface-review/10</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351153731899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 04:28:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351154723588-7</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is the next RIMM</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350510973251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:56:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'How about if we suffer from a flood of $25 ARM processors for low-end laptops? Have you heard that Windows 8 is ARM compatible.' A flood that just won't get sold. There are already $25 low-end laptop chips that unlike ARM are fully Windows legacy compatible, AMD and Via make them and they are faster than ARM chips and already 64-bit enabled yet they are the ones going out of business not Intel which has had no need to shift its prices and margins down due to their threat. ARM is a paper tiger threat to Intel, once that is fully understood by the market then both their prices will adjust to more realistic p/e in both cases with INTC doubling and ARMH halving or less. Performance leaderships allows you set any price you want for desktops/notebooks, ask Apple, so Intel will still be able to sell some $300 chips indefinitely going forward if they are quick enough and they will be. The fact you are willing to buy INTC at 17 shows even you don't really believe your #$%$.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351154723588</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 04:45:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351155075662-8</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is the next RIMM</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350510973251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:56:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's only in PCs that people buy the gadget for its "performance". If you look at ads for tablets or smartphones, the processor is only one of many factors being highlighted.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1351155075662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 04:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351155903649-9</Id><Title>INTC SHORT INTEREST 182,497,589</Title><Msg>short sellers are NOT investors</Msg><Username>dedrapop</Username><Timestamp>1351155903649</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 05:05:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351167547278-10</Id><Title>nearly 5% dividend yield and trading near 52 wk low. think i add some</Title><Msg>great blue chip and safe harbour for your money.</Msg><Username>magkandler</Username><Timestamp>1351167547278</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 08:19:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351170180979-11</Id><Title>Warren Buffett "dumping" shares... what a JOKE!</Title><Msg>I keep seeing articles (at least 1 a week) referencing Berkshire Hathaway (Buffett's holding company) "dumping" INTC... what A joke... If we look at the price range the stock was selling at when Berkshire bought INTC and the price range it was selling at when Berkshire sold INTC, they made at minimum $7,000,000 for holding if for less than a year, and if they bought and sold at the better ends of the equation, they made over $20,000,000 for holding for less than a year... what anyone in their right mind would call that "dumping" is beyond me... they made a VERY good profit on their trade no matter how you look at it... Freakin' articles are ridiculous... the guy's smart when it comes to trading, he DIDN'T make a bad investment, he made MONEY!</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351170180979</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:03:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351170498095-12</Id><Topic><Title>Might as well call this now... below $21 this Friday...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351090013959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was up this morning, back down to flat... will be under $21 by the end of Friday... the hope that I'm wrong is fading fast... and how far it goes from there is questionable, but we could see $19, however, there are some positives between now and the end of NEXT Friday... hopefully those can help it changes its course...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351170498095</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351170609686-13</Id><Topic><Title>Might as well call this now... below $21 this Friday...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351090013959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who cares in 2 years from now you will make a safe 10% p.a. no matter what the price might be on friday</Msg><Username>magkandler</Username><Timestamp>1351170609686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:10:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351170927503-14</Id><Topic><Title>Might as well call this now... below $21 this Friday...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351090013959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not sure why you keep giving your targets here that only shows you are wrong most of the time... lol btw,since to me it's clear you are not long on Intel. I was wondering if you shorted shares or just bought puts?</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351170927503</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:15:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351171271793-15</Id><Title>Acer won't even associate with ARMH chips</Title><Msg>Why Acer Is Holding Off on Windows RT for Now October 25, 2012 at 6:00 am PT inShare.SharePrint Acer will have a ton of Windows 8 machines on store shelves this week, but it will have no computers running Windows RT — the version of the operating system that can run on ARM-based chips from Nvidia and Qualcomm. The company has hardware designs ready, but won’t ship them until next year. “We thought about it,” Acer computer unit President Campbell Kan said in an interview. “We do have products ready.” For now, though, Acer is going with a lineup of touch-centric laptops, tablets and all-in-ones, all powered by Intel chips. Maybe that’s why Intel CEO Paul Otellini happily boasts about his experience with a touch-based Windows 8 laptop from Acer. Other PC makers are hedging their bets. Longtime Intel customer Dell, for example, has a convertible tablet using a Qualcomm processor, while Nvidia is powering Microsoft’s Surface and Lenovo. While not straying outside the processor mainstream, Acer has bet heavily on touch, saying it is a necessary ingredient for a good Windows 8 experience. Without it, “it makes no sense,” Kan said. The challenge, he said, is that few people have really played with Windows and touch. “When you start to use Windows 8, you will figure out you couldn’t live without touch.”</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351171271793</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351171767455-16</Id><Topic><Title>Might as well call this now... below $21 this Friday...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351090013959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're both right... I had planned on being short-term on INTC (like till the end of the year). I've never short-ed any stock, however would have liked to have shorted intel when I bought it instead of buying it, but that didn't happen, so I'm holding 2000 shares till I can at minimum get out without losing too much... I was just looking for some input and other's speculation of where the prices would be... I'll stop the speculation posting and stick to topics at hand..</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351171767455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351171821623-17</Id><Topic><Title>INTC SHORT INTEREST 182,497,589</Title><Username>dedrapop</Username><Timestamp>1351155903649</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 05:05:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope, but they're making good money right now...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351171821623</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351172449738-18</Id><Topic><Title>junk is junk</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351087519276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we need more UP! or Someone knows something posts or more letters!!!! Letters seem to move Intc, UP!</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351172449738</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:40:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351173138182-19</Id><Topic><Title>Acer won't even associate with ARMH chips</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351171271793</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:21:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's pretty obvious Clovertrail has aborted WinRT chips at birth. If they can't outperform and and can't outlast Clovertrail and have zero legacy support what exactly are they bringing to the table ? A $5-10 price difference ? Not enough to make up for all the deficiencies. Like I said before, Clovertrail is the right product at the the right time which makes a nice change for Intel who are used to being behind the curve in extreme mobility ;-). Clovertrail+ with the powerful dual gpu and LTE will carry on dishing out the punishment to ARM chips on Android pretty soon.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351173138182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351174025502-20</Id><Topic><Title>Housing Starts in U.S. Surged in September to Four-Year High</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350480833025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Home sales report just came in, FLAT ! Got to have a job to buy a home. Obama just doesn't get it, has no business sense whatsoever. And you want 4 mo of dat. We tried it and now we must go back even though they say you can't.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351174025502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:07:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351174134206-21</Id><Topic><Title>Surprise Jack Welch</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350067709848</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 14:48:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Welch is clueless? Did Jack call for $3 eps ? Did Jack call for $30 ? So who's clueless? you and your hot tub buddies. No one has been as wrong as you these last 2 years.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351174134206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:08:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351174710461-22</Id><Topic><Title>Options: SELLING JAN $21 CALLS</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351103682462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This makes the most sense so far as to what's going on... just hope the Q4 numbers blow away the Q3 numbers...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351174710461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:18:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351174813104-23</Id><Topic><Title>Acer won't even associate with ARMH chips</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351171271793</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:21:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>makes a nice change for Intel who are used to being behind the curve Causing extreme pain to Intel stockholders! Hope what you are saying is true...would like to reap some decent benefits soon.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1351174813104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:20:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351174994721-24</Id><Topic><Title>Surprise Jack Welch</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350067709848</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 14:48:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's hoping for another 80 cent or more up day today... KEEP IT GOING INTC!</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351174994721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351175340356-25</Id><Topic><Title>Surprise Jack Welch</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350067709848</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 14:48:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clueless or not, Jack Welch gave the impression that he acted more like a cheerleader than a sharp, rational businessman - very much like us ordinary folks... Even he himself admits that he should have added question marks at the end of his tweet...pretty bad judgment on his part when he sent that tweet.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1351175340356</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351175353567-26</Id><Title>no power</Title><Msg>will be lobster red, no power to hold the gains, i told you so! short short short! $$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351175353567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:29:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351175426242-27</Id><Topic><Title>no power</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351175353567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:29:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope your smart enough to also buy when it goes down in addition to buying to cover, then you make money both ways...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351175426242</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351175661801-28</Id><Topic><Title>no power</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351175353567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:29:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i short it every time when it goes up, because it couldn't hold the gains , it works all the time, easy money!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351175661801</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:34:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351177035051-29</Id><Topic><Title>Surprise Jack Welch</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350067709848</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 14:48:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can agree with part of that but how old is he now? At a certain age everyone declines a bit. Although Warren seemed sharp as usual on cnbc yesterday. I get a kick out of warren.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351177035051</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:57:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351177040461-30</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BATATAGGLIA SAID LAST NIGHT</Title><Username>xtremeskier33</Username><Timestamp>955040744000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2000-04-06 13:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There is no difference in that and me telling you your #$%$ wife should and probably will die of cancer. Your mother also deserved to suffer when she died you effing POS." I'm not married, and my mother passed away very peacefully while sleeping at home (quite a long time ago). But what has any of this to do with Joe the Batman Battapaglia's bullishness on Intel?</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1351177040461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:57:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351177455486-31</Id><Topic><Title>Surprise Jack Welch</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350067709848</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 14:48:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And "ratinal", what was rational about 8.1 to 7.8 at that time? that was political #$%$.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351177455486</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:04:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351177474096-32</Id><Topic><Title>Surprise Jack Welch</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350067709848</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 14:48:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>arrrrrrgh, rational.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351177474096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:04:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351177878321-33</Id><Title>Jack Welch</Title><Msg>Jack could give a crap about you and me, he threw people out the door at GE. People are what make a company. He might not pay here in this life, he will in the afterlife. All these CEO's letting people go, if they needed them 30 years ago why not now? Its all about greed and the bottom line.</Msg><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1351177878321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:11:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351179352577-34</Id><Topic><Title>Jack Welch</Title><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1351177878321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Businesses don't want obama. If you vote for him you are voting against yourself. That is reality. Just face it. If you want to have a job and prosper vote for romney.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351179352577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:35:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351179439512-35</Id><Title>Fabless margins will be squezed relentlessly</Title><Msg>Why node shrinks are no longer offsetting equipment costs Remember the M. Bohr article posted by Marvasian? In each paragraph Mark Bohr pointed out to cost whether SOI or TSV. Design and Manufacturing need to work together with real time cost checks - Moore's law is slowing for fabless eco system but not for Intel The real kicker here? Lower costs per transistor aren't even the real driving factor for semiconductor manufacturers, it's reducing power consumption while maintaining performance, the Gartner analysts note. That's the key functionality driving semiconductor content in mobile devices, and that's what is driving the market now. (It's a little different for memory which does rely on lower unit/production costs even if it's a slight improvement.) "Overall, the semiconductor and electronics industry will have to come to grips with the fact that traditional cost reductions with each new node are in jeopardy, and in the future, higher performance may very well come at a higher price," the analysts note. And one more factor to consider: semiconductor average selling prices (ASPs) have benefitted from the relentless node-shrink cost reductions, but semiconductor manufacturers are unlikely to (nor should they) swallow all these cost increases by themselves for the good of the rest of the supply chain. "What is more likely is that ASP trends will reverse after years of decline, and that reversal will change the supply-and-demand economics of the industry in ways that we don't really understand today," the Gartner analysts admit.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1351179439512</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351179656294-36</Id><Title>Colin Powell Endorses Obama</Title><Msg>http://www.cbsnews.com/8301-505263_162-57539893/colin-powell-endorses-barack-obama-for-president/</Msg><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351179656294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:40:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351180365232-37</Id><Topic><Title>no power</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351175353567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:29:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uggh... look at that, you were right again... sure would have liked to have shorted at 22.70 and 22.50 instead of being stuck there now... we'll here's to hoping the price shoots back up and you're smart enough to have made your money while it was possible...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351180365232</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:52:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351180397962-38</Id><Topic><Title>Jack Welch</Title><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1351177878321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I early voted yesterday for Romney/Ryan...We can't stand another 4 years of this. Romney will trim some of these entitlements, that is people that drive BMW's won't keep getting their food stamps.</Msg><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1351180397962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351180411082-39</Id><Title>Does Texas Istruments' decision in 2007 bode well for them today?</Title><Msg>Texas Instruments exits process development race Peter Clarke 1/24/2007 5:27 AM EST LONDON — Texas Instruments Inc., one of the largest and most successful integrated device manufacturers, has decided to drop the costly business of digital logic process development and rely on foundry partners for its processes. According to reports TI (Dallas, Texas) development has decided to stop internal development at the 45-nanometer node and use foundry supplied processes at 32-nm, 22-nm and thereafter. This would allow the company to save a great deal of money in both process development and fab building and allow it to focus on adding value in design. The extension of the strategy would see the company going fabless, at least in the digital arena. However, it also removes one of the companies advantages over fabless competitors such as Qualcomm Inc. TI (Dallas, Texas) made the announcement that it would exit digital CMOS process development as part of its fourth quarter and full year financial results although the news was mixed in with the announcement that the company would close its Kilby wafer fab in Dallas and move the manufacturing equipment into several of its existing analog fabs with a loss of about 500 jobs by the end of the year. However, the decision to stop developing digital chipmaking processes — by a company credited with the co-invention of the integrated circuit — is likely to be more significant in the long term. Many more fabs look set to close over time. "Entering 2007, we challenge ourselves to keep improving performance. One way we'll do this is by changing the way we develop advanced digital process technology. Instead of separately creating our own core technology, we will work collaboratively with our foundry partners to specify and drive the next generations of digital process technology, and we will continue making products on these technologies in our world-class factories," said Rich Templeton, TI president and chief executive officer, in a statement. TI has long used foundries, such as Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. Ltd., United Microelectronics Corp. and Semiconductor Manufacturing International Corp., as buffer suppliers whose proportion of TI output can ebb and flow with economic cycles. However, despite the fact that Templeton spoked of bringing foundry processes into TI wafer fabs that would seem set to be a transitionary measure. It seems unlikely that TI would ever construct a leading-edge wafer fab again and is set to let its own manufacturing of advanced digital CMOS wither on the vine.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351180411082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:53:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351180459724-40</Id><Title>Recession worldwide: Ford to shut more plants in Europe.</Title><Msg>Europe is in very bad economical condition which is affecting the US and the rest of the world, more unemployment, more people in the streets, this world is doomed.............</Msg><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351180459724</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:54:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351181854803-41</Id><Topic><Title>Jack Welch</Title><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1351177878321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If you want to have a job and prosper vote for romney." If your star is aligned with that of ROMNEY (you are wealthy and passive investment income), vote for ROMNEY because he will do well by you. If you are a social conservative who wants to impose your beliefs on everyone, vote for ROMNEY because he will have to pay off that wing. If you are out side these two groups, look to the BUSH record to see what your future is. ROMNEY advisors are the old BUSH team, sans CHENEY. But who knows, maybe ROMNEY will bring him back too, Otherwise, it is impossible to say which of the ROMNEY promises will be kept. He has been on both sides of every issue. WHORNEY will say anything to anyone to get elected. I voted too, too, too, too, too, too, too, too, too, too. I sent off 14 absentee ballots to Ohio this morning. TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYY!!!</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351181854803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351182803275-42</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney Has Empowered Women: Obama a Desperate Arrogant Attack Dog Want to Scare Women -Wow - Mr. President Please Wait for Halloween By democrat_ladies . 46 minutes ago . Permalink How Romney has empowered women By Jane Edmonds, Special to CNN updated 2:25 PM EDT, Wed October 24, 2012 Editor's note: Jane Edmonds served as a member of Gov. Mitt Romney's cabinet and as head of the Department of Workforce Development in Massachusetts. She also was an appointee of Gov. Michael S. Dukakis and served as chair of the Massachusetts Commission Against Discrimination (MCAD), the civil rights law enforcement agency for the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. She is a surrogate for Mitt Romney's presidential campaign. (CNN) -- "Baby, law isn't a good profession for girls," my father told me. "Stay with music, dear, that is what you and your people do so well," my high school dean said. I was 16, and asking them the most important question of my life: Will you tell me how to become a lawyer? My dad was a product of the segregated South. Orphaned at the age of 12, he pulled himself up by his bootstraps. After leaving Georgia for Washington, where he lived with a relative, he attended an integrated school, Dunbar High. Eventually, he earned his way into Syracuse University, where he was one of the first black men to graduate. In spite of his achievements, he and our family faced discrimination. Nevertheless, he kept his sense of humor, and worked hard to be a good provider. My father's message was loving and protective. He didn't want to see me hurt. My dean's message was scornful and discriminatory. She took a sledgehammer to my dreams, and when I left her office that day, I was crushed and fighting tears. I couldn't understand her answer. I wanted to go to a good college, attend a respected law school and advocate for people needing help and craving justice. I refused to abandon these high hopes. Opinion: Does Romney 'get' women who work? And I didn't. I followed my dreams and went to law school. More than 40 years later, I became one of the 10 women named to top policy-making posts in the early months of Gov. Mitt Romney's administration in Massachusetts. There, I headed up the Department of Workforce Development. During Gov. Romney's tenure, our state led the nation in terms of the ratio of women holding top spots in the administration, and to this day, that's something about which I am incredibly proud to have been a part of. And so, as I've heard criticism about Gov. Romney's admirable record of recruiting women to serve in his administration, I feel compelled to speak out about the Mitt Romney I know. I remember meeting him for the first time. I was struck by his authenticity, and over the years that I worked with him, I saw the accuracy of my first impression. Gov. Romney's overriding commitment was not to self-promotion -- as is so often the case for politicians -- but for the people he served, and the people he served with. He believes in empowering women. I would know, because I was one of those women he recruited and respected. Opinion: Romney's empty 'binders full of women' Today, there are more than 5 million women around this country -- mothers, daughters, breadwinners -- who are unemployed. They are not only robbed of their dignity and their self-respect; they are also robbed of the results of decades of hard work. More women are in poverty -- 25.7 million -- than at any time in our nation's history. And for too many young people, the doors of opportunity remain closed shut by these tough economic circumstances. Half of recent college graduates are either jobless or underemployed. The cost of college has continued to rise in the last four years and student loan debt stands at record levels. When Mitt Romney was governor, he worked with a legislature that was 87% Democratic to get things done. And to me, that really meant something: I consider myself a liberal Democrat. For him, it wasn't about who you were, it was about the quality of your ideas. That's how he improved the economy and balanced the budget, but that's not all he accomplished. Gov. Romney also initiated the John and Abigail Adams Scholarship to cover the cost of college at public institutions of higher education in the state for deserving high school students based on academic merit. During his time as governor, Massachusetts maintained its schools' ranking as first in the nation. Opportunity. Empowerment. That's what Mitt Romney has stood for while in politics and in business, and that's what matters to women. In government, he created opportunities for young people to attend college. In business, he took a chance on people to allow their dreams to flourish into realities. I've been able to rise in life because of people who see the world this way. Looking back, I'm grateful to those who believe that education is a civil right and that the dreams of all should be encouraged and cultivated. And that's precisely why I'm supporting Mitt Romney.</Msg><Username>political_gangsters</Username><Timestamp>1351182803275</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:33:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351182996780-43</Id><Title>"ARMH + RHT + AMCC" to develop disruptive 64-bit server platform.</Title><Msg>10/25/2012 12:20: Red Hat, ARM, Applied Micro to develop disruptive 64-bit server platform - ARM (ARMH), Red Hat (RHT) and Applied Micro Circuits (AMCC) announced a collaboration that aims to develop a disruptive 64-bit server design platform to dramatically lower the total cost of ownership of cloud computing, data centers and enterprises.</Msg><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351182996780</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:36:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351183759535-44</Id><Title>So our Gross Margins will go even lower if we succeed in Mobile??????</Title><Msg>Am I missing something, or are we done growing forever? And this looks like Intel getting to 14nm doesn't mean much. by David Manners 10/24/2012 Intel has no advantage in IC manufacturing when it comes to manufacturing processes used for mobile ICs, Warren East, CEO of ARM, tells EW. "This time last year there was a lot of noise from the Intel camp about their manufacturing superiority," says East, "we're sceptical about this because, while the ARM ecosystem was shipping on 28nm, Intel was shipping on 32nm. So I don't see where they're ahead." Furthermore, with the foundries accelerating their process development timescales, it looks increasingly unlikely that Intel will be able to find any advantage on mobile process technology in the future. "We're supporting all the independent foundries," says East. That includes 20nm planar bulk CMOS and 16nm finfet at TSMC; 20nm planar bulk CMOS and 14nm finfet at Samsung and 20nm planar bulk CMOS, 20nm FD-SOI and 14nm finfet at Globalfoundries. It gives the ARM ecosystem a formidable array of processes to choose from. "I'm no better equipped to judge which of these processes will be more successful than anyone else," says East, "our approach is to be process agnostic." The important thing is that the foundries' process roadmap is on track to intersect Intel's at 14nm. 14nm will be the first process at which Intel intends to put mobile SOCs to the front of the node i.e. putting them among the first ICs to be made on a new process. Asked if the foundries were prepping their next generation processes with the intention of putting mobile SOC at the front of the node, East replies: That's the information we're seeing from our foundry partners." Globalfoundries intends to have 14nm finfet in volume manufacturing in 2014, the same timescale as Intel has for introducing 14nm finfet manufacturing. In fact, GF's 14nm process may have smaller features than Intel's 14nm process because, says Mojy Chian senior vp at Globalfoundries, because "Intel's terminology doesn't typically correlate with the terminology used by the foundry industry. For instance Intel's 22nm in terms of the back-end metallisation is similar to the foundry industry's 28nm. The design rules and pitch for Intel's 22nm are very similar to those for foundries' 28nm processes." Jean-Marc Chery, CTO of STMicroelectronics points out that the drawn gate length on Intel's ˜22nm" process is actually 26nm. Furthermore Intel's triangular fins, which degrade the advantages of finfet processing could underperform GF's rectangular fins which optimise the finfet advantage. At the front of the GF 14nm finfet node will be mobile SOCs says Chian. GF has been working with ARM since 2009 to optimise its processes for ARM-based SOCs. At TSMC the first tape-out on its 16nm finfet process is expected at the end of next year. That test chip will be based on ARM's 64-bit V8 processor. Using an ARM processor to validate its 16-nm finfet process should give TSMC's ARM-based SOC customers great confidence. Asked about the effects of finfets on ARM-based SOCs, East replies: "There'ss no rocket science in what you get out of it. The question is does it deliver the benefits at an acceptable cost? You don't get something for nothing. How much does it cost to manufacture? How good is the yield? And that, of course, affects cost." And so on goes Intel beating its head against the wall to get into the low-margin mobile business. Recently Intel said it expected its Q4 gross margin to drop 6% from Q3's 63% to 57%. Shock, horror said the analysts But if Intel succeeds in the mobile business, its gross margin will drop a lot more than that. It's a funny old world.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1351183759535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:49:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351183924354-45</Id><Title>INTC is started yesterday trending UP</Title><Msg>Watch this stock will move significant higher in next few days.</Msg><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1351183924354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:52:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351183959261-46</Id><Title>Marsavian.............read it and weep</Title><Msg>ed Hat, Inc. : ARM, Red Hat and AppliedMicro Aim to Develop Disruptive 64-bit Server Platform 10/25/2012| 12:20pm US/Eastern Collaborate to Deliver Disruptive Hardware and Open Source Software for the Cloud, Data Center and Enterprise ARM, Red Hat, Inc. (NYSE:RHT) and Applied Micro Circuits Corporation (NASDAQ:AMCC) today announced a collaboration that aims to develop a disruptive 64-bit server design platform to dramatically lower the total cost of ownership (TCO) of cloud computing, data centers and enterprises. Fully compliant with the ARMv8 architecture, the AppliedMicro X-Gene? Server on a Chip? has been purpose-built for cloud and enterprise server deployment to deliver unprecedented low power, high performance and integration, with the goal of changing the way servers are designed for cloud, data center and enterprise applications. Red Hat, the world's leading provider of open source solutions, is actively engaged in developing support within the Fedora community for the new 64-bit ARMv8 architecture, also known as AArch64. "We have a multi-year history in the ARM space, and already have our community-powered Fedora Linux distribution running on AppliedMicro hardware in our labs," said Jon Masters, Chief ARM Architect at Red Hat. "Red Hat is collaborating with AppliedMicro to enable support for ARM's 64-bit ARMv8 architecture used in the upcoming X-Gene Server-on-Chip designs. We aim to have a remix of Fedora 19 available in time to support the roll out of that platform." "We are excited to support AppliedMicro's innovation as it develops 64-bit ARM powered server system-on-a-chips," said Tom Cronk, deputy general manager, processor division, ARM. "ARM's business model is centered on partnership, and this collaboration is a further example of ARM ensuring that a compelling software ecosystem coalesces. The ecosystem will enable the industry to take full advantage of the device innovation and integration underway for deployment in the server market." "The X-Gene platform is designed to enable web front end, big data, search and grid farm applications at a price/performance level previously not seen," said Vinay Ravuri, general manager, X-Gene, AppliedMicro. "Open source is a key piece of the equation that, when combined with our fully integrated, purpose-built Server-on-Chip, delivers the cost efficiency, power and performance needed to serve evolving data center workloads. We believe this collaboration with ARM and Red Hat will transform the cloud server market." A demonstration of the initial support for the X-Gene platform being added to the Fedora Linux distribution will be held by Jon Masters, Chief ARM Architect at Red Hat, at the upcoming 2012 ARM TechCon on November 1 at 11:00 a.m. during a panel "ARM 64-bit Architecture and the Ecosystem: The Intersection of Open Software and Hardware," co-hosted by ARM and AppliedMicro.</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1351183959261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:52:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351184031391-47</Id><Title>Marsavian read it and weep, Part deux</Title><Msg>by David Manners 10/24/2012 Intel has no advantage in IC manufacturing when it comes to manufacturing processes used for mobile ICs, Warren East, CEO of ARM, tells EW. "This time last year there was a lot of noise from the Intel camp about their manufacturing superiority," says East, "we're sceptical about this because, while the ARM ecosystem was shipping on 28nm, Intel was shipping on 32nm. So I don't see where they're ahead." Furthermore, with the foundries accelerating their process development timescales, it looks increasingly unlikely that Intel will be able to find any advantage on mobile process technology in the future. "We're supporting all the independent foundries," says East. That includes 20nm planar bulk CMOS and 16nm finfet at TSMC; 20nm planar bulk CMOS and 14nm finfet at Samsung and 20nm planar bulk CMOS, 20nm FD-SOI and 14nm finfet at Globalfoundries. It gives the ARM ecosystem a formidable array of processes to choose from. "I'm no better equipped to judge which of these processes will be more successful than anyone else," says East, "our approach is to be process agnostic." The important thing is that the foundries' process roadmap is on track to intersect Intel's at 14nm. 14nm will be the first process at which Intel intends to put mobile SOCs to the front of the node i.e. putting them among the first ICs to be made on a new process. Asked if the foundries were prepping their next generation processes with the intention of putting mobile SOC at the front of the node, East replies: That's the information we're seeing from our foundry partners." Globalfoundries intends to have 14nm finfet in volume manufacturing in 2014, the same timescale as Intel has for introducing 14nm finfet manufacturing. In fact, GF's 14nm process may have smaller features than Intel's 14nm process because, says Mojy Chian senior vp at Globalfoundries, because "Intel's terminology doesn't typically correlate with the terminology used by the foundry industry. For instance Intel's 22nm in terms of the back-end metallisation is similar to the foundry industry's 28nm. The design rules and pitch for Intel's 22nm are very similar to those for foundries' 28nm processes." Jean-Marc Chery, CTO of STMicroelectronics points out that the drawn gate length on Intel's ˜22nm" process is actually 26nm. Furthermore Intel's triangular fins, which degrade the advantages of finfet processing could underperform GF's rectangular fins which optimise the finfet advantage. At the front of the GF 14nm finfet node will be mobile SOCs says Chian. GF has been working with ARM since 2009 to optimise its processes for ARM-based SOCs. At TSMC the first tape-out on its 16nm finfet process is expected at the end of next year. That test chip will be based on ARM's 64-bit V8 processor. Using an ARM processor to validate its 16-nm finfet process should give TSMC's ARM-based SOC customers great confidence. Asked about the effects of finfets on ARM-based SOCs, East replies: "There'ss no rocket science in what you get out of it. The question is does it deliver the benefits at an acceptable cost? You don't get something for nothing. How much does it cost to manufacture? How good is the yield? And that, of course, affects cost." And so on goes Intel beating its head against the wall to get into the low-margin mobile business. Recently Intel said it expected its Q4 gross margin to drop 6% from Q3's 63% to 57%. Shock, horror said the analysts But if Intel succeeds in the mobile business, its gross margin will drop a lot more than that. It's a funny old world.</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1351184031391</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351184242389-48</Id><Topic><Title>"ARMH + RHT + AMCC" to develop disruptive 64-bit server platform.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351182996780</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:36:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A nice marketing press release from ARMH. Nov. 1st, they will have a demonstration of " the initial support for the X-Gene platform being added to the Fedora Linux distribution". THE REST OF THE ARTICLE: Fully compliant with the ARMv8 architecture, the AppliedMicro X-Gene™ Server on a Chip™ has been purpose-built for cloud and enterprise server deployment to deliver unprecedented low power, high performance and integration, with the goal of changing the way servers are designed for cloud, data center and enterprise applications. Red Hat, the world’s leading provider of open source solutions, is actively engaged in developing support within the Fedora community for the new 64-bit ARMv8 architecture, also known as AArch64. “We have a multi-year history in the ARM space, and already have our community-powered Fedora Linux distribution running on AppliedMicro hardware in our labs,” said Jon Masters, Chief ARM Architect at Red Hat. “Red Hat is collaborating with AppliedMicro to enable support for ARM's 64-bit ARMv8 architecture used in the upcoming X-Gene Server-on-Chip designs. We aim to have a remix of Fedora 19 available in time to support the roll out of that platform.” “We are excited to support AppliedMicro’s innovation as it develops 64-bit ARM powered server system-on-a-chips,” said Tom Cronk, deputy general manager, processor division, ARM. “ARM’s business model is centered on partnership, and this collaboration is a further example of ARM ensuring that a compelling software ecosystem coalesces. The ecosystem will enable the industry to take full advantage of the device innovation and integration underway for deployment in the server market.” “The X-Gene platform is designed to enable web front end, big data, search and grid farm applications at a price/performance level previously not seen,” said Vinay Ravuri, general manager, X-Gene, AppliedMicro. “Open source is a key piece of the equation that, when combined with our fully integrated, purpose-built Server-on-Chip, delivers the cost efficiency, power and performance needed to serve evolving data center workloads. We believe this collaboration with ARM and Red Hat will transform the cloud server market.” A demonstration of the initial support for the X-Gene platform being added to the Fedora Linux distribution will be held by Jon Masters, Chief ARM Architect at Red Hat, at the upcoming 2012 ARM TechCon on November 1 at 11:00 a.m. during a panel “ARM 64-bit Architecture and the Ecosystem: The Intersection of Open Software and Hardware,” co-hosted by ARM and AppliedMicro.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351184242389</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351185324744-49</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is started yesterday trending UP</Title><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1351183924354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:52:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Crossing fingers and sticking head in blender on the hope that you are right...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351185324744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:15:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351187564161-50</Id><Topic><Title>Jack Welch</Title><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1351177878321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First, Lots of high tech CEOs are backing Obama with their own money. You think Microsoft, Cisco, Oracle, and Intel are backing Romney? You are wrong. Intel is all Obama at the top. So is Microsoft. High tech companies of the west coast are behind the President. BUT oh well--Looks like it comes down to Ohio and there, Obama has already won. You rightwing trashnnnuts just do not know it yet. Early voting. Look it up for Ohio.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1351187564161</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:52:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351187574227-51</Id><Topic><Title>"ARMH + RHT + AMCC" to develop disruptive 64-bit server platform.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351182996780</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:36:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does this mean to Intel.. NOTHING...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351187574227</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:52:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351187898492-52</Id><Topic><Title>Jack Welch</Title><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1351177878321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The votes haven't been counted, so that makes you retarded... The won't work leaches have cast their ballots for their handout clown... Get the working man that understands and maybe things will change... either way, I don't think I'm voting for either of those 2 clowns...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351187898492</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:58:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351188540087-53</Id><Topic><Title>So our Gross Margins will go even lower if we succeed in Mobile??????</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1351183759535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:49:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The drop in Q4 is solely due to under capacity. Nvidia claims over 50% gross margin on a Tegra 3 chip that has 4 cores, a 12-core gpu and is priced at 20 something dollars. Gross margins won't be radically different for Atom over Core as the die size will be smaller. Even if gross margins dropped a few per cent if you double/triple your sales volume wouldn't that be a good tradeoff ?</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351188540087</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:09:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351188625213-54</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian.............read it and weep</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1351183959261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:52:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Talk is cheap.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351188625213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351188821281-55</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian read it and weep, Part deux</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1351184031391</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:53:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is how absurd that article is .... G-F have delivered no 28nm parts, they have delivered no 20nm parts yet all of sudden within 2 years they will start delivering 14nm parts in volume !! LOL</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351188821281</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351188832178-56</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is started yesterday trending UP</Title><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1351183924354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:52:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tommorow should wipe out all of today's gains and then some... below 21 tommrowo at some point... we'll see..</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351188832178</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:13:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351188922849-57</Id><Topic><Title>Jack Welch</Title><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1351177878321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess Ohio is one of the biggest "entitlement" states. Romney will bring all the entitlements to its knees. If you vote Obama you will get what you deserve.....no jobs, but you will have a WalMart to drive to in your BMW along with your food stamps....</Msg><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1351188922849</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:15:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351189363567-58</Id><Title>TSMC reports 62 percent rise in 3Q profit</Title><Msg>"mass production for the more cutting-edge 16-nanometer process could begin in a year." ------------------------------------------------------------------ TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) -- Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co., the world's largest contract chip maker, says its third quarter profit rose 62 percent year-on-year, fuelled by stronger-than-expected global demand for smartphones and tablet computers. The company said Thursday its third quarter net profit was New Taiwan dollars 49.3 billion ($1.7 billion) on revenues of NT$141 billion. TSMC supplies chips for use in gadgets including Apple's iPhones and iPads. TSMC Chairman Morris Chang says mobile devices are expected to propel the company's strong growth until 2016 at least, but inventory adjustments may lead to a modest dip in the next two quarters before a rebound. The company says shipments of 28-nanometer process technology more than doubled during the third quarter and mass production for the more cutting-edge 16-nanometer process could begin in a year.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351189363567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:22:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351189417432-59</Id><Topic><Title>So our Gross Margins will go even lower if we succeed in Mobile??????</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1351183759535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:49:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly right. Mobile volume is way too big to compensate any 'imaginable' gross margin drop. Remember, All these ARM based processor makers are living nice and well with ARM processor. The question becomes what if Intel can do the same thing but their own designs and process engineering. The margins will be much higher and sales will be even more higher with the volume of these mobile chips....will be sold like potato fries.</Msg><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1351189417432</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:23:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351189991145-60</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC reports 62 percent rise in 3Q profit</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351189363567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:22:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They can't even mass produce enough 28nmm to keep Nvidia from begging Intel to make its chips, Qualcom from being hopping mad or TMSC, itself, from telling them both to get off the ship before it sinks. LOL, all true stories! BUMP!</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351189991145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:33:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351190191142-61</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian read it and weep, Part deux</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1351184031391</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:53:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One has to appreciate the humor at the end of the article where East is saying how low the gross margins of the mobile IC business are, as if he trying to convince Intel not to pursue mobile for its own good. However while margins for the fabless ARM ecosystem may be very low - as everyone in the foodchain has to skim some of the profit - that economic model does not apply to Intel that makes everything under one roof and keeps it all. East is hilarious.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1351190191142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:36:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351190203509-62</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC reports 62 percent rise in 3Q profit</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351189363567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:22:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is the TSMC 20nm 'mass production' that obviously must come before the 16nm ? There is obviously a different definition of what constitutes 'mass' production in the ARM foundry world, maybe it means more than 1 wafer there ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351190203509</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:36:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351191318104-63</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC reports 62 percent rise in 3Q profit</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351189363567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:22:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In an interview after the keynote, Liu said TSMC will take a “modular fin” approach in finFETs. TSMC will marry a 16nm fin with a 20nm backend. “It has 20nm design rules,” he said.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351191318104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:55:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351193243083-64</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC reports 62 percent rise in 3Q profit</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351189363567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:22:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"mass production for the more cutting-edge 16-nanometer process could begin in a year." fool - I love how you this up - watch the equipments guys like ASML We see, however, sustained demand from the logic sector as the planned 28 nanometer node strategic build-up to a worldwide capacity of 300,000 wafer starts per month is expected to be achieved by mid-2013,</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1351193243083</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:27:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351195035029-65</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC reports 62 percent rise in 3Q profit</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351189363567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:22:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""mass production for the more cutting-edge 16-nanometer process could begin in a year." fool - I love how you this up - " ------------------------- Hmmm...what do you think I thought up ?? maybe you should read the articles directly quoting TSMC representatives... but tunnel vision is your game...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351195035029</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:57:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351195464300-66</Id><Topic><Title>Jack Welch</Title><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1351177878321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He did his job, grow up and stop the jealous rant. Businesses pay people for performance, they don't need them, they lay them off, duh. If you and I owned GE stock during his tenure, you'd be all wrong. I guess it depends on where you stand but he did his job.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351195464300</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 16:04:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351195695634-67</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Might Trend Downward for Months</Title><Username>profitgrowthfirst</Username><Timestamp>1350477611405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:40:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alexander, I tip my hat to you; you've done your homework. Yes, my Terex call seems to have fallen flat. Terex has beaten expectations in 4 of the last 6 quarters, but everytime the stock hits $25, it falls back down. It is a very cyclical stock and everytime we get 'scary' news regarding Greece, Spain, Portugal, or 'the China slowdown' the stock loses momentum. As for PSUN, I still think it is going bankrupt. PSUN had earned--and saved--a lot of money from 1995-2000, and again from 2003-2008. However, in the last 3 1/2 years they have squandered that entire pile of cash away and they have yet to right the ship. As for TheStreet, their management has been speaking up the company and its stock for years about how excited they are for the future. Their conference calls are always exactly the same: "(fill in the blank) will help us bring in more revenue per customer, (fill in the blank) will save us on our overhead, (fill in the blank) will bring in new customers. These measures will help us become profitable for the longterm". But it never happens. Maybe one day TheStreet will be profitable, but not for a while anyway.</Msg><Username>profitgrowthfirst</Username><Timestamp>1351195695634</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 16:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351195909831-68</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC reports 62 percent rise in 3Q profit</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351189363567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:22:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but tunnel vision is your game... Hey ASML is selling critical equipment to TSMC ... just quoting the CEO of the largest semi equipment maker ... We see, however, sustained demand from the logic sector as the planned 28 nanometer node strategic build-up to a worldwide capacity of 300,000 wafer starts per month is expected to be achieved by mid-2013,</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1351195909831</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 16:11:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351196468997-69</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC reports 62 percent rise in 3Q profit</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351189363567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:22:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No dispute on that... Appears you dropped your claim that posted internet articles are something I made up... It's a start...:)</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351196468997</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 16:21:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351197205216-70</Id><Title>haswell will be a game changer</Title><Msg>bet on it !!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1351197205216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 16:33:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351198960612-71</Id><Title>I don't want to buy aapl at $584</Title><Msg>But I love it here at $610. the stock market is out of control and I wouldn't put 10¢ in it. I no longer trust this game for idiots.</Msg><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351198960612</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:02:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351200272914-72</Id><Title>So the tablet is cannibalizing the PC?</Title><Msg>For the last three months, headlines have been that the PC is dying because of the tablet. Well, tablet sales for most have been anemic so let's just say the iPad. Within the past three months, Intel's PC revenue went from $8.68 Billion to $8.633 Billion. Pretty much flat. And this in a weak macro economic environment. No drop in unit sales of PCs due to the ASP being flat as well. How has the iPad been doing. Well, within the past three month, the very hot and very desired iPad sales went from 17 million units, down to 14 million units. This new and exciting product that only Apple seems to be successful in, saw a drop in sales of 17.6%. While a very mature product with over 80 million quarterly unit sales, did not drop at all during a very weak macro economic environment. But the headlines would have investors believe otherwise.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1351200272914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351200736901-73</Id><Topic><Title>So the tablet is cannibalizing the PC?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1351200272914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:24:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Solid post right there !</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351200736901</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:32:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351201483115-74</Id><Topic><Title>I don't want to buy aapl at $584</Title><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351198960612</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>....................../´¯/) ....................,/¯../ .................../..../ ............./´¯/'...'/´¯¯`·¸ ........../'/.../..../......./¨¯\ ........('(...´...´.... ¯~~/'...') .........\.................'...../ ..........''...\.......... _.·´ ............\..............( ..............\.............\....</Msg><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351201483115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:44:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351201547525-75</Id><Topic><Title>I don't want to buy aapl at $584</Title><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351198960612</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think Privat Equity, Bobby. You should axe Hair Bawl Doooosh if you can invest in his propane powered window fan installation company.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1351201547525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351202302694-76</Id><Title>Post Tablet Era</Title><Msg>Wow, where are all the eggsperts now, raving about the Post tablet toy era. MiniPAD overpriced! MaxiPAD sales sales weak! Just the other day, was asked to reccommend a notebook for a raving iPad owner (six month ago). She just cant do anythig worth while with the tablet. So she's now buying a Win8 intel inside Notebook. Though she did say the MaxiPad will be useful whilst cooking, and reading recipes from the internet. Translation, she couldn't come to admit the MaxiPad is near useless.</Msg><Username>gooddigger</Username><Timestamp>1351202302694</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351202659303-77</Id><Title>Hi, I'm Back Again and short INTC @ $21.67</Title><Msg>Made $215 on my INTC long &amp; Nov call options-accounted for commissions-and plan to make a boat load of ca$h tomorrow when INTC tanks because of AAPL. Get short TECH like marco and retire at 25, maybe sooner.</Msg><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1351202659303</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:04:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351202727614-78</Id><Topic><Title>I don't want to buy aapl at $584</Title><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351198960612</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do me a favor "freakshow" and mind your own business. The business of ripping off taxpayers. Maybe throw in a cut of a dead person or two. effing loser.</Msg><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351202727614</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:05:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351204032735-79</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Might Trend Downward for Months</Title><Username>profitgrowthfirst</Username><Timestamp>1350477611405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:40:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also, you left it out from one of my previous posts, but I knew that BBY was going to continue to collapse and would miss on its next earnings report, and sure enough, just like clockwork, the stock crashed again on last nights pre-announcement.</Msg><Username>profitgrowthfirst</Username><Timestamp>1351204032735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351204242543-80</Id><Topic><Title>So the tablet is cannibalizing the PC?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1351200272914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:24:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple's best days are behind with Steve Jobs gone. I have been using iPad3 for about 4 months. Never will I buy another pad like that. So limiting. My choice will be ultrabook...</Msg><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1351204242543</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:30:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351204662789-81</Id><Topic><Title>I don't want to buy aapl at $584</Title><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351198960612</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've got a great idea. Maybe you can bash the injured and dead American troops, then pump Obama and post the Joe Battapaglia and Mark Haines insult again. You've got it going on dude. I'm sure if the people that really know you knew the real person you are they would disown your loser self. Zero integrity.</Msg><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351204662789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351204914379-82</Id><Topic><Title>So the tablet is cannibalizing the PC?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1351200272914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:24:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Logic right here.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1351204914379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351205845417-83</Id><Topic><Title>I don't want to buy aapl at $584</Title><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351198960612</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I'm sure if the people that really know you knew the real person you are" So the people who really know me don't really know me? Is that what you're saying Bobby? Maybe you could write a new text book on elementary logic. I'm sure it would be a best seller among the ignorati.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1351205845417</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351206076911-84</Id><Topic><Title>I don't want to buy aapl at $584</Title><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351198960612</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>truth hurts don't it loser. you got my point.</Msg><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351206076911</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:01:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351207905639-85</Id><Topic><Title>I don't want to buy aapl at $584</Title><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351198960612</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"truth hurts" What could you possibly know about that, Bobby? Perhaps you should speak to something on which you're actually an expert, e.g., the bliss of ignorance. Boo Yah!</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1351207905639</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:31:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351208848423-86</Id><Title>I've got one for you loser liberals.</Title><Msg>It's called "benghazi gate" I guess Obama will get a free pass until the elections are over. This is criminal and I'm amazed the liberal media was able to sweep this under the rug. American people are not as stupid as the liberal media thinks and people will speak with their vote. Here's one for you juhhny........ ENTITLEMENTS will be cut so you better save up those food stamps loser.</Msg><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351208848423</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:47:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351210517452-87</Id><Topic><Title>I've got one for you loser liberals.</Title><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351208848423</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:47:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It really amazes me how some people can just let issues like this slide without a care in the world. It's only you and your familys life. Nothing important. Just the president of the United States of America committing a criminal act for the sake of being reelected. Get it?</Msg><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351210517452</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:15:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351210587528-88</Id><Topic><Title>So the tablet is cannibalizing the PC?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1351200272914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:24:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intc's best days are also behind it, but longs are loving the massive .50 bounce off the 52 week low. Yippee, hooray, such excitement and still below the low set back in June just under 25.00. Poor AAPL only rose from $5.00 to well over $500.00 as poor INTC topped out way back in 2004 at 34.00.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1351210587528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:16:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351211121994-89</Id><Topic><Title>I've got one for you loser liberals.</Title><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351208848423</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:47:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"American people are not as stupid as the liberal media thinks and people will speak with their vote." In fact, they are that stupid and more. The very fact that most of them think they have a real choice in an election tells you all you need to know. Furthermore, you need only look at what happened in 2004 to realize that the president can do anything he wants, tell the most egregious lies that lead to the deaths of thousands of US soldiers, the expenditure of trillions of dollars, and the deaths of at least hundreds of thousands of innocent civilians and even when it is known that all that was predicated on lies, he still gets elected. Unless I have overestimated you, you're not quite as stupid as your represent yourself to be in "in here", so I'm not telling you anything you don't already know.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1351211121994</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:25:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351211139888-90</Id><Title>THE TABLET IS DEAD!!!!</Title><Msg>Ultra weak aapl tablet sales! The kids with jewels in their navels are calling papa, for the fisrt time in healf a year, teary eyeed and pleading, "Papa, will you buy me a PC????"</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351211139888</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:25:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351211518130-91</Id><Topic><Title>And Trump never used/dealt coke???????</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351106113530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:15:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Letterman offered Trump $5M in exchange for setting free whatever it is that is stuck on the top of his head. The far right has got a cavalcade of mental midgets in their binder! Dubya, Newt, Palin, Bachman, Trump, Santorum, Coulter,... The list goes on and on. What a disgrace and an embarrassment in front of the whole world.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1351211518130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351211573376-92</Id><Topic><Title>I've got one for you loser liberals.</Title><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351208848423</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:47:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ENTITLEMENTS should be AXED completely... not this piddly-diddly cut non-sense... chop chop... but it will never happen... the dollar will come CRASHING down and then the revolution will follow...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351211573376</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351211814878-93</Id><Topic><Title>And Trump never used/dealt coke???????</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351106113530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:15:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, yet the poor, the down trodden, the indigent, still they vote for them...like voting for having yourself beheaded at the guillotine. Romney? let's see, is it 100,000 american jobs he extorted to Asian rim? Yet they vote for him.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351211814878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:36:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351212428766-94</Id><Title>Tablets/Convertibles with Intel inside blow the Ipads of the world out of the water</Title><Msg>Intel Is Ready For Windows 8, But More Importantly Ready For The Future Business InsiderBy Kevin Smith | Business Insider – 7 hours ago Your Windows PC is going to look radically different starting today. We're not just talking about the radical new interface. The change applies to the slew of wonky new hardware that will launch along with Windows 8 and throughout the coming months. Intel, a company at the forefront of Windows 8 hardware creation and design, is positioned well among the upcoming flurry of tablets, convertibles, Ultrabooks, and other types of Windows 8 PCs. Intel's chips power a majority of these devices and it works with manufacturers to ensure that users have the best experience possible. Something that consumers often fail to realize when looking at Windows 8 devices is that they are powerful. Much more powerful than the iPads and Android tablets of the world. Basically, the Windows 8 devices Intel and its partners are introducing into the market are full-powered PCs crammed into a tablet form factor. When you think about that, the possibilities are endless. There are convertibles powered by Intel like Dell's XPS, a hybrid Ultrabook, which combines touch and a physical keyboard. There are also devices like Lenovo's IdeaPad Yoga, a funky tablet hybrid that can twist and turn into different positions. Intel is under the hood of all these machines. "Intel is excited about this idea of converging a tablet and a notebook together. The bar is high. It has to be done right," Navin Shenoy, Intel's vice president and general manager, for mobile client platforms told Business Insider. Intel works very closely with PC makers to ensure that the PCs embrace both a touch aspect and a traditional keyboard with mouse experience. This means that consumers can expect to see a lot of different devices. "I think there will be a narrowing of field, as people vote with their wallets," Shenoy said. Intel and its partners are testing out a bunch of Ultrabooks, tablets, and hybrids, hoping something sticks with consumers. "We've built lots of mockups of these devices and tested them up the wazoo. A couple of things have come away from this. Consumers are fifty-fifty between detachables and the switchable platform, where you have a permanently attached keyboard but a moveable screen. It’s really all over the map. Some people like the slider, the yoga, the traditional swivel, the dual screen," Shenoy said. In August 2011, Intel invested $300 million into a fund, which studied its computer ecosystem to figure out what kind of form factors people want. "The way we're directing that money is in things like touch. Touch existed for small devices but it did not exist at all for 13-inch, 14-inch, or 15-inch notebooks," Shenoy said. The next year or two will be crucial for PCs as the consumers vote with their wallet on which new form factor is the best. Above all, "Intel is confident that the best Windows 8 experience will be by way of our chips," Shenoy said. "Bar none. Because we are going to have amazing performance, amazing power, amazing innovation and we're going to have the benefit of running the compatibility of the 3 million apps that have already been written, the apps that people are using today."</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351212428766</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:47:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351213311277-95</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm Back Again and short INTC @ $21.67</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1351202659303</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:04:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course it's going to go down tomorrow... tomorrow is 1 day before the big up climb next week and it's a day after a small gain and it's a friday... down down it goes tomorrow... SHORT it and make cash tomorrow, but be out before next week... oh yeah, welcome back..from what, I have no idea...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351213311277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 21:01:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351217364719-96</Id><Topic><Title>Tablets/Convertibles with Intel inside blow the Ipads of the world out of the water</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351212428766</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:47:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By combining the touchscreen with the keyboard, from an ergonomic standpoint, they've made the touchscreen as vestigial as the mouse was in the old PC. Small chance of users choosing this over the ergonomically designed iPad. Hype can only get you skin deep into the market. After that, your substance counts. Windows 8 tablets have no apps. I wouldn't call running a legacy Windows app on a tablet a tablet app. No one uses tablets this way. Otherwise, what's the difference between a tablet and a laptop. According to MS there is none -- mistake.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1351217364719</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 22:09:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351217599951-97</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm Back Again and short INTC @ $21.67</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1351202659303</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:04:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think INTC is on its way up next pays it's dividend so typically it climbs before that so bought Nov 13 $22 calls for .23 cents hope it doubles...good luck to everyone !</Msg><Username>xpectingu02</Username><Timestamp>1351217599951</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 22:13:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351220167485-98</Id><Topic><Title>Colin Powell Endorses Obama</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351179656294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:40:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The blacks stick together. Imagine if white people stuck together. Obama would never sit in the white house. Are white people stupid?</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351220167485</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 22:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351220246534-99</Id><Title>VOTE FOR AMERICA, VOTE FOR ROMNEY.</Title><Msg>IT IS VERY SIMPLE DECISION.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351220246534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 22:57:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351220615714-100</Id><Title>Windows 8 Commercials everywhere</Title><Msg>Intel finally getting some positive sentiment. Bought another 20K shares at 21.40.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351220615714</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 23:03:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351220665723-101</Id><Topic><Title>Jack Welch</Title><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1351177878321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My family, independent voters, support romney. Obama is on our s... List.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351220665723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 23:04:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351220797266-102</Id><Topic><Title>VOTE FOR AMERICA, VOTE FOR ROMNEY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351220246534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 22:57:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HIDE RYAN from the public so he won't goof</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351220797266</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 23:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351221201603-103</Id><Topic><Title>I've got one for you loser liberals.</Title><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351208848423</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:47:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>like he did the Olympic records. ROMNEY shedded all his records so there would not be any evidence of the crime. MITT SHREDNEY at work.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351221201603</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 23:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351221569709-104</Id><Title>global markets outlook</Title><Msg>Red-hot bloody lobster red !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! short short short short short short !!! short the whole to become rich !!!!!!!! $$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$ I told you so !!!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351221569709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 23:19:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351221884193-105</Id><Topic><Title>Colin Powell Endorses Obama</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1351179656294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:40:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GEORGE BUSH is black? WHORHEY appointed General Powell as Secretary of State. Are whte people stupid? Some are!!!! Some white people are just ignorant. Some white people are arrogant. Some white peopl are racist. Some while people are all the above ..... like penma1</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351221884193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 23:24:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351222127299-106</Id><Topic><Title>global markets outlook</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351221569709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 23:19:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe. Maybe not. You say the same thing every day. You suffer from the broken clock syndrome.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351222127299</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 23:28:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>