<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348633380063-1</Id><Topic><Title>finally bottomed out today 23.07</Title><Username>raygeo2003</Username><Timestamp>1348203876359</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 01:04:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well the news came out today, its one of the best picks for 2013 with big cap hight yield stocks for investing so.......</Msg><Username>raygeo2003</Username><Timestamp>1348633380063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 00:23:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348633623639-2</Id><Topic><Title>im in order filled monday 22.60 3.9+% div</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348597281866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>correct October 15th- may 2013 32$ a share</Msg><Username>raygeo2003</Username><Timestamp>1348633623639</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 00:27:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348634752558-3</Id><Title>More Evidence of Intel's Fabrication Dominance</Title><Msg>Intel is discontinuing large amounts of the Sandy Bridge 32nm line in favor of the new and improved Ivy Bridge 22nm line. Proof positive that the new fabs are fully ramped up. In the meantime ARM still struggles with 28nm and no one knows when 20nm will ever reach volume production. Intel moves closer and closer to volume production of 14nm. The release of Windows 8 is just around the corner. And Wall Street still thinks Intel is going to announce a $7 billion revenue miss come earnings. It's already priced in. On Thursday: "We know Light Peak is ready, at least in its 10Gbps copper form. We think that Apple will be the first to use it, possibly in a set of new MacBooks. Now, this Thursday, Intel has invited journalists to a San Francisco event, where it will "discuss a new technology that is about to appear on the market" and provide tech demos. There's no hard news here, but things appear to add up, and so the web's ablaze with rumors that Thursday's the day Intel will unveil the finished first generation of its interconnect technology to the world. Here's what happens now: We'll be in San Francisco this Thursday, reporting live from the event, to let you know for sure." From Engadget</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348634752558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 00:45:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348643121150-4</Id><Title>Intel closes green today</Title><Msg>Keep watch on A123 Systmes (AONE). Should move up strong by Friday.</Msg><Username>hankg1030</Username><Timestamp>1348643121150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 03:05:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348643522300-5</Id><Topic><Title>Intel closes green today</Title><Username>hankg1030</Username><Timestamp>1348643121150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 03:05:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>may be green at open, but it doesn't have the power to hold the gain, check the performance. one direction: down to south one color: lobster red one result: short it to become rich</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348643522300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 03:12:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348661115033-6</Id><Topic><Title>im in order filled monday 22.60 3.9+% div</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348597281866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i tort ud like itttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttt</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348661115033</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 08:05:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348663454158-7</Id><Title>Bearish equity option purchase for ARMH.</Title><Msg>ARM Holdings (ARMH): An investor bought 6,000 November 28 puts for $1.30 and sold an equal number of November 31 calls for $0.40. They paid $0.90 and will now profit from downside in the share price while being forced to sell above $31. ARMH rose 2.61 percent to $28.46.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1348663454158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 08:44:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348665517051-8</Id><Title>Did you see the write up on this (INTC)</Title><Msg>Has anyone seen this article? Look at the info this page is providing. Good stuff for the stock market Copy and Paste the link to your browser. : y.ahoo.it/27rDk</Msg><Username>deniceujk5465</Username><Timestamp>1348665517051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>27</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348666589582-9</Id><Topic><Title>Bearish equity option purchase for ARMH.</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1348663454158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 08:44:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>from optionmonster site: One investor is calling a top for ARM Holdings. optionMONSTER's Depth Charge monitoring program detected the purchase of 6,000 November 28 puts for $1.30 and the sale of an equal number of November 31 calls for $0.40. There was barely any open interest at either strike before the trade appeared, indicating that this is a new combination trade. The investor paid $0.90 to open the position and has the right to sell shares for $28 through expiration. Because the trader is also on the hook to sell for $31 if they go above that level, the trader probably owns stock in the name and is using the options for protection. Known as a collar, the strategy is a common hedging mechanism on long positions. The trade was done after ARMH rallied back to the same price area where it had traded in late 2012 and early 2012. The stock peaked around $31 in November, which is probably why it's being targeted as a sale point. ARMH rose 0.87 percent to $27.97 yesterday and is up 21 percent in the last three months. The chip maker has been trading in a sideways range since early 2011 after a giant rally in the two preceding years. Overall option volume in the maker of mobile chips was 21 times greater than average in the session, according to the Depth Charge.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348666589582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:36:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348667132610-10</Id><Topic><Title>Intel closes green today</Title><Username>hankg1030</Username><Timestamp>1348643121150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 03:05:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i told you so , no power</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348667132610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348667786675-11</Id><Topic><Title>Buy Intel Already It Is Undervalued</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348643280361</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 03:08:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and Intel has warned 2 out of the last 4 quarters.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348667786675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:56:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348667923157-12</Id><Topic><Title>Ya shoulda listened to marco :</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1348623506266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:38:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$15 b4 $25, I think you're wrong.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348667923157</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348667969946-13</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy capitulates, says buy INTEL</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1317740904000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-10-04 11:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>doubtful but fairly cretain ww does.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348667969946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:59:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348668603056-14</Id><Title>Wall Street Stupidity Reaches Epic Levels</Title><Msg>Wall Street has now priced in a $7 billion revenue miss into this quarter's earnings report. Hold up your hand if you think Intel's revenues are going to drop by $7 billion from the previous quarter. Wall Street thinks so....</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348668603056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:10:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348669207541-15</Id><Title>Notebook ODMs expect surging growth in cloud computing business in 2013</Title><Msg>As cloud computing business opportunities are expanding, several notebook ODMs have been aggressively pushing their related business segments and expect strong revenue growth from these departments in 2013. Quanta Computer expects its non-notebook business to contribute 30% of its total revenues in 2012 and aims to raise the proportion to 50% after three years, with the cloud computing business being the major driver for the growth. Wistron's cloud computing subsidiary Wiwynn estimated its revenues to surpass NT$10 billion in 2013, up significantly from 2012, with revenue contribution to reach 15-20%. In addition to Microsoft, Facebook and Baidu, Wiwynn has also landed orders from Japan-based KDDI to establish a new data center. From Digitimes [Gee, if Wall Street only knew of a company that would benefit from surging growth in cloud computing and data centers...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348669207541</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:20:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348669919615-16</Id><Topic><Title>Notebook ODMs expect surging growth in cloud computing business in 2013</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348669207541</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:20:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GEE, GOSH, GOLLY! Intel is down 20% since you recommended that everyone buy it at $29! You need to seek help ASAP! Is Intel still "good for 30" like you said here last May? Is a "HUGE HONKING $6 MISS ALREADY PRICED IN?" TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348669919615</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>26</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348669963270-17</Id><Title>Grandma Bought INTC</Title><Msg>She did this all yesterday: Paid 23.05, Sold April 25 Call Options for .7/sh and she'll collect two 1% dividends through April. She'll earn the 2% dividend, 4% option premium and another 9% if the stock is called away. Grandma needs income and INTC at current prices meets her needs.</Msg><Username>axpkocop</Username><Timestamp>1348669963270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348670052805-18</Id><Title>Dividend Arbitrage - STRADDLE</Title><Msg>Suppose I could buy an ITM call option AND an ITM put option that expire after the INTC ex-dividend day for only 10 cents premium over intrinsic value. (ITM=In the money) If I could do that, I could exercise the call option early before ex-dividend and capture the dividend. I could then use the put option to dispose of the shares. If the premium was only 10 cents, then I could LOCK IN a guaranteed 12 cent profit on the trade. OCT option pricing example ... just to show what normal premiums could be expected outside an arbitrage situation. Today is Sep. 26th (24 days before expiration) and the OCT $10 straddle is selling for $10.10. You can buy an OCT $16 CALL and an $26 PUT for $10.10. The long straddle is normally a volatility trade where the buyer is expecting the stock to trade outside the range. The low premium is indicates a low expectation that the stock will make it outside that range. The ex-dividend date is a bump in the pricing structure. The PUT and CALL will have AT LEAST the $10 value and your maximum loss is 10 cents. If similar pricing pattern happens in the NOV options: You BUY THE $10 STRADDLE for $10.10. You exercise the CALL early. Collect the 22.5 cent dividend You allow the PUT to be assigned. Your cost: $10.10 + fees + commisions Your return $10.22 If you are a big organization with access to low cost trading, like the options market maker, you can lock in (up to) 22.5 profit. ALREADY ..... NOV and DEC straddles are approaching dividend yield. The NOV $10 straddle is selling for $10.35. That is already only a 35 cent premium for NOV options. DEC $10 straddle is selling for $10.40 or only 40 cent premium. Large straddle orders collar INTC trading prices in a narrow range.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348670052805</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:34:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348670080896-19</Id><Title>Lucy_Nuff / Tooofunny /Lucifer_nuff has held the Intel bag from AT LEAST 29</Title><Msg>I've got the post where he claimed Intel was the "cornerstone" of his portfolio at 29. Look at him SEETHE here daily........Broke old coot! LMAO</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1348670080896</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:34:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348670141436-20</Id><Title>Looks like the letters to the SEC are working!</Title><Msg>Way to go, Wallus!</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1348670141436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:35:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348670209336-21</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy_Nuff / Tooofunny /Lucifer_nuff has held the Intel bag from AT LEAST 29</Title><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1348670080896</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:34:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've got the post where he claimed Intel was the "cornerstone ------- POST IT, douche nozzle!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348670209336</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>27</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348670239435-22</Id><Title>ARM TechCon probes road to 14-nm ICs</Title><Msg>And it's not a happy discussion. Problems galore as the ARM folks discuss the years it will take to move to 14nm production. Significant discussion centers around how ARM has not not even solved the problems of moving to 20nm, much less the move to 14nm. Here's one comment: "How about we not talk as an industry about 10nm or 14nm until we admit at even today at 20nm will still don't have a viable 20nm strategy. Today's 20nm due to the double patterning just does not offer much if any improvement over 28nm. Even over the next 5 years it does not appear cost per transistor will be lower in 20nm vs 28nm." [No viable 20nm solution? Just more evidence that the ARM fabrication crisis is very real. In the meantime Intel already has 14nm sample quantities and Wall Street still thinks fabrication is something it uses to manipulate the media...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348670239435</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348670491167-23</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like the letters to the SEC are working!</Title><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1348670141436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:35:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See Intel longs. These are the parasitic, cockroach, god-complex shills and manipulators we have to put up with. Show some backbone. Send the letters...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348670491167</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:41:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348670504254-24</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy_Nuff / Tooofunny /Lucifer_nuff has held the Intel bag from AT LEAST 29</Title><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1348670080896</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:34:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I want to wait until we drop to 20 to post it/shove it down your ancient throat. LMAO.</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1348670504254</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348670816557-25</Id><Topic><Title>New Yahoo Aliases</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1308932084000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2011-06-24 12:14:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For a new alias, I am considering "wallis_suxwang" or "herbaldude_suxwang" THOUGHTS?</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348670816557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:46:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348670926074-26</Id><Topic><Title>New Yahoo Aliases</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1308932084000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2011-06-24 12:14:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can use as many aliases as you want but you can't go back and change the fact that you've been proven to be a Fraud here that says he sold when it 's down and own it when it's up. You are a disease with no cure.</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1348670926074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:48:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348671106368-27</Id><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Msg>1.) ARM won't see 14nm for years and years and years. They are talking about it today at Tech-Con. Tech con is a good description for GloFlo saying they will have 14nm in 2014. Ha. 2.) Apple with riots at the manufacturing plant, a maps disaster, and caught in fabrication h*ll between Samsung and TSMC, neither having state-of-the-art technology. 3.) ARM tablets starting to feel the competitive impact from Ultrabooks and Intel tablets and notebooks. 4.) Intel moves closer to 14nm volume production. 5.) Bo may know technology, but Wall Street doesn't. Wall Street only knows manipulation. 6.) Intel remains stupidly and probably criminally (come on, SEC - get in the game!) under-valued...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348671106368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348671616832-28</Id><Title>MY ONE-STAR PUPPY IS FRUSTRATED TODAY</Title><Msg>He hasn't been right in the head since the new Yahoo format put him OUT OF BUSINESS. I'm off to the driving range. CIAO/CHOW</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348671616832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:00:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348671737382-29</Id><Topic><Title>MY ONE-STAR PUPPY IS FRUSTRATED TODAY</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348671616832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You always claim victory and run away......right after you've been kicked in the teeth and exposed as the FRAUD that you are. Enjoy the imaginary driving range. We know that's code words for "I'm going to log in under different aliases and insult people to make myself feel better."</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1348671737382</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:02:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348672003698-30</Id><Topic><Title>MY ONE-STAR PUPPY IS FRUSTRATED TODAY</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348671616832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ohhh the irony. One of the first things men do when THEY are frustrated is go to the driving range. Poor Lucy, gets his tail kicked EVERYWHERE he goes. Sad little man.</Msg><Username>golf_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348672003698</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348672113385-31</Id><Title>CARIS &amp; Co. DOWNGRADES INTEL SHARES</Title><Msg>LOOK OUT BELOW!</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348672113385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>21</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348672200046-32</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like the letters to the SEC are working!</Title><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1348670141436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:35:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear Madam, What sort of house of ill repute are you running anyway?</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1348672200046</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348672594585-33</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348671106368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lest we forget INTC and CSCO making a deal for 1 billion in chips a tear. Funny nobody even mensions it. Then we have QCOM bashing Oranges phone. If the phone was really no good, they wouldn't even bother to mension it. Looks like they may be getting nervous.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1348672594585</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348672669137-34</Id><Title>TAX-LOSS SELLING COMBINED WITH MULTIPLE DOWNGRADES MEANS....</Title><Msg>LOOK OUT BELOW!</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348672669137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>21</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348673019308-35</Id><Title>Look at poor Lucy go! An anomynous message board poster dictated whether he would go to the driving range or not. LOL!</Title><Msg>What a little twit. I control him like a puppet, tell him what to do and have never even met him. (nor would care to). LOL</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1348673019308</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348673102161-36</Id><Topic><Title>TAX-LOSS SELLING COMBINED WITH MULTIPLE DOWNGRADES MEANS....</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348672669137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You posted this EXACT same tax-loss vomit last year..............as the stock rose from 20 to 25 by the end of the year. LOL!</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1348673102161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348673562109-37</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like the letters to the SEC are working!</Title><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1348670141436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:35:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>22-Feb-12 05:04 pm Two out of every three people receiving stock dividend payments are rich, many totally, incredibly rich and should be paying more taxes instead of us soaking the middle class. I'm sick of the deadbeat rich who are unwilling to carry their fair share of the load... wallisweaver</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348673562109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:32:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348673618324-38</Id><Title>Intel rises about 30 percent in late December 2011 as LUCY says it will get CRUSHED, LOL!</Title><Msg>Tax Loss Selling of INTC Will Be Huge This Year By smarty_nuff . Aug 25, 2011 12:56 PM . Permalink Everyone is sick of this Dow dog. INTC will get axed bigtime in December.</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1348673618324</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:33:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348673769759-39</Id><Topic><Title>TAX-LOSS SELLING COMBINED WITH MULTIPLE DOWNGRADES MEANS....</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348672669137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said the same thing last year and were DEAD wrong as Intel rose big-time through the end of the year. You can waste your life here trying to con people if you want, but you won't get away with it. Tax Loss Selling of INTC Will Be Huge This Year By smarty_nuff . Aug 25, 2011 12:56 PM . Permalink Everyone is sick of this Dow dog. INTC will get axed bigtime in December.</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1348673769759</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:36:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348673846059-40</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see the write up on this (INTC)</Title><Username>deniceujk5465</Username><Timestamp>1348665517051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one. I will subscribe now.</Msg><Username>capriceecw895</Username><Timestamp>1348673846059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:37:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348675008687-41</Id><Title>Can INTC GAIN A DIME TODAY???</Title><Msg>The Magic 8-Ball sez: "NO WAY!"</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348675008687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:56:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>21</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348676965593-42</Id><Topic><Title>Can INTC GAIN A DIME TODAY???</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348675008687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:56:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lucifer nuff sounds the same as another pest named "too funny". Probably an alias. If you're not long or short, you need to disappear.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348676965593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:29:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348677306990-43</Id><Title>Rombo Romney going down HARD!!! He is ROADKILL!</Title><Msg>Super flip flop artist health-care passing former Mass Lib governor Romney is now in free fall in the polls. The Teabagging nimrods, mainly white older males, really picked a loser this time. Of course this is the same group that picked GW two times to lead the nation so they are not too bright are they. But really--you want your country back? That lady next to you in Ohio is polling 60% to 35% for Obummer as of today. She is not going to let your vote count for jack shhheeeet. In fact, Obummer is laughing at you old trashballs. If the election were held today, you GOPtards might just barely hold on to the House of Reps but it is not held today. So there is plenty of time for the Rombo meltdown to take all you GOP house teabagging clowns down with him. Of course you do not believe the polls or so you say. That is all you can say is it not? Oh well--at least you will not have to stay up late on election Tuesday because when Florida and Ohio go to Obummer early in the eve, you can simply cry like little pigs and go to bed. The next day you will show up at work and have to live with the fact that you told everyone that there was no way Obummer would win re-election. Gaaaaawwwdddang are you stupid. They will be laughing at you behind your back. Even your wife will be laughing at you. Hey? Where are the Tea party nuts now? No protest or anything? Glen Beck got fired at Fuxed up news. I love how Harry Reid keep trashing Romney. HAAA HAAA If Nancy Pelosi gets back her place has house majority leader, feel free to cry some more you LOSERS!</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348677306990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:35:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348677600185-44</Id><Topic><Title>Rombo Romney going down HARD!!! He is ROADKILL!</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348677306990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:35:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If obama wins, the market will be in free fall along with Intel. Democrats use people for their own crooked agenda. If you don't like rich people, then you shouldn't like many democrats like pelosi, obama, reid, kerry, etc. They've got more money than Romney.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348677600185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:40:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348677754559-45</Id><Topic><Title>Can INTC GAIN A DIME TODAY???</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348675008687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:56:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you need to disappear ------------------ Who put you in charge, douche nozzle? TOOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348677754559</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:42:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>26</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348677791293-46</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like the letters to the SEC are working!</Title><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1348670141436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:35:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if long the SQQQ as one should have been, monitor gains. correction may be relatively short in duration, expect support for the spy 500 at 1420.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348677791293</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348678020454-47</Id><Topic><Title>Can INTC GAIN A DIME TODAY???</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348675008687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:56:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>see, it's a tag team. You're like a thorn in one's side. You need to be extracted.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348678020454</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:47:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348678517314-48</Id><Topic><Title>Can INTC GAIN A DIME TODAY???</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348675008687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:56:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he is my dark brother. his mission is to just hang around, inflict pain and test the patience of those on the board. he is what is known in the trade as a "testis". a dark testis TOOOOOoooooooooooooooooooooo FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>pumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1348678517314</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:55:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348678572157-49</Id><Topic><Title>Rombo Romney going down HARD!!! He is ROADKILL!</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348677306990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:35:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good Post amdmonkey72: Markets always do better with Democrats in power. The markets are back under Obama. For the poster ahead of me kblank657, you must be to young to remember the Bush crash.</Msg><Username>oldmoss3</Username><Timestamp>1348678572157</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:56:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348678606504-50</Id><Title>everyone tells me im a genius bought mon 22.60 up 3 cents</Title><Msg>now give me your 2 cents</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348678606504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:56:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348678766213-51</Id><Topic><Title>everyone tells me im a genius bought mon 22.60 up 3 cents</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348678606504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:56:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cent cent there are my two cents.</Msg><Username>pumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1348678766213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348680060826-52</Id><Topic><Title>Can INTC GAIN A DIME TODAY???</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348675008687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:56:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so, pumpwad, too funny and lucifer nuff are all the same person. My wish is that when you reach the heavenly gates (hopefully in the near future), they won't be able to push the "down" button fast enough.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348680060826</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:21:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348680481626-53</Id><Title>Just Waiting</Title><Msg>For Wall Street to figure out that Intel isn't going to have the $7 billion revenue miss that they have priced in...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348680481626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:28:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348680605522-54</Id><Topic><Title>Just Waiting</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348680481626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:28:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holding up pretty well today considering NDX got hammered.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348680605522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:30:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348680675763-55</Id><Topic><Title>Rombo Romney going down HARD!!! He is ROADKILL!</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348677306990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:35:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>then he must also be way TOO young to remember 18% interest under Carter.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348680675763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348680821948-56</Id><Topic><Title>Can INTC GAIN A DIME TODAY???</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348675008687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:56:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the pumpwad is not same person as ... lucy-lucifer-toofunny-and many more aliases the dancing lucy is from the bash side. the pumpwad doesn't play golf. sissy pseudo-sport. the pumpwad especially doesn't play miniature golf like lucy. the pumpwad juggles knives.</Msg><Username>pumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1348680821948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348680891266-57</Id><Title>INTC IS ON FIRE!</Title><Msg>Up 14 cents today and DOWN more that $6 since last May. INTC is a stock that only a mother, and wallis, could love! TOOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348680891266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:34:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348680919065-58</Id><Topic><Title>Rombo Romney going down HARD!!! He is ROADKILL!</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348677306990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:35:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry guys and appreciate the young comment but am getting older by the day. Turned 60 in August. As strange as it seems, I actually had the best financial year when Clinton was president.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348680919065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:35:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348680942116-59</Id><Title>Enormous gap in technology between leading foundries and the rest</Title><Msg>[Of course, they don't mention the enormous gap in technology between the leading foundries and Intel. It's okay- all of us but Wall Street already know...] The process technology gap between the top foundries and the others is ‘enormous’, says IC Insights. Only four companies out of 18 pure-play foundries can make leading edge ICs and only four others have a 90nm capability. ‘In 2012, TSMC and Globalfoundries were in high-volume production of devices using 28nm feature sizes,’ says IC Insights, ‘the process technology gap between the other significant pure-play IC foundries and the leading-edge producers is enormous.’ Leaving aside the Big Four – TSMC, Globalfoundries, UMC and SMIC – there are only four other foundries - TowerJazz, Grace/HHNEC, Dongbu, and Xinxin - expected to be able to produce ICs using ≤90nm feature sizes in 2012, and this production is likely to be relatively limited, says IC Insights. Collectively, these 14 ‘non-major’ IC foundries are forecast to account for $4.6bn in sales, or about 15% of the total pure-play IC foundry market in 2012. Before Globalfoundries entered the IC foundry market, TSMC was by far the technology leader among the major pure-play IC foundries. In 2012, about 37% of TSMC’s revenue is expected to come from ≤45nm processing. Although Globalfoundries is expected to have a greater percentage of its sales dedicated to ≤45nm technology than TSMC this year, TSMC is forecast to have more than twice the sales volume at ≤45nm as compared to GlobalFoundries in 2012 ($6.23bn for TSMC and $2.79bn for GlobalFoundries). In contrast, China-based SMIC only entered initial production of 45nm technology in early 2012, more than three years after TSMC first put its 45nm process into production. In fact, less than 1% of SMIC’s 2012 sales are expected to come from devices having ≤45nm feature sizes, which is why its revenue per wafer ($759) is expected to be so low this year as compared to TSMC ($1,190) and GlobalFoundries ($1,157). From Electronics Weekly</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348680942116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:35:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348682265674-60</Id><Topic><Title>Rombo Romney going down HARD!!! He is ROADKILL!</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348677306990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:35:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Markets are doing well because Obama did not get his way so far on taxes and cap and trade. If oil drilling and corporate tax cuts had been implemented (and no Obamacare) the '08 crash and its effects would be well behind us and we'd be at 18,000 DOW. Bush never had over 8% unemployment. For 7 1/2 of his 8 years we had a great economy. Obozo gave us huge unemployment and he increased the debt by 3. Oh, and the great uniter can't give a speech without whining about how Bush made him do it. The Won is a big ZERO for sure. His foreign policy stinks too. Can't wait till this guy is history along with his socialist Jarrett, Axelrod and Geitner. They're all losers.</Msg><Username>readyforfncm</Username><Timestamp>1348682265674</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:57:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348682385644-61</Id><Topic><Title>Rombo Romney going down HARD!!! He is ROADKILL!</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348677306990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:35:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You still like Harry Reid after his bald faced lies? Sheesh. Yes, There's no doubt that Democrats are DUMB!</Msg><Username>readyforfncm</Username><Timestamp>1348682385644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:59:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348682601479-62</Id><Topic><Title>Rombo Romney going down HARD!!! He is ROADKILL!</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348677306990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:35:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>creation on Gore's internet created many jobs, a lot of people had that as well. Obama makes Clinton seem wonderful. What about those Carter years? turn your thermostat up in summer, down in winter, wait in gas lines, high interest, what a clueless President he was. Didn't he also cause Sammy to sing "I can't drive 55!!!!!!!!!"</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348682601479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348683161316-63</Id><Topic><Title>INTC News tempo up previous to the crowd on the scary enormous Multi take home</Title><Username>brownkendrick96</Username><Timestamp>1348665866855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:24:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy, hold and get rich! Something is up and we will know soon!</Msg><Username>vargasboris55</Username><Timestamp>1348683161316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348683243666-64</Id><Topic><Title>INTC News tempo up previous to the crowd on the scary enormous Multi take home</Title><Username>brownkendrick96</Username><Timestamp>1348665866855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:24:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fine. I'll buy now and hold It and after sometime .That was good information.</Msg><Username>vargasboris55</Username><Timestamp>1348683243666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:14:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348683481079-65</Id><Title>no power</Title><Msg>drop like a rock and up like a snail, down a dollar and up only a few cents, one step forward and five steps backward, will be lobster red. short it to become rich!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348683481079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:18:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348684533628-66</Id><Topic><Title>no power</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348683481079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:18:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too late to short INTC, other than for day trades. the odds favor a bounce, though a long on the SQQQ's would have been more profitable from yesterday's low way down there at 34.60 ish</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348684533628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348684557446-67</Id><Topic><Title>TAX-LOSS SELLING COMBINED WITH MULTIPLE DOWNGRADES MEANS....</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348672669137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bad news, tax selling, or analysts' downgrades, bring it on. The only thing it creates is a buying opportunity. Not much else to say aside from that.</Msg><Username>pointandclique</Username><Timestamp>1348684557446</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348684822125-68</Id><Topic><Title>everyone tells me im a genius bought mon 22.60 up 3 cents</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348678606504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:56:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5 cents now! now what?</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348684822125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:40:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348685078788-69</Id><Title>Analyst downgrades Intel on tablet concerns</Title><Msg>Analyst downgrades Intel on tablet concerns Analyst lowers Intel earnings estimates, stock price target, as tablet computers drain revenue Associated Press – 14 minutes ago</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348685078788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>25</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348685552357-70</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>The DJIA suffered its first triple digit loss since late August yesterday. The pickup in volume suggested that the selling may not be over. Sentiment has gotten too complacent since the QE announcements. We saw concerns growing in yesterday's market and that isn't likely to go away quickly as the Eurozone doesn't seem to have gotten its act together to implement the ECB's OMT initiative. Stocks are oversold on an intraday basis. We could get an intraday bounce but expect more profit taking on bounces. For the S&amp;P 500, watch for resistance near today's high at 1463. On the downside, watch for support near 1438, the high during the consolidation period before the Fed QE announcement, followed by the 1418-1422 area. Goodluck</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1348685552357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:52:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348685630176-71</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst downgrades Intel on tablet concerns</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348685078788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:44:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the same Caris downgrade you posted earlier. SAN FRANCISCO (AP) -- Caris &amp; Co. analyst Craig Ellis lowered his earnings estimate and stock price target for Intel Corp., because he believes tablet computers are hurting the chip maker more than he previously envisioned. The reassessment, issued Wednesday, comes nearly three weeks after Intel acknowledged that a weakening market for traditional personal computers running on its microprocessors will cause its third-quarter revenue to fall below last year's results. The company, which is based in Santa Clara, Calif., had previously expected to at least match last year's performance. Ellis predicted the growing popularity of tablet such as Apple Inc.'s iPad will cause Intel problems for the next few quarters. The rise of the iPad and other tablets is troubling for Intel, because most of those machines don't run on its microprocessors. In contrast, Intel's chips are used in most PCs running on Microsoft's Windows operating system.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348685630176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:53:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348685645844-72</Id><Title>Lower lows to come on INTC, BIG Defense cuts will not help INTC,HPQ and DELL</Title><Msg>Lower lows to come on INTC, BIG Defense cuts will not help INTC,HPQ and DELL no upgrading will be needed</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1348685645844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:54:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348686085164-73</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst downgrades Intel on tablet concerns</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348685078788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:44:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the same Caris downgrade you posted earlier ---------------- This was my first post today. You must have me confused with somweone else, Al.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348686085164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:01:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>26</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348686379466-74</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst downgrades Intel on tablet concerns</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348685078788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:44:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. Confused with lucifer_nuff.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348686379466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:06:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348686838148-75</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst downgrades Intel on tablet concerns</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348685078788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:44:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fwiw, d'Artagnan, the "fourth musketeer," is my favorite musketeer.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348686838148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:13:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348686895697-76</Id><Title>buy on the dips</Title><Msg>I have bought shares at the lows in 2009 and am buying again. The reason? This is a great company with some of the best engineers in this country, . I believe that this "going to tablets" is a little overblown. I have both a computer and tablet, The tablet is great for viewing but not very good at inputting. I use my computer to do word processing and spread sheets. There is a both a need for both computers and tablets. Computers may get lighter but one still needs a pretty good sized screen to to spreadsheets and presentations. Computers need Intel and I believe strongly that Intel will get into the tablet area very soon even if they have to buy their way in. Don't under rate Intel, buy on the dips and consider selling in the high $20's or low $30's.</Msg><Username>harold_saun</Username><Timestamp>1348686895697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:14:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348686899118-77</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see the write up on this (INTC)</Title><Username>deniceujk5465</Username><Timestamp>1348665517051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am looking for.</Msg><Username>marhtazii482</Username><Timestamp>1348686899118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:14:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348687266735-78</Id><Topic><Title>Lower lows to come on INTC, BIG Defense cuts will not help INTC,HPQ and DELL</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1348685645844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:54:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Lower lows to come on INTC, BIG Defense cuts will not help INTC,HPQ and DELL no upgrading will be needed." *** The stock has already been beaten down enough to take care of all of those things seven times over, cockroach boy. When are you #$%$ going to give it up? You think Intel is going to have a $7 billion revenue miss come earnings? You think all that verbal arm-flapping is going to help your case then? Why don't you get a job that doesn't involve trying to kill the US economy? You and the rest of the parasites are the single biggest problem with our current economic system. Is there anything that you wouldn't do to make an extra fifty cents? You could be the poster child for Wall Street's new paradigm of scamming a living instead of earning a living. New Wall Street Motto: We didn't build this but we sure as heck are trying to make some money tearing it down...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348687266735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348687533811-79</Id><Topic><Title>Lower lows to come on INTC, BIG Defense cuts will not help INTC,HPQ and DELL</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1348685645844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:54:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a buy order for 1,000,000,000 shares at $0.90. I figure with good cash flow coverage and product pipeline that 100% dividend yield will provide a good floor.</Msg><Username>pumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1348687533811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:25:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348687592528-80</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst downgrades Intel on tablet concerns</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348685078788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:44:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, the shills reposting this failed to mention that the new price target is $26 or over three bucks higher than where the stock is now. Too funny...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348687592528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348687924186-81</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst downgrades Intel on tablet concerns</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348685078788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:44:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the new price target is $26 or over three bucks higher than where the stock is now. Too funny... -------------------- What you failed to mention is that the stock is over 3 bucks lower than where it was when you recommended it 5 months ago at 29 and over 7 bucks lower than your $30 target, jackwad.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348687924186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:32:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>27</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348688025749-82</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst downgrades Intel on tablet concerns</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348685078788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:44:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HEY!!! Not pumpwad!!! The shills are not the brightest penny in the deck!! They are not playing with a full picnic. They are a sandwich short of a six-pack. You got to lighten up on the poor quadriplegic dude. He has to type all the spam with a stick duct-taped to his chin. His neck is getting tired.</Msg><Username>pumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1348688025749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348688196570-83</Id><Title>Undercover journo talks work conditions in Foxconn</Title><Msg>Apple’s logo makes him sick Whew, I thought I was the only one. But in all seriousness, journalist Wang Yu has spent some time working in Foxconn, specifically on iPhone 5 production lines, and what he lived through is quite shocking. Not that anyone will care, but still. Apparently, Yu now suffers from “painful muscle memory”, directly related to Apple’s iPhone 5. It is said this is a mental flashback to the pain experienced by repetitive, drone-like manufacturing of Apple’s shiny gear. Yu pointed out that the line he worked in required a minimum of 17 workers. However, many workers resigned and although there were only seven or eight left, their production target of 5,600 panels was unchanged. He noted that the cooling agent for the machines smells unbearably and is bad for the workers’ noses and throats. Still, the company does not give out masks every day, as it is supposed to, but rather every week. Most won’t care, because that’s just too far down the iHole for them to think, and quite understandably – the iPhone 5 is just to shiny to look beyond. However, for all Apple’s alleged interest into its supply lines, one of our readers said it best:” That damn sweatshop better deliver those new phones, otherwise Tim Cook will personally throw a couple dozen workers off the roof.” From Fudzilla [Meanwhile Intel manufactures in the US. Where does Wall Street come in on this issue? Wall Street loves to bash the All-American company while looking the other way for third world country exploitation. What exactly is Wall Street's problem?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348688196570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:36:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348688940646-84</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see the write up on this (INTC)</Title><Username>deniceujk5465</Username><Timestamp>1348665517051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>giselehsg77012</Username><Timestamp>1348688940646</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348689771396-85</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst downgrades Intel on tablet concerns</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348685078788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:44:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The elevator apparantly isn't a new one if the target is only 26.00. As I recall, there were buyers right there 26 ish, to capture a measly .225 dividend who gave up, 3.35. penny wise. pound foolish</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348689771396</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 16:02:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348691350027-86</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see the write up on this (INTC)</Title><Username>deniceujk5465</Username><Timestamp>1348665517051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be waiting for more great news to come.</Msg><Username>tanishacqs122</Username><Timestamp>1348691350027</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 16:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348692967098-87</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348671106368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, Intel says that Win 8 is not ready. And the video of Win 8 that is going around with the news item shows a page flipping style instead of an instant style. It wouldn't be unusual for MS to eat up the hardware for the purpose of making an operating system with a lot of features but then end up with a slower operating system even though the hardware is faster. Of course ARM tablets have a very fast screen refresh but probably have limits as to what they can load while keeping the performance. But the early Win 8 reviews have been good. Look for more news and reviews in October but the most recent item was from Intel .</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1348692967098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 16:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348694207452-88</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348671106368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, maybe a faster screen refresh makes a smoother page flipping style possible. Maybe it's a feature instead of slower. But overall, the the Win 8 video didn't seem to be great. Reviews in October and November.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1348694207452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 17:16:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348695543386-89</Id><Title>FAST MONEY SLAMMED INTC TONIGHT</Title><Msg>Talked about it possibly trading at 19 soon and speculated that it may be the new AMD. Also, said that Intel had missed the boat. WOW! I wouldn't slam a sheeethouse door that hard!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348695543386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 17:39:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>28</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348696164784-90</Id><Topic><Title>FAST MONEY SLAMMED INTC TONIGHT</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348695543386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 17:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i wouldnt think you would use a door.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348696164784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 17:49:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348697648122-91</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348671106368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Waldo may now tech geek, but he don't know squat about stocks. still need to go to chart school</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348697648122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 18:14:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348699695246-92</Id><Title>should only drop about 1 buck during correction</Title><Msg>I wouldn't bother selling this stock for a buck</Msg><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1348699695246</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 18:48:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348701512763-93</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see the write up on this (INTC)</Title><Username>deniceujk5465</Username><Timestamp>1348665517051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just joined.</Msg><Username>elodiafgo02646</Username><Timestamp>1348701512763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 19:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348701788192-94</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348671106368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is out with a statement that Win 8 is ready. Probably, they were just warning developers to test a few different approaches with the new OS touch features.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1348701788192</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 19:23:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348702388830-95</Id><Title>iPhone users are in for a long road of terrible</Title><Msg>Apple wasn't forced into a corner; it had full year left in its Google Maps contract, which could have been a full year of perfecting its own product. But the motivation to bring maps in-house—the long-term financial gain of all that localized advertising and user data—was too strong to wait on. And that's Apple's prerogative. It's a public company, which means it owes its shareholders an earnest attempt to gobble up as much money as it can in as many ways as it can. As early users of Google Maps will tell you, though, it takes years and years to get maps right. iPhone users are in for a long road of terrible. Eventually Apple will collect enough user GPS data and have enough erroneous business listings huffily corrected that its Maps app will, like Siri, become good. Great, even. But out of the box, both are failures. And Apple knew full well that they would be. That they had to be. From Gizmodo</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348702388830</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 19:33:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348704828219-96</Id><Topic><Title>buy on the dips</Title><Username>harold_saun</Username><Timestamp>1348686895697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:14:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC may never see the high twenties again, let alone 30.00 INTC peaked well after the tech bubble burst way back in 2004 at 34.00. The SMH was $45.00, AMAT was 26.00. During the market collapse into the March 09 lows, the SMH and INTC both took out the lows of March of 2003. Okay to rent these stocks, but no one is gonna get rich simply buying and holding them.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348704828219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348710846878-97</Id><Topic><Title>buy on the dips</Title><Username>harold_saun</Username><Timestamp>1348686895697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:14:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah sounds like another clueless short bashing with no info. I see INTC about to make another run. The Div Yield is pretty high. Will signal some funds to buy in. They lowered 3rd qrt to beat it and send it higher. Watch and learn how WS works. I own a lot of Oct calls. Which expire right after earnings. What timing.</Msg><Username>verioinc</Username><Timestamp>1348710846878</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 21:54:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348713700650-98</Id><Title>Negativity is at an all time high for missing one quarter. Analyst all downgrading. Must</Title><Msg>be time to buy.</Msg><Username>jay_r001</Username><Timestamp>1348713700650</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 22:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348714679516-99</Id><Title>INTC bash of Win 8 -- AAPL deal Imminent</Title><Msg>INTC may have a new lover. And it is dumping the fat old lady that is full of bugs.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348714679516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 22:57:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348715140977-100</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348671106368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What we know... it's along way to Tipperary ... Seikiguchi believes that 450mm will revolutionize the semiconductor industry and that only companies with strong financial fundamentals will survive due to the high cost of investment. With several years to go until the target of achieving mass production by 2018, Seikiguchi believes that the risks and uncertainty during this period makes proper communication and collaboration between customers, equipment suppliers, foundries and industry associations all the more important. The semiconductor industry should learn from past experience with 300mm transition to avoid making the same mistakes. and you're up to date: They are talking about it today at Tech-Con.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348715140977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 23:05:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348715560424-101</Id><Topic><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1348685552357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:52:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The DJIA suffered its first triple digit loss since late August yesterday. try this one Bock Zutaten für ca. 20 Liter: 6 kg Pilsner Malz 100 g Hopfen (Pellets, 4 % Alphasäure) 16 l Wasser zum Einmaischen 16 l Wasser für den Nachguss Untergärige Hefe Einmaischen bei 40 °C. (Eiweißrast: 15 Minuten bei 55 °C.) Maltoserast: 45 Minuten bei 64 °C. 1. Verzuckerungsrast: 20 Minuten bei 72 °C. 2. Verzuckerungsrast: 20 Minuten bei 78 °C. Stammwürzegehalt ca. 16 %. Reifezeit mindestens 7 Wochen.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348715560424</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 23:12:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>