<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355463411953-1</Id><Topic><Title>What can cause INTC stock to SKYROCKET!!!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1355453829553</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 21:57:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You make some good points, and obviously, INTC has to get it's phone and tablet chips out. You mentioned the PC refresh. One thing that is not mentioned (or maybe it is, but I miss it) is that in 2011, I believe, there were tax incentives to buy pc's. Like many recent programs it robbed sales from the future (2012). The media bashes pc's as being down 21%, and they were, but only in the US. The 2012 fall off in non-US pc's was far less than the US. And, of course, Europe and Asia were having tough economic times in 2012. So, long story short, Stacy Smith is probably right talking about better times for the pc area. The media likes to bash though.</Msg><Username>wgrsh</Username><Timestamp>1355463411953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:36:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355467300300-2</Id><Title>DRAM stocks close sharply higher on product price rebound 2012/12/13 17:12:32</Title><Msg>do your own DD</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1355467300300</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 01:41:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355471611222-3</Id><Topic><Title>AMD is exiting x86 market</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1355415180362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 11:13:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel has many options to allow for second sourcing or fabrication of all or part of its chip family." Are you suggesting INtel will have x86 second sourced... Sure would be interested to know any who would throw their hat in with x86 "Sole control of the architecture does not mean "sole supplier"." Repeat: Sure would be interested to know any who would throw their hat in with x86 "anyone that understands the business knows this. Clearly you don't." ARMH is near its 52-week high... INTC around its 52-week low... Evidence dictates you don't...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1355471611222</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 02:53:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355493171301-4</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement for Intel Corporation. Read Now!</Title><Username>anthonyphillips662</Username><Timestamp>1355489353010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 07:49:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So primed for the pickers over at this site following alert to rock.</Msg><Username>hirsch.roderick</Username><Timestamp>1355493171301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 08:52:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355493213401-5</Id><Title>Does new XOLO Smartphone have the new Intel Medfield - Z2000?</Title><Msg>Spec: 1 GHz dual-core processor, 512 MB of RAM =================== Intel-Powered Lava XOLO A800 With 4.5" Screen Launched For Rs 12,000 Offers an 8 mp camera, 1 GHz dual-core CPU, and dual-SIM functionality. A couple of years ago, Intel partnered LG to deliver a smartphone, which never moved beyond the prototype stage. Lava stepped up to the cause and its XOLO X900 helped the chip maker enter the lucrative mobile market. Although the phone wasn't a commercial success, but it gave a breakthrough nonetheless. The handset's Rs 22,000 price tag was one of the main reasons for its low adaptation rate. Hopefully, the newly launched XOLO A800 priced at Rs 12,000 shouldn't have a problem attracting consumers. This smartphone is powered by dual-core 1 GHz CPU, and 512 MB of RAM. It comes with an 8 mp rear and VGA front camera. Its 4.5" IPS screen has pixel dimensions of 960x540. The dual-SIM (GSM) handset runs Android 4.0 out of the box. The detailed list of features is as follows: 1 GHz dual-core processor, 512 MB of RAM. Android 4.0 (ICS). From Techtree</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1355493213401</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 08:53:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355494135664-6</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement for Intel Corporation. Read Now!</Title><Username>anthonyphillips662</Username><Timestamp>1355489353010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 07:49:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i been looking for some thing like this newsletter.</Msg><Username>fred.mckibben</Username><Timestamp>1355494135664</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:08:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355494190113-7</Id><Title>Intel foundry with Apple will be good, says Credit Suisse.</Title><Msg>Credit Suisse released their report on Dec. 13, about negative analysts steering investor to think negative when they should really think positive about an Apple and Intel foundry deal. They get into detail. Those with Ameritrade accounts can access this report. There may be other ways too, but it's definitely worth the read. Goldman is just blowing smoke and has no clue about Intel's business. Credit Suisse also maintained its buy rating with $32 target price. Too bad Yahoo doesn't post this kind of very relevant and positive stuff on Intel.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1355494190113</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:09:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355494784497-8</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement for Intel Corporation. Read Now!</Title><Username>anthonyphillips662</Username><Timestamp>1355489353010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 07:49:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>every thing is looking wonderful.</Msg><Username>lawsonthomas535</Username><Timestamp>1355494784497</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:19:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355495753327-9</Id><Topic><Title>Does new XOLO Smartphone have the new Intel Medfield - Z2000?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1355493213401</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 08:53:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>XOLO A800: The only guesses that I could find on this pointed to a MediaTek CPU.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1355495753327</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:35:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355496811207-10</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement for Intel Corporation. Read Now!</Title><Username>anthonyphillips662</Username><Timestamp>1355489353010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 07:49:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pick winners</Msg><Username>juanronald501</Username><Timestamp>1355496811207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:53:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355496902531-11</Id><Title>INTC is now KING again...</Title><Msg>$QCOM is getting the absolute tar beaten out of it.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1355496902531</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:55:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355497045929-12</Id><Title>$22 happy newyear!$$$$$$$$$$$$</Title><Msg>intc+msft+aapl.no nody can do things with out INTC!</Msg><Username>mcming</Username><Timestamp>1355497045929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:57:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355497126585-13</Id><Title>Really strange- Only buy orders today?</Title><Msg>That's similar to a statement that "too funny", etc would say, only instead would say only sell orders and act very mystified.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1355497126585</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:58:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355497327201-14</Id><Title>Intel did not warn - now quiet period</Title><Msg>IMO, Q4 warning would have happened by today. Now, Intel in its official quiet period. MANY analysts said Q4 numbers were at risk. Expect short covering, some buying, and CES 2013 in a few weeks (I'm hearing very good things), to bring INTC to $23.02 short term.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1355497327201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:02:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355497976315-15</Id><Title>Gotta believe they are exhausting this years buyback money</Title><Msg>They still had quite a bit to use before tapping the 6 billion next year. I gotta believe that earnings will be good if they are buying back.</Msg><Username>jakk_wagon</Username><Timestamp>1355497976315</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:12:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355498187982-16</Id><Topic><Title>Does new XOLO Smartphone have the new Intel Medfield - Z2000?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1355493213401</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 08:53:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The headline of this article clearly states that it is a Intel CPU: "Intel-Powered Lava XOLO A800 With 4.5" Screen Launched For Rs 12,000"</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1355498187982</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:16:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355498441458-17</Id><Topic><Title>Does new XOLO Smartphone have the new Intel Medfield - Z2000?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1355493213401</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 08:53:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel doesn't have a dual core mobile process, so the title of that article is WRONG. This is bad news as it means the previous XOCO powered by Intel stunk.</Msg><Username>jakk_wagon</Username><Timestamp>1355498441458</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:20:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355498459255-18</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is now KING again...</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1355496902531</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:55:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On extremely high volume...with less than 1-hour of trading, QCOM trades have reached their average daily volume. Hope this signals the beginning of the end for QCOM and a rapid turnaround for Intel.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1355498459255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:20:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355499662730-19</Id><Topic><Title>Really strange- Only buy orders today?</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1355497126585</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:58:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I were/was as poorly educated as you, buttplug, I'd be "mystified" most of the time. TOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1355499662730</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:41:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355500108992-20</Id><Title>SMART MONEY GUYS DALIO AND COHEN DUMP INTEL SHARES</Title><Msg>Intel (NASDAQ: INTC) is another big dividend paying stock – a 4.3% yield – which hedge funds are quickly falling out of love with. Intel is down almost 15% year to date given an uncertain future for PC demand. The onslaught of market share infringement by smartphones and tablets has caused recent downward revisions for next year’s EPS; consensus is now 15% lower than it was three months ago. This large-cap tech giant might be another value trap – much like Best Buy – where it trades at 9x forward earnings and boasts a 0.8 PEG. We cautious the use of these metrics might be compromised due to Intel’s lowered expectations next quarter, and continued weakness in developed markets. Intel also saw billionaire Steven Cohen and SAC Capital sell off a massive portion of their shares last quarter</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1355500108992</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:48:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355500140894-21</Id><Topic><Title>Really strange- Only buy orders today?</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1355497126585</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:58:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surprised you didn't find a spelling error you could crow about. Would you confirm coinmaker77 is another alias of yours?</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1355500140894</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:49:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355500918352-22</Id><Title>You can always tell the LOSER. They are the ones yelling.</Title><Msg>GOP Teabaggers Wallstreet trash AND---they are all making me laugh. YES---OB won and NO---you will not win this next fight against him. He will btccch slap mitchy McOnnel--who has a 38% approval rating in his state of Kentucky. The Bone man--will be out smoking and drinking when the New Year hits. Johnny Boahner--NAZI--will fold like a little bbbtch before the first week of January is done. OB will avoid debt ceiling #$%$ for the next 4 years as part of the deal--OR--there will be NO DEAL. You idiotssss on the right have given the pres the gun and he can simply fire it. All taxes go up and the military gets the shhiet cut out of it if OB does nothing. What? You are against tax cuts for the 98%? see how long you can hold out on that Boneee man.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1355500918352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:01:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355501216882-23</Id><Topic><Title>SMART MONEY GUYS DALIO AND COHEN DUMP INTEL SHARES</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1355500108992</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:48:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>recommend that you go ahead and sell the 50 shares you bought at 29 if you're so fearful. No one on the board would hold it against you.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1355501216882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:06:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355501491503-24</Id><Title>Acer Iconia W700 review: a Core i5 Windows 8 slate that doesn't skimp on battery life</Title><Msg>engadgetDOTcom/2012/12/14/acer-iconia-w700-review/ ' What's funny about the W700 is that it has the same chipset as other Windows 8 machines we've tested, along with a 1080p touchscreen -- precisely the sort of thing that would normally suck the life out of a battery. And yet, the three-cell, 4,850mAh battery lasts hours longer than bigger touchscreen Windows 8 systems with similar internals. Specifically, we got seven hours and 13 minutes of runtime after looping a video off the local disk with WiFi on and the brightness fixed at 65 percent. The next runner-up in our list is the Lenovo IdeaPad Yoga 13, and if you look at the numbers, it wasn't even a close contest: it managed just five and a half hours in the same test, even though it probably has room for a larger-capacity battery than the W700. It only gets worse from there: we've seen touchscreen Windows 8 systems that barely cracked four hours. The W700 looks even more impressive when you compare it to lighter-weight, ARM-powered tablets. You wouldn't expect that to be the case -- this really isn't a fair fight -- but in fact the difference in battery life isn't as drastic as you'd imagine, especially if you take into account tablets that offer merely average endurance. The ASUS Transformer Pad TF300, for instance, lasts only about an hour longer than the W700; the Nexus 10 edges out the W700 by a mere 13 minutes. We'll admit, the Nexus 10 offers skimpy battery life (we complained about it in our initial review). But here's the thing: we don't know of another Core i5 tablet that can even come close. Take the Surface Pro, for instance: it's expected to last half as long as the Surface for Windows RT -- i.e., about four and a half hours in our rundown test. If that's true, then the W700's battery life would seem that much more exceptional: after all, the W700 and the Surface Pro are close cousins, at least as far as key specs go. It's incredible, then, that the W700's battery life is more typical of a low-powered ARM device.'</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1355501491503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:11:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355501816719-25</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy capitulates, says buy INTEL</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1317740904000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-10-04 11:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at the loser down on his knees giving up and bowing to Intel. Too Ironic.</Msg><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1355501816719</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:16:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355501846697-26</Id><Topic><Title>SMART MONEY GUYS DALIO AND COHEN DUMP INTEL SHARES</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1355500108992</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:48:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>value trap, margins are coming way down even if they beat the tar out of ARMH.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1355501846697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:17:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355501940928-27</Id><Topic><Title>I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1293550442000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-12-28 10:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL....Tooofunny capitualted and bought at 24, then capitulated again and sold at 20........right before it ran to 29. He's also been down on his Cisco purchase for 2 years. You cannot make this stuff up.</Msg><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1355501940928</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:19:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355502642762-28</Id><Title>Intel has positioned itself the last decade to be strong in next bull market</Title><Msg>Share count down from 7 billion to soon-to-be 4.5 billion. That will only compound the stock price higher in the next bull market. Don't let the bears fool you, there is NOTHING wrong with Intel other than the economy.</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1355502642762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:30:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355502850019-29</Id><Topic><Title>SMART MONEY GUYS DALIO AND COHEN DUMP INTEL SHARES</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1355500108992</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:48:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The firms are notable. The SAC options trades would likely be more visible that the share liquidations, depending on strike and month. Bridgewater held 523,000 shares of INTC and it was 0.22% of its portfolio. They liquidated. SAC Capital Advisors had a more complex position in INTC. They owned 100,000 put option contracts and increased to 110,200. 290,374 shares decreased to 113,371 1,985,600 call options.decreased to 285,600</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1355502850019</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:34:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355503165884-30</Id><Topic><Title>INTC might blow up tomorrow! This is the key reasons why.</Title><Username>mellis438</Username><Timestamp>1355497112970</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:58:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It seems other newsletters really like this guy. You can find him in their twitter timeline.</Msg><Username>dula.franklin</Username><Timestamp>1355503165884</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:39:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355503173716-31</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement for Intel Corporation. Read Now!</Title><Username>anthonyphillips662</Username><Timestamp>1355489353010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 07:49:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>holding</Msg><Username>jessieriley78</Username><Timestamp>1355503173716</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:39:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355503308428-32</Id><Topic><Title>Acer Iconia W700 review: a Core i5 Windows 8 slate that doesn't skimp on battery life</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1355501491503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:11:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very cool ! Portends well for the CES announcements on new low-power Ivy Bridge chips and soon-to-follow Haswells.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1355503308428</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:41:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355503830973-33</Id><Topic><Title>SMART MONEY GUYS DALIO AND COHEN DUMP INTEL SHARES</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1355500108992</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:48:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Margin is important because it determines what percentage of revenue is available for earnings. The more important measure of value to the investor is margin dollars per share and growth of margin dollars per share. Anyone who disconnects margin from revenue does not understand the relationship. Value trap? Only for the unimaginative. Not if you are looking for a 4.5% yield on a chunk of money. Not if you acquire share selling put options at a 4% discount. Collect the dividends (at 4%) and sell call options while you own it at 2%.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1355503830973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:50:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355507147138-34</Id><Title>Lucy nuff joke for you</Title><Msg>Two queers: Lucifer nuff and roommate were getting ready to leave for the day. Roommate begins pounding on the bathroom door telling Lucy to hurry up and asks what he's doing. Lucy yells out, "hold on, I'm packin a lunch!"</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1355507147138</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:45:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355507197122-35</Id><Title>20 kids shot? There has got to be some gur control you rightwing trash.</Title><Msg>You people are idiots--rightwing.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1355507197122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:46:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355507407277-36</Id><Topic><Title>20 kids shot? There has got to be some gur control you rightwing trash.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1355507197122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:46:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And The Republicans in Congress will say we NEED MORE guns/</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1355507407277</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:50:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355507525699-37</Id><Topic><Title>20 kids shot? There has got to be some gur control you rightwing trash.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1355507197122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:46:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You using the death of children to pound your political drum makes you the lowest of all life forms. Utterly dispicable.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1355507525699</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:52:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355507546700-38</Id><Topic><Title>20 kids shot? There has got to be some gur control you rightwing trash.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1355507197122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:46:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wait a second now. We do not know that this gunmen was not a terrorist. Maybe---internal but maybe external from another nation. All heck could break lose.</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1355507546700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:52:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355507646926-39</Id><Title>26 dead in a school. AND our Congress is useless trash.</Title><Msg>They will do nothing and we are all screwed.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1355507646926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:54:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355507757328-40</Id><Title>Why is our society so full iof hate?</Title><Msg>It will only get worse.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1355507757328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:55:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355508143572-41</Id><Title>Don't let twinkle toes FLUMOXED fool you</Title><Msg>He's all the AMD monkey's and cornholers. He like's wearing skinny jeans and makeup. He'll throw a post out there every now and then saying the Apple/Intel deal isn't going to happen to make it look like it's not him, but he's not fooling anybody.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1355508143572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:02:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355508336212-42</Id><Topic><Title>20 kids shot? There has got to be some gur control you rightwing trash.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1355507197122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:46:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The tone of your message is the root of the problem. Name calling just helps create these killers.</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1355508336212</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:05:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355508416661-43</Id><Title>Credit Suisse does research, actually provides numbers....and disagrees with James Covello</Title><Msg>Eric Savitz, Forbes Staff 12/14/2012 @ 12:53PM |4 views Intel: Why They Might Want To Be Apple's Processor Foundry There has been growing speculation that Intel might leverage its expertise in semiconductor manufacturing with an aggressive move into the foundry business, in effect taking on Taiwan Semiconductor and others in the business of producing chips for others. Part of the reason for the speculation has revolved around Apple. Intel already makes processors for the Mac; but iPhones and iPads use a proprietary ARM-based processor that has been produced for Apple by Samsung. Given the frosty relationship between Apple and Samsung, the scuttlebutt is that Apple has been looking for alternatives – and that the options might include Intel. The issue that always comes up when this idea surfaces is that a move into the foundry business would come at the cost of lower gross margins – making microprocessors is an inherently more profitable activity than manufacturing parts for others. But Credit Suisse analyst John Pitzer took a closer look at this issue, and makes a case in a research note issued this morning that there are reasons to think it would be a smart move for Intel to move into contract manufacturing with Apple as a customer. “Moore’s Law – smaller, faster and cheaper – has been the cornerstone of tech economics for 40 year,” he notes. “It is our view that technical, financial and scale issues are driving towards a last-man-standing advantage for Intel relative to Moore’s Law and that Intel will leverage that advantage not only in its core business but increasingly as a specialized foundry.” Pitzer notes that Intel Foundry Services (IFS) already has three small, privately held customers – Acrhnoix (which makes FPGAs, field programmable gate arrays), Tabula (programmable logic devices) and Netronome (which makes network processors.) But he says there are a number of other potential customers, including not only Apple but also Cisco, Altera and Xilinx. “To date IFS has remained mostly a niche effort, but we would argue that as Intel’s manufacturing lead continues to widen at 14nm and especially at 450mm, IFS will become a more meaningful driver of top and bottom line performance,” he writes. “Investors worry about the impact to corporate profitability from foundry business, especially relative to an Intel and Apple relationship. On the surface, Intel’s MPU ASPs of $120 versus the Apple ASP of $20-$25, Intel’s corporate gross margin of 60-65% versus TSMC’s at 45-50% and Intel’s cost/wafer of $10,500-$11,500 versus leading edge wafers at TSMC at $5,000-$5,500 would all suggest that any entry into foundry would be margin dilutive with little bottom line impact.” But he adds: “We disagree.” Pitzer writes that he looked at the impact of a foundry relationship between Intel and Apple using ARM chips ”and concludes that the profitability profile is much better than the consensus view.” His view: If Intel were to produce 100% of Apple’s demand at 14 nm the company generate an extra $5.8 billion in revenue, 47% gross margins (which is below the 60%-65% of the core business) but with operating margins of 35%, above the core of 28%-32%. He thinks that arrangement would produce an extra 28 cents a share in annual profits, with an ROI of 20%-25%.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1355508416661</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:06:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355508496944-44</Id><Title>Credit Suisse does research, actually provides number and disagrees with J. Covello</Title><Msg>Eric Savitz, Forbes Staff 12/14/2012 @ 12:53PM |4 views Intel: Why They Might Want To Be Apple's Processor Foundry There has been growing speculation that Intel might leverage its expertise in semiconductor manufacturing with an aggressive move into the foundry business, in effect taking on Taiwan Semiconductor and others in the business of producing chips for others. Part of the reason for the speculation has revolved around Apple. Intel already makes processors for the Mac; but iPhones and iPads use a proprietary ARM-based processor that has been produced for Apple by Samsung. Given the frosty relationship between Apple and Samsung, the scuttlebutt is that Apple has been looking for alternatives – and that the options might include Intel. The issue that always comes up when this idea surfaces is that a move into the foundry business would come at the cost of lower gross margins – making microprocessors is an inherently more profitable activity than manufacturing parts for others. But Credit Suisse analyst John Pitzer took a closer look at this issue, and makes a case in a research note issued this morning that there are reasons to think it would be a smart move for Intel to move into contract manufacturing with Apple as a customer. “Moore’s Law – smaller, faster and cheaper – has been the cornerstone of tech economics for 40 year,” he notes. “It is our view that technical, financial and scale issues are driving towards a last-man-standing advantage for Intel relative to Moore’s Law and that Intel will leverage that advantage not only in its core business but increasingly as a specialized foundry.” Pitzer notes that Intel Foundry Services (IFS) already has three small, privately held customers – Acrhnoix (which makes FPGAs, field programmable gate arrays), Tabula (programmable logic devices) and Netronome (which makes network processors.) But he says there are a number of other potential customers, including not only Apple but also Cisco, Altera and Xilinx. “To date IFS has remained mostly a niche effort, but we would argue that as Intel’s manufacturing lead continues to widen at 14nm and especially at 450mm, IFS will become a more meaningful driver of top and bottom line performance,” he writes. “Investors worry about the impact to corporate profitability from foundry business, especially relative to an Intel and Apple relationship. On the surface, Intel’s MPU ASPs of $120 versus the Apple ASP of $20-$25, Intel’s corporate gross margin of 60-65% versus TSMC’s at 45-50% and Intel’s cost/wafer of $10,500-$11,500 versus leading edge wafers at TSMC at $5,000-$5,500 would all suggest that any entry into foundry would be margin dilutive with little bottom line impact.” But he adds: “We disagree.” Pitzer writes that he looked at the impact of a foundry relationship between Intel and Apple using ARM chips ”and concludes that the profitability profile is much better than the consensus view.” His view: If Intel were to produce 100% of Apple’s demand at 14 nm the company generate an extra $5.8 billion in revenue, 47% gross margins (which is below the 60%-65% of the core business) but with operating margins of 35%, above the core of 28%-32%. He thinks that arrangement would produce an extra 28 cents a share in annual profits, with an ROI of 20%-25%.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1355508496944</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:08:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355508517256-45</Id><Topic><Title>Acer Iconia W700 review: a Core i5 Windows 8 slate that doesn't skimp on battery life</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1355501491503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:11:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The W700 looks even more impressive when you compare it to lighter-weight, ARM-powered tablets."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1355508517256</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:08:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355508548711-46</Id><Topic><Title>20 kids shot? There has got to be some gur control you rightwing trash.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1355507197122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:46:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's an idiot. Angry idiot Liberals like him (Flumoxed is his normal ID) are why America is a disaster.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1355508548711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:09:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355508549316-47</Id><Title>Intel: Why They Might Want To Be Apple's Processor Foundry</Title><Msg>INtel would have to fab ARM SOCs... -------------------------------------------------------- There has been growing speculation that Intel might leverage its expertise in semiconductor manufacturing with an aggressive move into the foundry business, in effect taking on Taiwan Semiconductor and others in the business of producing chips for others. Part of the reason for the speculation has revolved around Apple. Intel already makes processors for the Mac; but iPhones and iPads use a proprietary ARM-based processor that has been produced for Apple by Samsung. Given the frosty relationship between Apple and Samsung, the scuttlebutt is that Apple has been looking for alternatives – and that the options might include Intel. The issue that always comes up when this idea surfaces is that a move into the foundry business would come at the cost of lower gross margins – making microprocessors is an inherently more profitable activity than manufacturing parts for others. But Credit Suisse analyst John Pitzer took a closer look at this issue, and makes a case in a research note issued this morning that there are reasons to think it would be a smart move for Intel to move into contract manufacturing with Apple as a customer. “Moore’s Law – smaller, faster and cheaper – has been the cornerstone of tech economics for 40 year,” he notes. “It is our view that technical, financial and scale issues are driving towards a last-man-standing advantage for Intel relative to Moore’s Law and that Intel will leverage that advantage not only in its core business but increasingly as a specialized foundry.” Pitzer notes that Intel Foundry Services (IFS) already has three small, privately held customers – Acrhnoix (which makes FPGAs, field programmable gate arrays), Tabula (programmable logic devices) and Netronome (which makes network processors.) But he says there are a number of other potential customers, including not only Apple but also Cisco, Altera and Xilinx. “To date IFS has remained mostly a niche effort, but we would argue that as Intel’s manufacturing lead continues to widen at 14nm and especially at 450mm, IFS will become a more meaningful driver of top and bottom line performance,” he writes. “Investors worry about the impact to corporate profitability from foundry business, especially relative to an Intel and Apple relationship. On the surface, Intel’s MPU ASPs of $120 versus the Apple ASP of $20-$25, Intel’s corporate gross margin of 60-65% versus TSMC’s at 45-50% and Intel’s cost/wafer of $10,500-$11,500 versus leading edge wafers at TSMC at $5,000-$5,500 would all suggest that any entry into foundry would be margin dilutive with little bottom line impact.” But he adds: “We disagree.” Pitzer writes that he looked at the impact of a foundry relationship between Intel and Apple using ARM chips ”and concludes that the profitability profile is much better than the consensus view.” His view: If Intel were to produce 100% of Apple’s demand at 14 nm the company generate an extra $5.8 billion in revenue, 47% gross margins (which is below the 60%-65% of the core business) but with operating margins of 35%, above the core of 28%-32%. He thinks that arrangement would produce an extra 28 cents a share in annual profits, with an ROI of 20%-25%. INTC is up 11 cents, or 0.5%, to $20.60.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1355508549316</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:09:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355508617005-48</Id><Title>Credit Suisse tells James Covello he's wrong....and provides numbers</Title><Msg>“To date IFS has remained mostly a niche effort, but we would argue that as Intel’s manufacturing lead continues to widen at 14nm and especially at 450mm, IFS will become a more meaningful driver of top and bottom line performance,” he writes. “Investors worry about the impact to corporate profitability from foundry business, especially relative to an Intel and Apple relationship. On the surface, Intel’s MPU ASPs of $120 versus the Apple ASP of $20-$25, Intel’s corporate gross margin of 60-65% versus TSMC’s at 45-50% and Intel’s cost/wafer of $10,500-$11,500 versus leading edge wafers at TSMC at $5,000-$5,500 would all suggest that any entry into foundry would be margin dilutive with little bottom line impact.” But he adds: “We disagree.” Pitzer writes that he looked at the impact of a foundry relationship between Intel and Apple using ARM chips ”and concludes that the profitability profile is much better than the consensus view.” His view: If Intel were to produce 100% of Apple’s demand at 14 nm the company generate an extra $5.8 billion in revenue, 47% gross margins (which is below the 60%-65% of the core business) but with operating margins of 35%, above the core of 28%-32%. He thinks that arrangement would produce an extra 28 cents a share in annual profits, with an ROI of 20%-25%.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1355508617005</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:10:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355508670862-49</Id><Title>worst school shooting in US history! Thanks GOP.</Title><Msg>Unbelievable. What the GOP has done to the USA makes Osama Bin Laden look like a mosquito.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1355508670862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:11:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355508719709-50</Id><Topic><Title>20 kids shot? There has got to be some gur control you rightwing trash.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1355507197122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:46:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>go shoot yourself, att.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1355508719709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:11:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355508721313-51</Id><Topic><Title>worst school shooting in US history! Thanks GOP.</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1355508670862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:11:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep using the death of children to push your political agenda so all doubt can be removed that you are a cowards, and a skummbag.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1355508721313</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:12:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355508759344-52</Id><Topic><Title>worst school shooting in US history! Thanks GOP.</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1355508670862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:11:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are the coward and #$%$ and now everyone knows it.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1355508759344</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:12:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355508769733-53</Id><Topic><Title>worst school shooting in US history! Thanks GOP.</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1355508670862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:11:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PS, amazing how cornholers and monkeys always show up at the same time as Flumoxed. Idiot.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1355508769733</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:12:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355509537279-54</Id><Title>Wearable computers makes Intel an absolute steal at 20/share</Title><Msg>Wearable Computing Brightens Long-Term Outlook For Intel By Maxwell Fisher - December 14, 2012| If you thought the internet and computers have reached a saturation point in their evolution, think again. Intel is closely working on several technologies that will help us to use wearable and portable computers in the near future. Wearable computers are small electronic devices that can be worn above or beneath clothing. This technology was intended for general as well as special purpose IT. Wearable computers are gaining traction. Today, they are primarily being used out in the field where other computer devices, such as laptops, tablets and smartphones hinder a workers ability to record data and perform other duties. There are new examples of wearable computers popping up every day. Sony Ericcson, for example, recently unveiled its new SmartWatch, an Android based smartphone watch which can utilize Google Play apps like Twitter and Facebook. According to Electronista, the market for wearable computers is expected to hit $1.5 billion in revenues by 2014. If Intel could capture just a piece of this market, it could see a significant boost in its bottom line. Intel will begin to mass produce tiny chips that can be used in wearable computers, as early as a few years. Wearable and portable computing have wide ranging market scope and almost all market and industrial sectors will begin to adopt Intel's new technology. This will lead to increased sales of Intel's chips and processors, resulting in increased profits and revenue. This will boost Intel's share value in the long-term. Intel is working on chips that will make it possible to bring "portable computers" to consumer market in less than two to five years. Intel is working on computer chips smaller than their low-voltage Atom processors used in phones and tablets, which can be used to power 'wearable computers'. The chips may have less than half or even a quarter the size of an atom chip. To help reduce the size and power of these small chips, they will not have instruction sets typically found on a microprocessor. The future of computing and microchips lies in wearable technology. Wearable computers have extensive use in the army, medicine, mining, oil and gas and just about anywhere it is not possible for humans to work safely. With the touch of a finger, pictures and videos can be transferred unchanged from a computer to any smooth surface like that of a bowl, table, or wall. Intel will need to bring wearable technology to mass consumers as soon as possible, as the competition will only grow robust. The U.S. military is expected to spend a lot more money on landmine removal, on research into bionic arms and limbs and also on clothing for marines that can act as information processors. When Intel will launch its tiny processors and chips, U.S. military will be the first client to order these tiny chips by the hundreds of thousands. My point is, wearable technology and portable computing have huge potentials that may change the way we understand computers, Internet and information processing. Certainly, Intel is at the forefront of this research and development. All this will translate to increased revenue for Intel, as manufacturers and organizations across healthcare, security, military and energy sectors will depend on Intel for its tiny chips. Intel wants to make it possible to display images of any type on any surface, said Manny Vara, senior technology evangelist at Intel. A system that changes the way we interact with things and makes the images more interactive, according to Vara. Researchers have demonstrated technology, which is still in development, at the European Conference on Research and Innovation Intel in Barcelona last month. Vara demonstrated the project, called "Display without Borders", with a laptop computer, a Microsoft Connect sensor and a projector. At the beginning Vara expects the technology to be used in homes to show pictures and video, Vara also said he expected it to be useful for businesses, allowing workers to collaborate more easily in a meeting, for example. In time, more uses of this technology will be developed. If Intel succeeds in developing the "wearable computers" in the short term, this will be a revolution in how people communicate. Moreover, by being the first company to develop this type of product, its profits would be astronomical, because who would not want to be connected in a way simpler than a smartphone?</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1355509537279</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:25:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355509620650-55</Id><Topic><Title>20 kids shot? There has got to be some gur control you rightwing trash.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1355507197122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:46:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For sure.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1355509620650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:27:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355509782204-56</Id><Topic><Title>20 kids shot? There has got to be some gur control you rightwing trash.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1355507197122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:46:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only an angry out of control Liberal would tell someone to go kill themselves. Keep posting Flumoxed, ya 60 year old gay degenerate.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1355509782204</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:29:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355510313227-57</Id><Title>Flumoxed...</Title><Msg>You've put me on triple top secret super duper Ignore at least 3 times now yet you respond to me. Hitten home, aren't I? I own you.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1355510313227</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:38:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355511729070-58</Id><Topic><Title>Why is our society so full iof hate?</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1355507757328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's because of evil like too funny/aliases that make false &amp; reckless statements just to irritate/annoy/taunt other people. Finally, you snap, stop by a gun shop, track down the person and finally relieve society of the infection. You do a public service.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1355511729070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:02:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355512941070-59</Id><Title>Wow</Title><Msg>Undoubtedly, Intel is the most powerful processor maker at the moment and holds the largest market share. Consequently, Intel has a market cap of $102 billion and an enterprise value of $97 billion. With a profit margin of 22.13%, an operating margin of 30% and revenue of $53.75 billion, Intel is a very powerful company with great benefits for investors. I strongly believe that those numbers will increase when Intel's tiny chips for wearable and portable computers are launched in the mass market. Although the market in general is bearish, Intel is having a great growth in developing countries. Intel is one stock that we cannot ignore solely because of the amount of interest that ordinary consumers, government establishments, research organizations, consumer goods manufacturers and the military have in wearable and portable computing. The ramifications of Intel's tiny chips are going to be profound and the company will see a vertical growth in terms of profit and revenue. This is one reason why Intel's stock will continue to be a great long-term investment in the years to come.</Msg><Username>jakk_wagon</Username><Timestamp>1355512941070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:22:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355512953174-60</Id><Title>Tick Tock Tick Tock-----shorts will be blown up soon.</Title><Msg>Apple Intel deal.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1355512953174</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:22:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355512982098-61</Id><Topic><Title>Why is our society so full iof hate?</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1355507757328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Drugs.</Msg><Username>jakk_wagon</Username><Timestamp>1355512982098</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:23:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355513294492-62</Id><Topic><Title>Why is our society so full iof hate?</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1355507757328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes you are so correct. Drugs</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1355513294492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:28:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355513488762-63</Id><Title>Child victims were just 5-10 years old. CBS says they were killed execution-style.</Title><Msg>This is as bad as 9-11 or even worse. This is our own killing our babys.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1355513488762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:31:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355513548842-64</Id><Topic><Title>Why is our society so full iof hate?</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1355507757328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a Hypocrite, Flumoxed's roadkill alias is........His LIBERAL filth brothers legalize drugs! OMG, what a SKUMMBAG HYPOCRITE!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1355513548842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:32:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355513888016-65</Id><Topic><Title>Child victims were just 5-10 years old. CBS says they were killed execution-style.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1355513488762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:31:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very disturbing and depressing. We had hand guns 30 years ago and this was not happening so what is going on? Drugs? So what do we do? Who needs terrorists when our own young men are becoming the terrorists like in Colorado and now here. The Arabs on the plane would not have shot kids execution style. This is some sick stuff. YES--if we take their guns away these nuts will use machetes to cut their heads off in mass murder. It is the nuts. Why are we producing such hate?</Msg><Username>amdroadkilldec2009</Username><Timestamp>1355513888016</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:38:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355514121124-66</Id><Topic><Title>Why is our society so full iof hate?</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1355507757328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only an absolute idiot would call murder a public service</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1355514121124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:42:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355514807947-67</Id><Topic><Title>Why is our society so full iof hate?</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1355507757328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bet the CIA would sanction such a thing directed at you, Mrs. Nuff. It would be similar to getting rid of Osama bin Laden. Mankind would celebrate the demise.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1355514807947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:53:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355515013105-68</Id><Title>This killer was EVIL</Title><Msg>He killed the children in the roon execution style and shot and killed 8 teachers one after another as they entered the room attempting to save children. This thing is really going to hurt us all. 18 kids and 8 teacherd executed by home grown insanity. His mother was a teacher.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1355515013105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:56:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355515298483-69</Id><Topic><Title>Why is our society so full iof hate?</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1355507757328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney lost so GET OVER IT you crybaby.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1355515298483</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:01:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355515299345-70</Id><Topic><Title>Why is our society so full iof hate?</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1355507757328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just FYI people, here is a trick too funny/L Nuff does: he makes a post then gives it a thumbs up with one of his aliases.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1355515299345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:01:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355515487019-71</Id><Title>Oh well--at least Romney lost. HAAA HAAA</Title><Msg>That means you LOST too rightwingnuts.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1355515487019</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:04:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355515814333-72</Id><Title>INTC taking a hit</Title><Msg>No end to this sh@t market.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1355515814333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:10:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355516074843-73</Id><Topic><Title>INTC taking a hit</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1355515814333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:10:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUY right here</Msg><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1355516074843</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:14:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355516132185-74</Id><Title>Are we going to have a new CEO monday</Title><Msg>anyone?</Msg><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1355516132185</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:15:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355516734872-75</Id><Title>AAPL is $23.00/share stronger</Title><Msg>that's great!</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1355516734872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:25:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355516756686-76</Id><Title>27 Dead, incl 18 Kids: Thanks you GOP</Title><Msg>The GOP wingnuts own this..all of this. Outlaw Guns. Throw out the wingnuts.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1355516756686</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:25:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355516795031-77</Id><Title>It will be closed GREEN today and Monday too</Title><Msg>So just relax and enjoy your weekend.</Msg><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1355516795031</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:26:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355517123022-78</Id><Title>How much revenue will Intel derive from China Mobile? Anybody?</Title><Msg>Does this below mean big money for Intel and does Apple have to work with Intel to work with China Mobile? This article is hard to understand. Yet the news might not be all that bad considering that Mobile China's shift to TD-LTE may not take as long as some analysts are claiming. In our latest IDF report that we posted in September titled "Intel's Next Wave: Transparent Computing," we covered a fascinating segment which revealed how Intel has been working with Mobile China since 2009 in a revolutionary new wireless infrastructure called C-RAN. Our September report stated that "In China, Intel is working on this next generation C-RAN with China Mobile Research Institute, the largest wireless service provider in the world with more than 680 million subscribers. They currently have about a million base stations throughout China. Their goal is to have roughly one third of these base stations upgraded to 4G LTE. Such a huge undertaking would have hit the company's bottom line if it weren't for Intel's next generation wireless infrastructure solution based on C-RAN." If you have a moment, you should check out more information about this revolutionary new wireless system in our September report that could provide you with greater details. With Mobile China having a third of their base stations rapidly converting to the new C-RAN model, it will open up the TD-LTE market to a whopping 233 million subscribers. That's roughly double the number of US market subscribers clocking in at close to 120 million for 2012. It's a large enough market that could see Apple on board with Mobile China sooner rather than later. This is a factor that the Asian analysts haven't considered and one that could make the world of difference in the timing of Apple being able to increase their sales in China dramatically.</Msg><Username>jakk_wagon</Username><Timestamp>1355517123022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:32:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355517227340-79</Id><Title>Can anybody makes sense of this article? What kind of revenue will this mean for Intel?</Title><Msg>Yet the news might not be all that bad considering that Mobile China's shift to TD-LTE may not take as long as some analysts are claiming. In our latest IDF report that we posted in September titled "Intel's Next Wave: Transparent Computing," we covered a fascinating segment which revealed how Intel has been working with Mobile China since 2009 in a revolutionary new wireless infrastructure called C-RAN.</Msg><Username>jakk_wagon</Username><Timestamp>1355517227340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:33:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355517298120-80</Id><Title>What's the deal with China Mobile, Intel and Apple?</Title><Msg>Does this below mean big money for Intel and does Apple have to work with Intel to work with China Mobile? This article is hard to understand. Yet the news might not be all that bad considering that Mobile China's shift to TD-LTE may not take as long as some analysts are claiming. In our latest IDF report that we posted in September titled "Intel's Next Wave: Transparent Computing," we covered a fascinating segment which revealed how Intel has been working with Mobile China since 2009 in a revolutionary new wireless infrastructure called C-RAN.</Msg><Username>jakk_wagon</Username><Timestamp>1355517298120</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:34:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355517421129-81</Id><Topic><Title>27 Dead, incl 18 Kids: Thanks you GOP</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1355516756686</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:25:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is your type who foster hate.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1355517421129</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:37:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355517467238-82</Id><Title>How big of an oppurtunity is China Mobile for Intel?</Title><Msg>Anybody know? I found this and am curious. In China, Intel is working on this next generation C-RAN with China Mobile Research Institute, the largest wireless service provider in the world with more than 680 million subscribers. They currently have about a million base stations throughout China. Their goal is to have roughly one third of these base stations upgraded to 4G LTE. Such a huge undertaking would have hit the company's bottom line if it weren't for Intel's next generation wireless infrastructure solution based on C-RAN."</Msg><Username>jakk_wagon</Username><Timestamp>1355517467238</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:37:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355517564198-83</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL is $23.00/share stronger</Title><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1355516734872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:25:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huh?</Msg><Username>jakk_wagon</Username><Timestamp>1355517564198</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:39:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355517714692-84</Id><Title>Just found this. Doesn't this alone solidify Intel's future in Mobile???????</Title><Msg>Instant Response to Your Every Command from the First Motorola Mobility Smartphone with an Intel® Atom™ Processor Available in China BEIJING – November 19, 2012 – The world is running at full speed and you are setting the pace. What could be more helpful than a lightning-fast partner that responds instantly to your every request? Introducing Motorola MT788, the Android™-powered smartphone with Intel Inside, brought to you by Motorola Mobility and China Mobile. The Motorola MT788's incredibly fast Intel Atom processor can achieve speeds of 2GHz, so you can jump from a game to a text message to a playlist to a Web browser without missing a beat. "Motorola MT788 is the first smartphone in China to feature the Intel's fastest smartphone CPU," said Frank Meng, Senior Vice President and President of Greater China, Motorola Mobility. "The Motorola MT788 combines the expertise and passion of Motorola and Intel in a single device to bring people an amazingly fast and responsive mobile Internet experience." "The launch of MT788 marks a great step toward forward in bringing the best of Intel computing to the smartphone," said Ian Yang, Intel corporate vice president and president of Intel China. "As the smartphone continues to become a vital part of people's lifestyles, our goal is to provide compelling technology options that translate into great user benefits and experiences. We believe that the new smartphone from Motorola and China Mobile delivers on this promise, and that people across China will enjoy the device." The Instant Phone Featuring the Intel's fastest smartphone CPU that can achieve speeds of 2GHz and Android 4.0 (Ice Cream Sandwich), the Motorola MT788 instantly responds to your touch as you maneuver between apps, content and browsing. Load and view web pages in the blink of an eye and start and enjoy 3D games without any hesitation. With an instant-launch 8-megapixel camera you will never miss a precious moment. When there's action and movement involved, multi-shot mode lets you snap ten pictures in less than a second and continuous shot allows you to take up to 30 pictures. With up to 12 modes of the camera, including HDR mode and Night Shot mode, you can create pictures that exceed your imagination even in challenging lighting conditions. And with 1080P video capture/playback, you are able to relive your memories in vivid high-definition at any time. Thin and Fashionable The Motorola MT788 features a stylish, sophisticated aluminum body created with an advanced manufacturing process that makes the phone surprisingly strong and thin. The expansive 4.3-inch display is protected by the latest Corning® Gorilla® Glass to withstand all kinds of bumps and scratches. Motorola MT788 comes in Licorice and Ultra White, so you can choose the model that reflects your personal style. Additional features include:•TD-SCDMA 1880/2010, HSDPA; GSM (900/1800/1900), GPRS/EDGE Class 12 •4.3-inch 960x540 qHD display •4GB ROM •1735 mAh battery for up to 170 hours of standby time* •Intelligent shot modes to capture photos automatically when you are ready •Front camera for video chat •SmartActions™ for extending battery life and automating everyday tasks •MotoSwitch user interface for ultimate device personalization Availability Starting from mid-December, Motorola MT788 is available through China Mobile stores across China and authorized Motorola resellers.</Msg><Username>jakk_wagon</Username><Timestamp>1355517714692</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:41:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355517942830-85</Id><Title>We will see $21 next week folks</Title><Msg>Relax !</Msg><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1355517942830</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:45:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355519057750-86</Id><Title>Intel real trooper today....</Title><Msg>manages to eke out over 3 cent gain, despite market being down horribly and government in political chaos/turmoil. Should be over 25 possibly as early as mid Jan. J. Blown</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1355519057750</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:04:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355519760750-87</Id><Topic><Title>We will see $21 next week folks</Title><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1355517942830</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:45:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I need at least $23... but $21 is better than $19...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1355519760750</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:16:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355520585097-88</Id><Topic><Title>20 dead kids: Thank you GOP!</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1355520131118</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:22:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot about Jared Lee Loughner a KNOWN RADICAL LIBERAL. Get lost you filth of the earth loser. From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia Jared Lee Loughner Mug shot of Loughner taken by U.S. Marshals on January 22, 2011 Born September 10, 1988 (age 24) Residence Tucson, Arizona, U.S. Nationality American Education Mountain View High School (dropped out) Pima Community College (withdrew) Known for 2011 Tucson shooting Criminal charge 49, including 2 first-degree murder of federal employees (federal), 4 first-degree murder (state), attempted murder of a member of Congress (federal), 2 attempted murder of federal employees (federal), 10 attempted first-degree murder (state) Criminal status Pled guilty on August 7, 2012 to all charges, sentenced to life in prison without the possibility of parole Jared Lee Loughner ( /ˈlɒfnər/; born September 10, 1988)[1] is an American who plead guilty to 19 charges, of murder and attempted murder, in connection with the shooting in Tucson, Arizona, on January 8, 2011, that killed six people, including Chief U.S. District Court Judge John Roll, as well as a 9-year-old girl, Christina-Taylor Green.[2][3][4][5][6] The shooting also left 14 others injured, including U.S. Representative Gabrielle Giffords.[7</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1355520585097</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:29:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355520685559-89</Id><Title>SKUM Radical Liberal shoots 6 people, including congresswoman because she didn't support Nanci Pelosi</Title><Msg>Jared Loughner twice worked for Gabrielle Gifford’s campaign but later formed a grudge against her for voting against the reelection of Nancy Pelosi to the post of Minority Leader. So on January 8th at ten a.m. he went to a town hall meeting Gifford was holding in her Arizona district and proceeded to shoot her, a Federal judge and a number of bystanders. When Loughner tried to escape other nameless bystanders tackled him to the ground.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1355520685559</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:31:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355521309744-90</Id><Topic><Title>SKUM Radical Liberal shoots 6 people, including congresswoman because she didn't support Nanci Pelosi</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1355520685559</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:31:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>my pile is bigger than your pile!!! you just smell like your pile is bigger!!</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1355521309744</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:41:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355522964387-91</Id><Title>More evidence of imminent APPL/INTC deal?</Title><Msg>Read Peter Clarke of EE Times regarding FAB 24 and 14nm introduction. I find the comment section extremely interesting: ----------------------------------- Chipmonk: "There seems to be a shift at Intel from CPUs for PCs to SoCs for Mobiles. 14 nm process may have to be reoptimized for SoCs ( analog, I/O,.. ). This might take some time. Perhaps not much point in keeping 600 Irish stuck in the Desert ( AZ ) during the Holidays while all this goes on. " Peter Clark: @chipmonk You may have put your finger on it. And the issue remains that the longer Leixlip is only running a 65-nm process and does not get P1272 the more chance senior Intel management has to change their mind. That said Intel Ireland has won a number of manufacturing excellence awards within Intel and did management to beat out Intel Israel for the chance to run P1272. So probably Leixlip deserves its "chance to shine." ----------------------------------- If it is true that Intel shifting from CPUs to SoCs, that would explain the delay and give further evidence of imminent deal with AAPL? This shift also means that Intel is planning a big move into the mobile market (phones and tablets) and could explain why P. O is stepping down. They need someone fresh who can deal with this new direction. eetimesDOTcom/electronics-news/4403409/Ireland-still-set-for-FinFETs--says-Intel-exec</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1355522964387</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:09:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355523031791-92</Id><Title>More evidence of imminent AAPL/INTC deal?</Title><Msg>Read Peter Clarke of EE Times regarding FAB 24 and 14nm introduction. I find the comment section extremely interesting: ----------------------------------- Chipmonk: "There seems to be a shift at Intel from CPUs for PCs to SoCs for Mobiles. 14 nm process may have to be reoptimized for SoCs ( analog, I/O,.. ). This might take some time. Perhaps not much point in keeping 600 Irish stuck in the Desert ( AZ ) during the Holidays while all this goes on. " Peter Clark: @chipmonk You may have put your finger on it. And the issue remains that the longer Leixlip is only running a 65-nm process and does not get P1272 the more chance senior Intel management has to change their mind. That said Intel Ireland has won a number of manufacturing excellence awards within Intel and did management to beat out Intel Israel for the chance to run P1272. So probably Leixlip deserves its "chance to shine." ----------------------------------- If it is true that Intel shifting from CPUs to SoCs, that would explain the delay and give further evidence of imminent deal with AAPL? This shift also means that Intel is planning a big move into the mobile market (phones and tablets) and could explain why P. O is stepping down. They need someone fresh who can deal with this new direction. eetimesDOTc o m/electronics-news/4403409/Ireland-still-set-for-FinFETs--says-Intel-exec</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1355523031791</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:10:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355523063434-93</Id><Title>More evidence of APPL/INTC deal?</Title><Msg>Read Peter Clarke of EE Times regarding FAB 24 and 14nm introduction. I find the comment section extremely interesting: ----------------------------------- Chipmonk: "There seems to be a shift at Intel from CPUs for PCs to SoCs for Mobiles. 14 nm process may have to be reoptimized for SoCs ( analog, I/O,.. ). This might take some time. Perhaps not much point in keeping 600 Irish stuck in the Desert ( AZ ) during the Holidays while all this goes on. " Peter Clark: @chipmonk You may have put your finger on it. And the issue remains that the longer Leixlip is only running a 65-nm process and does not get P1272 the more chance senior Intel management has to change their mind. That said Intel Ireland has won a number of manufacturing excellence awards within Intel and did management to beat out Intel Israel for the chance to run P1272. So probably Leixlip deserves its "chance to shine." ----------------------------------- If it is true that Intel shifting from CPUs to SoCs, that would explain the delay and give further evidence of imminent deal with AAPL? This shift also means that Intel is planning a big move into the mobile market (phones and tablets) and could explain why P. O is stepping down. They need someone fresh who can deal with this new direction.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1355523063434</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:11:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355523270824-94</Id><Title>More evidence of imminent APPL/INTC deal?</Title><Msg>Read Peter Clarke of EE Times regarding FAB 24 and 14nm introduction. I find the comment section extremely interesting: ---------------------------------- Chipmonk: "There seems to be a shift at Intel from CPUs for PCs to SoCs for Mobiles. 14 nm process may have to be reoptimized for SoCs ( analog, I/O,.. ). This might take some time. Perhaps not much point in keeping 600 Irish stuck in the Desert ( AZ ) during the Holidays while all this goes on. " Peter Clark: chipmonk, You may have put your finger on it. And the issue remains that the longer Leixlip is only running a 65-nm process and does not get P1272 the more chance senior Intel management has to change their mind. That said Intel Ireland has won a number of manufacturing excellence awards within Intel and did management to beat out Intel Israel for the chance to run P1272. So probably Leixlip deserves its "chance to shine." ----------------------------------- If it is true that Intel shifting from CPUs to SoCs, that would explain the delay and give further evidence of imminent deal with AAPL? This shift also means that Intel is planning a big move into the mobile market (phones and tablets) and could explain why P. O is stepping down. They need someone fresh who can deal with this new direction. eetimesDOTcom/electronics-news/4403409/Ireland-still-set-for-FinFETs--says-Intel-exec</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1355523270824</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:14:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355523313497-95</Id><Title>More evidence of imminent APPL/INTC deal?</Title><Msg>Read Peter Clarke of EE Times regarding FAB 24 and 14nm introduction. I find the comment section extremely interesting: ---------------------------------- Chipmonk: "There seems to be a shift at Intel from CPUs for PCs to SoCs for Mobiles. 14 nm process may have to be reoptimized for SoCs ( analog, I/O,.. ). This might take some time. Perhaps not much point in keeping 600 Irish stuck in the Desert ( AZ ) during the Holidays while all this goes on. " Peter Clark: chipmonk, You may have put your finger on it. And the issue remains that the longer Leixlip is only running a 65-nm process and does not get P1272 the more chance senior Intel management has to change their mind. That said Intel Ireland has won a number of manufacturing excellence awards within Intel and did management to beat out Intel Israel for the chance to run P1272. So probably Leixlip deserves its "chance to shine." ----------------------------------- If it is true that Intel shifting from CPUs to SoCs, that would explain the delay and give further evidence of imminent deal with AAPL? This shift also means that Intel is planning a big move into the mobile market (phones and tablets) and could explain why P. O is stepping down. They need someone fresh who can deal with this new direction.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1355523313497</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:15:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355523416081-96</Id><Title>More evidence of deal coming?</Title><Msg>Read Peter Clarke of EE Times regarding FAB 24 and 14nm introduction. I find the comment section extremely interesting: [ Chipmonk: "There seems to be a shift at Intel from CPUs for PCs to SoCs for Mobiles. 14 nm process may have to be reoptimized for SoCs ( analog, I/O,.. ). This might take some time. Perhaps not much point in keeping 600 Irish stuck in the Desert ( AZ ) during the Holidays while all this goes on. " Peter Clark: chipmonk, You may have put your finger on it. And the issue remains that the longer Leixlip is only running a 65-nm process and does not get P1272 the more chance senior Intel management has to change their mind. That said Intel Ireland has won a number of manufacturing excellence awards within Intel and did management to beat out Intel Israel for the chance to run P1272. So probably Leixlip deserves its "chance to shine." ] If it is true that Intel shifting from CPUs to SoCs, that would explain the delay and give further evidence of imminent deal with AAPL? This shift also means that Intel is planning a big move into the mobile market (phones and tablets) and could explain why P. O is stepping down. They need someone fresh who can deal with this new direction. eetimesDOTcom/electronics-news/4403409/Ireland-still-set-for-FinFETs--says-Intel-exec</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1355523416081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:16:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355523456976-97</Id><Title>Interesting read</Title><Msg>Read Peter Clarke of EE Times regarding FAB 24 and 14nm introduction. I find the comment section extremely interesting: ---------------------------------- chipmonk: "There seems to be a shift at Intel from CPUs for PCs to SoCs for Mobiles. 14 nm process may have to be reoptimized for SoCs ( analog, I/O,.. ). This might take some time. Perhaps not much point in keeping 600 Irish stuck in the Desert ( AZ ) during the Holidays while all this goes on. " Peter Clark: chipmonk, You may have put your finger on it. And the issue remains that the longer Leixlip is only running a 65-nm process and does not get P1272 the more chance senior Intel management has to change their mind. That said Intel Ireland has won a number of manufacturing excellence awards within Intel and did management to beat out Intel Israel for the chance to run P1272. So probably Leixlip deserves its "chance to shine." ----------------------------------- If it is true that Intel shifting from CPUs to SoCs, that would explain the delay and give further evidence of imminent deal with AAPL? This shift also means that Intel is planning a big move into the mobile market (phones and tablets) and could explain why P. O is stepping down. They need someone fresh who can deal with this new direction.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1355523456976</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:17:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355523489182-98</Id><Topic><Title>20 dead kids: Thank you GOP!</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1355520131118</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:22:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>flumoxed...you are not only out of line but a jerk to boot. it didn't take long for an idiot like you to say something this stupid!</Msg><Username>kjmpk24</Username><Timestamp>1355523489182</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:18:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355523550254-99</Id><Title>more evidence?</Title><Msg>Read Peter Clarke of EE Times regarding FAB 24 and 14nm introduction. I find the comment section extremely interesting: ---------------------------------- Chipmonk: "There seems to be a shift at Intel from CPUs for PCs to SoCs for Mobiles. 14 nm process may have to be reoptimized for SoCs ( analog, I/O,.. ). This might take some time. Perhaps not much point in keeping 600 Irish stuck in the Desert ( AZ ) during the Holidays while all this goes on. " Peter Clark: chipmonk, You may have put your finger on it. And the issue remains that the longer Leixlip is only running a 65-nm process and does not get P1272 the more chance senior Intel management has to change their mind. That said Intel Ireland has won a number of manufacturing excellence awards within Intel and did management to beat out Intel Israel for the chance to run P1272. So probably Leixlip deserves its "chance to shine." ----------------------------------- If it is true that Intel shifting from CPUs to SoCs, that would explain the delay and give further evidence of imminent deal with AAPL? This shift also means that Intel is planning a big move into the mobile market (phones and tablets) and could explain why P. O is stepping down. They need someone fresh who can deal with this new direction. eetimesDOTcom/electronics-news/4403409/Ireland-still-set-for-FinFETs--says-Intel-exec</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1355523550254</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:19:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355523600451-100</Id><Title>more evidence?</Title><Msg>Read Peter Clarke of EE Times regarding FAB 24 and 14nm introduction. I find the comment section extremely interesting: ---------------------------------- Chipmonk: "There seems to be a shift at Intel from CPUs for PCs to SoCs for Mobiles. 14 nm process may have to be reoptimized for SoCs ( analog, I/O,.. ). This might take some time. Perhaps not much point in keeping 600 Irish stuck in the Desert ( AZ ) during the Holidays while all this goes on. " Peter Clark: chipmonk, You may have put your finger on it. And the issue remains that the longer Leixlip is only running a 65-nm process and does not get P1272 the more chance senior Intel management has to change their mind. That said Intel Ireland has won a number of manufacturing excellence awards within Intel and did management to beat out Intel Israel for the chance to run P1272. So probably Leixlip deserves its "chance to shine." ----------------------------------- If it is true that Intel shifting from CPUs to SoCs, that would explain the delay and give further evidence of imminent deal with AAPL? This shift also means that Intel is planning a big move into the mobile market (phones and tablets) and could explain why Paul is stepping down. They need someone fresh who can deal with this new direction.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1355523600451</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:20:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355524676158-101</Id><Topic><Title>Just found this. Doesn't this alone solidify Intel's future in Mobile???????</Title><Username>jakk_wagon</Username><Timestamp>1355517714692</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:41:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>guardianDOTcoDOTuk/technology/2012/dec/14/iphone-5-launch-china-smartphones 'Apple shares fell 3.9% in early trading on Friday after the launch of its iPhone 5 received a frosty reception in China, and two analysts cut shipment forecasts. It was a dramatic contrast to the scenes at the iPhone 4S launch in January when an angry crowd pelted the store in Beijing with eggs and fights broke out between would-be touts aiming to resell new phones. On Friday there was one person waiting at Apple's store in Shanghai's financial district before it opened. But the lack of queues may have been down to the online lottery scheme introduced by Apple to prevent a repeat of January's chaos. It used the same method earlier this month for the launch of its iPad mini, and enforced a two-per-person limit. Although the company has 300,000 pre-orders for the phone from China Unicom, one of the three big mobile providers, and will also sell it through mobile company China Telecom, it has still not sealed a deal with China Mobile, the biggest player with 703 million users of whom 79m are 3G (ie smartphone) users. Despite years of talks, the two sides have disagreed on revenue splits and business models. That means Apple is unable to increase its shipments there as fast as the market for smartphones is growing. There are already 290 million smartphone users and that is forecast to double in the next 12 months. Nokia's shares rose earlier this month after it tied up a deal to sell its Lumia smartphones through China Mobile. Even so, China Mobile announced in March that an estimated 15 million people use iPhones on its network, despite their being incompatible with its data services. More broadly, But Apple and Nokia are struggling in the face of competition from devices powered by versions of Google's Android software: those make up roughly 90% of the smartphones sold in China, although many connect to Chinese services rather than Google's. "In absolute terms, this (iPhone 5) launch will certainly result in strong sales for Apple in China. However, in relative terms, I don't believe it will move the needle enough in market share," Shiv Putcha, a Mumbai-based analyst at Ovum, a global technology consultant, told the Reuters news agency. Peter Misek of Jefferies said he was lowering his iPhone shipment estimates for the first quarter of 2013 by 5m to 48m, on the basis that the company was cutting orders to suppliers. He also cut his estimates for the company's gross margins by 2 percentage points, to 40%. He said it was unclear how much the snowy weather and requirement to pre-order were factors in the small queues. That seems to have helped push down Apple shares, which have lost a quarter of their value since hitting an all-time high of $705.07 on 21 September. Steven Milunovich, an analyst at UBS Research, told clients in a research note that he didn't expect the iPhone 5 to do as well in China as the iPhone 4S. The brokerage cuts its price target for Apple's stock to $700, substantially down from $780, on the expectation of lower iPhone and iPad shipments in the first quarter of 2013.'</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1355524676158</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:37:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355525471404-102</Id><Title>Ireland still set for FinFETs, says Intel exec</Title><Msg>Interesting read, especially the comments section between chipmonk and author eetimesDOTcom/electronics-news/4403409/Ireland-still-set-for-FinFETs--says-Intel-exec</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1355525471404</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:51:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355525784759-103</Id><Topic><Title>Ireland still set for FinFETs, says Intel exec</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1355525471404</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:51:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>comment at bottom...chipmonk sugggests that Intel sent 600 staffs from FAB 24 site home early because, they are shifting from CPU to SoCs, so it takes time to make this change. If this shift is true, then it would indicate that Intel will be pushing hard into mobile and perhaps this is why Paul Otellini stepped down. Intel needed someone new for this change in direction. Shift to SoCs could give further evidence of imminent deal with Apple?</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1355525784759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:56:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355527561303-104</Id><Title>Intel on Track to Expand Addressable Markets for Atom Processors.</Title><Msg>When will Valleyview SoC be available? Anybody know? Article from xbitlabs says late 2013; is it true?</Msg><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1355527561303</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:26:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355527919600-105</Id><Topic><Title>20 dead kids: Thank you GOP!</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1355520131118</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:22:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The party of death, obstruction, neanderthalic beliefs. Time to get rid of guns. Time to get rid of the GOP." Dems created 'Fast &amp; Furious'</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1355527919600</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:31:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355530681726-106</Id><Topic><Title>20 dead kids: Thank you GOP!</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1355520131118</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:22:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What kind of terrible human being starts a thread like this one. I just lost my appetite for dinner, and I'm Liberal. Do us all a favor and move to another country, Flumoxed.</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1355530681726</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 19:18:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355531660163-107</Id><Title>Is qualcomm's loss Intel's gain?</Title><Msg>From pcmag Can Intel Save Apple From the LTE Mess? By Sascha Segan September 15, 2012 11:30am EST Can Intel Fix Apple's Problems? Fortunately, across the street from the iPhone event, I saw a potential solution. Intel's Developer Forum was going on just across the street from Apple this week. Up on the second floor, the company was showing off the four relatively lackluster Intel phones so far, as well as a modem technology that could really change things. Intel's XMM6260 modem, which has been in the market for a while, uses a single power amplifier for multiple bands, and it can be extended in software to support as many bands as necessary. It doesn't support LTE or CDMA, which is part of why we haven't seen it in many U.S. products. But the point here, an Intel engineer told me, is that the company will be able to put an unlimited number of bands on a single LTE modem, possibly as soon as late next year. Intel's modems will be able to mate with processors from Samsung, Nvidia, TI, and others. Apple used its modems up until 2010, when it switched over to Qualcomm in part to get Verizon and Sprint compatibility. Modems are only half of the solution, though. Dermot O'Shea, co-founder of antenna firm Taoglas, said antenna design gets difficult when you're covering such a wide range of frequencies. Active antennas for smartphones, which have just started to hit the market this year, can adapt to different bands without being huge, although they add to the cost and complexity of smartphones. We're likely to see more of them next year. Between active antennas and multi-frequency power amplifiers, it looks like phone makers are starting to get their hands around the riot of LTE frequencies; they're just not there yet. Maybe we'll see them in the iPhone 7.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1355531660163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 19:34:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355532418449-108</Id><Topic><Title>How big of an oppurtunity is China Mobile for Intel?</Title><Username>jakk_wagon</Username><Timestamp>1355517467238</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:37:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Intel Brand is VERY BIG and very well known in China. Intel will get a lot of sales of its smartphones from motorola, just based on Intel inside.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1355532418449</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 19:46:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355534131212-109</Id><Topic><Title>Is qualcomm's loss Intel's gain?</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1355531660163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 19:34:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Shah a few days ago said the razor i WAS NOT more efficient than the razor m because the razor m had LTE and that caused it to use 25%to 30% more energy. http://blogs.barrons.com/techtraderdaily/2012/12/12/intels-medfield-has-no-edge-on-qcom-snapdragon-says-nomura/?mod=yahoobarrons What would happen if Intel's LTE is more efficient? Could Intel become a LTE modem fab for Apple and others, thus taking qualcomm's business?</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1355534131212</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:15:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355547254983-110</Id><Topic><Title>20 dead kids: Thank you GOP!</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1355520131118</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:22:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said, flumoxed. Seems a lot of people, some self professed "liberals" can't connect the dots. No one ever loved the bearer of the truth. Fact is, GOP = Koch Brothers = NRA = end of days. Some of you get it. And those who don't will find out the hard way.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1355547254983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 23:54:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>