<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353733204850-1</Id><Topic><Title>Broadwell in 2013 now that 14nm roadmap bumped forward?</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1353728775300</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 22:46:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Q4 2013. 1 year from Clover Trail release, unless Intel can bring it forward...</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1353733204850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 00:00:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353735518429-2</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith said last earnings that all focus was on 14nm</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1353706995341</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 16:43:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"All this 14nm hype is not going to work" [Singh, you are just like the fat lady. When you come out we know any downturn is done. The reality of 14nm volume production is totally going to work. It's game over for ARMH...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353735518429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 00:38:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353737675039-3</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith said last earnings that all focus was on 14nm</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1353706995341</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 16:43:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow are you in for a rude awakening. ARMH is just getting started in servers.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1353737675039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 01:14:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353737992995-4</Id><Title>Freescale's i.MX 7 canned as firm refocuses - ARM canabilizes ARM</Title><Msg>weeks after TI announcement.... 11/21/2012 8:14 AM EST The mobile and tablet market can be a money maker for some and a deal breaker for others. For Freescale, it seems to be the latter, with the firm choosing to discontinue its high end i.MX 7 mobile processor line, in favor of lower powered chips aimed more at the internet of things. Rumors have been swirling for weeks that Freescale would be scaling back on its i.MX roadmap, though the firm itself vehemently denies planning to get rid of the product line entirely. Communications Manager for Freescale Rob Hately said the confusion may have resulted from the fact that Freescale recently announced several changes after an “extensive, strategic review of the business,” but said the firm continued to support the i.MX line and see “strong acceptance for this portfolio.” Hately said Freescale was simply sharpening its focus, but admitted that “unfortunately, there are some employees who will be affected by these changes.” Freescale itself is not disclosing the specific numbers of layoffs, but a recent report in Israel’s Globes business news said the firm’s local division was laying off “100-200 of its 500 employees.” Globes said those layoffs were centered around two departments - the DSP department and the multimedia chip department (which includes i.MX 7). Sources have also claimed AMD has hired the team Freescale let go in Israel to take a run at the high end SoC app processor market, though those rumors have yet to be confirmed. Freescale’s strategy shift does make sense. In an industry already over served with strong ARM processors, there is precious little market to go around for more than just the top players. Even Texas Instruments recently admitted this by realigning its OMAP strategy, in similar fashion to Freescale. Development costs for the high end chips run into the tens of millions of dollars for players serving the high end market, which has led to a situation where only around four top players can compete and justify the cost, Nvidia, Qualcomm, Samsung and Apple have managed to carve out the most lucrative niche of the high powered mobile processing market, leaving smaller players to fight over the scraps. Freescale also continues to be massively burdened by debt, much of it incurred from the high R&amp;D costs it has needed to try to keep pace. The firm’s new strategy seems to be a more viable one, honing in on the higher volume, lower price chip market for the Internet of Things. “Freescale’s i.MX 6 product line has been extremely strong, with a broad array of design wins secured with leading manufacturers across a range of application spaces,” Hately said. In short, sometimes you have to amputate a finger to save the hand. Mobile. It’s a great market to be in if you’re a winner, a terrible market to be in if you’re not.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1353737992995</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 01:19:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353738580362-5</Id><Title>Apple will be fighting Samsung and Intel</Title><Msg>Samsung (DRAM, NAND) is not really intrested in "destroying" PC bizz Market analyst says Samsung's use of its own ICs in a Galaxy S3 smartphone iteration could be the start of a platform war with Apple. Galaxy S3 teardown reveals Samsung LTE modem Peter Clarke 11/23/2012 6:09 AM EST LONDON – A deconstruction of the Galaxy S3 E210s mobile phone from Samsung by ABI Research has revealed that Samsung has dropped an externally supplied modem in favor of an internally developed one. The market research firm speculates that Samsung's use of its own ICs in the Galaxy S3 phone iteration could be the start of a platform war with Apple as Samsung and Apple both attempt to take control of more of the underlying semiconductor technology that drives their equipment businesses. ABI said that while Samsung has been known for its high-end application processors under the Exynos brand it has typically used modem ICs supplied by companies such as Qualcomm, Intel, Broadcom, ST-Ericsson and Via Telecom. "Mid last year it [Samsung] introduced a CDMA/LTE phone that was produced with a Via Telecom CDMA modem, a Samsung LTE modem, and a Samsung application processor," said James Mielke, vice president of engineering at ABI Research, in a statement. "What makes this variant of the Galaxy SIII so interesting is the modem is a single-chip HSPA/LTE integrated circuit designed and manufactured by Samsung." In an earlier teardown of the Galaxy S3 smartphone UBM Techinsights showed Intel had taken advantage of its recently purchased Infineon wireless business unit with design wins for the X-GOLD 626 PMB9811 baseband processor and the PMB5712 GSM/CDMA RF transceiver. Intel is not mentioned in account of the ABI teardown. In the third quarter of 2012 the Samsung Galaxy S3 was the leading smartphone in the market selling 18 million units to grab about 10.7 percent of the smartphone market of 167.8 million units, according to another market research firm Strategy Analytics. The same firm said Apple sold 16.2 million iPhone 4S handsets and 6.0 million iPhone 5 handsets. As Samsung's position in the smartphone market rises its growing reliance on captive ICs could be a major concern for the likes of Qualcomm and Via Telecom, according to ABI Research. Samsung also fabricates the A6 and A6X ARM-based processors for Apple. Samsung's recent purchase of the CSR handset IC business also indicates a move towards a platform battle between Samsung and Apple, said ABI.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1353738580362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 01:29:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353740177696-6</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Guys, this is a $2K+ chip and can be viewed as an ultra extreme edition chip." [How many units does ARM have to sell to make $2k in revenue? About a billion?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353740177696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 01:56:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353742061307-7</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe they will sell for more later or not. The first bunch sold for 400 $ each. Remember this is a market that other players are coming at fast and furious. Maybe they sold them cheap to get a foot in the door.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1353742061307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 02:27:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353744094690-8</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From PC Mag on November 12: Intel introduced two Xeon Phi product lines at SC'12. The Xeon Phi 5110P (pictured below), priced at $2,649, is already shipping to partners and will be officially released on Jan. 28. The Xeon Phi 3100 product family will be made available in the first half of 2013 carrying prices under $2,000 per coprocessor, Intel said.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353744094690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:01:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353744139678-9</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From NY Times on November 12: Ninety-one percent of all newly listed systems on the recently announced Top500 list of the world’s most powerful supercomputers are powered by Intel processors. Intel Xeon Phi coprocessors are already featured in 7 systems including the most power-efficient supercomputer on the list –“Beacon” delivering 2.44 GFlops/Watt.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353744139678</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:02:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353744350190-10</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"maybe they will sell for more later or not. The first bunch sold for 400 $ each. Remember this is a market that other players are coming at fast and furious. Maybe they sold them cheap to get a foot in the door." *** "Thus, the nature of the $400 price can be traced with the fact that TACC took most of pre-production Xeon Phi boards." [Nice try at distortion. Skumbag...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353744350190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:05:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353749549791-11</Id><Topic><Title>Broadwell in 2013 now that 14nm roadmap bumped forward?</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1353728775300</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 22:46:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>14nm in 2014, but 22nm "Silvermont" should put an end to the ARM v.s. Intel debate, and 14nm will be the node at which Intel dominates the non-Apple/Samsung markets in tablets and smartphones. ----- If you are assuming that Silvermont will have a compelling performance advantage over ARM and thus drive into the broader tablet/phone SoC market then you'll be disappointed. You can compare Clovertrail to the A15 over at geekbench. Clovertrail has a slight clock advantage and 2 extra threads yet the A15 has roughly the same integer performance and double the floating point performance. I've seen claims of 50/60% performance increased for Silvermont over Clovertrail, which will be split between IPC, memory IO, clock boost and 4 real threads V 2 real/2 hyper. By the time Silvermont is in the market, quad A15's will be common place. Its Airmont@14nm that things get really interesting:)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1353749549791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 04:32:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353763273275-12</Id><Topic><Title>Freescale's i.MX 7 canned as firm refocuses - ARM canabilizes ARM</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1353737992995</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 01:19:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is also very much aware of the Internet of Things and that's just one more chip revenue stream that Intel will be carving out.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353763273275</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 08:21:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353769158527-13</Id><Title>When will Avoton enter service?</Title><Msg>From the q3 conference call...... Jim Covello - Goldman Sachs So my follow-up question stands specific to the Data Center Group, some of the ARM based server players are arguing that they can now address a significant part of the workload from the Google’s and the Amazon’s and Facebook’s data centers. Is that some competitive dynamic that you're seeing in that area or do you think that ARM still isn't competitive in that realm? Paul Otellini - President &amp; CEO They need to add features sets like 64-bits and ECC and RAS features to be particularly in those environments to be considered, so that maybe a roadmap planning opportunity that they are pushing but the products that are being shipped today certainly don't have those feature sets. You can look at some of the workloads, things like Hadoop, Jim that would be conducive to let me say in a ray of micro servers, and those can easily be run on Atom; we've got our second generation of the Atom micro server chips out now, the first one is on 32-nanometers. Now we’re now sampling the 22-nanometer one and what we’ve decided that we are just going to push Atom as hard as possible in this space and have it be a better offering for our customers than having to switch all their software and worry about all the reliability features.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1353769158527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 09:59:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353770588425-14</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, the 2000 $ price is a distortion of the market price. Also these just replace selling a bunch of x86 processors no ? Anyway a lot of other players in and going in the space so margins and prices are going to be less than the good old days. Interesting that Intel sold them for a fifth of 2000 $.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1353770588425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:23:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353770614158-15</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will hit $29 in 6 months</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353653014738</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 01:43:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems like a great buying opportunity. I think these levels $19 - 20 will be gone for some time . Good, solid , safe buy here.</Msg><Username>carolganz2</Username><Timestamp>1353770614158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:23:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353770735176-16</Id><Topic><Title>Freescale's i.MX 7 canned as firm refocuses - ARM canabilizes ARM</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1353737992995</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 01:19:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel should plug the entire lower-end with its own SoCs for IoT/embedded, in-vehicle, low-end and high-end smartphones, tablets, etc. and provide cut-throat competition to each of the ARM vendors. Marketing case studies have demonstrated for decades that you don't allow competition to enter any part of the market (typically, they enter the low-end). Toyota and Honda (and other manufacturers) have repeatedly demonstrated how new manufacturers can enter the low-end of the chain and creep up with higher-end and luxury products....and destroy or vastly diminish the incumbents. It is high time Intel started shipping something that would be competitive to ARM at each level of the SoC/CPU chain. And it doesn't matter if the lower-end products do not provide the same level of margins as the higher end SoCs/CPUs. This should be done purely for strategic, corporate, and brand perception...and there is considerable value in all that.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1353770735176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:25:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353770806219-17</Id><Topic><Title>Broadwell in 2013 now that 14nm roadmap bumped forward?</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1353728775300</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 22:46:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi Ashraf, I enjoy reading your posts on SA. What do you make of the digitimes report that Intel is rushing development of next gen mobile chips? I don't remember where I read that this meant 14nm was being pushed forward, I just now read the digitimes article which does not mention this at all.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1353770806219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:26:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353771131751-18</Id><Title>Windows 8 is most likely the best Windows ever as work as PC+Tablet, Mouse/Keyboard+touch</Title><Msg>Windows RT in no man's land Soon Ultrabooks, will be affordable and with Convertibles &amp; 5" smartphones to cannibalize Tablets</Msg><Username>khaledmrd</Username><Timestamp>1353771131751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:32:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353771931068-19</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 is most likely the best Windows ever as work as PC+Tablet, Mouse/Keyboard+touch</Title><Username>khaledmrd</Username><Timestamp>1353771131751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:32:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>win8 is so good MSFT canned the lead developer Steve Sinofsky several days ago. I run it and it is fast, but not what it should have been, it makes you go all over the desktop to get things done. It is selling slower than MSFT internal goal. They did no favors for Intel with this system, none at all.</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1353771931068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:45:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353772841155-20</Id><Title>You never know everything</Title><Msg>Conventional wisdom, never trust spam. But there are exceptions. Decide if this is one of them. SAPX news - Tomasina, the production of the newest film to be distributed by its subsidiary Seven Arts Filmed Entertainment Louisiana (SAFELA) in New Orleans. 10,000 shares may prove to be a reasonable amount to risk for a possible 2013 turnaround. Having checked a 2 year chart, there have been two very significant upside trends that carried this post-reverse split stock to the reverse-split adjusted prices of $300+ and $400+. A 10K block can be owned for under $400 based on Friday's close.</Msg><Username>stole_some_shares</Username><Timestamp>1353772841155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:00:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353773240965-21</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 is most likely the best Windows ever as work as PC+Tablet, Mouse/Keyboard+touch</Title><Username>khaledmrd</Username><Timestamp>1353771131751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:32:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I upgraded to WIN8 10 days ago. and it's great - 10 sec boot time. You can work in classic mode if you don't have touch screen and it's similar to WIN7 or with one click you can be in touch screen app mode. Basically you are productive in what ever environment you are unlike the ipad that is used for games and emails mainly</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1353773240965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:07:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353773643850-22</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend typically doubles every seven years or so</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353717122778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:32:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So will this hold true if they don't keep growing revenue? They can't pay a 2.00 dividend 7 years from now if they are still making around $ 2.00 a share, can they? How does this work? Will they eventually not be able to raise the dividend at some point and when will that point occur?</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1353773643850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:14:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353773889398-23</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 is most likely the best Windows ever as work as PC+Tablet, Mouse/Keyboard+touch</Title><Username>khaledmrd</Username><Timestamp>1353771131751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:32:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it is faster, but they removed the START button, so you need another parties software to get that back !! Otherwise you have to make extra clicks and find the correct area to shut it down. It could have been better and has made a lot of people say "Really ?" Android is much better on the touchscreen and so is Apple, use them all.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1353773889398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:18:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353775201115-24</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend typically doubles every seven years or so</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353717122778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:32:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would hope that EPS continues to grow from here.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1353775201115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:40:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353776448041-25</Id><Title>With Intel pushing Avoton hard, will it arrive in Q1 2013?</Title><Msg>From the q3 conference call...... Jim Covello - Goldman Sachs So my follow-up question stands specific to the Data Center Group, some of the ARM based server players are arguing that they can now address a significant part of the workload from the Google’s and the Amazon’s and Facebook’s data centers. Is that some competitive dynamic that you're seeing in that area or do you think that ARM still isn't competitive in that realm? Paul Otellini - President &amp; CEO They need to add features sets like 64-bits and ECC and RAS features to be particularly in those environments to be considered, so that maybe a roadmap planning opportunity that they are pushing but the products that are being shipped today certainly don't have those feature sets. You can look at some of the workloads, things like Hadoop, Jim that would be conducive to let me say in a ray of micro servers, and those can easily be run on Atom; we've got our second generation of the Atom micro server chips out now, the first one is on 32-nanometers. Now we’re now sampling the 22-nanometer one and what we’ve decided that we are just going to push Atom as hard as possible in this space and have it be a better offering for our customers than having to switch all their software and worry about all the reliability features.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1353776448041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:00:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353777794153-26</Id><Title>WALLIS PUMPED INTEL FROM $29 DOWN TO $19!</Title><Msg>GOOD JOB, Walldolt! TOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353777794153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:23:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353778873752-27</Id><Topic><Title>WALLIS PUMPED INTEL FROM $29 DOWN TO $19!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353777794153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:23:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sold Intel for Cisco at 20...........and pumped it here.......then Intel went up 50 percent to 29 and Cisco down over 50 percent to 13. Those are FACTS and the posts and stock prices show it. You can try try try as hard as you can................................but you can't escape the fact that you are a massive hypocrite and utter loser. Tooofunnny!</Msg><Username>lucy_cisco</Username><Timestamp>1353778873752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:41:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353779019475-28</Id><Topic><Title>I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1293550442000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-12-28 10:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Worst stock trade ever. Cisco at 20 for Intel at 20 as Cisco then dropped to 13 and Intel ran up to 29. LOL! How's that Cisco Dividend workin' out for ya?</Msg><Username>lucy_cisco</Username><Timestamp>1353779019475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:43:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353779283234-29</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend typically doubles every seven years or so</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353717122778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:32:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Going down for now. $40 in 3 years. Big building + new products = Future of tech. Fyi INFN !! See you on the bottom.</Msg><Username>arthor_arthor</Username><Timestamp>1353779283234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:48:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353781710779-30</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend typically doubles every seven years or so</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353717122778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:32:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dividend is 40% of Intel cash flow. So, if there is negative growth, something has to give. My guess is they will cut R&amp;D &amp; workforce before they touch the dividend. Cutting dividend is a big no-no.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1353781710779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:28:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353782101064-31</Id><Topic><Title>Broadwell in 2013 now that 14nm roadmap bumped forward?</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1353728775300</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 22:46:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to not know what you are talking about. Clovertrail is dual core with two threads per core. A15 is quad.core. Silvermont will be quad core no hyperthreading and it will be out of order execution. Just the quad core aspect will boost the integer by 60% and double foating poin. The out of order will also substantially boost performance along with other archetectuaral changes. The 22nm will allow for higher clock speeds if desired. It will kill A15 on performance and power. Intel will have 14 nm in 2014 and ARM will have no substantial improvemnet. It is over when Intel adds LTE. Except for a few possible big cell phone manufacturers, everyone will convert product line to Intel reference designs..</Msg><Username>redwood1205</Username><Timestamp>1353782101064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:35:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353782507534-32</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend typically doubles every seven years or so</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353717122778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:32:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The responses sure don't make me confident that Intel's Dividend will double in 7 years, haha. I'm now wondering if it will grow at all from here.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1353782507534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:41:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353782679270-33</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend typically doubles every seven years or so</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353717122778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:32:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cutting R&amp;D unlikely. Stopping buybacks is very likely.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1353782679270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:44:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353782800821-34</Id><Topic><Title>WALLIS PUMPED INTEL FROM $29 DOWN TO $19!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353777794153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:23:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lucy/tooofunny/whateveralias he's using today finds meaning in life by the fact that he's found a loser on the internet that's as big a loser as he is. That's the only thing that gets him through each day. True, and woefully sad story.</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1353782800821</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:46:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353783884268-35</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will hit $29 in 6 months</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353653014738</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 01:43:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unlikely. Stock will piddle around in the $18 - $22 range over the next 6 months.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1353783884268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:04:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353784982384-36</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will hit $29 in 6 months</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353653014738</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 01:43:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel makes some great stuff, but so do a lot of other folks. It is facing competition like it has never seen and the market is changing in ways that are hard to imagine.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1353784982384</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:23:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353785278087-37</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will hit $29 in 6 months</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353653014738</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 01:43:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gartner, a leading information technology research company, announced in October that worldwide PC shipments totaled 87.5 million units in the third quarter, representing an 8.3 percent decline from a year earlier. IDC, another research firm, also showed that shipments fell more than 8 percent in the most recent three month period. It is the largest drop for the industry since at least 2001. Taking into account the components of our CHEAT SHEET investing framework, we find that Intel is a STAY AWAY until shares can stabilize and the company increases its exposure to non-PC products.</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1353785278087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:27:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353785541505-38</Id><Title>New CEO Rumors</Title><Msg>I heard that they are trying to entice ex INTC senior VP , Pat Gelsinger back from his CEO role @ VM Ware...that's a very credible rumor. Pat has very broad INTC experience and was well liked, but he was never going to get the CEO role if he stayed there.</Msg><Username>kev.roberts</Username><Timestamp>1353785541505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:32:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353785759155-39</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 is most likely the best Windows ever as work as PC+Tablet, Mouse/Keyboard+touch</Title><Username>khaledmrd</Username><Timestamp>1353771131751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:32:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i am using it for a week, no need for a start menu, you just switch beteen the tiles - start screen and the desktop with a touch of the button you could put all control panel as tiles, enjoy, use mouse or touch all work simultiniuosly it is like Mac+ipad+live informatiove tiles</Msg><Username>khaledmrd</Username><Timestamp>1353785759155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:35:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353785770280-40</Id><Topic><Title>WALLIS PUMPED INTEL FROM $29 DOWN TO $19!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353777794153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:23:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What happened to adults talking in a civil manner without all the personal attacks ? Can we just attack Intel's late progress in mobile and how they let ARMH have a 90 percent market share ?</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1353785770280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:36:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353785959522-41</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 is most likely the best Windows ever as work as PC+Tablet, Mouse/Keyboard+touch</Title><Username>khaledmrd</Username><Timestamp>1353771131751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:32:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah....but now you have to do extra clicks. You could do same thing in less steps before. Progress denied.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1353785959522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:39:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353786036840-42</Id><Topic><Title>New CEO Rumors</Title><Username>kev.roberts</Username><Timestamp>1353785541505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:32:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but, he could get it if he left ??</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1353786036840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:40:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353786615501-43</Id><Topic><Title>You never know everything</Title><Username>stole_some_shares</Username><Timestamp>1353772841155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:00:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>haven't Intel owners been through enough without this trash ?</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1353786615501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:50:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353786633483-44</Id><Topic><Title>New CEO Rumors</Title><Username>kev.roberts</Username><Timestamp>1353785541505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:32:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>of course he could - Pat now has a couple of years of CEO experience under his belt at a ~$40Bn Company with ~14k employees. INTC need a turnaround , they need a CEO how ideally knows the culture - Pat is 50 , he ticks all the right boxes except he a wasnt a mobile guy when he was there.</Msg><Username>kev.roberts</Username><Timestamp>1353786633483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:50:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353787199013-45</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 is most likely the best Windows ever as work as PC+Tablet, Mouse/Keyboard+touch</Title><Username>khaledmrd</Username><Timestamp>1353771131751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:32:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah....but now you have to do extra clicks. ---------------------------------------------------------- No extra clicks - for example , if previously you had a shortcut on your desktop to office word also in WIN8 you can create a shortcut on your desktop for office word. And you can stay in the classic mode as usual . only now you have the option to use touch in case you have touch screen.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1353787199013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:59:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353787310802-46</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend typically doubles every seven years or so</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353717122778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:32:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are going into the dip between old and new tech that will run the world for next 10 years. They will not stop R&amp;D or buyback. Buyback at low pps makes for a good buy and paying div's on low earnings drives the price lower for even better buyback pricing. They know that they have the future locked and the div is safe even on declining earnings.</Msg><Username>arthor_arthor</Username><Timestamp>1353787310802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:01:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353787663348-47</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'I agree, the 2000 $ price is a distortion of the market price. Anyway a lot of other players in and going in the space so margins and prices are going to be less than the good old days.' Don't be absurd, $2K is cheap for a 1 TFlops accelerator if you bothered to look at Nvidia and AMD's prices. 'Also these just replace selling a bunch of x86 processors no ?' More likely to be replacing a gpu accelerator card. You will still need the original x86 processor for Scalar FP as all these accelerator cards specialty is Vector FP. In fact I can see the Workstation market receiving a good long term boost where the Phi replaces a high end gpu as a computational accelerator. Imagine selling a high end Haswell and Xeon Phi on each Workstation, it will be an awesome all x86 combination for the engineering professional. 'Interesting that Intel sold them for a fifth of 2000 $.' I impressed they actually got much for them on the TACC supercomputer. Time after time you hear about the chips going into supercomputers being given away free just for the PR value.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353787663348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:07:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353787884271-48</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 is most likely the best Windows ever as work as PC+Tablet, Mouse/Keyboard+touch</Title><Username>khaledmrd</Username><Timestamp>1353771131751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:32:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>win7 shutdown: go to startbutton and click, go to shutdown choice and click. done. NO searching for corner areas to pop up charms bars. win8 shutdown: go to corner, hope charms bar get activated, find power choice and click, click again to shutdown. There are workarounds and 3rd party shells, just sayin they could have done better. It is quick booter though and IE10 is nice. The Apple and Android tile system is better and more intuitive, shocker. Remember when Intel was even bad mouthing Win8 ? That was strange.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1353787884271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:11:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353788699146-49</Id><Title>Intel working on 48 core chip for Smartphones and Tablets</Title><Msg>Bet against Intel R &amp; D and Manufacturing over the long run??? D.U.M.B. Intel working on 48-core chip for smartphones, tablets A smartphone with 48 cores could change our concept of what it is and what it does By Sharon Gaudin October 30, 2012 06:00 AM Computerworld - Intel researchers are working on a 48-core processor for smartphones and tablets, but it could be five to 10 years before it hits the market. "If we're going to have this technology in five to 10 years, we could finally do things that take way too much processing power today," said Patrick Moorhead, an analyst with Moor Insights and Strategy. "This could really open up our concept of what is a computer... The phone would be smart enough to not just be a computer but it could be my computer." Enric Herrero, a research scientist at Intel Labs in Barcelona, said the lab is working on finding new ways to use and manage many cores in mobile devices. Today, some small mobile devices use multi-core chips. However, those multi-cores might be dual- or quad-core CPUs working with a few GPUs. Having a 48-core chip in a small mobile device would open up a whole new world of possibilities. Emerging tech Intel researchers work on new way to display, share images Intel working on 48-core chip for smartphones, tablets Intel readies for programmable smart cars Autonomous cars will arrive within 10 years, Intel CTO says NASA's Curiosity makes first drive at Bradbury Landing 'Talking' smart cars begin year-long test aimed at accident reduction Harvard stores 70 billion books using DNA IBM claims spintronics memory breakthrough Watch out Google: Apple gets patent for wearable device Google Glass launches new age of personal computing More: Emerging Tech page At this point, researchers are working to see how to best use so many cores for one device. "Typically a processor with one core would do jobs one after another," Herrero told Computerworld. "With multiple cores, they can divide the work among them." He explained that with many cores, someone could, for instance, be encrypting an email while also working on other power-intensive apps at the same time. It could be done today, but the operations might drag because they'd have to share resources. Tanausu Ramirez, another Intel research scientist working on the 48-core chip, said that if someone was, for example, watching a high-definition video, a 48-core chip would be able to use different cores to decode different video frames at the same time, giving the user a more seamless video experience. Ramirez also said that instead of one core working at near top capacity and using a lot of energy, many cores could run in parallel on different projects and use less energy. "The chip also can take the energy and split it up and distribute it between different applications," he added. Justin Rattner, Intel's CTO, told Computerworld that a 48-core chip for small mobile devices could hit the market "much sooner" than the researchers' 10-year prediction. "I think the desire to move to more natural interfaces to make the interaction much more human-like is really going to drive the computational requirements," he said. "Having large numbers of cores to generate very high performance levels is the most energy efficient way to deliver those performance levels." Rattner said functions such as speech recognition and augmented reality will push the need for more computational power. "If it's doing speech recognition or computer vision... that's very computational intensive," he added. "It's just not practical to just take sound and pictures and send it up to the cloud and expect that some server is going to perform those tasks. So a lot of that will be pushed out to the client devices." Rob Enderle, an analyst with the Enderle Group, said being able to have different device functions, as well as apps all running on their own cores would be a great advance. You move to a massive multi-core model and you'll have massive multi-tasking," he said. "You can have some big apps running and nothing will steal performance from each other. You get that huge range of performance across the spectrum and you get the benefits of things you can't even run on a PC now. Plus you'd get a potential low battery drain." Enderle also pointed out that running so many cores would enable the phone to scale way down when it's just sitting in someone's purse or pocket and then scale well up when it's being used. One issue the researchers are running into, however, is making sure there is software for small mobile devices that can take advantage of so many cores. "This is a more limiting factor," said Herrero. "We need to modify how operating systems and apps are developed, making them far more parallel. Now, [having] cores doesn't matter if I can't take advantage of it." Enderle agreed that it's going to be critical to make sure the software is keeping up with the advances in the hardware. "There aren't many apps now to light up eight cores, let alone lighting up 48," he said. "Even on the PC now, it's really unusual in an 8-core machine to light up more than six cores. Writing for massive multi-core... Well, we haven't even really started to do that yet." Moorhead, though, has faith that by the time the hardware is ready, the software will be, too. "Five to 10 years is somewhat of an eternity in technology time," he said. "If we're going to have this technology in five to 10 years, [the smartphone] won't have just one camera. It would have two to three cameras that are always on. It could build a three-dimensional map of what it's looking at and do object recognition. You could finally do things that take way too much processing power today." Zeus Kerravala, an analyst with ZK Research, said there simply is never a shortage of demand for processing power. And in 10 years, when a 48-core smartphone or tablet chip could be ready for market, devices likely will be in need of that boost. "I suspect in 10 years, the devices we carry will be continually using any information available to them to make better decisions," said Kerravala. "So a continuous stream of location, identity, ad-driven information and presence status will all continually be calculated to help us do the stuff we do better and faster. And I would think you'll need multi-core to do that in 10 years. Whether it's 36 or 48, who knows." Moorhead also projected that with that many cores and smarter software, our smartphones could someday be our main computers. "My one compute device is in my hand and when I walk into my office, it automatically and wireless connects to my 30-inch display," he explained. "I have touch, a keybord, a mouse and voice to interact with it... It changes the whole concept of what it is and what it can do."</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353788699146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:24:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353788883860-50</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't be absurd, $2K is cheap for a 1 TFlops accelerator if you bothered to look at Nvidia and AMD's prices. They supposedly get 3100 $ for a unit, Intel now is saying they will get 2000$. I see a trend here ...</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1353788883860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:28:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353789162539-51</Id><Title>LESS THAN ONE DOLLAR SEPARATES CSCO FROM INTC</Title><Msg>Looks like CSCO will eclipse INTC very sooooooooon. Swap out of INTC for CSCO now and pocket a buck a share!!! TOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353789162539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:32:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353789825078-52</Id><Title>Intel 48 Core Smartphone Supercomputer</Title><Msg>Intel’s 48-core supercomputing smartphone CPU is less than a decade away By Grant Brunner on October 31, 2012 at 1:44 pm Cell phones are rapidly growing ever more dominant as computing devices. Not only are they becoming vital parts of our everyday lives in the English-speaking western world, but also in developing nations around the globe. It’s clear that dumbphones are on the way out, and our current smartphones will look like dunces in the next decade. Intel has been working hard on an impressive 48-core mobile processor for a few years now, and it’s looking like it could be ready for prime time in a mere five-to-ten years — and inside of our mobile devices, not just servers. Computerworld has a fantastic story with direct quotes from Intel upper management and the actual research scientists working on making small and power efficient parallel computing a reality. Justin Rattner, Intel’s CTO, says “It’s just not practical to just take sound and pictures and send it up to the cloud and expect that some server is going to perform those tasks. So a lot of that will be pushed out to the client devices.” That really stands out as an ambitious goal that is worthy of consideration. Siri Immediately, services like Siri and mobile speech-to-text come to mind. Right now, every command you give to Siri involves a lot of interaction with Apple’s servers. Your voice command is sent via the network, processed by Apple’s servers, and returned to your device as text. Then, the servers grind and grind in hopes of understanding what you meant. If all of the planets are aligned properly, your command is executed a few seconds later. Sometimes, for whatever reason, Siri just spins and spins until it times out. If your iPhone had a true large-scale parallel processor, instead of few measly cores between the CPU and GPU, all of this could be done locally on your device. It wouldn’t even matter if you had cell service or not. Most impressively, these chips being developed are very power efficient. Back in 2009, Intel claimed that the processor uses about the same amount of power as two lightbulbs. In 2010, it was made public that the cores were clocked between 1.66GHz and 1.83Ghz, and are roughly on par with Atom-class chips. The individual cores themselves don’t have to be super computers, but the technology that allows them to work together in concert is what has massive potential. Sadly, Intel hasn’t given us a name or a specific architecture, but it would be fairly safe to assume that we’re talking about a mobile variant of the Xeon Phi/Knights Corner MIC. Encoding massive videos, always-on augmented reality, and large-scale multitasking are just some of the benefits we’ll see from technology like this 48-core parallel processor. Not only will our phones be able to power our traditional computing needs, but also tasks we’re not even dreaming about yet. In combination with an increased number of sensors and receivers in your device and the world around you, your phone could be controlling your HVAC, automatic shifting in your car, and creating a realistic 3D replica of your current environment all while you’re looking at cat pictures or composing an email. A decade is a long way away, and this is all still very much in development. This is a big shift in technology that could make our devices even more integrated in our lives, and we need to be on the look out for applications for this awesome amount of power we’ll have. It would seem that Sebastian’s dream of smartphones replacing every other PC form factor might be rather accurate.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353789825078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:43:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353789908515-53</Id><Topic><Title>LESS THAN ONE DOLLAR SEPARATES CSCO FROM INTC</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353789162539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:32:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're either 13 years old or 60 years old and have the mental capacity of a 13 year old. Either way, feel sorry for you man.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353789908515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:45:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353790506880-54</Id><Title>FORBES COMMENT</Title><Msg>Otellini’s achievements haven’t done much for investors. Over the last ten years, Intel stock has risen about 1% a year – that’s better than Microsoft’s slight decline, but it pales in comparison to chip stocks that are hitched to the mobile market.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353790506880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:55:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353792117623-55</Id><Topic><Title>Intel 48 Core Smartphone Supercomputer</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353789825078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:43:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The cloud really isn't a very smart idea. It harkens back to the days of big central computing in business, IBM 360's and ceramic drives and punch card typists. The US serverplex is scarfing down some 80 Gwatts (80 nuclear power plants) worth of juice. And, really, who wants every bit of your personal existence on a server somewhere? Well, big brother's already here, but it will get worse. That Siri example in the above article shows the ultimate stupidity of it all and why 80 Gwatts are going up in smoke. With 48 fast smart parallel cores in my smartphone I am Mr. distributed computing. My smartphone plugs into a dock where my keyboard and 3 monitors and all the classic paraphenalia are so I can do some real computing. Yes, then the PC is dead, and INTC will have killed it (tho I'll still need a screen and a keyboard for travel. That;s it. the ultima-book, just the super multicore smartphone that transforms out of a PC form factor.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353792117623</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:21:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353792250630-56</Id><Topic><Title>FORBES COMMENT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353790506880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:55:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not his fault, he grew revenues over 50% during the same period, it's idiot Wall Street talking heads who keep repeating how PCs are dying or dead, yet somehow Intel keeps growing. One bad quarter and the stock falls to less than half the P/E of the S &amp; P. This is unsustainable, buy and cover now boys.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1353792250630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:24:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353792291679-57</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend typically doubles every seven years or so</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353717122778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:32:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look for INTC dividend to quadruple in next 7 years. Once it breaksout and people will see ARMH in smouldering rubble behind, a pile of short's corpses, and INTC doing $200 bills and smokin' at $250/share.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353792291679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:24:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353792311016-58</Id><Topic><Title>FORBES COMMENT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353790506880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:55:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking only for myself, I have done well for mine and me, buying at close to the right time. I bought a lot in the last two weeks.</Msg><Username>schwartzhymie</Username><Timestamp>1353792311016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:25:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353792387753-59</Id><Title>I would appreciate opinions about the piece on p.16 of the Current:</Title><Msg>Barrons.</Msg><Username>schwartzhymie</Username><Timestamp>1353792387753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:26:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353792777663-60</Id><Title>RECENT RATINGS CHANGES</Title><Msg>Sep 25, 2012 Caris &amp; Company Downgrade Buy Above Average Sep 17, 2012 RBC Capital Mkts Downgrade Outperform Sector Perform Sep 16, 2012 Longbow Downgrade Buy Neutral Jan 19, 2012 Kaufman Bros Downgrade Buy Hold Jan 5, 2012 Sterne Agee Downgrade Buy Neutral Jan 2, 2012 Barclays Capital Downgrade</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353792777663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:32:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353792908852-61</Id><Topic><Title>I would appreciate opinions about the piece on p.16 of the Current:</Title><Username>schwartzhymie</Username><Timestamp>1353792387753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:26:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That rag still in business, that is amazing.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1353792908852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:35:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353793132775-62</Id><Topic><Title>FORBES COMMENT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353790506880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:55:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>might just be because pcs and servers as we think of them are going away. Free market is tough love.</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1353793132775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:38:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353793354137-63</Id><Title>What do Forbes, Barrons and Tooofunnny have in common?</Title><Msg>They are all worthless and say whatever outrageous thing they can in order to get attention.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353793354137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:42:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353793406050-64</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The $400 pricing was determined by the NSF $27.5 million award from NSF, targeting the creation of 10 PFLOPS machine. Intel shipped the early boards but hit the price target to allow TACC to hit their target. The 2.6PF TOP500 submission had a partial build out of the 10petaflop final systems. There were less than 2,000 of the PHI boards installed. "In order to reach the 10 PFLOPS target, the computational power in Stampede is split in two parts. First 2 PFLOPS come from 6,400 nodes carrying two Intel Xeon E5 Series processors (Sandy Bridge-EP) and 32GB of DDR3 memory. Second part of the system comes from the countless MIC cards (now known as Xeon Phi), which were supposed to deliver 8 PFLOPS. As it turns out, the "countless MIC coprocessors" fell a bit short of the target, with TACC expecting more than 7PFLOPS, but less than 8PFLOPS. Third part of the Stampede system is 16 memory nodes with 1TB of DDR3 memory and two NVIDIA Tesla K20 boards. Furthermore, Tesla K20 boards are located in 128 out of 6,400 compute nodes for computational purposes, bringing the total number of K20 boards to 144. This number pales in comparison to around 6,500 Xeon Phi boards. The ScaleMP virtual SMP solution is used in order to create a shared memory environment, spanning across all 16TB of memory. This part will mostly target "big data". While the prices of Intel Xeon E5 systems and the Tesla boards were delivered at special but still realistic pricing, we were quite surprised to learn that the computing center only paid around $400 per Xeon Phi board. Given that competing Tesla K20 boards retail for $3199 (available in December), this can be viewed from a price dumping perspective. Bear in mind the TACC only had $2.4 million for Xeon Phi boards, and reaching 8PFLOPS e.g. 7+ PFLOPS requires around 6,000-7,000 boards. At $400, it is quite a steal. "</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1353793406050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:43:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353794763493-65</Id><Topic><Title>What do Forbes, Barrons and Tooofunnny have in common?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353793354137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:42:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They all predicted Romney to win and are run by idiots.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1353794763493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 17:06:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353796949392-66</Id><Topic><Title>I would appreciate opinions about the piece on p.16 of the Current:</Title><Username>schwartzhymie</Username><Timestamp>1353792387753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:26:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are referring to the Ray Tiernan editorial. I subscribe to the online version and it does not have page numbers. Intel: Building on Otellini's Legacy Can the legendary chip giant rethink and retool itself for a smartphone and tablet universe? My comments ... Tiernan gives Paul Otellini credit for trigate, 56% revenue increase, 46% operating revenue increase and the agressive fab build out. I just hope that Paul's decision was not driven by health problems (him or close family member). He is well respected by the BOD and those he works with. Tiernan suggests that Intel's ability to shop out is fab capacity "may" be the driver to Intel success in 2013. Intel will not fab for Samsung since they have their own. Apple is the other big player and Apple will use their size to drive vendor prices down. Apple will have to offer a bigger advantage than just filling Intel fabs. Just consuming fab capacity at low margins will not benefit Intel. "Whether Intel's stock can rally in 2013 may hinge upon how successfully it deploys its manufacturing expertise to make chips for other companies, rather than on how well it pushes its own chips. That's a big shift in strategy—and one fraught with challenges—but it looks increasingly necessary. " Tiernan suggests that Intel will have to sell lots of smartphone and tablet chips for "tens of dollars" to make up for the "lost revenue" for the Intel $100 average CPU revenue. This is very complex. People are trying to determine future Intel revenue and operating profits based on what they think is going to happen to the mix of computing devices from servers through smartphones. What are the volumes of each segment, how does each segment affect other segments and what CPU is going to be in the device. IMO, Haswell is the first Intel designed from bottom up for power efficiency to take advantage of the 22nm trigate process. The Haswell core in part or whole across the device spectrum. CES 2013 will show what that means. Surprises. ""If the PC market falters at all, it's hard to see how you can replace that revenue—it's just not there with smartphones," says the Linley Group's principal analyst, Linley Gwennap. "</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1353796949392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 17:42:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353797056798-67</Id><Topic><Title>I would appreciate opinions about the piece on p.16 of the Current:</Title><Username>schwartzhymie</Username><Timestamp>1353792387753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:26:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are referring to the Ray Tiernan editorial. I subscribe to the online version and it does not have page numbers. Intel: Building on Otellini's Legacy Can the legendary chip giant rethink and retool itself for a smartphone and tablet universe? My comments ... Tiernan gives Paul Otellini credit for trigate, 56% revenue increase, 46% operating revenue increase and the agressive fab build out. I just hope that Paul's decision was not driven by health problems (him or close family member). He is well respected by the BOD and those he works with. Tiernan suggests that Intel's ability to shop out is fab capacity "may" be the driver to Intel success in 2013. Intel will not fab for Samsung since they have their own. Apple is the other big player and Apple will use their size to drive vendor prices down. Apple will have to offer a bigger advantage than just filling Intel fabs. Just consuming fab capacity at low margins will not benefit Intel. "Whether Intel's stock can rally in 2013 may hinge upon how successfully it deploys its manufacturing expertise to make chips for other companies, rather than on how well it pushes its own chips. That's a big shift in strategy—and one fraught with challenges—but it looks increasingly necessary. " Tiernan suggests that Intel will have to sell lots of smartphone and tablet chips for "tens of dollars" to make up for the "lost revenue" for the Intel $100 average CPU revenue. This is very complex. People are trying to determine future Intel revenue and operating profits based on what they think is going to happen to the mix of computing devices from servers through smartphones. What are the volumes of each segment, how does each segment affect other segments and what CPU is going to be in the device. IMO, Haswell is the first Intel designed from bottom up for power efficiency to take advantage of the 22nm trigate process. The Haswell core in part or whole across the device spectrum. CES 2013 will show what that means. Surprises. ""If the PC market falters at all, it's hard to see how you can replace that revenue—it's just not there with smartphones," says the Linley Group's principal analyst, Linley Gwennap. "</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1353797056798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 17:44:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353797131340-68</Id><Topic><Title>I would appreciate opinions about the piece on p.16 of the Current:</Title><Username>schwartzhymie</Username><Timestamp>1353792387753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:26:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are referring to the Ray Tiernan editorial. I subscribe to the online version and it does not have page numbers. Intel: Building on Otellini's Legacy Can the legendary chip giant rethink and retool itself for a smartphone and tablet universe? My comments ... Tiernan gives Paul Otellini credit for trigate, 56% revenue increase, 46% operating revenue increase and the agressive fab build out. I just hope that Paul's decision was not driven by health problems (him or close family member). He is well respected by the BOD and those he works with. Tiernan suggests that Intel's ability to shop out is fab capacity "may" be the driver to Intel success in 2013. Intel will not fab for Samsung since they have their own. Apple is the other big player and Apple will use their size to drive vendor prices down. Apple will have to offer a bigger advantage than just filling Intel fabs. Just consuming fab capacity at low margins will not benefit Intel. "Whether Intel's stock can rally in 2013 may hinge upon how successfully it deploys its manufacturing expertise to make chips for other companies, rather than on how well it pushes its own chips. That's a big shift in strategy—and one fraught with challenges—but it looks increasingly necessary. " Tiernan suggests that Intel will have to sell lots of smartphone and tablet chips for "tens of dollars" to make up for the "lost revenue" for the Intel $100 average CPU revenue. This is very complex. People are trying to determine future Intel revenue and operating profits based on what they think is going to happen to the mix of computing devices from servers through smartphones. What are the volumes of each segment, how does each segment affect other segments and what CPU is going to be in the device. IMO, Haswell is the first Intel designed from bottom up for power efficiency to take advantage of the 22nm trigate process. The Haswell core in part or whole across the device spectrum. CES 2013 will show what that means. Surprises. ""If the PC market falters at all, it's hard to see how you can replace that revenue—it's just not there with smartphones," says the Linley Group's principal analyst, Linley Gwennap. "</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1353797131340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 17:45:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353798106164-69</Id><Topic><Title>I would appreciate opinions about the piece on p.16 of the Current:</Title><Username>schwartzhymie</Username><Timestamp>1353792387753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:26:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A well respected independent analyst once said that he wouldn't even use Barrons as fish wrap...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353798106164</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 18:01:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353798268670-70</Id><Topic><Title>FORBES COMMENT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353790506880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:55:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's not his fault, he grew revenues over 50% during the same period, it's idiot Wall Street talking heads who keep repeating how PCs are dying or dead, yet somehow Intel keeps growing. One bad quarter and the stock falls to less than half the P/E of the S &amp; P. " [Indeed. Chump Street promised us a an $8 billion revenue miss last earnings and there wasn't any. Where's the miss, chumps???]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353798268670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 18:04:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353798293700-71</Id><Topic><Title>I would appreciate opinions about the piece on p.16 of the Current:</Title><Username>schwartzhymie</Username><Timestamp>1353792387753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:26:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are referring to the Ray Tiernan editorial. I subscribe to the online version and it does not have page numbers. Intel: Building on Otellini's Legacy Can the legendary chip giant rethink and retool itself for a smartphone and tablet universe? My comments ... Tiernan gives Paul Otellini credit for trigate, 56% revenue increase, 46% operating revenue increase and the agressive fab build out. I just hope that Paul's decision was not driven by health problems (him or close family member). He is well respected by the BOD and those he works with. Tiernan suggests that Intel's ability to shop out is fab capacity "may" be the driver to Intel success in 2013. Intel will not fab for Samsung since they have their own. Apple is the other big player and Apple will use their size to drive vendor prices down. Apple will have to offer a bigger advantage than just filling Intel fabs. Just consuming fab capacity at low margins will not benefit Intel. "Whether Intel's stock can rally in 2013 may hinge upon how successfully it deploys its manufacturing expertise to make chips for other companies, rather than on how well it pushes its own chips. That's a big shift in strategy—and one fraught with challenges—but it looks increasingly necessary. " Tiernan suggests that Intel will have to sell lots of smartphone and tablet chips for "tens of dollars" to make up for the "lost revenue" for the Intel $100 average CPU revenue. This is very complex. People are trying to determine future Intel revenue and operating profits based on what they think is going to happen to the mix of computing devices from servers through smartphones. What are the volumes of each segment, how does each segment affect other segments and what CPU is going to be in the device. IMO, Haswell is the first Intel designed from bottom up for power efficiency to take advantage of the 22nm trigate process. The Haswell core in part or whole across the device spectrum. CES 2013 will show what that means. Surprises. ""If the PC market falters at all, it's hard to see how you can replace that revenue—it's just not there with smartphones," says the Linley Group's principal analyst, Linley Gwennap. "</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1353798293700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 18:04:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353799245945-72</Id><Title>AMD Cannot Survive The Graphics War Like This</Title><Msg>Things do not look good for AMD in the discrete graphics space. It lost the X86 CPU space by falling too far behind, and it is now about to lose the graphics war for good if it does not continue to innovate where it counts by developing products that carry high margins and sell well. Shifting focus to ARM-servers with SeaMicro fabric all sound great... until you realize that this will likely be a super cutthroat, low-margin business that will be swallowed whole with Intel's upcoming "Avoton" server SoC. Built with Intels' very own, license-fee-free, 22nm cores.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353799245945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 18:20:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353799383912-73</Id><Title>Intel planning 22nm quad-core Atom with DirectX 11 GPU for tablets</Title><Msg>Intel’s Atom processor line became popular powering netbooks and nettops. The lower power use, cheap price, and good-enough performance worked for small laptops and web-browsing PCs. More recently Intel has started pushing the Atom as a smartphone and tablet processor using 32nm Cloverview SoC. Mobile is certainly a key focus going forward for Intel, and 32nm Atom chips are the solution for the near future. However, leaked slides have revealed what Intel has planned for Atom when we reach 2014. Clover Trail and the Cloverview SoC will be replaced with Bay Trail-T and the Valleyview-T SoC for the tablet market, which brings with it a number of improvements. We’ll see Atom chips move from 32nm to 22nm, the clock speed will be increased to 2.1GHz (it will range from 1.6-2.1GHz), and instead of dual core we’ll get quad core processing supported by 2MB L2 cache. Memory support is also being upgraded from DDR2 to DDR3. Intel believes a Valleyview-T Atom will use half the power of Clover Trail while offering up to a 60% performance gain in terms of pure processing power. We also can’t forget the on-board GPU, which will be upgraded to support DirectX 11 (HD 4000) and boasts a 3x performance gain over Clover Trail’s DirectX 9 GPU.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353799383912</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 18:23:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353800410350-74</Id><Title>Haswell 20 percent of market in 2H 13</Title><Msg>Intel has accelerated its plans to transition to the next generation 22nm Haswell core. The current plans for desktop CPU transition state that in the first half of 2013 less than five percent of all Intel desktop processors shipped will have a Haswell core. Sandy Bridge E will remain fixed at its one to two percent, as it always was, while Ivy Bridge is destined to take some 75 percent of total processor shipped. [Consider the amazing Ivy Bridge-22nm ramp in comparison to the TSMC struggle with its 28nm ramp. And what will TSMC experience when moving to the significantly more complex and demanding 20nm ramp problems?] Ivy Bridge will decline to 60 to 65 percent while Haswell could occupy a massive 20 percent of market share in the second half of 2013. This is definitely a smaller ramp than with Ivy Bridge, that started with some less than five percent in first half of 2012, only to grow to 35 percent in second half of 2012. Haswell won’t be able to grow that fast, and we remain curious about the cause. It might be that Haswell will have an aggressive role on the mobile front as with its 10 W TDP possibility it might end up quite attractive.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353800410350</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 18:40:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353801832909-75</Id><Title>This is my rig: ExtremeTech’s Sal Cangeloso</Title><Msg>Having built my previous desktop in October 2008, I’ve been long overdue for a new system. I had delayed the build a number of times, usually waiting for the next cool thing in the pipeline — an occupational hazard when you look at technology news all day long — but with the release of Intel’s Ivy Bridge and Microsoft’s Windows 8, it was clearly time to put together my next PC. This article will walk through the parts I bought and include some explanation of why I chose each of them. It’s not a buying guide or set of recommendations; it’s just a list of the components that made sense for me. When choosing components my main considerations were stability, quietness, performance, and cost, in that order. The build wasn’t particularly price sensitive. My goal was to keep the investment at a reasonable level, while bearing in mind that my previous rig lasted four years so any expenses should amortize over time and seem relatively minor. CPU: Intel Core i7-3770S When I decided to put together a new machine, it was pretty obvious to me that I was going to go with the latest (but not quite the greatest) from Intel. I considered the Core i7-3770K, which has been the most popular choice for enthusiasts as it’s unlocked and top-shelf, and the $200 Core i5-3570K which offers a lot of bang-for-the-buck. Ultimately I went with the 3770S, the 65W TDP version of the quad-core 3770 chip. It runs at lower base frequency (3.1GHz) than the K but has the same Turbo frequency (3.9GHz). I don’t suspect that the power consumption or heat production differences will be significant but I won’t ever be overclocking the system so I saved some money (OK, just $15, but still) and kept heat and power usage to a minimum. I’ve been using stock CPU coolers for some time, based on the assumption that the amount of engineering Intel can put into them is much more than what a smaller firm could afford. Even so, after getting numerous recommendations about it, I went with the Noctua NH-D14. This gargantuan set of fins and heatpipes has 120mm and 140mm fans but remains near-silent. While it’s certainly impressive, the cooler’s huge size means working inside the case can be a pain once it’s in place, so make sure your memory and any hard-to-reach connectors are installed before the D14 (unless you have exceedingly tiny hands). I doubt I’ll go with something this large again, but I couldn’t resist the lure of customizable quiet cooling. Motherboard: Intel DZ77BH-55K Today, many aspects of PC building are easier than ever. Unfortunately this doesn’t hold true for picking a motherboard. Every manufacturer releases a number of models running a given chipset, and the differences between them are nearly impossible to discern. This is especially true when the model names are nonsensical jumbles like “AGA-Z77X-UD3H.” (End of rant.) With maximum stability in mind I went with an Intel motherboard, as I usually do. The DZ77BH-55K offers up the features I wanted and, at $170, the price isn’t that bad either. Intel’s Z77 motherboards range from $120 to $270, so this one seemed like a great choice (though the top model does have Intel’s trademark skull logo on it). Graphics: EVGA GeForce GTX 660 While I was tempted to invest heavily in graphics, I realized that for some time now I’ve been getting by on an ATI Radeon 4670, so ultimately I didn’t feel compelled to overspend. I wanted to go with Nvidia, despite generally being an ATI/AMD guy, and the GTX 660 has gotten high marks across the board. The GTX 660 fit my price range and came with a sweet $20 mail-in-rebate. I had been recommended against getting anything that used the stock Nvidia cooler, so the EVGA fit the bill. Storage: Intel 335 SSD 240GB I’ve been using Intel SSDs for a couple of years now and I’ve had good results. With the 20nm 335 just released, this seemed like a perfect option — the performance difference between this and the next model up (the 500 series) seems negligible for my needs and a price of $199 for a 240GB SSD put it well under the $1/GB mark. For a moment I was skeptical about the drive due to a possible longevity issue identified by Anandtech, but it seemed unlikely that it identified a systemic problem so I bought it anyway. A recent post confirmed that this was a non-issue (at least for me). For mass storage I took the 2TB Western Digital drive that I was running in an external eSATA enclosure and put it in the case. It’s nothing special, but I need something large for my photos and video. I also dropped an old Kingston 60GB SSDNow in the case, which I’ll use for extra storage and doing thankless tasks like housing virtual machines and acting as a scratch disk.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353801832909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 19:03:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353801840462-76</Id><Title>Servers are Intel's sweetspot and guess what?</Title><Msg>Forget the guesswork by analysts..........the head man at VMware said ARM servers aren't happening anytime soon and a big dog at AMD, ARM's new server partner, admitted that by the time the servers come out it could be futile........their own partner doubted ARM servers! Ouch.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353801840462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 19:04:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353803426776-77</Id><Topic><Title>New CEO Rumors</Title><Username>kev.roberts</Username><Timestamp>1353785541505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:32:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gelsinger was responsible for the Larabee fiasco... GPU architecture was too complex...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353803426776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 19:30:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353803564116-78</Id><Topic><Title>What do Forbes, Barrons and Tooofunnny have in common?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353793354137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:42:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>toofunny aka loosy is a mentally disturbed Fing idiot.,Barrons/Forbes use the same sheap sensationalistic tactics to get people to read their rags</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1353803564116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 19:32:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353803792757-79</Id><Topic><Title>I would appreciate opinions about the piece on p.16 of the Current:</Title><Username>schwartzhymie</Username><Timestamp>1353792387753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:26:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The article is just a summary of Ray Tiernan's blog articles. Ray is pushing the Intel foundry idea. I have not seen Tiernan articulate any depth of thinking on Intel outside splicing together the opinions of those analysts that he aggregates in his blog.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1353803792757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 19:36:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353804034542-80</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Cannot Survive The Graphics War Like This</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353799245945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 18:20:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why is it a given intel is going to swallow up this whole business ? and if it is super cut throat low margin it might not be so tasty. The chip wars have players like never before.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1353804034542</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 19:40:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353804511116-81</Id><Topic><Title>New CEO Rumors</Title><Username>kev.roberts</Username><Timestamp>1353785541505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:32:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>once u leave....u can't comeback....all good parents know this.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1353804511116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 19:48:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353806033022-82</Id><Title>Hayyyyyyy Getanid61</Title><Msg>VMware CEO said ARM servers aren't happening anytime soon AND ARM's new server partner, AMD, went so far as to say that by the time ARM servers do come out, it might be a waste of time. Giggles.</Msg><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1353806033022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 20:13:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353806386345-83</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"$2K+ chip" "a million chips a year and Intel has made another $2bn revenue !" "Nvidia has shown that there is a viable market for these devices " NVidia has 90% market share, and I've read $400M/yr for their Tesla sales... So NVidia sells far more Quadros than Teslas... Quadros can also be used as a GPGPU....</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353806386345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 20:19:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353806596512-84</Id><Topic><Title>New CEO Rumors</Title><Username>kev.roberts</Username><Timestamp>1353785541505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:32:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel's Phi is a direct outcome of Intel's work on Larabee so indeed that effort is contributing directly to Intel's HPC product mix today." Yes...but Gelsinger had NOTHING to do with it for the past few years as someone else fixed it...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353806596512</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 20:23:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353814323179-85</Id><Title>Is there anything more EVIL than Liberals?</Title><Msg>Mentally Disabled to Vote Friday, 23 Nov 2012 09:52 AM By David Horowitz I am incredibly steamed this Thanksgiving Holiday over what the Democrats are doing to my country. Everybody by now knows – or should know – how readily Democrats conduct election fraud, and how determined they are to defend it. James O’Keefe and others have taken videos of paid Democratic operatives encouraging citizens to vote twice. O’Keefe was even able to claim Attorney General Eric Holder’s own ballot at a district polling place by claiming to be him, and then to vote in his place. Democrats have promoted Motor Voter laws and same day registration, and month-long election days to help them mobilize the votes of people who are so unconnected to the political process and so uninterested in the country’s future, and perhaps so incompetent to understand what voting entails, that they require keepers to see that they get to the polls and then vote the “right” way. In the election that put Al Franken in the Senate by a few hundred votes, more than a thousand felons voted illegally because of the loose laws that govern the polling booth – laws the Democrats want to make more loose. It is in fact the number one civil rights issue of the NAACP this year to give felons the right to vote. So we know that Democrats have little respect for the election process, and we should assume will attempt to pursue their victories by any means necessary. But even knowing this, I was not prepared for a conversation I had at Thanksgiving dinner with my brother-in-law, Henry, who has lived most of his life in a home for the mentally disabled and although now in his 40s, has the intelligence level of a 6-year-old. “Obama saved me,” he said to me out of the blue. “What do you mean?” “I voted for him for president and now he’s saving me.” I was taken aback by these words, since Henry had no idea who Obama was, or what a president might be, and would be unable to fill out a registration form let alone get to the polling place by himself. So I asked him how he knew that and how he had registered and cast his vote. In halting, impeded speech he told me that the people who take care of him at the home filled out “the papers” to register him to vote, told him how Obama cared for him, even taught him the Obama chants, and then took him to the polling place to vote. They did the same for all of the mentally disabled patients in their care, approximately 60 in all. This is so appalling in its contempt for the voting process, which is the very foundation of our democracy, and in its cynical exploitation of my brother-in-law and the other patients in the home, many whose mental capacities are even more limited than Henry's. I am at a loss for words to express it. I hope poll-watching groups like “True the Vote” will comb the rolls of residents at other homes for the mentally disabled, and attempt to stop this particular abuse. I hope that people who care about our country will make electoral fraud a focus of their political efforts, and work to protect the integrity of the voting process.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353814323179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:32:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353814529541-86</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more EVIL than Liberals?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353814323179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:32:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure why I'm surprised at this disgusting behavior since more than 50 percent of the country is mentally ill.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353814529541</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:35:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353814998668-87</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more EVIL than Liberals?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353814323179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:32:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and, of course, republicans are above rapproach..lily white...as usual. DUHHH! Get an effin brain.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353814998668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:43:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353815020269-88</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more EVIL than Liberals?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353814323179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:32:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>takes one to know one.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353815020269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:43:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353815511153-89</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more EVIL than Liberals?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353814323179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:32:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libtards are satans decipiles!!!!!!</Msg><Username>nk499</Username><Timestamp>1353815511153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:51:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>