<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349928648751-1</Id><Topic><Title>Vice presidential debate up next, Romney says ‘I’m not going to raise taxes on anyone’</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1349915874825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This country will be a COMPLETE WRECK is this lazy bum gets 4 more years. It's certainly not Obama's fault that the US #$%$ away its manufacturing base pleasing WS _ Germany now exporter #2 - yeah right American Idiots poured $100 billion into F...Book - stupid is as stupid does</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1349928648751</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 00:10:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349931216504-2</Id><Title>How Romney plans to pay for his tax cut for the RICH</Title><Msg>Obama took $712 billion out of Medicare to pay for Obamacare. Romneyhood plans to use the $712 billion (after he kills Obamacare) to fund his tax cut plan which ,as Obama says, greatly favors the rich. So, Romney/Ryan want to use Medicare as a piggy bank too. At least under Obamanomics, somebody besides rich people get something for what they're stealing off of seniors. Both Obama or Romney want to use more medicare money for their stimulus programs and tax breaks, but, Obama wants to trash the rich fat cats at the same time. Romney, on the other hand, plans to trash Medicade, welfare, food stanps and student loans to balance the budget. Romney also wants to "broaden" the tax base, meaning reduce deductions which force more low income people into paying more taxes. Subtract the earned income tax credit, a Romney proposal, and poor W2 workers who used to get $400 will get $0. Capping the total deductions at $19,000 under Romney, forces millions of middle class families into paying Federal taxes who, because of their exemptions, paid no Federal tax. So, the millionaire and billionaire marginal rate on earned income goes from 35% to 25%, but, the lower middle class get to fund that tax break along with the seniors. Under Romney/Ryan nothing will change for current seniors, yea, right. He forgot to mention that increases in medicare will be limited to GDP growth + .5%, or 1.8% based on Q3 GDP. So, where does the difference between the 10% growh in medical costs and the 1.8% cap on Medicare come from? Yea, you guessed it, THE SENIORS. Obama, on the other hand, will take the increased cost out of the doctors and hospitals, who in turn, will take it out of Medicare patients. Face it seniors, you're getting it up the #$%$ by both partys.</Msg><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1349931216504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 00:53:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349933777594-3</Id><Topic><Title>How Romney plans to pay for his tax cut for the RICH</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1349931216504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 00:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are worse at political analysis than you are equities.</Msg><Username>dumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1349933777594</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 01:36:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349934323542-4</Id><Topic><Title>Reminds Me of People on this Board</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349568097571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:01:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If you piled up all the Demorats and Republicans exhibiting this behavior, the piles would be about equal." This is a real REPUBLICAN TOE TAPPER: Scott DesJarlais, Pro-Life Republican Congressman And Doctor, Pressured Mistress Patient To Get Abortion Posted: 10/10/2012 10:13 am EDT Huffington Post WASHINGTON -- A pro-life, family-values congressman who worked as a doctor before winning election as a Tea Party-backed Republican had an affair with a patient and later pressured her to get an abortion, according to a phone call transcript obtained by The Huffington Post. The congressman, Rep. Scott DesJarlais of Tennessee, was trying to save his marriage at the time, according to his remarks on the call, made in September of 2000. And, according to three independent sources familiar with the call and the recording, he made the tape himself. DesJarlais, who was provided a copy of the transcript by HuffPost, did not deny its contents, but in a statement released through his campaign characterized it as just another sordid detail dredged up by the opposition. "Desperate personal attacks do not solve our nation's problems, yet it appears my opponents are choosing to once again engage in the same gutter politics that CBS news called the dirtiest in the nation just 2 years ago."</Msg><Username>dumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1349934323542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 01:45:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349935959338-5</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think it's really important to decide whether design or fabrication will be the most important factor in Intel's success, but it has been a waste of time to discuss design, what with all the fanbois and quite a few others who considered ARM micro-architecture to be the greatest thing since sliced bread. I will happily leave that argument for you to make. Otellini himself felt that fabrication would be the distinguishing factor in the competition with ARM so at least I have one person on my side of the argument. Intel's tick-tock strategy is effective. While I rarely commented on the design side I never denigrated its importance to Intel's overall performance. My primary comment was that ARM's design would not be strong enough to preclude the need for them to keep pace with fabrication. I stand by that statement. I agree that it is not necessary to make things up, but just because the story itself is good enough doesn't mean the Wall Street cretins or the shills on this board will understand it or stop subverting it. Recent action is evidence enough of this. Given Wall Street's continuous effort to trap Intel in a trading range, I believe it is necessary for some of us to present the very many positives. If I err in this I'm sure you will correct me. I also may have confused you with the blackandblueredmonk. I can see why this might be considered horribly offensive. My apologies. At least I didn't confuse you with Lucy even when Lucy was pretending to be Vinnie Bag O Donuts, fixing computers in his garage and connecting iPads to corporate mainframes. What a joke. Well, Lucy is too busy expressing his incurable angst over getting fired from Intel. He is in too much emotional, whiny pain to discuss design or fabrication. I hope you survive the beatings you will get for appearing to agree with any of my statements or conclusions. If the Wall Street analysts weren't such a bunch of wimps they would prolly come over to your house. Saying Intel will reach $50 is considered blasphemy on Wall Street, you know...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349935959338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 02:12:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349945795652-6</Id><Title>80% success ratio in Trading the Emini S&amp;P market?</Title><Msg>Yes in fact there is a trading secret code in the Emini S&amp;P market that will bring you a success ratio of 80% in your trades! This is not a scam! This is a real deal. Just google "Emini S&amp;P Trading Secret" to learn more about this.</Msg><Username>joana1joana</Username><Timestamp>1349945795652</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 04:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349948365806-7</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>Stocks are at risk of breaking down. Although the S&amp;P 500 continued to hold its support near 1430, the DJIA broke its up trendline started in June on a closing basis today. In addition, the inability to bounce showed buying interest wasn't there. Stocks could continue this week's path of drifting lower. With that said, yesterday's overall action wasn't as bad as the triple digit decline in the DJIA would have suggested. Financials were the bright spots of this market. Keep your eyes on Friday's earnings report from JPM and WFC. They could make or break the overall market. have a nice day</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1349948365806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 05:39:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349950711361-8</Id><Topic><Title>Blueredmonk pumping TSMC 20nm OR TSMC HEAD MAN telling customers to "make other arrangements"</Title><Username>getsome_nads</Username><Timestamp>1349879655310</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:34:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who would you believe? An anonymous message board pumper OR the head man of the company that told ACTUAL customers to find better options than TSMC? lol. ----- :) All I did was post articles showing that TSMC claim to have 20nm volume up and running next year... Now will they have it up and running? No idea...</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1349950711361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 06:18:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349950869759-9</Id><Topic><Title>$19 next folks</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1349949041496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 05:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'll buy that</Msg><Username>wallstsx</Username><Timestamp>1349950869759</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 06:21:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349951258481-10</Id><Topic><Title>How Romney plans to pay for his tax cut for the RICH</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1349931216504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 00:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Marc. I watched the debate also, and I heard Romney say he would return the $712 billion to Medicare, not fund his tax plan as you say. Obama, to the contrary, just slipped the money out of Medicare without saying much in order to bankrole his beloved Obamacare. Just thought I'd let you know you had the facts wrong. Have a good one.</Msg><Username>weewillie08</Username><Timestamp>1349951258481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 06:27:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349951541668-11</Id><Topic><Title>How Romney plans to pay for his tax cut for the RICH</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1349931216504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 00:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How in the world could anyone support obama after these four years. Amazing.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1349951541668</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 06:32:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349953981335-12</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think we are in broad agreement Wallis with perhaps one exception 'My primary comment was that ARM's design would not be strong enough to preclude the need for them to keep pace with fabrication. I stand by that statement.' I have a feeling that Apple's A6 processor maybe the current exception to that rule of thumb as it is quite a tour de force (similar performance/clock to Intel's first mobile chip, Banias/Dothan aka Pentium-M) but here's the deal it doesn't really matter if it is because Apple products are a closed proprietary system which is why Wintel PCs took off in the first place and not Macs. Intel is truly competing against ARM on Windows 8 and Android and I have no doubt Silvermont will clean A15/S4's clocks in that regard. Intel doesn't need to beat Apple just the other half of the market and any success in that regard will send bright neon lights to the market that Intel is not a PC dinosaur but a continual maker of the world's best chips in whatever devices they are designed to go. Once that Eureka moment dawns on both the market and the dumb AnaLysts then INTC will start appreciating to its true valuation which is around $40-50. Until then for longs it will just be a question of trying to time the bottom for further accumulation. On a further note about phone chips Medfield is like the advance front special forces soldier making the initial foray on ARM territory but the shortly upcoming dual-core dual-gpu LTE Z2580 is the chip that will be heavy duty enough to mix it up successfully with the multi-core ARM chips on all cpu/gpu performance benchmarks/specifications and not just javascript. But just as important as that is CloverTrail. It is a truly unique product, a fully functional full legacy touch-enabled Windows PC in a truly mobile iPad format. It should really sell well to enterprises and more than make up for the death of the netbook and is truly the right product at the right time for 2013. Finally it is an Intel mobile invasion like you claimed but we are only at the storming of the beach front stage but the end result I suspect will be like D-Day in the end ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349953981335</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 07:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349956030329-13</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I also may have confused you with the blackandblueredmonk. I can see why this might be considered horribly offensive. My apologies. ----- :) Unlike some on this board I didn't have the cash to buy 10k of Intel shares on a whim, if I did I'de be underwater as may of the current posters. For me, Intel was a server play and by luck I didn't get burned by going long (I had to liquidate many of my holdings for personal reasons). That said, I know the phone market well enough to know that Intel is going to struggle to gain traction over the next few years. Even if Intel "owned" the app processor market, it would add little to the bottom unless Intel is able to increase prices. Basic stuff like this goes over peoples heads.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1349956030329</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 07:47:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349956201904-14</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a feeling that Apple's A6 processor maybe the current exception to that rule of thumb as it is quite a tour de force (similar performance/clock to Intel's first mobile chip, Banias/Dothan aka Pentium-M) ----- The A15 will have a higher IPC than the A6... The real question hanging over the A15 is it's size and power consumption and whether you'll need to pair it with the A7 to get a decent power/performance curve.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1349956201904</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 07:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349956703773-15</Id><Title>buy intc and msft %100 up to new yer hi.</Title><Msg>buy buy buy intc and msft ,going up up up.</Msg><Username>ymkhail</Username><Timestamp>1349956703773</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 07:58:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349957107861-16</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'The A15 will have a higher IPC than the A6' I don't believe it will but we shall both have to wait and see on that score ;-). Now here's a description you would have never thought you would see to describe the power consumption of an x86 processor .... pcproDOTcoDOTuk/reviews/smartphones/377155/motorola-razr-i Verdict Exceptional battery life and an enviable turn of speed make this a tempting buy if high-end phones are out of reach More notable than all these results, however, is the phone’s battery life. Although Intel hasn’t made much of the current range of mobile processors’ battery life, contenting itself with claiming the chip is merely “competitive”, we found the Razr i blitzed our 24-hour battery test. In combination with a 2,000mAh power pack, the Motorola finished with 76% remaining on the battery gauge, the best result we’ve seen from any smartphone in recent memory, with most modern smartphones achieving 50 to 60%.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349957107861</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 08:05:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349958333486-17</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Even if Intel "owned" the app processor market, it would add little to the bottom unless Intel is able to increase prices.' Volume will be the key for the single core and the upcoming quad-cores will command premium mobile prices.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349958333486</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 08:25:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349961221090-18</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this.</Msg><Username>jonellroal49541</Username><Timestamp>1349961221090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349961226672-19</Id><Title>Actually up 5 cents in the pre-market, will it hold?</Title><Msg>Hopefully we can get some updraft today, although I have a feeling not, but I'm ok until we get down to below 20, then I'll likely get a margin call and be forced to sell...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349961226672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349961340351-20</Id><Topic><Title>How Romney plans to pay for his tax cut for the RICH</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1349931216504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 00:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep drinkin' the water, they love ya!</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349961340351</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:15:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349961428889-21</Id><Topic><Title>$19 next folks</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1349949041496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 05:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd buy at 19 too, if I wasn't already all in... I think only a smack in the face earnings report would put it down there though... Although, that may be exactly what happens, but I hope you're wrong.</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349961428889</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349961485882-22</Id><Topic><Title>Actually up 5 cents in the pre-market, will it hold?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349961226672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Movin' on UP... up 9 cents now... like to see that...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349961485882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:18:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349961602474-23</Id><Topic><Title>Actually up 5 cents in the pre-market, will it hold?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349961226672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>qqq up .75 percent, intc up about .41 percent. sell intc, take your lumps and buy the qqq, qld, or for the bold the tqqq.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349961602474</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349961708235-24</Id><Topic><Title>Congrats longs!!!!!!</Title><Username>tonyclitfon2000</Username><Timestamp>1293116311000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2010-12-23 09:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Up 9 cents now... and your GUESS is as good as mine as to where it goes today... I'm still thinking we're heading on a steady decline till earnings, then it may get MUCH worse or MUCH better... time will tell...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349961708235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349961863335-25</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'The A15 will have a higher IPC than the A6' I don't believe it will but we shall both have to wait and see on that score ;-). ----- Indeed:) Yes, the Razr I has got great battery life, but lets see what it's like when it's got a decent GPU and LTE:) Apple A6 Includes Custom CPU October 8, 2012 Author: Linley Gwennap At the iPhone 5 announcement, Apple did not disclose what CPU it used in its new A6 application processor. Recent information, however, indicates that it designed its own CPU rather than licensing a Cortex-A9 or next-generation Cortex-A15 from ARM. Rumors about Apple working on a CPU design have swirled for years, but the company had never publicly confirmed them. Initial analysis of shipping iPhone 5 units, however, confirms that the A6 uses a unique ARM-compatible CPU design that has never been seen before. The new processor is a dual-core design, eschewing the trendy quad-core approach used in high-end smartphones from Samsung and others. Except on the relatively small number of apps that can effectively use four CPUs, the A6 will easily outperform any quad-core Cortex-A9 processor. While competitors push their CPUs to 1.5GHz and beyond, the iPhone 5 clocks the new processor at 1.3GHz, although we expect the chip to achieve faster speeds in a future iPad. Benchmark testing confirms Apple’s claims that the new CPU delivers twice the performance of the Apple A5 processor in the iPhone 4S. Apple also beefed up the GPU, giving the A6 twice the graphics performance of the A5 and roughly the same as the massive A5X. Yet the A6 chip measures 95mm2, making it 22% smaller than the original A5. Die analysis by UBM TechInsights confirms that the A6 processor is manufactured in Samsung’s 32nm HKMG technology, a full generation improvement from the 45nm technology that Samsung used to build the original A5. Samsung also uses the 32nm process to build a shrink version of the A5, which is currently shipping in a revised iPad 2, in the third-generation Apple TV, and in the newest iPod Touch, so the technology is well proven. Despite the global legal battle between Apple and Samsung over smartphone design, the companies continue to work together on Apple’s processors. The 2x gain in CPU performance implies that the A6 CPU executes 20% more instructions per cycle (IPC) than the Cortex-A9 CPU in the A5 processor. Both Cortex-A15 and Krait are rated at about 30% more IPC than Cortex-A9, putting the A6 CPU in or near the same performance class. Although some comparisons show the 1.3GHz iPhone 5 outperforming smartphones using 1.5GHz Krait processors, we believe these apples-to-oranges results are influenced by the greater memory bandwidth of the A6 and the better performance of iOS versus Android.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1349961863335</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:24:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349962493106-26</Id><Topic><Title>The 8% drop in world PC sales is not good....</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1349921497345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:11:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1 stock i own is red..............only 1 today</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349962493106</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:34:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349962517988-27</Id><Topic><Title>Actually up 5 cents in the pre-market, will it hold?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349961226672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, that was short lived, down again...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349962517988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349962626331-28</Id><Topic><Title>Congrats longs!!!!!!</Title><Username>tonyclitfon2000</Username><Timestamp>1293116311000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2010-12-23 09:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>alas, poor INTC, take losses and move elsewhere</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349962626331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:37:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349962788753-29</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'we believe these apples-to-oranges results are influenced by the greater memory bandwidth of the A6 and the better performance of iOS versus Android.' The first part is an intrinsic part of the chip and the second an unavoidable fact of shipping parts so delivered performance will rely on this. Have you checked Geekbench for an A6 vs Krait comparison to verify even to yourself A6 is inferior per clock in all the subtests ? You really can't rely on something as generic as Gwennap's 2x as Anand measured it more than that in some apps, e.g. Geekbench integer as 2.3x, Geekbench floating point as 2.85x anandtechDOTcom/show/6324/the-iphone-5-performance-preview</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349962788753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349963252140-30</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"That said, I know the phone market well enough to know that Intel is going to struggle to gain traction over the next few years. Even if Intel "owned" the app processor market, it would add little to the bottom unless Intel is able to increase prices. Basic stuff like this goes over peoples heads." *** You chide people for not knowing basic stuff when your own failure to understanding the common principles of accounting comes shining through. Intel's superior fabrication and manufacturing will allow them to set prices that produce a profit. Because of the volumes you don't really need much of an individual item profit. If ARM can make a profit in mobility so can Intel. Intel is the only company whose fabrication prowess allows them to control the economics at 14, 10 and 7nm and to continuously reduce costs. ARM is at the situation where it no longer can count on lower unit prices at those die sizes. Basic stuff like this goes over peoples heads.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349963252140</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:47:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349963455774-31</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job! very informative.</Msg><Username>shantaubzmw178819</Username><Timestamp>1349963455774</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:50:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349963510073-32</Id><Title>SEC: Subpoena James Covello's Phone Records!!!</Title><Msg>Just check for calls to Romit Shah, Gus Richard and Stacy Rasgon. Could the collusion at this point be any clearer??? Why is Wall Street targeting US manufacturing???</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349963510073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349963572643-33</Id><Title>intel's future</Title><Msg>Intc has a tremendous tech advantage. the further integration of the electronic components will drive the intc into the mobile business. the mobile uses more and more powerful devices will give intc a huge opportunity to compete with other componies.</Msg><Username>freeland001</Username><Timestamp>1349963572643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349963576702-34</Id><Topic><Title>The 8% drop in world PC sales is not good....</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1349921497345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:11:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That last REAL major interface overhaul Microsoft did was Windows 95 and it was a SMASH hit. Windows 8 is the first MAJOR interface overhaul Windows has had since Windows 95. I tried it and I liked it. I think word of mouth will sell this os (and processors) like hot cakes. I never had much faith in it till I tried it. I work with computers all day as an IT admin and I was really impressed, I think the general public will be as well. Quarter 4 should see INTC back in the 23 to 24 range, but time will tell for sure. If you haven't tried the new interface, give it a go and see what you think for yourself.</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349963576702</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:52:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349963657481-35</Id><Topic><Title>Actually up 5 cents in the pre-market, will it hold?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349961226672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When a big shop recommends buying a Bear Put Spread, it will put negative pressure on the stock. They will be buying the high strike put options near $22 strike and selling the lower strike put options near $19 strike for some DEBIT price. When the INTC stock price goes up, the price of the put spread DEBIT goes down and the option market maker starts executing the orders. He will be trying to place as many of the put options as possible but those that he holds will have to be hedged. How will he neutralize the possibility/likelihood that he will get $22 shares back? He will be shorting a percentage of shares to lower his risk and lock profits. There is a good chance that Intel will not likely trade above $22 until after next Tuesday earnings. It will take some effort and good news to change the negative senitment that weigh it down. Watch option volumes for next Friday 10/20 for earnings plays and Nov expiration for dividend hedging.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349963657481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:54:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349963692988-36</Id><Topic><Title>Congrats longs!!!!!!</Title><Username>tonyclitfon2000</Username><Timestamp>1293116311000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2010-12-23 09:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Down 23 cents now... a buying opportunity for those with money... and anyone who shorted it first thing this morning did well as well</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349963692988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:54:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349963803297-37</Id><Title>The SEC needs to supoena a copy ...</Title><Msg>of the Wall Street Journal.</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1349963803297</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:56:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349963810022-38</Id><Topic><Title>SEC: Subpoena James Covello's Phone Records!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349963510073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:51:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The sec should investigate you for constantly and incessantly pumping INTC.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349963810022</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:56:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349964032733-39</Id><Topic><Title>Actually up 5 cents in the pre-market, will it hold?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349961226672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome info... I'm a begging trade so I only understood a portion of that, but it sounds like good news.. I don't understand options at all and don't risk short selling... My investment in INTC was meant to be for the upward momentum due to the coming dividend, but I had no idea it would be down over a dollar from my in price, but I'm stuck there now with myself fully margined and no where to go. Thank you for the info, I do appreciate it.</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349964032733</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:00:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349964085246-40</Id><Topic><Title>Actually up 5 cents in the pre-market, will it hold?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349961226672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That should have said beginning trader... sorry..</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349964085246</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:01:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349964150245-41</Id><Title>Earnings on Tuesday</Title><Msg>Shorts fantasy that Intel will go out of business this week comes to an end. $8 billion revenue miss now priced in. What was Chump Street thinking?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349964150245</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:02:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349964213066-42</Id><Topic><Title>intel's future</Title><Username>freeland001</Username><Timestamp>1349963572643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has a fab technology and execution advantage. Unfortunately the company is just so-so in architecture and logic design, and is truly second-class in vision and innovation. This is a company that wants to perfect doing the same thing over and over with incremental improvement. On the next proxy vote I'm voting against the entire BoD. They are incompetent for supporting a management team that called innovation copying a Macbook Air. I'm so ashamed that I was stupid enough to keep a position in this stock.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1349964213066</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:03:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349964236414-43</Id><Title>Finally, Someone is scooping up this.</Title><Msg>Sudden spikes are a clear indication of that.</Msg><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1349964236414</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349964274784-44</Id><Title>Even HPQ and DELL are UP today, CRUS is on FIRE... what is wrong with INTC?</Title><Msg>Seriously hope we get a good report at earnings on Tuesday... this is not looking well... Just hoping it doesn't drop to a margin call and mess me up big time...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349964274784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:04:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349964338462-45</Id><Title>internet articles</Title><Msg>the SEC should make the authors reveal their position when they write about stocks. Of course they will say no position but their buddy at JPM or GS is short INCT from 22.50 and the author helps them drop the price of INTC and they get paid on the side. All of this #$%$ press is just as bad as inside information. It should stop as too many fund managers and people react to the news. I still say 22.50 or higher on earnings day (AH's and then wed).</Msg><Username>chevymalibu1966</Username><Timestamp>1349964338462</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349964439940-46</Id><Topic><Title>Finally, Someone is scooping up this.</Title><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1349964236414</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:03:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We might end up up today... will see...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349964439940</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349964602326-47</Id><Topic><Title>Even HPQ and DELL are UP today, CRUS is on FIRE... what is wrong with INTC?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349964274784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:04:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Financial tare oh rism from Rupert Murdock's Wall Street Journal and he's not even American! The committee on unamerican activities needs to investigate! Write the letters!</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1349964602326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:10:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349964725049-48</Id><Title>INTC Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Msg>See all INTC charts - all on one screen - for free. I use this free standalone lightweight tool (does not install anything on your web browser or computer - this is not an annoying browser toolbar nor an add-in). It is called Yahoo Finance 7 Ways and lets me see all charts (e.g. 1 day, 5 days, 1 month, 3 months, etc.) on the same page for any given security. Do a web search for the website RSTNL and download it from the Downloads section of that website. You can also go to the website CNET, do a search for Yahoo Finance 7 Ways in the downloads section, and download it from there.</Msg><Username>donaldinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1349964725049</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:12:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349964784719-49</Id><Topic><Title>intel's future</Title><Username>freeland001</Username><Timestamp>1349963572643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel has a fab technology and execution advantage." [Make that a huge advantage. A three to four year advantage...] "Unfortunately the company is just so-so in architecture and logic design, and is truly second-class in vision and innovation." [Read Marsavian's posts. He understands the design issues much better than I do. He thinks Intel will be worth $50. FinFet was universally hailed as a huge innovation. Dunno what planet you live on. Lucy's World, maybe...] "This is a company that wants to perfect doing the same thing over and over with incremental improvement. On the next proxy vote I'm voting against the entire BoD. They are incompetent for supporting a management team that called innovation copying a Macbook Air." [Your ignorance comes shining through here. Intel makes the processors for the Mac Air. Intel doesn't make computers. And not even Apple has a Steve Jobs anymore. Intel's mobility strategy is solid as you will clearly see in 2013...] "I'm so ashamed that I was stupid enough to keep a position in this stock." [You should be ashamed of your analytic skills. And you should be spending your time looking for your backbone instead of mindlessly throwing rocks...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349964784719</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:13:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349964864692-50</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings on Tuesday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349964150245</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What was Chump Street thinking --------------------- What were you thinking when you recommended this pos stock at 29? How many innocent/novice investors bought into your streaming 24 x 7 line of beee esss and are now underwater? You are either very stupid or extremely evil!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1349964864692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349964947651-51</Id><Title>Good strategy</Title><Msg>A good way to get long on intel at these levels would be through Leaps. Jan 2015 strike 22 calls are selling dirt cheap @2.60 per contract. Intel will bottom out at around $21.50, if Paul O comes out and calm nerves on Tuesday, wednesday this is going to soar.......wall street is all about emotions and manipulation these days. Invest in Intel for their R&amp;D, strong Balance sheet and 4+% divy.............long term investors .....Leaps is the way to go!!!! ( No divy for calls but upside potential is huge downside is limited to premium paid which is not a great amount IMO).</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1349964947651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:15:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349964977317-52</Id><Title>Scuttle on Along Now</Title><Msg>Time for all you cockroaches to be covering your positions. The exterminator arrives on Tuesday. You had best be gone by then...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349964977317</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:16:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349965157214-53</Id><Topic><Title>Scuttle on Along Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349964977317</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:16:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seeing that you said the same exact thing at 28, explain to me how saying it at 21 makes you anything more than a lowlife manipulator? You can't...</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349965157214</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349965857950-54</Id><Topic><Title>Actually up 5 cents in the pre-market, will it hold?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349961226672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The option market maker makes markets for options. He has to provide a BID and ASK price for options across various strikes and expirations. If someone offers to WRITE/SELL an option at the BID price and he cannot find a HOLDER/BUYER for the option, he becomes the HOLDER/BUYER. If someone offers to BUY/HOLD an option at the ASK price and he cannot find a WRITER/SELLER for the option, he becomes the WRITER/SELLER. He wants risk to be near or at zero and will blend a mix of PUT options, CALL options and EQUITY positions. Good reading topics: SYNTHETIC OPTION POSITIONS PUT SELLING CONSERVATIVE BUYING SIMPLE CASE: Say he has to SELL/WRITE some $25 NOV PUT options. He gets about a $3.50 premium for selling the put but will likely be faced with having to buy shares at $25 in NOV. How does he neutralize his risk to zero. He will short the shares of Intel so when he has to buy the shares for $25 in 37 days, he will not lose any money on the down side. If he has to buy shares in 37 days at $25 and he has $3.50 premium from the PUT BUYER, his effective cost is $21.50. With Intel trading at $21.85, the option market maker locks in a 35 cent profit ($21.85 - $21.50 = $0.35) by shorting Intel. If someone buys 10,000 $25 NOV INTC PUT contracts, they will cause the option market maker to short shares as long as the option market maker can cover the order and still make a profit. If the share price moves down, he stops shorting. If Intel moves up, he shorts. This is why you see INTC trade in a VERY NARROW price range. It gets MUCH, MUCH more complex and it is very hard to figure out option combination orders where multiple options are linked.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349965857950</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:30:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349965888512-55</Id><Title>Windows 8</Title><Msg>Stock down 25% from high because pc sales are down 1%. #$%$! Maybe a lot of people are waiting for Windows 8, just like people waited for the new iPhones right before a new model came out. Who wants to upgrade software on a brand new computer. While iPads are great, they are not a true replacement for a pc. Don't forget they also have chips in servers and lots of other products..</Msg><Username>nickster135796</Username><Timestamp>1349965888512</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:31:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349965989415-56</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings on Tuesday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349964150245</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How many innocent/novice investors bought into your streaming 24 x 7 line of beee esss and are now underwater?" ___________________________________________________________________________ How many innocent/novice investors bought into your streaming 24 x 7 line of beee esss AND SOLD INTEL AT 20 TO BUY CISCO AT 20 AND WATCHED CISCO DROP TO 13 AS INTEL ROSE TO 29 and are now underwater/living under a bridge? By YOUR VERY OWN WORDS........You are either very stupid or extremely evil!</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349965989415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349966045941-57</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8</Title><Username>nickster135796</Username><Timestamp>1349965888512</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:31:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Maybe a lot of people are waiting for Windows 8" Does that also explain why Otellini warned that PC manufacturers were scaling back instead of stocking up on chips as the release of Windows 8 and the holiday season looms?</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1349966045941</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349966190122-58</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings on Tuesday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349964150245</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gutless, spineless conman Hypocrite = Lucy Nuff I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO By lucy_nuff.Dec 28, 2010 10:34 AM.Permalink. CSCO will outperform INTC in 2011.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349966190122</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:36:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349966494747-59</Id><Topic><Title>intel's future</Title><Username>freeland001</Username><Timestamp>1349963572643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis, what do you think the Ultrabook strategy is? As for Intel's mobility strategy, it is still based on selling discrete chips to companies that want to do on-die and in-package integration. A rear view mirror, let's-do-what-we've-been-doing plan. As for my analytic skills, you may be correct. I am long in this stock because I thought Win8 would give it a big bump, and I didn't foresee the slowdown in Asia. For shame.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1349966494747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349966808850-60</Id><Topic><Title>intel's future</Title><Username>freeland001</Username><Timestamp>1349963572643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>from CNN MONEY- "Ultrabook sales have disappointed. IHS iSuppli slashed its forecast for the thin laptops in half last week, and NPD DisplaySearch recently forecast that Ultrabooks will make up just a quarter of the total mobile PC market by 2015 -- far short of Intel's forecast."</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1349966808850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349966893067-61</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one, I will subscribe now.</Msg><Username>particiapuhk36937</Username><Timestamp>1349966893067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349966954309-62</Id><Topic><Title>Actually up 5 cents in the pre-market, will it hold?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349961226672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has the wind caught its sails, down to 21.52 and now up to 21.81... keep it climbing...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349966954309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:49:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349966962041-63</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8</Title><Username>nickster135796</Username><Timestamp>1349965888512</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:31:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The analysts believe the "PC is dead" and that Intel is a PC company. The analysts believe that ARM will make a significant impact on the Intel ASP, profit margin and may take significant market share. Especially IF Apple converts its MAC lines to ARM (Note to Wallis .... I said this is what I think is influencing ANALYSTS and I am not saying it is true or false) . The analysts believe that Intel cannot be successful in the new product market and compete with the low priced ARM based products. SInce Intel has a VERY large percentage of the PC and SERVER computing market, there is more risk in them losing share than gaining (since their share is at 90%). The analysts do not believe that Intel knows what is going on. Intel has warned on earnings twice in the last 4 quarters. Once for a flood that wiped out an overly concentrated disk drive operation in Thailand and the second time this quarter after Intel customers changed their orders. I doubt that Intel would have warned before their customers. Laptop, desktop and server CPU chips are still a dominant part of their revenue.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349966962041</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349967018866-64</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Alert!</Title><Username>albinagbz192</Username><Timestamp>1349966033983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DOTA rocks!!! but THIS is better than DOTA!</Msg><Username>burgess_christina611</Username><Timestamp>1349967018866</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:50:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349967138060-65</Id><Title>Lucy_Nuff and his aliases just admitted that he was very stupid or very Evil</Title><Msg>LOL! See the thread "Earnings Tuesday" and watch Lucy admit that he's sick and or Evil. He also posts under all of these aliases below: He's a bad person, admits it but doesn't care. tooofunnny l Lucy_nuff lucifer_nuff vinnie_bagofdonitz wilder_blitch win_dexit coinmaker wallisschmallis stupidstewie gordon.greco kored65 obamaloveswallst kohighbloodpressure Jimbohomegamedyou CrazyWally Foxnewzzz(with three z's) maximumwalrus winteldead t hink5pm pedroexressway wallisweiner walldexit trixeee777777 jessejames_blitch wallywiththereddress_nuff</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349967138060</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349967326331-66</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Alert!</Title><Username>albinagbz192</Username><Timestamp>1349966033983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope it contains great info. I just joined. Many thanks</Msg><Username>mckinney_lara552</Username><Timestamp>1349967326331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349967446332-67</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You chide people for not knowing basic stuff when your own failure to understanding the common principles of accounting comes shining through. Intel's superior fabrication and manufacturing will allow them to set prices that produce a profit. Because of the volumes you don't really need much of an individual item profit. If ARM can make a profit in mobility so can Intel. Intel is the only company whose fabrication prowess allows them to control the economics at 14, 10 and 7nm and to continuously reduce costs. ARM is at the situation where it no longer can count on lower unit prices at those die sizes. Basic stuff like this goes over peoples heads. ----- When you talk about ARM (in the above context), you actually mean ARM's customers, Nvida, QCOM and the rest. ARM (the company) earns royalty on shipping cores (typically 1 to 2%) on the billions it ships every quarter. Intel is on a completely different scale. As for the accounting principles of principles, I understand them well, by the look of things, better than you. You clearly don't know that the foundries (historically at least) pump out silicon cheaper than Intel can. A fact admitted by Intel when it signed the deal with TSMC for Atom IP a couple of years back. There is a reason why Intel hasn't moved it's basebands from TSMC to it's own process tech. Currently Intel's (atom) CPU cores are significantly larger than the ARM CPU's, resulting in larger chips (Cloverview is 15% larger than Tegra 3 even with a process advantage - yes, Cloverview should also be faster, at least on paper). However, there is some truth to your argument. It only holds if Intel can far enough ahead of the foundries in (low power) node terms...</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1349967446332</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:57:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349967473215-68</Id><Title>Unemployment Drops to Four Year Low</Title><Msg>Foreclosure filings drop to five year low. More defeats for the doom and gloom crowd on Wall Street whose firms continues to assault US manufacturing and the US economy...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349967473215</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:57:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349967488111-69</Id><Title>what up ?</Title><Msg>Was down now up.....Whats happening? Seems to want to start back up. Any of you market guys have an answer?</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1349967488111</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:58:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349967573996-70</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Intel's superior fabrication and manufacturing will allow them to set prices that produce a profit.' This is the true strength of fabrication advantage, it allows you to be the last man left standing in any price war. Having your own Fabs also helps to accentuate this price advantage. Any ARM vendors who currently don't have volume are dead men walking when they are faced in 2013 by premium x86 mobile chips on the n process and cheap but still fast x86 mobile chips on the n-1 process e.g. 22nm Silvermont and 32nm Medfield. East wanted an ARMs race with Intel, well be careful what you wish for for it might come true ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349967573996</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:59:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349967590555-71</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy_Nuff and his aliases just admitted that he was very stupid or very Evil</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349967138060</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:52:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why even respond to that clown? Ignore him then report abuse,end of problem.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1349967590555</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349967634450-72</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Alert!</Title><Username>albinagbz192</Username><Timestamp>1349966033983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finally! I found something informative.</Msg><Username>bates_anne556</Username><Timestamp>1349967634450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:00:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349967951324-73</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8</Title><Username>nickster135796</Username><Timestamp>1349965888512</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:31:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I said this in another thread, but I'll re-post it here as it seem appropriate to the topic: "That last REAL major interface overhaul Microsoft did was Windows 95 and it was a SMASH hit. Windows 8 is the first MAJOR interface overhaul Windows has had since Windows 95. I tried it and I liked it. I think word of mouth will sell this os (and processors) like hot cakes. I never had much faith in it till I tried it. I work with computers all day as an IT admin and I was really impressed, I think the general public will be as well. Quarter 4 should see INTC back in the 23 to 24 range, but time will tell for sure. If you haven't tried the new interface, give it a go and see what you think for yourself."</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349967951324</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:05:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349968020383-74</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Alert!</Title><Username>albinagbz192</Username><Timestamp>1349966033983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DONAIRE vs NISHIOKA live streaming..subscribe now!</Msg><Username>haynes_jeanette559</Username><Timestamp>1349968020383</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349968071640-75</Id><Topic><Title>intel's future</Title><Username>freeland001</Username><Timestamp>1349963572643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Unfortunately the company is just so-so in architecture and logic design' Intel has left a trail of broken bodies amongst its RISC and x86 rivals in the PC and Server market over decades and is now turning its undoubted architectural prowess to the mobile arena. Don't be surprised if the end result is no different ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349968071640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349968425412-76</Id><Title>AMD had more weapons than ARMH does and look at AMD now</Title><Msg>Anybody that thinks Intel won't, at worst case, be a strong player in Mobile is just pulling your leg or clueless. Intel has its eyes fixated on ARMH, and Warren East is scrambling like he's never scrambled before........Intel will run him down sooner than later.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349968425412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:13:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349969174771-77</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Alert!</Title><Username>albinagbz192</Username><Timestamp>1349966033983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>loosing weight is easy! join now!</Msg><Username>love_maria569</Username><Timestamp>1349969174771</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349969477487-78</Id><Title>China and emerging markets won't be down forever</Title><Msg>Stacy Smith sat right there on CNBC one day earlier last year and specifically told Maria that Intel goes in Cycles. There will be a huge upcycle soon, my guess is around the end of next year or early 2014 with Haswell and 14nm.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349969477487</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:31:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349969718662-79</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Alert!</Title><Username>albinagbz192</Username><Timestamp>1349966033983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great! It's so useful , i just subscribed!</Msg><Username>powers_carol565</Username><Timestamp>1349969718662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:35:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349970000260-80</Id><Title>Wednesday</Title><Msg>Can't wait for Wed. The insanity of INTC's stock price will finally have a date with reality. will be interesting.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349970000260</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:40:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349970067179-81</Id><Topic><Title>intel's future</Title><Username>freeland001</Username><Timestamp>1349963572643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Twice in my life, I have invested contrary to Warren Buffett. The first time was when he was dumping FNM. Ouch. INTC was the second time I did it, but at least I didn't do it to the same degree. Minor ouch. In the future, I plan on never investing in something Buffett is dumping. Lesson learned. Not that it helps me with my INTC holdings.</Msg><Username>bassdws882002</Username><Timestamp>1349970067179</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:41:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349970138157-82</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Alert!</Title><Username>albinagbz192</Username><Timestamp>1349966033983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for this guys! So goes for you gals! LOL</Msg><Username>young_deborah573</Username><Timestamp>1349970138157</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:42:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349970246744-83</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok cool! Thank you for sharing this.</Msg><Username>joettatbejx15013</Username><Timestamp>1349970246744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349970411170-84</Id><Topic><Title>China and emerging markets won't be down forever</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349969477487</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:31:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think it will happen long before that. AAPL is getting it from Galaxy III and Droid big time. If AAPL doesn't do something relatively quick they will be on harder times than INTC. Their Ipad is also getting it from all sids too. Easy way out on all sides is to get 22nm from INTC. They get faster processors and they will run windows 8. That would also get them in corp. america as they will be able to run all their programs and have an anti virus. Yes I believe INTC will make ARMH processors for them for a limited time. Paul even said he would on a previous conf. call.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349970411170</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:46:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349970638636-85</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Alert!</Title><Username>albinagbz192</Username><Timestamp>1349966033983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this here.</Msg><Username>wright_vickie569</Username><Timestamp>1349970638636</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:50:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349970676095-86</Id><Topic><Title>Unemployment Drops to Four Year Low</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349967473215</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:57:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not helping INTC one bit</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349970676095</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:51:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349970941278-87</Id><Title>INTC: Put OCT 20 strike 19 0.02 cents will be 1$ next week</Title><Msg>=============== eom =========================</Msg><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1349970941278</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:55:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349970975318-88</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Alert!</Title><Username>albinagbz192</Username><Timestamp>1349966033983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like these guys, they're really good.</Msg><Username>mullins_ashley574</Username><Timestamp>1349970975318</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:56:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349971308816-89</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Alert!</Title><Username>albinagbz192</Username><Timestamp>1349966033983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just joined. Heard a lot about these guys</Msg><Username>graham_natalie576</Username><Timestamp>1349971308816</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:01:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349971413486-90</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Alert!</Title><Username>albinagbz192</Username><Timestamp>1349966033983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Useless SPAM SPAM SPAM</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1349971413486</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:03:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349971726191-91</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Alert!</Title><Username>albinagbz192</Username><Timestamp>1349966033983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love it. thanks</Msg><Username>reeves_catherine585</Username><Timestamp>1349971726191</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:08:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349971857279-92</Id><Topic><Title>INTC: Put OCT 20 strike 19 0.02 cents will be 1$ next week</Title><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1349970941278</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:55:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd really like to understand what that means, cause I don't very well get it...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349971857279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:10:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349971935102-93</Id><Title>Perhaps $21.50 is the resistance mark... very cool if it stays above that...</Title><Msg>If it drops below it, will it tumble down... down... I hope it doesn't get that low, so we don't have to find out...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349971935102</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:12:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349972022772-94</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Alert!</Title><Username>albinagbz192</Username><Timestamp>1349966033983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great share. Many thanks</Msg><Username>cross_tara587</Username><Timestamp>1349972022772</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:13:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349972713724-95</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Alert!</Title><Username>albinagbz192</Username><Timestamp>1349966033983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome..this helps me a lot..two thumbs UP!</Msg><Username>edwards_katie592</Username><Timestamp>1349972713724</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:25:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349973005178-96</Id><Topic><Title>Wednesday</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349970000260</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:40:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The weekly options expiring after earnings just opened up strikes on all the 50 cent levels ($16.50 through $25.50) and there is volume. There will be lots of option games played around earnings. Lots of put buying for insurance and general gambling. There is also the early Nov dividend and arbitraging pricing has started. Reality? There will always be those who will try to influence share price to their advantage both by words and deeds. It will not end.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349973005178</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:30:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349973373667-97</Id><Topic><Title>Wednesday</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349970000260</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:40:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not the best with options, but I just bought 200 more contracts of Jan 15 20's at 3.60. I figure this is a steal with all the things INTC is ramping up.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349973373667</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349973622748-98</Id><Topic><Title>INTC: Put OCT 20 strike 19 0.02 cents will be 1$ next week</Title><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1349970941278</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:55:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Assuming you are serious about wanting more info .... Think of owning a put option as like insurance. The HOLDER or BUYER of the put option can make the WRITER or SELLER of the put option take the shares at the strike price. Think of buying a put option as shorting shares but with a maximum loss equal to the optoin purchase price if share prices goes way up. Short term shorting with limited risk. What this guy is saying is to BUY $19 put options that expire next Friday the 20th for 2 cents per share and next week they will be worth $1. Because there is no time value on the options, he is saying that Intel will drop to $18 per share by next Friday. The thread is "bear spam".</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349973622748</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:40:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349973822914-99</Id><Title>i told you so</Title><Msg>it's natural color is lobster red, junk is junk, no power to hold the gains, down a dollar and up only one to few cents, up only one day and down more than a week, it will keep falling and new lows will keep coming ! short it to become a millionaire! short short short</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349973822914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349974328269-100</Id><Topic><Title>i told you so</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349973822914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:43:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure not gonna get rich buy and holding this. if the market ever falls apart, INTC will get crushed. the semis made new lows in 2009, unlike the QQQ</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349974328269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349974396052-101</Id><Title>Deutsche Bank Upgrades Audience to Buy on Valuation, Established $15 Price Target</Title><Msg>Deutsche Bank Upgrades Audience to Buy on Valuation and Established $15 Price Target. theflyonthewall Deutsche Bank raised its rating on Audience , Inc (NASDAQ: ADNC) from Hold to Buy and established a $15 price target on shares. Deutsche Bank said, "We think it's now widely recognized that 3Q rev trends will again be soft due to Apple withdrawal . We think a 2012 guidance cut is well priced into the shares, but we believe it's a better than even chance that Audience will maintain its 2012 guidance, partially due to better than expected Asian sales, which we think would take the shares higher. "</Msg><Username>rogerabc100</Username><Timestamp>1349974396052</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349974396464-102</Id><Topic><Title>INTC: Put OCT 20 strike 19 0.02 cents will be 1$ next week</Title><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1349970941278</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:55:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why the Jan-13 20$ so expensive: 2.18$? does it mean i can buy 100 INTC shares per contract at 20$ upon expiration?</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1349974396464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349974444070-103</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy_Nuff and his aliases just admitted that he was very stupid or very Evil</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349967138060</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:52:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He just looked in the mirror and saw something he didn't like and it was himself! LOL!</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349974444070</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:54:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349974526349-104</Id><Topic><Title>INTC: Put OCT 20 strike 19 0.02 cents will be 1$ next week</Title><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1349970941278</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:55:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok that makes more sense now. Thank you.... I guess I'm still a little confused on the use of the term Strike price... But I got what the thread is about now. Thank you again.</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349974526349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349974724663-105</Id><Topic><Title>Wednesday</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349970000260</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:40:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can see the impact of the Intel dividend on those options. The call has $1.80 intrinsic value at $20 and the put option is out of the money by $1.80 . The put option is selling for the same $3.50 price. There is a built in dividend drop included in the option pricing. That is why the Intel call options are so cheap and the puts are comparatively expensive. 8-) I AM NOT THE BEST at options either. I like writing them and have the premium leak into my pocket which is why I am more active at puts than calls. When you write them, you can roll them out to avoid execution. If you keep premium on them they will not be exercised early. The only problem is to watch out for exdividend if you are in the money.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349974724663</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 12:58:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349975632030-106</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's the combination of design and fabrication that will do it but design is the most important and always has been" Agree !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349975632030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 13:13:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349976154062-107</Id><Topic><Title>INTC: Put OCT 20 strike 19 0.02 cents will be 1$ next week</Title><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1349970941278</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:55:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Short answer is yes. You can also take the difference and pocket it if you don't want the shares. Hope that helps.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349976154062</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 13:22:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349976169539-108</Id><Title>lying Ryan cannot compete with full of sheeiit Mit in a #$%$ contest.</Title><Msg>Mit virtually lied about every single thing he was asked. I doubt that Ryan will risk ruining his reputation with that move. After all--after Mitt full of #$%$ Romney loses, Ryan still has a political life.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349976169539</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 13:22:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349976423998-109</Id><Title>Max Pain</Title><Msg>Oct 12 options max pain at 24. If the settle near it we could see a $2.00+ bounce by next Fri on expiration.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349976423998</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 13:27:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349976520031-110</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm looking for great articles, Nice to be here.</Msg><Username>albinadlqa63483</Username><Timestamp>1349976520031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 13:28:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349976936165-111</Id><Topic><Title>INTC: Put OCT 20 strike 19 0.02 cents will be 1$ next week</Title><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1349970941278</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:55:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The STRIKE PRICE is the price of the STOCK that you are "insuring". If I BUY a $19 STRIKE PRICE PUT option that expires on OCT 20th, then the sellers are agreeing to buy the INTC shares at the $19 strike price. Someone will sell me the right to make them buy my INTC shares at $19. That is not very valuable when Intel is trading at $21.80. How much would I have to pay to have someone buy my shares at a $20 strike price, on or before Oct 20th. 6 cents $21 strike = 20 cents $22 strike = 60 cents IN THE MONEY $23 strike = $1.34 $24 strike = $2.27 $30 strike = $8.25 Notice that there is near zero premium for deep in the money option strikes. $30 - $8.25 = $21.75</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349976936165</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 13:35:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349977441236-112</Id><Topic><Title>INTC: Put OCT 20 strike 19 0.02 cents will be 1$ next week</Title><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1349970941278</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:55:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yum... Bear Spam</Msg><Username>dwv4</Username><Timestamp>1349977441236</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 13:44:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349978007460-113</Id><Topic><Title>INTC: Put OCT 20 strike 19 0.02 cents will be 1$ next week</Title><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1349970941278</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:55:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The $2.18 pricing implies that you are looking at the $20 JAN2013 Call options. The call is IN THE MONEY. I think you are saying it correctly. If you buy one call option contract for $2.18 per share, you will pay $218 plus trade costs and you can then purchase 100 shares of Intel at $20 anytime up to the expiration day. You own the option you bought and can exercise it at your descretion ... any time before expiration. Your reward will be you effectively own the shares by owning the call option and your risk is limited to the $2.18 if Intel goes lower than $20. The CBOE and Option Clearing Corporation have some good online training courses. Look under EDUCATION or COURSES.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349978007460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 13:53:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349978154464-114</Id><Topic><Title>INTC: Put OCT 20 strike 19 0.02 cents will be 1$ next week</Title><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1349970941278</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:55:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It tastes remarkably similar to "Bull Spam", "Political Spam" and "Religious Spam".</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349978154464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 13:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349978713132-115</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy_Nuff and his aliases just admitted that he was very stupid or very Evil</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349967138060</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:52:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally's not evil, just a lot poorer than he was one could guess</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349978713132</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 14:05:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349980106254-116</Id><Topic><Title>Max Pain</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349976423998</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 13:27:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this might run past 22 on mon/tues if earnings leak is positive but if they aren't good, then we'll be lucky to hold 20. I doubt INTC sees 24 for months let alone next spring. I bought some in sept at 24's and am dying.</Msg><Username>chevymalibu1966</Username><Timestamp>1349980106254</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 14:28:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349981362216-117</Id><Title>Down still but I am glad I got back in long a few days ago.</Title><Msg>Likely, very bad news for shorts will be out soon. Does anyone on earth know what Romney would do if elected? NO He says one thing and then says the opposite 20 minutes later. He might be a raving LIB for all we know.. I mean, a Harvard grad being a LIB would not be so surprising would it? The Nest Rombo-Obummer debate will quickly go out of control and Wold--LIB--Blited will likely laugh as it does. They are supposed to talk about International stuff --forieign affairs. But you can be 99% sure that Obummer will completely ignore those rules and go after Rombo on Domestic stuff too. Likely he will have days and times of all the #$%$ Rpmney has said. It will go like this. Would walks up to a person--do you have a question for the President? Person--Yes--what would you do to make peace for the palistinions and Israel? Obummer--that is an important question yet we have so many unemployed in America and on march 12, 2012, Mr. Romney said to a crowd of rich Doners that he ------------ The exact quote and date will be given of Romney saying he does not care about the 47%. Wolf--Mr. president--please stay on the topic--- But Governor romney--do you have a reply? if he does not reply---he looks like a fool but if he does reply--he is a fool because this will simply open the door to President Obama attacking Romney date and time for another flip flop. Romney will reply and call The Pres some names but Obama will simply reply with more facts and dates. Wolf will ask Romney--You know--we all know you said it--we saw it so why or how is it you can say you did not say it? Next question Woman--When do we get out of Afghanistan-- Romney--we should stay longer than the President--Blah blah blah. Wolf--mr Presidnt? I think we will get out on this date I gave but what on earth is Mitt talking about when he said on ---- that he is for a woman's right to choose and then said he is for outlawing abortion--time and dates. I think he is either without conviction or he is simply trying to foll the American public. If obummer rips into Rombo and turns it into a war of facts--Rombo will implode after the debate fiaco and we will be looking at a 10% or more Obummer landslide which will wreck the GOP for years and years to come. Rombo has simply opened the door for a massive and devastating attack--and you can be sure that Libtard wold Blittzed head will not stop the Obummer attacks and push it back on topic. In fact--most of the crowd will stop asking about foreign affairs and go into domestic questions and Wolf will go with it. Rombo will be toast. I am putting some massive cash on a bet in London on Obummer to win. I layed 5-2 and it is easy money. After all--Ohio is already gone or do you idiots on the ruight not know that yet? 20% of the voters have already voted there and Obummer is winning by 2-1. Rombo will not catch up and likely he will implode on the next two debates and The Chicago in Obummer kicks Rombo in the nuggets.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349981362216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 14:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349982471990-118</Id><Topic><Title>intel's future</Title><Username>freeland001</Username><Timestamp>1349963572643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think folks are missing the point regarding Intel's challenges. Intel's has strong technology and manufacturing. Intel also has cash. But that's not the challenge Intel faces. Inte's challenges are its relevance in the growth market and its bsuiness model. Since the dawn of the PC era, Apple used a different processor (initially Motorola then PowerPC) and a different OS than the common PC (IBM-architecture with Intel X86). More precisely, Intel's X86 won the IBM design partly because it is different than Apple/Motorola. In 2005, Apple adopted Intel X86 architecture in its desktop and notebook computers. Intel (Otellini) was elated! Intel (and Otellini in particular) had pursued Apple for years to get this design win. However, Otellini read the tea-leaves incorrectly. In reality, Jobs recognized that the processor/architecture is no longer the controlling point and therefore, it wouldn't matter if Apple uses the X86 architecure. The control point had moved from hardware/software to data and apps. If you look at Apple's business model today (and Google's, Amazon's, Microsoft's as well), the hardware is merely a conduit to bring business to the data/apps. Once they won your data and apps, they OWN you!! In so doing, the relevance of hardware/processor is on the declined. This trend in turn led to the emergence of ARM, Nividia, Qualcomm, Apple's A4/A5/A6 etc.. Consumers today don't care about what processors they have. What they want is their data and apps! In conclusion, if Intel were to retain its dominance, Intel must find/buy a path to this new reality.</Msg><Username>billsuxx</Username><Timestamp>1349982471990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 15:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349982513038-119</Id><Topic><Title>Down still but I am glad I got back in long a few days ago.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349981362216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 14:49:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting to hear you say you just got back in Long the other day...........when you've been pumping Intel to 40 on an Apple announcement all year. Repeat after me: I'm a Liberal with no morals, no values and couldn't care less about anybody but myself.......the prototype Lib filth.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349982513038</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 15:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349982626926-120</Id><Topic><Title>Down still but I am glad I got back in long a few days ago.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349981362216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 14:49:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You dont sound near as positive as you did a couple of weeks ago. Romney is doing pretty good.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1349982626926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349982659009-121</Id><Topic><Title>Down still but I am glad I got back in long a few days ago.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349981362216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 14:49:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flumoxed/Amdmonkey slash millions more aliases..................A broke Conman. A Liberal that would shake your hand and then steal your wallet. Intel to 30 before Christmas. By amdmonkey72.Aug 11, 2012 2:49 PM.Permalink 40 if Apple deal struck on phones. Thanks Yahoo for blocking teabaggers from pumping Rightwing trashtalk. My pet dog who eats #$%$ is smarter than a teabagger.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349982659009</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 15:10:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349982707208-122</Id><Topic><Title>Down still but I am glad I got back in long a few days ago.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349981362216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 14:49:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, if nothing else, that was an entertaining read... no doubt that Obama will win the election, the republican votes should have voted for Ron Paul as their candidate... but oh well.... Obama is awful and will cause the even more rapid deterioration of the dollar and then WE all lose, including other countries as their economies will be shaken heavily by the destruction of the dollar as well...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349982707208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 15:11:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349982730839-123</Id><Topic><Title>Down still but I am glad I got back in long a few days ago.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349981362216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 14:49:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they are worse than that. they pretend like they care and lead the uneducated and immoral around to get their votes and put themselves in power. teddy being the ultimate POS liberal there ever was.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349982730839</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 15:12:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349982811376-124</Id><Topic><Title>Actually up 5 cents in the pre-market, will it hold?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349961226672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems to have settled down now.... I'm guessing by the day's end we see it up or down a penny...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349982811376</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 15:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349982815744-125</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy_Nuff and his aliases just admitted that he was very stupid or very Evil</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349967138060</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:52:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll go with he's evil.......................... 22-Feb-12 05:04 pm Two out of every three people receiving stock dividend payments are rich, many totally, incredibly rich and should be paying more taxes instead of us soaking the middle class. I'm sick of the deadbeat rich who are unwilling to carry their fair share of the load... wallisweaver Romney Proves His Dickishness By wallisweaver . Oct 4, 2012 12:14 AM . Permalink by wanting to fire Big Bird. Old, rich, out-of-touch and a pure scrooge. Bah, humbug. No Big Bird and no Christmas says the Grinch. By the way, you guys posting up about markets are idiots. It's the Republicans on Wall Street who are driving Intel's stock price into the dirt. They are not your friends and neither is Romney. Come on, who did you think was beating up on Intel? Democrats??? But the Big Bird stuff is not going to play well with anyone who has kids...</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349982815744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 15:13:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349983080812-126</Id><Topic><Title>Scuttle on Along Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349964977317</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:16:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is Intel going to forecast $3 eps ?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349983080812</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 15:18:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349983680983-127</Id><Topic><Title>lying Ryan cannot compete with full of sheeiit Mit in a #$%$ contest.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349976169539</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 13:22:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You guys do not lose well. Romney kicked his butt....Why not admit it. Makes obama look bad all this lieing crap.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1349983680983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 15:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349984117952-128</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am looking for.</Msg><Username>alexamgoop57592</Username><Timestamp>1349984117952</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 15:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349984352172-129</Id><Topic><Title>DRAM $0.64 with $6.5M Market Cap is a Potential Multi-bagger......DRAM and AMD signed an agreement to launch an aggressive campaign to market all editions of AMD's AMD Memory modules for desktops......Per the agreement, DRAM will develop a special edition RAMDisk utility, which will be called AMD Radeon RAMDisk...... AMD Radeon RAMDisk loading times are expected to be 525% higher than those offered by conventional products</Title><Username>bt.bigten</Username><Timestamp>1349843797174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:36:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seems like buyers are starting to line up. Don't forget that AMD-DRAM will make an announcement monetarily about the formal launch of this program in October as DRAM readies its contribution to this potentially lucrative application. More applications are expected for tablets and mobile devices later.</Msg><Username>bt.bigten</Username><Timestamp>1349984352172</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 15:39:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349984634625-130</Id><Topic><Title>Down still but I am glad I got back in long a few days ago.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349981362216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 14:49:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Teddy the ultimate GUILT RIDDEN Liberal that ever was...</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1349984634625</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 15:43:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349985322398-131</Id><Title>The Pre Earnings Ramp Up Should Begin Tomorrow</Title><Msg>Should get a nice bounce ahead of earnings. $30 coming soon.</Msg><Username>wallisweiner</Username><Timestamp>1349985322398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 15:55:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349985805318-132</Id><Topic><Title>The Pre Earnings Ramp Up Should Begin Tomorrow</Title><Username>wallisweiner</Username><Timestamp>1349985322398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 15:55:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're very hopeful... what INTC positions do you hold?</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349985805318</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:03:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349985880919-133</Id><Topic><Title>All the Risk on the Short Side</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349821530787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:25:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another math whiz...you must be a democrat.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349985880919</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349986361313-134</Id><Topic><Title>All the Risk on the Short Side</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349821530787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:25:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was hoping to grab some more shares around the 21.60 area, missed my chance during the day, thought I'd catch it after hours, but it's going the wrong way...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349986361313</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349986809206-135</Id><Title>the wish=risk on the long side</Title><Msg>Keep falling, every day makes a new 52 weeks new low! It is real a wake up call ! Short short short short short</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349986809206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:20:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349987379382-136</Id><Topic><Title>All the Risk on the Short Side</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349821530787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:25:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you disagree with that? and no, i work for my money and think others should also, therefore I am not a dimocrat.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349987379382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:29:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349987778709-137</Id><Topic><Title>the wish=risk on the long side</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349986809206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:20:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will keep falling because it is a junk! No matter the market is up or down, it just keep falling!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349987778709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349988010475-138</Id><Title>AMD just warned</Title><Msg>Macro economy has weak demand.</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349988010475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:40:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349988122178-139</Id><Topic><Title>All the Risk on the Short Side</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349821530787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:25:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>poor Waldo, holding INTC from 24 in 2010, through the drop to 17 and change, back up again, then then the drop to the 19's, then up again, does he sell at 29, 28, 27, 26, 25, 24, 23, 22. Nope, but always and forever with a strong buy on INTC no matter the price, and now, not a gain at all on 24's, not even with 1.80 in dividends factored in. All the risk on the short side and then then lower lows for INTC. Will INTC ever see 24.00 again. Plenty of new longs who will jump at the exits if they ever get back to breakeven</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349988122178</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:42:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349988274332-140</Id><Topic><Title>intel's future</Title><Username>freeland001</Username><Timestamp>1349963572643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Um, in case you haven't noticed, Intel is not in the data or apps business. Intel is in the processor business. Their path to success isn't through apps and data or through Apple necessarily. The path is to provide the best combination of value and cost in processors. Intel has to make inroads into mobility. They are well prepared to do this. With their fabrication lead they control their destiny. 14nm is the tipping point...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349988274332</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:44:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349988281642-141</Id><Topic><Title>AMD just warned</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349988010475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:40:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, Herbal, at least you're not too much underwater, assuming you didn't sell the am gap up that collapsed.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349988281642</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349988368095-142</Id><Topic><Title>AMD just warned</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349988010475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:40:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey HERB, ya gonna sell at a loss after hours like you did with HP? I mean, that's your THANG A'INT it?? Buy low, sell lower. ROFL! Motorsickle trash!</Msg><Username>herbal_dud</Username><Timestamp>1349988368095</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349988535803-143</Id><Topic><Title>the wish=risk on the long side</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349986809206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:20:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lucy this ID creation reminds me of your Agent Orange persona except this one is even more lame. Throw it in the ID scrap heap along with Vinnie Bag O Donuts. It's not T &amp; T, it's D &amp; D - dumb and dumber. Earnings on Tuesday. Prepare to assume the position. I'm sure you remember how...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349988535803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:48:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349988758963-144</Id><Title>New closing LOW for INTC</Title><Msg>Just when you thought things were getting better ....They get worse. Is there a pattern here? Only greater fools pay more than $19 for INTC, especially when nobody's buying PC anymore. Say good bye to that dividend, after which INTC should be where it belongs, $12. :</Msg><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1349988758963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:52:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349989180572-145</Id><Title>AMD Announces Preliminary Third Quarter Results - BAD</Title><Msg>Revenue Expected to Decrease Approximately 10 Percent Sequentially; Gross Margin Expected to Be Approximately 31 Percent SUNNYVALE, CA--(Marketwire - Oct 11, 2012) - AMD ( NYSE : AMD ) today announced that revenue for the third quarter ended September 29, 2012 is expected to decrease approximately 10 percent sequentially. The company previously forecasted third quarter 2012 revenue to decrease 1 percent, plus or minus 3 percent, sequentially. The lower than anticipated preliminary revenue results are primarily due to weaker than expected demand across all product lines caused by the challenging macroeconomic environment. The company now expects third quarter gross margin to be approximately 31 percent; less than the previous expectation of approximately 44 percent primarily due to an inventory write-down of approximately $100 million due to lower anticipated future demand for certain products. Third quarter gross margin was also negatively impacted by weaker than expected demand, which contributed to lower than anticipated average selling prices (ASPs) for the company's Computing Solutions Group products and lower than expected utilization of its back-end manufacturing facilities. Operating expenses for the third quarter are expected to decline approximately 7 percent sequentially as a result of tightly controlled expenses in the quarter. AMD will report third quarter 2012 results after market close on Thursday, October 18, 2012.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349989180572</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:59:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349989326318-146</Id><Topic><Title>New closing LOW for INTC</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1349988758963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:52:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New closing low? Since October 4, 2011...well ok Then it preceded to rally $4</Msg><Username>wbobeli</Username><Timestamp>1349989326318</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:02:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349989647053-147</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT: Desperate Marcopubio, part 2</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1349791661015</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:07:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He needs Intel to go to 12 so he can pay for his wife's funeral....lol..........yikes.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1349989647053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:07:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349989656097-148</Id><Topic><Title>New closing LOW for INTC</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1349988758963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:52:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is a beast and a buy !</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349989656097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:07:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349989970069-149</Id><Topic><Title>intel's future</Title><Username>freeland001</Username><Timestamp>1349963572643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has been leading the industry in silicon techology and manufacturing since the 1990. I have strong respect for Intel's technology leadership but taht's not the answer. Do the math....if Intel wins all of Qualcomm's mobile business and there is a 1:1 trade of smartphone vs. PC, would Intel be growing or shrinking? What if it is 2:1 trade (i.e., 2 smartphone win for 1 PC loss)? Reality is that the ASP is much lower in the smartphone/Tablet space. Therefore, if smartphone and tablets cannibalize PCs, Intel's revenue will decline even if it wins a signficant amount of mobile business. Before you say "but the margins are good", Intel's massive technology and manufacturing machine needs a huge amount of REVENUE and MARGIN to feed I am TOTALLY for Intel to go agresive in the smartphone/tablet space but I am cautioning it is not a penacea</Msg><Username>billsuxx</Username><Timestamp>1349989970069</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:12:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349990306473-150</Id><Title>AMD warning</Title><Msg>looks like Intel grabbed market share from AMD !!!!!</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1349990306473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:18:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349990336318-151</Id><Title>Where's that Seeking Alpha idiot Ashraf?</Title><Msg>He said he was scooping up AMD shares a week or so ago and also went from saying nothing good about Intel to nothing but bad things about it.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1349990336318</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:18:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349990411270-152</Id><Title>JBHT</Title><Msg>Up 5.4% after hours. PE=22.71 and 1% div. Forward PE=18. Just like YUM but just met earnings.YUM PE=20.56 and 2% div. Forward PE=18. INTC PE=9.4 and 4.1% div. Forward PE=10. What the @#$% is wrong with this picture. AAPL PE=14.76,QCOM PE=17.45,ARMH PE=56.56. Sooner or later, one either comes down or the other goes up.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349990411270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:20:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349990464494-153</Id><Title>Do some math on AMD</Title><Msg>AMD forecasts a 10% revenue decline for a company exclusively in the low end PC market. INTC is only about 40% PC. (40% servers, high end, + 20% other). A worst case 4% revenue decline for INTC is 4%*15 $G = $200 Million, much less than their warning, and much less than what analanalysts are predicting..</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349990464494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:21:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349990528701-154</Id><Topic><Title>New closing LOW for INTC</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1349988758963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:52:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>every prior time that INTC rallied, the markets as a whole were oversold, ie back in June, the qqq were at rsi 30, ditto INTC, the rally up in INTC stopped, the rally to higher highs in the QQQ did not. each recent oversold rsi 30 bounce in INTC has led to only a bounce, then a lower low, creating massive overhead resistance at all those this is the Bottom calls of Wally's who would love to get back out. At current price levels, the SMH is not down at rsi 30, nor is the QQQ.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349990528701</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349990659736-155</Id><Topic><Title>Do some math on AMD</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349990464494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:21:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Revenue decline would most likely be negligible. I expect EPS to be around 52 cents.</Msg><Username>warmninja</Username><Timestamp>1349990659736</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:24:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349990665690-156</Id><Topic><Title>Do some math on AMD</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349990464494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:21:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They're counting on people not doing the math and scaring them out of their shares. They count on fear and lazyness to do their own research to pry the shares away from them.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349990665690</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:24:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349990715955-157</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you shared this to us.</Msg><Username>piarjmo92755</Username><Timestamp>1349990715955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:25:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349990753016-158</Id><Topic><Title>Do some math on AMD</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349990464494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:21:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then you must be expecting a very large margin decreas. I expect neither, so my earnings are a beat at around $0.60. Stock should be at $26-$28.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349990753016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349991263017-159</Id><Topic><Title>Do some math on AMD</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349990464494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:21:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go the the AMD board this is Intel.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349991263017</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:34:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349991326902-160</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>scam</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349991326902</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:35:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349991347348-161</Id><Topic><Title>AMD just warned</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349988010475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:40:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imitation is the sincerest form of flattery.... hey freakshow...... If you remember I sold in a few days for around $100 loss on the HPQ. Admitted it was a mistake and took the loss. Look at what it's done since then. I've moved on freakshow, what is your problem?</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349991347348</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:35:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349991439169-162</Id><Topic><Title>All the Risk on the Short Side</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349821530787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:25:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>soooo that makes you THE Turd...learn to spell idiot.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349991439169</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349991449768-163</Id><Topic><Title>Scuttle on Along Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349964977317</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:16:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorties will suffer major PAIN next week</Msg><Username>imdacynic</Username><Timestamp>1349991449768</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:37:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349991560974-164</Id><Topic><Title>AMD just warned</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349988010475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:40:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you think I'm worried because I'm down 7¢ you're wrong. I do think the market is heading much lower but not so much INTC. I'm wanting to buy some stocks on the cheap. Bout' time this Fed inflated bubble ended.</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349991560974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:39:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349992041354-165</Id><Topic><Title>New closing LOW for INTC</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1349988758963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:52:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I tend to agree . not much holding this dog up.</Msg><Username>lt1warrior</Username><Timestamp>1349992041354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:47:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349992222835-166</Id><Topic><Title>Do some math on AMD</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349990464494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:21:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DUH...when I read a post like yours I realize that it is better to sit in the woods and talk to tree stumps.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349992222835</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349993027345-167</Id><Topic><Title>AMD just warned</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349988010475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:40:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Herbal, I would not count of a market going down a lot and INTC going up at the same time. In the bear market that started in 2007, semiconductors were down substantially more than the qqq. smh went down 66 percent, INTC took out the March 03 low in March of 09. There is massive overhead resistance in INTC, 23.00 was a former support point. hope you do get a bounce, but if the fed inflated bubble does burst, you do not want to be long any semi stock. checked the SMH chart, not rsi 30 yet, but close.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349993027345</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 18:03:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349993949226-168</Id><Title>INTEL a strong buy</Title><Msg>While Intel (NASDAQ: INTC) shares have dipped nearly 11% since the company reduced guidance earlier this month, this has pushed the dividend yield to 4.2% and given investors an even more attractive entry point for this solid core holding. Not only does Intel continue to be one of the most skilled companies at managing its public face, its growth prospects are improving heading into the new year. New 3D Ivy chips under development will compete against QUALCOMM in the mobile space and its server division continues to grow. The company is scheduled to release earnings in mid-October, and I believe buying shares ahead of this announcement will prove solid in both the near and longer-terms.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349993949226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 18:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349994030038-169</Id><Topic><Title>AMD just warned</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349988010475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:40:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Herbal, I would not count of a market going down a lot and INTC going up at the same time ------------ I agree. INTC can't even gain ground in a rising market. HD's judgement is impaired. He's beginning to sound like Wallis. TOOOOO FUNNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349994030038</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 18:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349994284213-170</Id><Title>What better time to buy?</Title><Msg>Think about it...this company is the best chip designer and fabricator in the world. What better time to buy at these cheap levels when everyone is downgrading the stock and panicking over the PC being dead. Intel is a fast mover and its agility in design/fab is tested and established again and again. Once its 3D Ivy chips rule...if you are a device mfg and don't have one of these chips in it...guess what you will be left behind. Looking ahead into 2013 this stock will form a base soon and start to climb once it releases news on its latest mobile chips. In addition, while you wait you get paid a 4+ dividend. Thank you ANALysts for the cheap price.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349994284213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 18:24:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349995196121-171</Id><Topic><Title>What better time to buy?</Title><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349994284213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 18:24:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I certainly no of no better time to buy, but evidently we live in a world full of COMPLETE #$%$ who think the sky has fallen. Did I say ***COMPLETE #$%$*** with sufficient verve?</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349995196121</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 18:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349995325250-172</Id><Title>Open low @ $21.35 tomorrow</Title><Msg>Next week, INTC is looking for its new low below $20 and AMD will drag down INTC below $21 tomorrow</Msg><Username>pple64</Username><Timestamp>1349995325250</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 18:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349995521244-173</Id><Topic><Title>Fantastic Update for INTC . **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>fairclothcharles962</Username><Timestamp>1349806664263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:17:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>scam</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349995521244</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 18:45:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349996288177-174</Id><Topic><Title>What better time to buy?</Title><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349994284213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 18:24:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The markets have barely corrected, hardly a sky is falling scenario, only the worst buy and hold stocks in the technology sector have skidded back into bear markets, (down over 20 percent) ie semiconductor stocks, with a very distinct pattern of lower lows and lower highs. on the way up, 23.00 was pretty significant resistance, see a 3 year chart, on the way down, 23.00 offered short term support. If this dog bounces despite the move back down, 23 may be as good as it gets for a very long time. Waldo's sugar plum fairy dreams of 30, 50 are just that, Waldo's fantasy land. I do hope the longs get a relief rally, so they can get out before the next economic down cycle hits with a vengeance.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349996288177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 18:58:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349996542766-175</Id><Topic><Title>What better time to buy?</Title><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349994284213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 18:24:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The economy hasn't even started growing yet dummy. GDP is neutral at best and Europe is in shams. The Fed will continue to pump 40B into the system until the economy shines therefore the stock market has a bottom with the Fed on their side. This is not the markets we are used to its buy on dips until the Fed cuts out. You need to know the new now or you will never make money...no pain no gain.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349996542766</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 19:02:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349997402985-176</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm subscribed. Cool</Msg><Username>regancfpo542874</Username><Timestamp>1349997402985</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 19:16:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349997686159-177</Id><Topic><Title>What better time to buy?</Title><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349994284213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 18:24:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So a drop of over 25 percent is a dip, from 29, over 20 percent from the lofty 27.50, I'll bet kids would just love your ice cream cones.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349997686159</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 19:21:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350000641837-178</Id><Topic><Title>AMD just warned</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349988010475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:40:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the 4% dividend puts a floor under INTC. SMH will get crushed. Semi's are a leading indicator. I'm taking a very small gamble with INTC. IMO</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1350000641837</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 20:10:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350001035877-179</Id><Title>earnings is gonna hurt</Title><Msg>I hope, therefore I hurt. Holding for the long run.</Msg><Username>sharppolly</Username><Timestamp>1350001035877</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 20:17:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350002070748-180</Id><Topic><Title>the wish=risk on the long side</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349986809206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:20:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't dream on it, it will keep falling, check the history prices and its' funny performance, up one day and down ten days,down like a rock and up like a snail,and finally it's a cooked lobster----RED.</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1350002070748</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 20:34:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350003373106-181</Id><Topic><Title>earnings is gonna hurt</Title><Username>sharppolly</Username><Timestamp>1350001035877</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 20:17:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its gonna hurt you only if you bed over F&amp;g.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350003373106</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 20:56:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350004164558-182</Id><Topic><Title>intel's future</Title><Username>freeland001</Username><Timestamp>1349963572643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really don't understand what's going on, do you? This isn't like the RISC/x86 wars of the late 1980s / early 1990s. The big phone and tablet guys aren't interested in buying discrete CPU chips that virtually define their product for them. Like I said, they want to define the dies and the packaged chip for themselves. They also see no win in going down the PC commoditization path, where Intel defines all of the important hardware value and Microsoft (or now Google) takes the software value. So in your view its Intel / Android, and Apple, Samsung and everyone else just become packaging and logistics companies like the PC guys did? I doubt it. The world is different. When the PC was king there wasn't the IP or the tools or the integration technologies available like there are now. And at mobile volumes the cost of a mask set divides away quickly. ARM isn't the big winner beating Intel, it's the system-level guys adding the real value, and CPUs aren't much of a differentiator.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1350004164558</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 21:09:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350005430827-183</Id><Title>Ryan just CRUSHED Biden, LOL!</Title><Msg>Biden thinks he can roll his eyes and shake his head and laugh and act like Ryan is a little kid not worthy.......it won't work for all those un and underemployed. Biden just tried to pull out the 47% card and Ryan said "as Joe knows, sometimes things don't come out of your mouth the right way." LOL. The crowd howled in laughter. Biden is an idiot and trying to bully Ryan will backfire.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350005430827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 21:30:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350008611809-184</Id><Title>Biden basically just said he's religious when it's convenience for him.</Title><Msg>LOL! Lying through his teeth on the abortion issue.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350008611809</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 22:23:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350009443625-185</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan just CRUSHED Biden, LOL!</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350005430827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 21:30:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A very accurate assesment!</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350009443625</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 22:37:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350009762843-186</Id><Title>Smokin Joe Puts Ryan through a Hay Baler</Title><Msg>Wow, if that was a prize fight they would have stopped it early. Ryan was bleeding from every orifice...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350009762843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 22:42:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350010261781-187</Id><Topic><Title>Smokin Joe Puts Ryan through a Hay Baler</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350009762843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 22:42:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He came off as rude and smug..........typical Liberal. He whined about not getting enough time......but the time breakdown shows he got 41 minutes to Ryan's 40. LOL! Ryan was professional and kept his composure even though the botox and veneers were deafening. Joltin Joe's blatant lie about not getting enough info about what was going on in Libya won't sit well with A LOT of voters.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350010261781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 22:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350010821720-188</Id><Topic><Title>Smokin Joe Puts Ryan through a Hay Baler</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350009762843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 22:42:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WASHINGTON -- An hour into the debate, a survey of more than 300 debate watchers from across the political spectrum finds that Vice President Joe Biden is handily beating Rep. Paul Ryan (R-Wis.) by a margin of 65 percent to 35 percent.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350010821720</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 23:00:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350011473802-189</Id><Topic><Title>Smokin Joe Puts Ryan through a Hay Baler</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350009762843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 22:42:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't the way a bunch of us saw it. Bidn lost so many debate points with his smiles and mannerisms etc that I lost count. sorry Wally, keep up the good work with INTC updates.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350011473802</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 23:11:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350011494501-190</Id><Topic><Title>Smokin Joe Puts Ryan through a Hay Baler</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350009762843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 22:42:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've read resonse after response from people that said he was rude, childish and no wonder other countries hate us if that's how he handles himself. By the way, Wally, when's that Big Bird effect gonna start? OH wait, Big Bird IS mad...........at Obama. BWAH-AH-AH.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350011494501</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 23:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350011542002-191</Id><Topic><Title>Smokin Joe Puts Ryan through a Hay Baler</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350009762843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 22:42:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ha ha ha... your comment tells me that Joe crushed your loser Ryan.</Msg><Username>sabnis01</Username><Timestamp>1350011542002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 23:12:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350011602724-192</Id><Topic><Title>Smokin Joe Puts Ryan through a Hay Baler</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350009762843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 22:42:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, that's what I thought about the first debate.LOL At least we can agree on Intel...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350011602724</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 23:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350012125652-193</Id><Topic><Title>Biden basically just said he's religious when it's convenience for him.</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350008611809</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 22:23:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting. Biden said that his beliefs conformed to his Catholic doctrine. Same as Ryan. The difference seemed to be that Ryan wants to impose his beliefs on everyone where Biden doesn't. Ryan just does not believe that others deserve the freedom and liberty protected by the Constitution.</Msg><Username>dumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1350012125652</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 23:22:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350012846463-194</Id><Title>with a few exceptions the posters in here</Title><Msg>know nothing..NOTHING..nada..zilch... and are completely devoid of common sense,and basic arithmetic math skills.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350012846463</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 23:34:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350014283133-195</Id><Topic><Title>Smokin Joe Puts Ryan through a Hay Baler</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350009762843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 22:42:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>even the 1 you like to sniff around?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350014283133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 23:58:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>