<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354338389640-1</Id><Topic><Title>Will Microsoft cancel Windows RT surface tablets?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1354336352735</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 23:32:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Upstream supply chain sees Surface RT orders cut by half IT + CE | Nov 28, 21:28 The upstream supply chain of Microsoft's Surface RT has recently seen the tablet's orders reduced by half, and with other Windows RT-based tablet orders also seeing weak performance, sources from the upstream supply chain believe the new operating system may not perform as well as expected in the ma...</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1354338389640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 00:06:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354338451959-2</Id><Topic><Title>Why ARM servers don't seem to be threatening...</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1354256604568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 01:23:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>".even if it is their own designed core, it doesn't come free. They need to spend R&amp;D/Engineering dollars to design them....so they have costs..." "Whereas, Intel can mop it up from all 3 areas....IP, design, as well as fabrication." --------------------------------------------------------- INtel licenses Power VR for their GPUs... INtel pays NVidia a royalty for their GPU patents...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1354338451959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 00:07:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354340461850-3</Id><Topic><Title>Wally</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1354286886018</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 09:48:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haswell: Still appears to be projected for March to June 2013 Intel’s Haswell is an unprecedented threat to Nvidia, AMD Intel’s next-generation architecture, codenamed Haswell, isn’t just another “tock” in Intel’s tick/tock cadence; it’s a serious threat to both AMD and Nvidia. For the first time, Intel is poised to challenge both companies in the mainstream graphics market while simultaneously eroding Nvidia’s edge in the GPGPU business. Its low-power, 10W TDP ULV parts will challenge the price/performance ratio of AMD’s second-generation Brazos SoC (codenamed Kabini) as well as any ARM-based Windows 8 notebooks that companies like Qualcomm might bring to market. *** Intel's Haswell CPUs will fit in everything from tablets to servers An improved GPU and lower power consumption make for a versatile chip. If Intel's upcoming Atom processors are getting serious about competing with Cortex A9 and A15-based ARM processors, then Haswell is about giving us tablets in a whole new class of performance—benchmarks for Ivy Bridge Ultrabooks are five or six times higher than they are for the quad-core Tegra 3 in the Nexus 7, just to pick an example. ARM is still superior from a power usage standpoint, since even at full-tilt ARM SoCs are still sipping power compared to x86 SoCs, but the option to have that kind of performance in a tablet would be mighty tempting to a lot of companies and consumers. All of that is to say nothing of the advancements that Haswell will bring to laptops and Ultrabooks, which stand to gain both better battery life and integrated graphics that you'd actually want to use for gaming; to desktops, which will be both more power-efficient and powerful than before; and to servers, which of course stand to benefit from all the power and performance enhancements of the consumer devices. Intel's confusing portfolio aside, Haswell looks like another solid incremental improvement on what came before. Intel is taking a "mobile first" approach to Haswell's launch, which means that laptops and tablets should be the first devices to see these processors when they launch in early 2013.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354340461850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 00:41:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354341150528-4</Id><Topic><Title>Wally</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1354286886018</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 09:48:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel LTE: Projected "early" in 2013 Next year will see 22nm, new architecture dual core SoC with 4G LTE on a chip, or nearby, with much higher performance and much lower power. Does Intel Have A Mobile Strategy? Judge For Yourself Intel investors have repeatedly heard over the past two years that "Intel missed the mobile business," or that "Intel doesn't have a mobile strategy." Intel is the world's largest semiconductor manufacturer, routinely producing its products with, by far, the most advanced manufacturing process technology and processor architecture technology. It would be reasonable for investors to expect that a company with the resources of Intel would have something better than a primitive mobile strategy. Let's take a look at the progress to date. Early this year, Intel announced several non-U.S. partners in the mobile business. One of these is Lenovo, which is in the process of passing Hewlett-Packard as the world's largest PC manufacturer. As such, we can assume that Lenovo and Intel have "met." Lenovo has also entered the smartphone business with some impressive results: In last year's third quarter, the company had a 1.7% share of the market, according to Gartner. A year later, the company was ranked second in China's smartphone market for the third quarter, with a 14.8% share. This put it right behind Samsung, which had a 16.7% share. 'We know that Lenovo is one of the strongest local companies in China,' said Gartner analyst Sandy Shen on Wednesday. 'But we just didn't expect the change to come so fast... We thought it would take them several years to grow their business in mobile devices.' Lenovo grew 870% in smartphones in a single year and shipped 7 million smartphones in the third quarter. Intel has also entered into agreements with Google to make Android and x86 more compatible. Intel has entered into a comprehensive agreement with Google's Motorola Mobility business unit. The results of that agreement are just now being recognized. Motorola has introduced the Intel-powered Razr i in Europe as a complement to the nearly identical non-Intel Razr M in the U.S. Motorola is also releasing an Intel-powered smartphone in China through China Mobile, the world's largest mobile service provider with over 700 million subscribers. Yes, that number is twice the entire population of the U.S. This phone carries the Intel Z2460 and an Intel baseband chip. The Lava ZOLO carries Intel parts to India, another market of "interest". Orange brings Intel SoCs to the U.K. Even Russia gets some Intel smartphone parts. Not bad for a company with "no strategy." None of these smartphones are market leaders or iPhone killers. They are mid-market, inexpensive, capable smartphones. All of these products use the Z2460 Medfield SoC. This device is a four-year-old architecture manufactured on Intel's trailing edge (but cheap) 32nm process. Next year will see 22nm, new architecture dual core SoC with 4G LTE on a chip, or nearby, with much higher performance and much lower power. Since there is a dire shortage of 28nm devices from TSMC, what is available is going into high-end phones, primarily in the U.S. Because of the above situation, we could get a pleasant surprise regarding the international progress of Intel's mobile effort. The Intel 32nm devices are built on fully depreciated production lines. Depreciation on state-of-the-art fabs could run as high as $2,000 per wafer. I would expect the Z2460 has a manufacturing cost of less than $4 and a selling price of $8-$10. That would be tough for competitors to match, especially in a 28nm shortage environment. Obviously, the Intel strategy does not include the U.S. at this time due to the lack of a 4G LTE solution. That problem is expected to go away by the end of the year. The strategy cannot include Samsung or Apple since devices for both companies are produced by Samsung. What's left is Google and Motorola. Low-cost international phone makers in immense markets are being addressed by Intel in a very capable way. Early next year we should see some truly market-leading smartphone products from Motorola (Google) utilizing the dual core Z2580 SoC. The 2012 strategy has been to begin penetration of the world beyond the U.S., and Intel seems to be knocking on the right doors. The 2013 strategy will include the U.S. Someday, the Apple fab business will come Intel's way as well. In the end, Intel will have a near monopoly in mobile just as it does in PCs and servers. The company doesn't know any other way. As Paul Otellini transitions into retirement, I would say, "Job well done."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354341150528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 00:52:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354341495231-5</Id><Topic><Title>Wally</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1354286886018</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 09:48:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel LTE: Projected "early" in 2013 Next year will see 22nm, new architecture dual core SoC with 4G LTE on a chip, or nearby, with much higher performance and much lower power. Early next year we should see some truly market-leading smartphone products from Motorola (Google) utilizing the dual core Z2580 SoC. The 2012 strategy has been to begin penetration of the world beyond the U.S., and Intel seems to be knocking on the right doors. The 2013 strategy will include the U.S. Someday, the Apple fab business will come Intel's way as well. Google "Does Intel Have A Mobile Strategy? Judge For Yourself" for an interesting read on Intel's smartphone prospects...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354341495231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 00:58:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354342439616-6</Id><Title>Facts Chump Street Chooses to Ignore</Title><Msg>Samsung’s contract to provide chips to Apple expires in 2014...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354342439616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:13:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354342902455-7</Id><Title>Per Forbes</Title><Msg>Intel Should Be A $33 Stock As The Market Overlooks Its Dominance</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354342902455</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:21:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354343022252-8</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL SEE A $18 HANDLE NEXT WEEK</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1354324553680</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:15:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i agree the pc is on its last run.there is nothing to promote anyone to buy. You have to understand the big picture people !!!!!!</Msg><Username>lt1warrior</Username><Timestamp>1354343022252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:23:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354343063235-9</Id><Title>Is Intel Apple’s Newest Buddy?</Title><Msg>Apple is trying to reduce its processor supply dependence on Samsung and is in talks with Intel to take over, RBC Capital analyst Doug Freedman said. However, Freedman added that the start of any relationship between Apple and Intel will be accompanied by significant changes for both companies, Fortune said. Why Would Apple Need to Switch Suppliers? Speculation is already rife about the Apple-Samsung supply relationship because of the two companies’ fierce rivalry in the smartphone and tablet market. According to the analyst, another potential problem is that Apple’s demand for mobile processors is set to surpass Samsung’s capabilities by next year. Freedman’s colleague Amit Daryanani had earlier written in a research note of his own that Intel was a possible alternative for Apple, along with TSMC and GloFo. How May Apple and Intel Be Affected? Of the three, Intel had “the upper-hand due to the limitations of capacity at alternative sources” to land Apple’s $2 billion chip-making contract, Freedman said. For a potential deal with Apple to go through, Intel will have to build chips based on the ARM structure for the iPhone and iPod touch. So far, Intel has only built chips based on its own x86 architecture. Apple, in turn, may have to switch the iPad’s processor to x86. How Does the News Affect the Stocks? The news will come as a positive one for Intel, considering the estimated size of the contract and the added connection with Apple’s bestselling products. Apple shareholders will not be impressed by the talk of possible uncertainty vis-à-vis a critical product component, but a reduced dependence on Samsung is not really bad news.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354343063235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:24:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354343129603-10</Id><Topic><Title>Facts Chump Street Chooses to Ignore</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354342439616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:13:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL) is trying to reduce its processor supply dependence on Samsung and is in talks with Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) to take over, RBC Capital analyst Doug Freedman said. However, Freedman added that the start of any relationship between Apple and Intel will be accompanied by significant changes for both companies, Fortune said.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354343129603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:25:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354343162158-11</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer said Sell INTC at $19.25</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1354298021769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:53:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>uh yea , that would be a wise thing to do</Msg><Username>lt1warrior</Username><Timestamp>1354343162158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:26:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354343185484-12</Id><Topic><Title>Facts Chump Street Chooses to Ignore</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354342439616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:13:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How May Apple and Intel Be Affected? Of the three, Intel had “the upper-hand due to the limitations of capacity at alternative sources” to land Apple’s $2 billion chip-making contract, Freedman said. For a potential deal with Apple to go through, Intel will have to build chips based on the ARM (NASDAQ:ARMH) structure for the iPhone and iPod touch. So far, Intel has only built chips based on its own x86 architecture. Apple, in turn, may have to switch the iPad’s processor to x86.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354343185484</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:26:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354343451818-13</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL SEE A $18 HANDLE NEXT WEEK</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1354324553680</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:15:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You have to understand the big picture people !!!!!!" [Yeah, we do because you don't...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354343451818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:30:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354343948751-14</Id><Topic><Title>INTC ready to rumble = Strong BUY</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1354286247126</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 09:37:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And what do you base your reasoning for a strong buy ? pc is on the decline. intc is not ready to do anything.</Msg><Username>lt1warrior</Username><Timestamp>1354343948751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:39:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354348308256-15</Id><Title>Microsoft is spending billions in marketing, trying to ram Win 8</Title><Msg>down peoples throat. This time, they may not succeed. Microsoft software has always been difficult to use, but people had no choice but to use it. Now there is a choice. Win 8 UI designed by nerds for nerds, with Ballmer RAMMING that crap down peoples throat. LOL.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354348308256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 02:51:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354348589513-16</Id><Title>Intel will not fab ARM chips for Apple. To do so, will mean</Title><Msg>the death of the x86, and Intel's high margins. Intel's only choice is to make the x86 better than ARM in all respects including pricing. Which will make it a compelling choice in the cuthroat mobile component market. Eco systems can be penetrated thru pricing. Thats what AMD did to Intel the last 10 years.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354348589513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 02:56:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354362827809-17</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will not fab ARM chips for Apple. To do so, will mean</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354348589513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 02:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am sure you haven't read anything becasue you are an idiot. The deal is INTC fabs ARMH chips for Iphones, and AAPL agrees to x86 atoms in their tablets. Its a win-win. Duhh.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354362827809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 06:53:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354363065879-18</Id><Title>Intel fabs ARMH for AAPL Iphones; AAPL uses atom in Tablets</Title><Msg>That's gonna be the deal. I have wanted to say this for sometime (recall att4glte what I said a few months back, that BIG news was coming? Well, here it is) Hopefully deal won't snag..INTC is being very firm as they don't want to lose their roadmap in the process...AAPL is free to join them. If AAPL isn't run by idiots (and without Jobs it ain't so clear) they'll sign on the dotted. If Jobs were still around this deal would've been done a year ago.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363065879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 06:57:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354363165482-19</Id><Title>Oh, and, PC is NOT on a decline</Title><Msg>maybe someday we'll get back to common sense. Until then you have the investment oppty of a lifetime: Buy INTC.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363165482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 06:59:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354363260107-20</Id><Title>INTC is a $100 stock</Title><Msg>Once the street gets it, this thing will go up and overshoot.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363260107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 07:01:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354363357684-21</Id><Topic><Title>Oh, and, PC is NOT on a decline</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363165482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 06:59:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing we know is in decline, for sure, is the average IQ of people who work at Goldman-Sachs and market news commentators.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363357684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 07:02:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354366553230-22</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will not fab ARM chips for Apple. To do so, will mean</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354348589513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 02:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC fabs ARMH chips for Iphones ============= Temporarily perhaps. But with a transition to x86 down the road. Both Otellini and CFO Stacy Smith have indicated that x86 cores is the end-goal...but they are willing to accommodate and help implement the transition from ARM to x86.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1354366553230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 07:55:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354368186208-23</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will not fab ARM chips for Apple. To do so, will mean</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354348589513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 02:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly what I was about to say. They also said that custom IP such as Apple's A series processors can be wrapped around their x86 cores, so we might see some unique x86 CPUs in Apple's line up as well. "If you build it, they will come." -field of dreams Seems to me Intel will have a whole lot of capacity for building 14nm and below by 2014, way more than analysts project for their own products.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354368186208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 08:23:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354368644434-24</Id><Topic><Title>Oh, and, PC is NOT on a decline</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363165482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 06:59:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The talking heads don't do DD they repeat the garbage others such as GS spew. PC market is slowing, only growing a downward revised 0.6% in 2012. The macro conditions attributing to this are going to be a thing of the past, sooner than most people think. The Euro and Yen will need to become weaker, the people who have been trying to prevent this will be voted out soon, central banks will take care of the rest. A new era is about to begin, literally. Welcome to the age of Aquarius kiddos.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354368644434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 08:30:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354368954805-25</Id><Topic><Title>Intel fabs ARMH for AAPL Iphones; AAPL uses atom in Tablets</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363065879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 06:57:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These things take time, I would not be surprised to find out that Jobs was involved early on. Don't be too sure that Atom will power the iPad, Haswell or Broadwell may very well be power efficient enough, the ULV versions anyhow. I've been saying this for years.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354368954805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 08:35:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354370202258-26</Id><Title>Things that happen on Hussein Obama's watch</Title><Msg>Kinky Sex Club approved at Harvard by a bunch of scathing Liberals without morals.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354370202258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 08:56:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354370936685-27</Id><Topic><Title>Oh, and, PC is NOT on a decline</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363165482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 06:59:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I meant to emphasize that 0.6% growth is still growth, and therefore not on a decline. I agree.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354370936685</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 09:08:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354371320288-28</Id><Topic><Title>Intel fabs ARMH for AAPL Iphones; AAPL uses atom in Tablets</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363065879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 06:57:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I could see intel providing chips for the ipads. The mini is taking market share from the larger ipad because it does the same things and cost half as much. Put a clovertrail (maybe a haswell next fall) in the larger ipad that runs the mac os. These would compete with window 8 tablets. Put clovertrail in the mini and run the ios (like clovertrail runs andriod). The iphone will continue to use arm chip and tsmc will manufacture those.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1354371320288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 09:15:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354371744569-29</Id><Topic><Title>I hate to say it</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1354221073207</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 15:31:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf, don't listen to idiots and their whining. Finger pointing and name calling is for grade school children, not adults. You were right to be concerned, as was I. As soon as I learned of the downgrade while watching INTC slide in pre-market, I sold 100% of my shares. I even pulled my 19.55 lowball bid and decided to wait another day, and then went all in at 19.43 again yesterday. This happened to be $.01 away from the bottom, which means I got very lucky as this almost never happens, at least not for me. A GS downgrade is expected for INTC, happens each and every year without fail, usually at or near the bottom of it's trading range. I seriously doubt the $16 target is even close to reality, at worst a re-test of the 52 week low may be in the cards. To the idiots bashing you, I offer this advice, listen to Ashraf in regard to the technology and long term stock outlook. I have yet to read any article or forum post of his which indicates that he is day trading, or that he is offering day trading advice. GLTA.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354371744569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 09:22:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354372583576-30</Id><Title>INTC traders add MU to your watch list</Title><Msg>This is not a buy/sell recommendation, disclosure I am long MU. The Elpida take-over will be finalized in 2013, this should be a catalyst for big gains. Analysts project EPS growth of 350%, granted they have been losing money, but others have gone bankrupt and they had enough cash to buy Elpida effectively doubling their size and propelling them to #2 in the DRAM market, ahead of Hynix and second only to Samsung. Some other catalysts include DDR4 which will be available starting in Q1 2013 and be mainstream by 2014, Hybrid Memory Cube which should be ready by 2015, also SSD and NAND which are increasingly replacing HDD's and provide far better stability and speed. MU is trading near 52 week lows, and with more than 50% upside potential as the consensus price target is above $10. GLTA.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354372583576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 09:36:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354372761946-31</Id><Title>Intel's technology partner Micron</Title><Msg>This is not a buy/sell recommendation, disclosure I am long MU. The Elpida take-over will be finalized in 2013, this should be a catalyst for big gains. Analysts project EPS growth of 350%, granted they have been losing money, but others have gone bankrupt and they had enough cash to buy Elpida effectively doubling their size and propelling them to #2 in the DRAM market, ahead of Hynix and second only to Samsung. Some other catalysts include DDR4 which will be available starting in Q1 2013 and be mainstream by 2014, Hybrid Memory Cube which should be ready by 2015, also SSD and NAND which are increasingly replacing HDD's and provide far better stability and speed. MU is trading near 52 week lows, and with more than 50% upside potential as the consensus price target is above $10. GLTA.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354372761946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 09:39:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354374797281-32</Id><Title>Hey Greg Lynn</Title><Msg>How about all those abusive and heckling posts on the ARM board about how you were going to short it from high 20's to single digits. How's that working out for you, loud mouth?</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354374797281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:13:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354374845764-33</Id><Title>Intel's systemic problems</Title><Msg>Till the late 90s, Intel was a thriving company. After that, all the smart people left, most of them rich from the phenomenal growth of the stock in the preceding years. Since then, smart people haven't been joining Intel. Stock option grants have become worthless and Intel only pays about market average. Therefore, Intel went from being the employer of choice to a second option. In the past, you had smart people who could cut through the layers of process in corporate communications and get their ideas across. Not so any longer. With the mediocre engineers that started working there, people started hiding behind the process and it became much like a third world bureaucracy -- lots of process and little forward motion. That is still the situation today. It's a chicken and egg problem for Intel. If they can get their stock growing again, better engineers will choose to join them which will rekindle the spirit of innovation that once used to be there. But to get their stock growing again, they need better engineers than the ones they currently have.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354374845764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:14:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354375332339-34</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is a $100 stock</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363260107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 07:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Man, they really need to make people pass IQ tests before posting!</Msg><Username>stlcardsfan30</Username><Timestamp>1354375332339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:22:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354375379355-35</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Greg Lynn</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354374797281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:13:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARMH will trade below $10, it's only a matter of time. As I've already responded to you on this same exact question (do you have adult ADD?) here it goes again. I covered my short from $30 at $24, could have held on longer for even more profit but I never ever get upset when I make money. Only once have I lost money shorting ARMH and that was this week as I underestimated the momentum carrying it. I lost just about 10% of what I have already made shorting that PIG. I will short it again soon.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354375379355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:22:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354375494457-36</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's systemic problems</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354374845764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:14:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In your very limited and very finite wisdom can you point to a product of Intel's 'poor' engineers ? Frankly all the words above were a complete waste of time reading as they don't reflect anything that resembles reality in the real world.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1354375494457</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:24:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354376031728-37</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Greg Lynn</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354374797281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:13:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you miss me on the ARMH board? I posted there again just for you. As I have always said, ARM is a decent technology and will always have a place in the market for cheap toys and so will never go bankrupt, in the future look for ARM in Hasbro and Fisher Price, but their days as market leader in smart phones is going to end when performance/watt for Intel powered devices is overwhelmingly better, this will happen at 14nm but possibly sooner than that. PS: how fast do you think ARMH will drop after the Apple deal is announced?</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354376031728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:33:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354376104360-38</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's systemic problems</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354374845764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:14:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Low power IA</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354376104360</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:35:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354376506403-39</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is a $100 stock</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363260107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 07:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At current earnings levels, this would give Intel a trailing P/E of less than 50, still cheaper than ARMH in comparison.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354376506403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:41:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354376770665-40</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's systemic problems</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354374845764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:14:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Okay, point me to the exact benchmarks/reviews where you think these products, currently Medfield and Clovertrail, are poor and I don't mean your general hand waving comments. Let's discuss specifics.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1354376770665</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:46:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354376969699-41</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's systemic problems</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354374845764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:14:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Project started around 2006. 2012 market share ~0.2%</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354376969699</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:49:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354378297332-42</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's systemic problems</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354374845764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:14:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's just smartphones in the first half of 2012 when the phones were only just introduced and does not include the tablet/netbook market which Atom has always had a sizable share of, about a billion dollars of chips sold each year. Atom was not really targeted for phones when first envisioned as there is not much profit in phone chips which is why Intel sold the Xscale phone business in the first place and which had 35% of the market in 2004 ... internetnewsDOTcom/dev-news/article.php/3079201/Intel+Unveils+Next+Round+of+Mobile+XScale+Chips.htm Marvell is only a $4bn company with this phone business so as you can see Intel is interested in making money not scoring points with fanbois.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1354378297332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:11:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354378702922-43</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's systemic problems</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354374845764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:14:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess what you're saying is that we should only look at Atom's success with netbooks as an indicator of success for low power IA and not the phone chip market which was always too small for Intel to be interested in.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354378702922</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:18:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354379697033-44</Id><Title>PFE going down - single digits here we come</Title><Msg>lipitor going generic, no more blockbusters....$15 today but soon single digits coming...mark my words bag holders...divvy bye-bye.... ooops, wrong board, wrong time.....sorry about that</Msg><Username>quantuon</Username><Timestamp>1354379697033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:34:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354381446629-45</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is a $100 stock</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363260107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 07:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you can buy a practice book from amazon and get started.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354381446629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 12:04:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354381812746-46</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's systemic problems</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354374845764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:14:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>khitchdee, you are the biggest idiot on these boards. And that is saying a lot, given such notables as att4glte and all the lucy's (of which you may be one).</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354381812746</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 12:10:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354382523146-47</Id><Topic><Title>Facts Chump Street Chooses to Ignore</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354342439616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:13:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Wally, holding INTC from the lofty heights of 24.00 since June 2010, and not a penny of gains to show for it. Old dogs are supposed to learn new skills, not relying on skill sets that fail to provide results, akin to being happy with a "10 figure dividend" which means a 100 figure drop in capital since the loft price of 29.20, a loss of more than the ten figure dividend in market value during the Thursday drop of .56. Only fools hold any semi stock as long term investments, a habit a certain old fool should definitely learn to break.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1354382523146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 12:22:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354383123010-48</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will not fab ARM chips for Apple. To do so, will mean</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354348589513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 02:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes Mr Flux. You are correct. The deal they are negotiating is Intel Fabs Iphone Arm chips and Apple uses Intel X86 chips in all of its Ipads, and Macs. Likely, although there was no news on the negotiations, Intel sets power and benchmarks for the Intel chips where by Apple agrees to use Intel chips for its Iphones as well. Apple? It wants some exclusivity from Intel on the X86 chips to be used with Iphones in the future and that would mean Intel making an Intel chip designed to work at a premium for Apple Iphones and sold only to Apple. Intel would at the same time be making chips for Motorola and its other buyers of Intel phone chips. Obviously the market does not believe this rumor yet. Because the minute the markets see this deal being made, Intel shoots up 25% and then makes it to 30 in a couple of weeks. Do I believe the rumor? YES--they are in talks and that is true. But whether or not they make a deal is something no one knows yet. I sure would be laughing at the shorts that day though if it happened.</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1354383123010</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 12:32:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354383397116-49</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's systemic problems</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354374845764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:14:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Something like that but if you want to be super critical 2011 was the date Medfield was originally planned to be released as a competitive phone chip but Nokia screwed that idea with the dropping of Meego. So Intel then had to spend about a year doing an Android and ARM emulator port and building a reference phone which was a good recovery from Plan A. MSFT doing a not so subtle architectural takeover of Nokia was not really foreseeable when the Medfield ecosystem was originally being planned. The important thing for Intel in 2013 on the mobile front is having a clear successor to the netbook chips with Clovertrail which has brought power down to ARM levels while still keeping the relatively high x86 performance. Clovertrail is in time for the whole Windows 8 touch screen evolution and has probably killed Windows RT at birth. Any phone chips Intel sells in 2013 will just be icing on that cake. 2014, when the 22nm generation is released is when Atom goes on the offensive deep in ARM territory in Android and phone marketshare.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1354383397116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 12:36:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354383596473-50</Id><Topic><Title>PFE going down - single digits here we come</Title><Username>quantuon</Username><Timestamp>1354379697033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:34:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was going to say, go back to playing your toys, lol such a post on INTC is a wrold away</Msg><Username>nysstocks</Username><Timestamp>1354383596473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 12:39:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354385198989-51</Id><Topic><Title>PFE going down - single digits here we come</Title><Username>quantuon</Username><Timestamp>1354379697033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:34:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorts are lowlife parasites not investors IMO no matter where they post.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1354385198989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 13:06:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354385260817-52</Id><Title>OK---Intel stock has sucked for 12 years. The CEO was pushed out. An inflexion point is here.</Title><Msg>Inflection point, a curve and a start of a change. The stock is priced as if Intel was going to go down and was never going to recover. Why is it the street mob has this view? Phone chips and Apple. Apple is seen as an Intel killer. Apple has a fanatic following in the stock market and since it went from 20 to 700, one cannot blame these Apple droids for being religiously connected to Apple. BUT--it is not just Apple, Intel is not seen in volume in any smart phones yet. Android based phones in America are NOT using Intel chips. NO good news is being priced into Intel shares. So to my point. Inflection point--the curve or change--it is here. Intel has removed its CEO. A new CEO will be much younger and ready to push Intel into areas where it has never gone before. The markets? Well they respond to money. Likely Intel will have breathtaking profits in the years ahead after it gets into volume production of phone chips. In fact, likely the phone chips will become just another branch of a computer chip and the phone will become just a talking computer machine in your pocket. The new CEO might push Intel into retail and have Intel making its own Phones for sale. What? You cannot do that? Why not--Apple and Samsung already do that. Near term---a deal with Apple could be announced. Stock would go up 50% or more soon after that announcement. Google-Motorola phones with Intel chips start shipping in the spring. Great news. Yes shorty has done well with Intel from 29 down to 19. But that idiot James Cavello will never see his 16 on Intel. When a n Apple deal or Motorola shipments start--30 and higher fast.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1354385260817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 13:07:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354385445382-53</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's systemic problems</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354374845764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:14:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Low power IA was origionally touted as Intel's home-grown answer to ARM and XScale because the instruction set didn't matter and it was all in the micro-architecture. Intel's vision at that time was to provide IA based chips across the spectrum of power usage scenarios. Now the pitch seems to be more its targeted at netbooks and tablets and to a lesser extent phones. The project vision has changed -- signs of a failed project. They couldn't get the power low enough in time.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354385445382</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 13:10:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354385478295-54</Id><Title>Poor Wdblawgrow</Title><Msg>Another passionate post from him today expressing how horny he gets when he can hide behind a computer and kick people in the teeth when they are down............but we must not forget his debacle from last year. He bought Intel at 19.58, sold it hours later at 19.78, paid maximum capital gains on a pitiful gain, scolded Longs for not following his charts, promised everyone that it would take YEARS, if EVER, for Intel to reach 24 again....................and then he vanished for 6 months as Intel rose to 29. LOL, what an unmitigated and miserable excuse for a human being......one that has a tax payment coming up for, well, basically nothing. LOL...........who runs this place?</Msg><Username>wdblowhard</Username><Timestamp>1354385478295</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 13:11:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354385512676-55</Id><Topic><Title>INTC ready to rumble = Strong BUY</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1354286247126</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 09:37:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has so much money that they will start doing mobile chips in no time, faster and cheaper than other companies... 2013 14 will be the best for intel... dont get the propaganda fool u...</Msg><Username>fvelezdevilla</Username><Timestamp>1354385512676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 13:11:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354385589376-56</Id><Topic><Title>Things that happen on Hussein Obama's watch</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354370202258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 08:56:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unavoidable braindead stooopid posts &amp; IDs are always the loosy tell.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1354385589376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 13:13:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354385774082-57</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL SEE A $18 HANDLE NEXT WEEK</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1354324553680</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:15:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U are a fool if u think a big company like intel will not do anything about it, they are smart and with money u can get back to business in no time...</Msg><Username>fvelezdevilla</Username><Timestamp>1354385774082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 13:16:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354386245208-58</Id><Topic><Title>Things that happen on Hussein Obama's watch</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354370202258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 08:56:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RUINED AND CORRUPTED AMERICA.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354386245208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 13:24:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354386246166-59</Id><Topic><Title>PFE going down - single digits here we come</Title><Username>quantuon</Username><Timestamp>1354379697033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:34:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorts are lowlife parasites not investors IMO no matter where they post. --------- IMO, you , buttplug, are another of Wallooooooon's many aliases.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354386246166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 13:24:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354386821205-60</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Wdblawgrow</Title><Username>wdblowhard</Username><Timestamp>1354385478295</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 13:11:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL @ short term gain taxes on a 20 cent trade b4 the stock went up 50%.</Msg><Username>wdblueball</Username><Timestamp>1354386821205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 13:33:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354387014135-61</Id><Title>Romney was REJected so get over it and move on teabagging losers.</Title><Msg>Healthcare is law The idiots in the House wil end up giving Obummer everything because they bet all on winning the election and so Now Obummer gets it all. The automatic 30% military cuts will get GOP house members to back Obummer because they will do anything to avoid base closings in their congressional districts. I bet you--the cry babay here, really thoght Romney was gonna win. HAAA HAAAA You mean rightwing trash in the media lied to you? How shocking. And you still believe them? Pathetic</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1354387014135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 13:36:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354388244330-62</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is a $100 stock</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363260107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 07:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd say it's a $30 - $40 stock...conservatively pricing it in-line with market multiples. With some serious hyper-dominance of tablets/smartphones, $50 is not unreasonable.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1354388244330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 13:57:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354389472605-63</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL SEE A $18 HANDLE NEXT WEEK</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1354324553680</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:15:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would recommed that you make your investments based on your due diligence. Please bet the farm. You are, however, arguing "form factor". You are arguing poorly. The MP3 player is an entertainment device. Intel had no interest in battling for the MP3 player sockets (iPod). The smartphone form factor is a communication device. (Apple introduced the iPhone to protect their MP3 market). The tablet form factor is portable and solves a particular problem: media consumption and touch data entry. The laptop form factor has a keyboard, has a larger screen and more weight. It can solve different problems than a tablet. A desktop form factor allows expandability and more flexible non-portable configurations. Hard to run large apps on a tablet. If you argument is that the tablet is the thin client for a cloud based server, then the heavy application will be running on an Intel server somewhere. Intel valuation: In March 2009 when the SP500 hit a low of 666, Intel dropped to a low of $12.41. The Intel revenues have increased from $7b/quarter to $13b. The Intel gross profit has increased from $3.1b/quarter to $8.5b The Intel cash from opperations has incresed from $2.5b/quarter to $4.7b The number of Intel shares have dropped from 6.5b shares to 5.0b. The Intel book value per share has incresed from $7.30 to $9.80. The size of Intel has doubled (based on revenue, profits, ...), 50% book value and the number of shares is down by 20%. IDC and Gartner group projects 10% PC growth. If you consider the $12.41 low of Intel in March 2009 and adjust its value up by the $20% share reduction, then you get $12.41 + $2.48 = $14.99. If you then consider that one Intel share represents twice the revenue and twice the profit in March 2009, twice the dividend, twice the value. Go for it. Intel is currently price below its 2009 lows based on valuation. If the market takes a big drop, Intel might even reach $15 since ETF trading volume exerts substantial pressure on Intel.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354389472605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 14:17:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354390196525-64</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is a $100 stock</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363260107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 07:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trefis models $31.77. TSM with full fabs is trading at 16.7 PE. 16.7 PE times $2 consensus Intel earnings is $33.40. TXN trades at 19.3 PE, similar to TSM 19.3 PE times $2 consensus Intel earnings is $39.60. Your $30 to $40 valuation seems reasonable. Of course, I did not think Intel would go below $25 so what do I know.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354390196525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 14:29:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354390666326-65</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is a $100 stock</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363260107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 07:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What an stupid post from a stupid out of control Liberal. Just ignorant waste of time. What he won't tell you is that he'll take 29 and run away like the swine that he is.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354390666326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 14:37:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354391252589-66</Id><Title>Intel: Integrated Digital Radio</Title><Msg>Analyzing the Apple (AAPL) iPhone teardown and bill of materials shows that, of the semiconductor devices identified, 10 are radio related and eight, including the A6 chip and memory, run everything else. The radio components and non-radio components are nearly equal in value at about $46 for each group.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354391252589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 14:47:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354391339087-67</Id><Title>Integrated Digital Radio</Title><Msg>Enter Intel. At the International Solid-State Circuits Conference In February of 2012, Intel demonstrated and discussed an SoC, called Rosepoint, with an integrated Wi-Fi radio on a chip with two Atom CPUs. That apparently left everyone scratching their heads about how Intel could get a radio to work without RF interference with the CPUs.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354391339087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 14:48:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354391407366-68</Id><Topic><Title>Integrated Digital Radio</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354391339087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 14:48:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On the third day of the Intel Developers Conference in September, 2012, when most attendees are snoozing, Intel demonstrated the Rosepoint chip again, but this time they revealed that the on-chip Wi-Fi radio was actually a completely digital implementation of radio. Digital radio was thought to be an "impossible" technology, but after ten years of work, Intel demonstrated, not pieces, but an entire digital radio transceiver.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354391407366</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 14:50:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354391450047-69</Id><Topic><Title>Integrated Digital Radio</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354391339087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 14:48:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The conclusion here is that LTE radio is no more difficult than Wi-Fi radio. If that is true nobody should be surprised if Intel offers a complete digital radio smartphone-on-a-chip SoC within the next year. The size of such a chip would be approximately 50 square mm run on a 14nm process. The manufacturing cost of that chip could be as little #$%$ As we can see from the above bill of materials, the value of that chip to a handset manufacturer might be $35-45.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354391450047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 14:50:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354391510945-70</Id><Title>Intel LTE: Projected "early" in 2013</Title><Msg>Intel LTE: Projected "early" in 2013 Next year will see 22nm, new architecture dual core SoC with 4G LTE on a chip, or nearby, with much higher performance and much lower power. Does Intel Have A Mobile Strategy? Judge For Yourself Intel investors have repeatedly heard over the past two years that "Intel missed the mobile business," or that "Intel doesn't have a mobile strategy." Intel is the world's largest semiconductor manufacturer, routinely producing its products with, by far, the most advanced manufacturing process technology and processor architecture technology. It would be reasonable for investors to expect that a company with the resources of Intel would have something better than a primitive mobile strategy. Let's take a look at the progress to date. Early this year, Intel announced several non-U.S. partners in the mobile business. One of these is Lenovo, which is in the process of passing Hewlett-Packard as the world's largest PC manufacturer. As such, we can assume that Lenovo and Intel have "met." Lenovo has also entered the smartphone business with some impressive results: In last year's third quarter, the company had a 1.7% share of the market, according to Gartner. A year later, the company was ranked second in China's smartphone market for the third quarter, with a 14.8% share. This put it right behind Samsung, which had a 16.7% share. 'We know that Lenovo is one of the strongest local companies in China,' said Gartner analyst Sandy Shen on Wednesday. 'But we just didn't expect the change to come so fast... We thought it would take them several years to grow their business in mobile devices.' Lenovo grew 870% in smartphones in a single year and shipped 7 million smartphones in the third quarter. Intel has also entered into agreements with Google to make Android and x86 more compatible. Intel has entered into a comprehensive agreement with Google's Motorola Mobility business unit. The results of that agreement are just now being recognized. Motorola has introduced the Intel-powered Razr i in Europe as a complement to the nearly identical non-Intel Razr M in the U.S. Motorola is also releasing an Intel-powered smartphone in China through China Mobile, the world's largest mobile service provider with over 700 million subscribers. Yes, that number is twice the entire population of the U.S. This phone carries the Intel Z2460 and an Intel baseband chip. The Lava ZOLO carries Intel parts to India, another market of "interest". Orange brings Intel SoCs to the U.K. Even Russia gets some Intel smartphone parts. Not bad for a company with "no strategy." None of these smartphones are market leaders or iPhone killers. They are mid-market, inexpensive, capable smartphones. All of these products use the Z2460 Medfield SoC. This device is a four-year-old architecture manufactured on Intel's trailing edge (but cheap) 32nm process. Next year will see 22nm, new architecture dual core SoC with 4G LTE on a chip, or nearby, with much higher performance and much lower power. Since there is a dire shortage of 28nm devices from TSMC, what is available is going into high-end phones, primarily in the U.S. Because of the above situation, we could get a pleasant surprise regarding the international progress of Intel's mobile effort. The Intel 32nm devices are built on fully depreciated production lines. Depreciation on state-of-the-art fabs could run as high as $2,000 per wafer. I would expect the Z2460 has a manufacturing cost of less than $4 and a selling price of $8-$10. That would be tough for competitors to match, especially in a 28nm shortage environment. Obviously, the Intel strategy does not include the U.S. at this time due to the lack of a 4G LTE solution. That problem is expected to go away by the end of the year. The strategy cannot include Samsung or Apple since devices for both companies are produced by Samsung. What's left is Google and Motorola. Low-cost international phone makers in immense markets are being addressed by Intel in a very capable way. Early next year we should see some truly market-leading smartphone products from Motorola (Google) utilizing the dual core Z2580 SoC. The 2012 strategy has been to begin penetration of the world beyond the U.S., and Intel seems to be knocking on the right doors. The 2013 strategy will include the U.S. Someday, the Apple fab business will come Intel's way as well. In the end, Intel will have a near monopoly in mobile just as it does in PCs and servers. The company doesn't know any other way. As Paul Otellini transitions into retirement, I would say, "Job well done."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354391510945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 14:51:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354391611072-71</Id><Title>Early Next Year</Title><Msg>"Early next year we should see some truly market-leading smartphone products from Motorola (Google) utilizing the dual core Z2580 SoC. The 2012 strategy has been to begin penetration of the world beyond the U.S., and Intel seems to be knocking on the right doors. The 2013 strategy will include the U.S. Someday, the Apple fab business will come Intel's way as well. In the end, Intel will have a near monopoly in mobile just as it does in PCs and servers. The company doesn't know any other way. As Paul Otellini transitions into retirement, I would say, "Job well done."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354391611072</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 14:53:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354392669646-72</Id><Title>GDP 2.7%. Is the bad news you Teabaggers expected?</Title><Msg>Real GDP growth for the third quarter was revised up significantly, reaching a 2.7 percent annualized growth, the Bureau of Economic Analysis (BEA) reported Thursday. Economists had forecast a 2.8 percent growth rate from the first estimate of 2.0 percent reported last month. Real GDP growth for the third quarter was revised up significantly, reaching a 2.7 percent annualized growth, the Bureau of Economic Analysis (BEA) reported Thursday. Economists had forecast a 2.8 percent growth rate from the first estimate of 2.0 percent reported last month.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1354392669646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:11:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354393047619-73</Id><Title>I got a call from SEC regarding my naked short "whistle"</Title><Msg>I filed a very, very narrow complaint about Intel trading with the SEC's Whistleblower Rewards Program. Friday, I received a call from them. He indicated that he understood my complaint and said that it did look strange. He said that he would be looking at it further. I will share more as new information becomes available. It does not appear to be a complex complaint but .... The "whistleblower" award is 30% of the settlement. 30% award of what ... curious? Intel went ex-dividend on Nov 3, 2011 and the naked short volume jumped from an average of 50,000 per day to 10,000,000 just before ex-dividend. On the surface, it appears that someone shorted 10,000,000 Intel shares across the dividend payment, then covered and did not bother to borrow the shares. Since they shorted 10,000,000 Intel shares and did not bother to borrow, they did not have to pay the 21 cent dividend on the borrowed shares. 10,000,000 shares shorted times the $0.21 dividend at the time = $2,000,000 fraud by not paying dividend. 30% Award of $2,000,000 = $600,000 10,000,000 shares naked shorted on Oct 27th for the naked short volume to be reported to the SEC. 10,000,000 shares covered on Nov 3nd for naked short volume to go down on Nov 3rd. Oct 27th Open $24.93 High $25.20 Low $24.85 Close $25.13 Nov 3rd Open $23.79 High $24.23 Low $23.28 Close $24.20 If they shorted on Oct 27th at middle of the high/low of $25.02, and covered at the middle of the Nov 3rd high/low of $23.75 They also made "about" $1.27 per share or $12,700,000 30% award of $12,700,000 = $3,810,000 dividend + naked short profit awards = $4,410,000 Intel nake short volume history DATE VOLUME PRICE 20111018 745 $23.28 20111019 27,707 $23.40 20111020 213,480 $24.24 20111024 10,142 $24.04 20111025 6,571 $24.59 20111026 494,407 $24.63 20111027 11,606 $24.70 20111028 4,898 $25.13 20111031 38,499 $24.98 20111101 10,596,564 $24.54 20111102 11,131,138 $23.89 20111103 40,200 $23.85 3-Nov-11 0.21 Dividend 20111104 27,971 $24.20 20111107 869,091 $23.74 20111108 264,647 $24.28 20111109 45,231 $24.75 20111110 80,461 $23.84 20111114 86,637 $24.85 20111116 48,375 $25.34 20111117 32,057 $24.94 20111118 52,161 $24.34</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354393047619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:17:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354393644137-74</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's systemic problems</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354374845764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:14:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kitchdee, I don't have enough insight to agree or disagree with your specific points. But from the outcome I am seeing from Intel, I see some sence in what you say. Intel spends 5-10X times it rivals in R&amp;D but not coming out with substantially competitive poducts to justify that much spending. Apple, Samsung, QCOM are doing uphill tasks better than Intel is doing downhill task. But I think the main problem plagueing Intel today is not the egineering performance. I think Intel today has already surpassed ARMH in performance/watt through R&amp;D muscle power. The problem with Intel is miserable PR and marketing performance. A right guy at the top will change the things downside up.</Msg><Username>stocktrade14</Username><Timestamp>1354393644137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:27:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354394393479-75</Id><Title>ipad 4 V Clovertrail</Title><Msg>For those who think that Clovertrail might appear in a future apple tablet... [multi-threaded benchmarks, higher is better] iPad (4th generation) Apple A6X @ 1.40 GHz 1 processor, 2 cores Geekbench: 1788 Integer Processor integer performance 1360 Floating Point Processor floating point performance 2260 Memory Memory performance 2066 Stream Memory bandwidth performance 1082 SAMSUNG ELECTRONICS CO., LTD. 500T Intel Atom Z2760 @ 1.80 GHz 1 processor, 2 cores, 4 threads Geekbench: 1386 Integer Processor integer performance 1566 Floating Point Processor floating point performance 1374 Memory Memory performance 1172 Stream Memory bandwidth performance 1232</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1354394393479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:39:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354395837150-76</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's systemic problems</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354374845764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:14:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The higher Intel RD cost is driven by their investment in advanced processes. Today, the high cost is driven by 14nm investments and related to the way Intel aggressively charges off the process development costs. Apple and Qualcom don't have these process development costs since the costs are shouldered by their foundries. The foundries are not making the large investments in processes that Intel is. Samsung has a large retail product element to its business that makes their RD a smaller overall percentage. You have described the foundry dilemma. Who pays for the risk of developing costly advanced processes and building expensive fabs. Ultimately foundry customers pay. Apple and Qualcom have problems building their products and Intel has the fabs and is developing products that will match the market to fill their fabs. Why not earlier? Intel fabs have been running capacity constrained for many years and they could not build the MP3 player chips for customers for new customers without abandoning current customers. Intel did not know that 22nm yield would be as good as it is and built an extra fab as insurance against low yields. That extra fab is the current 25% overcapcity that Intel is now charging off and converting early to 14nm.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354395837150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 16:03:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354397055202-77</Id><Topic><Title>Early Next Year</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354391611072</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 14:53:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So just because some guy who's Long Intel says what he thinks (more like hopes) online, you quote it like it's destiny? You really are desperate. I mean seriously.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1354397055202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 16:24:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354399006310-78</Id><Topic><Title>ipad 4 V Clovertrail</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1354394393479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:39:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suspect that Apple is concerned with screen refresh rates and power usage. Clover Trail at 3 watts doesn't make it for the iOS. Bay Trail at 1.5 watts just might. And consider the supply of Intel. But Apple also has laptops for the Mac operating system. So look for Mac tablets. Then does Apple have two Mac operating systems or just one ? In other words, does Apple have an iOS operating system for ARM tablets, a Mac operating system for non-touch Macs, and another Mac operating system for Mac tablets ? Or does the iPad become a iPad-MacPad with Bay Trail ? The iPad could only consider Bay Trail but a MacPad could use Haswell or Bay Trail. In other words, a iPad-MacPad would continue with extra long battery life while a MacPad could give up some battery life for performance.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1354399006310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 16:56:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354399368400-79</Id><Topic><Title>ipad 4 V Clovertrail</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1354394393479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:39:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have no faith in any one benchtest.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354399368400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 17:02:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354400323353-80</Id><Title>Getanid61, theblueredmonk, Kitchdee..........terrified ARMH tech geeks</Title><Msg>If Intel wasn't a serious threat in Mobile, they would NOT be on here every single day. This board would be the furthest thing from their minds if Intel was not a threat. Them being here actually makes ARMH look weak.</Msg><Username>getsome_nads</Username><Timestamp>1354400323353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 17:18:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354402201273-81</Id><Topic><Title>Early Next Year</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354391611072</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 14:53:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess I am also. kinda believe him</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1354402201273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 17:50:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354402331052-82</Id><Title>How long will it take to design Apple's ARM chip on 22nm?</Title><Msg>If rumors are true and Apple and Intel make a deal, how long would it take to design Apple's ARM chip for Intel's 22nm process?</Msg><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354402331052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 17:52:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354402553894-83</Id><Topic><Title>How long will it take to design Apple's ARM chip on 22nm?</Title><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354402331052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 17:52:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Basically, I'm wondering if they would be able to design an iPhone 5S chip on 22nm and have it go on sale by Thanksgiving 2013.</Msg><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354402553894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 17:55:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354403858103-84</Id><Title>Xbox 720 and Xbox Surface tablet</Title><Msg>I read that the Xbox 720 might have Intel's chip inside...same with the rumored Xbox Surface gaming tablet. If rumors are true, what kind of revenue would that produce for Intel?</Msg><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354403858103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 18:17:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354405024131-85</Id><Topic><Title>Xbox 720 and Xbox Surface tablet</Title><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354403858103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 18:17:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>720 has AMD in it.</Msg><Username>swamb</Username><Timestamp>1354405024131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 18:37:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354405199489-86</Id><Topic><Title>Getanid61, theblueredmonk, Kitchdee..........terrified ARMH tech geeks</Title><Username>getsome_nads</Username><Timestamp>1354400323353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 17:18:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You, sir, are absolutely correct. I salute you for the smartest post in weeks.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354405199489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 18:39:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354406338250-87</Id><Topic><Title>Xbox 720 and Xbox Surface tablet</Title><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354403858103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 18:17:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>May be reasonable to believe the AMD, but I'm pretty sure Microsoft hasn't released the specs yet and the only real thing known is speculation and a possible release date... however, I'm guess they are already being manufactured...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354406338250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 18:58:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354406975293-88</Id><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Msg>December 1, 2012 Another rumor just hit the news wires today, courtesy of RBC Capital. I caution my readers to, of course, take any and all rumors with a grain of salt. A few weeks ago, the buzz was about Apple (AAPL) dropping Intel (INTC) chips from its iMac and MacBook Pro products. Today, the rumor is a complete 180 degree turn from that pessimistic view, claiming that Intel and Apple are in talks for an elaborate deal that would consist of the following: Intel acts as a foundry to Apple to build its A-series of mobile processors for the popular iPhone In return, Apple uses Intel designed-and-built chips in its iPad.</Msg><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354407360460-89</Id><Title>Intel inside iPad.</Title><Msg>Here's another article about Intel inside Apple's iPad. A few weeks ago, the buzz was about Apple (AAPL) dropping Intel (INTC) chips from its iMac and MacBook Pro products. Today, the rumor is a complete 180 degree turn from that pessimistic view, claiming that Intel and Apple are in talks for an elaborate deal that would consist of the following: Intel acts as a foundry to Apple to build its A-series of mobile processors for the popular iPhone In return, Apple uses Intel designed-and-built chips in its iPad. On the surface, we can see why this deal would be mutually beneficial. Right now, Apple has its custom-designed A6 and A6X system-on-chip solutions built by Samsung, since it is -- other than Intel -- the only company in the world that can guarantee the volumes and manufacturing space that Apple needs. However, tensions are high between Samsung (SSNLF.PK) and Apple, especially as lawsuits over software and physical design patents seem to be escalating to brand-new highs each day. Reportedly, Samsung allegedly increased the price of manufacturing Apple's A6 processors to Intel by 20%. For Apple, a company that is hit with fears of gross-margin compression, this is unwelcome. Apple likely wants out of the fabrication deal that it has with Samsung, and it needs to find a partner that's as reliable, and who isn't a direct competitor. Enter Intel. Apple Fabbing At Intel Makes A Lot Of Sense Intel designs, builds, and sells chips. It doesn't matter who buys the chips, and it doesn't matter which devices they end up in, as long as Intel is selling them. In addition to having the best micro-processor designs for everything from ultra-thin laptops to the biggest and baddest dataceneters, it also sports the best manufacturing technology in the world. While the majority of Intel's competitors -- Taiwan Semiconductor (TSM) is the most advanced one -- are still struggling to add 28nm capacity, Intel is idling 22nm capacity and moving some of its older fabs to its brand-new, next-generation 14nm process technology. In such a potential partnership, Apple would be guaranteed to avoid shortages of its latest applications processor for its iPhone in addition to access to leading-edge process technology. Intel has more capacity than it can fill currently (utilization in Q4 is sub 50% to bring inventories down), so this works out for both parties economically. In the low-power space, Intel currently ships a 32nm HKMG process, which puts it in the same class as the foundries (which are generally shipping 28nm either with or without HKMG at the bleeding edge). Intel's process roadmap on the low power space is being accelerated to be available at roughly the same time as the higher performance processes: This means that in a couple of generations, likely in the 2014 time frame (when the Samsung/Apple contract is set to expire), Intel will offer a tangible process lead over the rest of the foundry industry. With smaller geometries, SoC designers can either produce smaller and cooler chips than the competition at the same transistor count, or produce superior and more featured designs in the same area. This is an advantage that cannot be overstated. The best design in the world could always be better if it had a bigger transistor budget and/or lower power per transistor. It also goes without saying that since Intel is not a direct competitor to Apple on devices, there is much less of a conflict of interest than there is with Samsung building Apple's chips. Apple Should Want Intel's "Tablet" Chips In such a deal, Intel would benefit greatly. While acting as a foundry to Apple for the smartphone processors is nice business, the real jewel would be an Intel chip in the iPad. Intel is very serious about being in tablets/convertible laptops, so scoring the iPad with its processors would be a noteworthy win for both its Atom and Core based processors. With the more performance-oriented iOS device running on Intel's chips, along with the Apple software ecosystem extended to include Intel Architecture, Intel would have the bulk of the personal computer industry. Now, I am keenly aware that Apple's A6X ARM-compatible chip is a quite powerful upscaling of the iPhone 5's A6 SoC. However, a key trend to notice is that "Ultrabook convertibles" and eventually high end "tablets" will be running on Intel's high end "Core" processors rather than the budget-oriented "Atom" processors that compete with the ARM (ARMH)-based designs. At the Intel developer forum, Intel demonstrated its next generation "Haswell" CPU, running at a power-consumption level of merely 8W (compared to 17W in today's lowest power "Ivy Bridge" Ultrabook processors). To put this in perspective, Anandtech tested the latest-and-greatest Samsung Exynos 5250 based on a dual-core "Cortex A15," ARM's finest CPU core design, which is faster than Apple's already fine A6/A6X design. The power results were rather shocking: At idle, the Cortex A15-based machine consumed 6.3W. At full CPU load (remember: the SoC's TDP also included graphics processors, which would introduce additional power usage in full "real" load), the chip consumed an average of 10.5W, or 4.2W. So we can safely estimate that the Exynos 5250 for Chromebooks/tablets has a TDP of 5W. Still lower power than the up-and-coming Haswell. However, this is not the end of the investigation. The Linux-oriented website Phoronix recently published benchmarks of the Chromebook running against the Atom D525 (it is equivalent in speed to the Atom Z2760 in tablets, but in a higher power envelope since it is older), a Core i3 330M, and an Nvidia (NVDA) Tegra 3. Now, to add some color here, the Core i3 330M is a 32nm dual-core design based on the now old "Westmere" CPU core (two generations behind "Ivy Bridge," and three generations behind "Haswell") running at 2.13GHz. The chip also has a 35W Thermal Design Power or "TDP." The Atom processor from 2010 (based on a 2008 core design) being slower-to-on-par with the dual Core A15 (as expected). However, the older "Core" design regularly proved itself to be multiple times faster than the Exynos design. Granted, this is at a much higher power envelope. 35W versus 5W should not even be allowed, right? Well, here's why it's permissible. At that IDF demo, the 8W "Haswell" was shown to be on-par in performance to the 17W "Ivy Bridge". In the 17W power envelope, at the 22nm process node, we have a 1.9GHz base clock, dual-core/four-thread "Ivy Bridge." On a per-clock basis, the "Ivy Bridge" is faster, since it is based on a newer, more sophisticated micro-architecture, and the two designs run at roughly the same clock speed. Now, imagine a 10W or less iteration of "Haswell" with roughly the same performance characteristics of the 2010 Core i3 part in the benchmarks. This would imply that in the 10 watt (or less -- Intel referred to the ultra-low power part as "sub 10-watt" at the Credit Suisse Conference), Intel would have a very significant performance per watt advantage over the latest-and-greatest ARM design. The lead should only widen at the 14nm node with "Broadwell" as lower power levels are enabled. If Intel is able to bring its very-highest performing processors to the tablet power level, then Apple will have very compelling reasons to move its iPad to Intel designed and built processors. But there is one snag -- software. Software Compatibility A Big Problem, But Not A Showstopper The big thing that would keep Apple from moving to an Intel chip, even if it were superior, is software compatibility. iOS runs on ARM-compatible processors, and all of the apps for iOS are compiled for and run on ARM-compatible chips. Now, moving most of the applications would be tough, especially since iOS developers do not submit source-code, but simply finished executables. On Google's (GOOG) Android, Intel caught a break because almost all of the code runs via the Dalvik Virtual Machine (meaning if the OS supports the instruction set and has the proper virtual machine, then the applications will work seamlessly). Nothing stops Intel, however, from using the same kind of software-voodoo that it did with native (i.e., compiled) Android applications: binary translation. Intel could provide a similar tool for iOS products. In fact, since the high-end Intel chips would have a tangible performance advantage over the ARM-based products, the penalty felt from the overhead involved with binary translation for existing applications would likely be nonexistent. There are technical hurdles, but they can be overcome. Conclusion I have no idea if this rumor is true or not. However, with Intel moving its very highest performing processors to lower and lower power levels, thanks to a combination of a sophisticated process as well as a highly optimized design, it is likely that Intel will attack the high end tablet/convertible space with "Core" and attack the low end of the market as well as phones with the new "Atom" architecture. If true, then this sheds significant light on the fairly delayed introduction of the next generation "Bay Trail" platform based on the next-generation "Silvermont" Atom core. Should Intel actually capture the iPad with its Atom and/or Core products while filling its fabs with Apple A-series chips for the iPhone, this could represent very real and significant upside for shares of the company.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1354407360460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:16:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354407719229-90</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel would have to really lower the margin on its chips, but still would be much better than apple dropping Intel.</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354407719229</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:21:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354407835320-91</Id><Topic><Title>How long will it take to design Apple's ARM chip on 22nm?</Title><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354402331052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 17:52:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm under the understanding that they still have to use Samsung until 2014...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354407835320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:23:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354407935082-92</Id><Title>IA architecture inside iPhones &amp; iPads = Negotiation NOT talks</Title><Msg>Intel and Apple have been 'in talks" for 2 years over this, in the meantime Intel builds way more capacity than they need, and now Samsung contract is coming near the end of the road. Seriously, this isn't a discussion they are having, it is a negotiation. Consider the difference, if Apple was in talks over this and not negotiating a deal, who else are they in talks with? TSMC?? Not if they want to actually be able to compete with Samsung, whose fabs are second only to Intel's.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354407935082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:25:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354408124022-93</Id><Topic><Title>IA architecture inside iPhones &amp; iPads = Negotiation NOT talks</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354407935082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:25:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Seriously, this isn't a discussion they are having, it is a negotiation." produce a shred of evidence to support your claim... or do you have NONE... and this is just your hope &amp; fantasy...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1354408124022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:28:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354408171487-94</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The cost of production goes down with each die shrink, in addition 450mm wafers are coming. I expect margins will be doing fine even with price reduction, if the volume is as great as expected.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354408171487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:29:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354408531586-95</Id><Topic><Title>I got a call from SEC regarding my naked short "whistle"</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354393047619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope you are successful... Naked shorting may be necessary, but when the market makers use it to screw the rest of us... it's wrong...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354408531586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:35:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354408582148-96</Id><Topic><Title>How long will it take to design Apple's ARM chip on 22nm?</Title><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354402331052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 17:52:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, Samsung can still build the chips for iPhone 5 and earlier versions until 2014, those versions of iPhones still sell even when iPhone 5S comes out. The point i'm trying to get at is if deal takes place and they can design iPhone 5S for sale by Thanksgiving 2013, then revenue for this deal will come in for 2013!!!</Msg><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354408582148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:36:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354408685111-97</Id><Topic><Title>ipad 4 V Clovertrail</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1354394393479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:39:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is interesting is that Atom has a higher Stream Memory bandwidth performance but a lower Memory Memory performance. I had to look. All the memory benchmarks are the same except two std libc routines. stdlib Write (memset) : iPad 3260, Atom Z2760 654 stdlib Copy (memcpy): iPad 2670, Atom Z2760 1017 This looks like Apple has written custom versions of memset and memcpy like Intel has done with the Intel compiler. If so, the comparison is with a hand tuned ARM libc routine and a dynamically linked Win8 version. This does not compare silicon performance. It compares the performance MSFT libc routine. 32-bit memory bandwidth on both is similar. geekbench problem. Insufficient disclosure when comparing two different results.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354408685111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:38:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354409878762-98</Id><Topic><Title>IA architecture inside iPhones &amp; iPads = Negotiation NOT talks</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354407935082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:25:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Once you eliminate the impossible, whatever remains, no matter how improbable, must be the truth.” ~Sherlock Holmes</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354409878762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:57:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354410824913-99</Id><Title>Getanid61 ripping his eyeballs out, LOL!</Title><Msg>1st Intel chips replaced ARMH chips in his own backyard of Europe and now this. LOL!</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1354410824913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 20:13:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354411106848-100</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting article,I like the conclusion: "Conclusion "I have no idea if this rumor is true or not. However, with Intel moving its very highest performing processors to lower and lower power levels, thanks to a combination of a sophisticated process as well as a highly optimized design, it is likely that Intel will attack the high end tablet/convertible space with "Core" and attack the low end of the market as well as phones with the new "Atom" architecture. If true, then this sheds significant light on the fairly delayed introduction of the next generation "Bay Trail" platform based on the next-generation "Silvermont" Atom core. Should Intel actually capture the iPad with its Atom and/or Core products while filling its fabs with Apple A-series chips for the iPhone, this could represent very real and significant upside for shares of the company". "Additional disclosure: I'm short ARMH"</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1354411106848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 20:18:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354411498893-101</Id><Topic><Title>I got a call from SEC regarding my naked short "whistle"</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354393047619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how naked shorting is necessary ?</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1354411498893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 20:24:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354411967276-102</Id><Topic><Title>I got a call from SEC regarding my naked short "whistle"</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354393047619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Explain to me how using someone elses stock without permission or paying for it should ever be necessesary ?</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1354411967276</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 20:32:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354412399440-103</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even if over-all margin profile drops, as long as top and bottom line grows, who cares?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1354412399440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 20:39:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354412547266-104</Id><Topic><Title>How long will it take to design Apple's ARM chip on 22nm?</Title><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354402331052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 17:52:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they started on this last year at the same time as they started working on the 22nm Atom, it will be ready by next summer. Just my WAG.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354412547266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 20:42:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354413073955-105</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Disclaimer says only that you are short ARMH; does this mean you are no longer long INTC?</Msg><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354413073955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 20:51:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354413854545-106</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry did not see the disclosures at the top.</Msg><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354413854545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 21:04:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354415362756-107</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Burger Boy that wrote this SA article said on this very message board two days ago that "he hated to say it" but he was worried about Intel. The guy knows absolutely NOTHING and is a terrified day-trader that gets sexually aroused when he sees his articles posted on yahoo for the world to see.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354415362756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 21:29:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354416591473-108</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you know less. Now you are seeing the "big news" I was talking about several weeks back.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354416591473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 21:49:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354416697973-109</Id><Topic><Title>Getanid61, theblueredmonk, Kitchdee..........terrified ARMH tech geeks</Title><Username>getsome_nads</Username><Timestamp>1354400323353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 17:18:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the INTC bashers are doomed. Those who held with strong hands are the winners. And, this is a great buying oppty...the coming of the AAPL INTC deal is obvious to any 4 year old kid.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354416697973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 21:51:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354416723160-110</Id><Topic><Title>I got a call from SEC regarding my naked short "whistle"</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354393047619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do you get naked short info on a daily basis?</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1354416723160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 21:52:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354416774856-111</Id><Title>panties a little wet, perhaps?</Title><Msg>Getanid61, theblueedmonk, and the biggest snowflake of all, kitchdee?</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354416774856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 21:52:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354416872856-112</Id><Topic><Title>ipad 4 V Clovertrail</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1354394393479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:39:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spot on, Alexander, as usual!</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354416872856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 21:54:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354416923784-113</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf is 1 of the most knowledgeable Intel posters, behind me &amp; Alexander. His article makes a lot of sense.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1354416923784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 21:55:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354418081499-114</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Crap monkies! I covered my ARMH short too soon, thinking I would just short again before it fell off the cliff. I sure hope it doesn't fall too hard too fast before I can short again on Monday. Then again, market has always believed the ARM rumors and discounted the Intel + Apple ones, maybe this happens long enough for me to re-short above $37.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354418081499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 22:14:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354418466105-115</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf is 1 of the most knowledgeable Intel posters, behind me &amp; Alexander. His article makes a lot of sense. ________________ Yeah, you're a great poster. Your history shows you own about 600,000 shares of Intel (fantasy land) and you said there was a concrete floor at 25, 24, 23, 22, 21, and 20 due to the Dividend. lol.... you're a disgrace, and even you know it.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354418466105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 22:21:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354420246380-116</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf may be knowledgable about chips, but when it comes to stock picks, he's 'tarded... he was pumping AMD when it was $4 a share... Not good...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354420246380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 22:50:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354420571249-117</Id><Topic><Title>I got a call from SEC regarding my naked short "whistle"</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354393047619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The SEC releases the data every two weeks. The link below generates a chart for the data. search for fails to deliver or failstodeliverDOTcom</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354420571249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 22:56:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354420798545-118</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also recommended RIMM @ $6.50, VRA @ $22, FSII @ $3, QCOM @ $56, $VZ @ $37</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1354420798545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 22:59:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>