<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352613224392-1</Id><Topic><Title>I just increased my Intel holding by 30%. You should too.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1352578642393</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 15:17:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good synopsis. Hopefully the middle class DOES rebound and give extra kick to the 15K DOW run. Eventually, we need healing among the consumer class to sustain any rally. Otherwise you go into cash in late 2014 and start buying drums of peanut butter. GOPs in Congress have been an utter embarrassment, Dems not much better. China finning in the water as Congress argues about birth certificates and minor solar power company failures.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1352613224392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 00:53:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352625959970-2</Id><Topic><Title>Can ARM cpus match Intel's Performance/watt ??</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1352397480335</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 12:58:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>marsavian's response to Calxeda's response to Intel... One of the issues with Seamicro was that it didn't/couldn't embed the Atom CPU into the SoC which added cost, size and power. Hence the move from AMD to add ARM to the seamicro fabric. We are focusing on the CPU but for me the really interesting thing is the fabric (in both the seamicro and Calxeda) servers. The amount of (memory/io) bandwidth these things have is amazing. A 24 nodes (96 cores) cluster, 24x 256GB SSD drives, 4GB Ram per node (96GB in total) burns 150-200 watts underload measured from the wall. Clearly it has to be the right work load. There is a limited market for these things - it's just a question of how big/little. I also think that Intel will find it easy enough to reduce power consumption to blunt part of the argument for these things, but don't forget it's not just about the CPU TDP, it's the memory, chipset, fans and then other things such as switches and external cooling. I'll be honest, I'd like to play with one of these boxes just for techie curiosity, but doubt I could shoehorn one into our workloads:)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1352625959970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 04:25:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352636745330-3</Id><Topic><Title>Can ARM cpus match Intel's Performance/watt ??</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1352397480335</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 12:58:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'A 24 nodes (96 cores) cluster, 24x 256GB SSD drives, 4GB Ram per node (96GB in total) burns 150-200 watts underload measured from the wall. Clearly it has to be the right work load.' Not bad specs if true. Still x86 processors will leave it no space in traditional integer based server application environments BUT for floating point applications e.g. HPC/Render Farms I could see a small niche they could exploit. You can design FP apps that simultaneously use all the functional units i.e. reducing the benefits of hyperthreading and need high bandwidth per core so this Calxeda strucure might be ideal for that so non threaded ARM cores good at floating point apps might be ideal for this so perhaps they should be changing the emphasis of the market they are targeting. Sure HPC is only about 10% of the market and they will probably only get about 10% of that at most leaving them with about 1% of the server market but hey I could see that technically working and really they are after PR and validation of concept and it would give them that.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1352636745330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 07:25:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352641772135-4</Id><Topic><Title>I just increased my Intel holding by 30%. You should too.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1352578642393</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 15:17:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wait for things to play out, 19's is the price to buy.</Msg><Username>smathan75</Username><Timestamp>1352641772135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 08:49:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352642789728-5</Id><Topic><Title>One OT question:</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352576944024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 14:49:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's an interesting suggestion..I didn't see any 4+" screens at BBuy. I'll check amazon. Thanks,.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352642789728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 09:06:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352650738073-6</Id><Topic><Title>One OT question:</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352576944024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 14:49:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at amazon: $39.49 Pyrus Electronics / Sigo (TM) 8gb Mp3 / mp4 / mp5 Player with 4.3 Inch Touch $59.12 Coby MP977-4G 7-Inch 1080p HD Video MP3 Player with 4 GB Flash Memory with HDMI Output I've seen others with 4.7 inch &amp; 5 inch screens... but forget what search I did... good luck</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1352650738073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 11:18:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352652907621-7</Id><Topic><Title>I just increased my Intel holding by 30%. You should too.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1352578642393</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 15:17:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you please keep political stuff out of this. Congress has zero to do with intel succeeding or failing in the mobile space. Unless congress is appropriating a stock buyback or free money for INTC R/D #$%$ do they care what this silicone microchip company does ?</Msg><Username>bbkenno</Username><Timestamp>1352652907621</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 11:55:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352653115683-8</Id><Topic><Title>I just increased my Intel holding by 30%. You should too.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1352578642393</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 15:17:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't mean to be snarky, I understand that if we avoid fscal cliff INTC will ofc rally, but any sustained move needs Intel to be on a smaller process node by a good year or so than their rivals so the phones they make will be 2x as powerful and 3 or 4x power savings.</Msg><Username>bbkenno</Username><Timestamp>1352653115683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 11:58:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352653270666-9</Id><Topic><Title>Can ARM cpus match Intel's Performance/watt ??</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1352397480335</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 12:58:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC perfected 3d gates, imo if they can continue to deliver on process node shrinks and other on chip innovations they will dominate the mobile space in 3 years.</Msg><Username>bbkenno</Username><Timestamp>1352653270666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 12:01:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352653506951-10</Id><Topic><Title>4 MORE YEARS OF MISERY AHEAD.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352272744072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 02:19:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your racism is coming through. Very few very skilled high tech jobs exist to provide employment to the mass of people looking for work. Even if every unemployed person had the skills to be programmers, chip designers, system engineers etc there would not be enough jobs to satisfy the supply of people. PH.D jobs in teaching and industry are relatively scarce, i doubt there are 1 million such openings across the entire nation.</Msg><Username>bbkenno</Username><Timestamp>1352653506951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 12:05:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352653697865-11</Id><Topic><Title>4 MORE YEARS OF MISERY AHEAD.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352272744072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 02:19:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A careful application of capitalism and socialism is the best of both worlds. Pure capitalism is destructive, as it evenutally leads to lawlessness and rule of the strong by all means necessary, pure socialism leads to lifestyles that are unsupportable. Also, humans as a rule are not driven purely by self discovery and self development. The Star Trek NG universe is a good example of meritocracy and socialism spread throughout the the hypothetical federation. People strive to be the best they can, but basic things are provided by the technology at hand. That technology is not a crutch but a tool to drive people to greater heights.</Msg><Username>bbkenno</Username><Timestamp>1352653697865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 12:08:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352659754695-12</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL going away from INTC chips not good for INTC, The hope to get in phones is gone INTC was to late</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1352568155778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 12:22:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I told you to sell at 29.25 , its not my fault that you did not sell, keep riding it lower, because INTC is going lower</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1352659754695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 13:49:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352660800639-13</Id><Title>Intel 4G LTE</Title><Msg>A number of Intel people have said that Intel will ship LTE-capabile chips in 2012 and ramping in 2013. I think "shipping" means "product for revenue" when no products have been currently introduced. Are there any events in the next 6 weeks where Intel would introduce this kind of product? I thought they would target CES Jan. 8-11, 2013 or Barcelona in early Feb. 23-28, 2013. 2013 International CES, January 8 - 11 Northern Voices Online (blog) quote New Mobile Chips from Intel Early this year, Intel made its formal entry into mobile chipset making sphere. Competing with ARM, the world’s leading computer chipmaker launched mobile chips like Intel Z2460 that you can see inside Motorola Razr I. The company may follow up this chip with dual-core Z2580 at CES 2013, say analysts. The new chip may support 4G LTE and other advanced features. “ARM-based chips, while found in major money makers like the iPad and various Android tablets, aren’t terribly up to snuff when it comes to processing prowess,” says TechRadar. Well, Intel wants to take advantage of this loophole to become a major player in mobile chip business. Indeed, the company may try for valuable partnerships with companies like Apple or Microsoft to make its mobile chips a gain momentum in the growing smartphone and tablet market. 11/14/12 4:00 PM ET UBS Global Technology ConferenceSpeaker: Kirk Skaugen, Vice President, General Manager, PC Client Group "TechCrunch writes that Intel product marketing director Sumeet Syal said that the current Medfield generation does not support LTE at this time, but first LTE-capable chips would be shipping this year and ramping up in 2013."</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1352660800639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 14:06:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352661194985-14</Id><Topic><Title>Intel 4G LTE</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1352660800639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 14:06:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CES or MWC in Q1 2013 would be a common time to launch...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1352661194985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 14:13:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352669134420-15</Id><Title>Obama 332 Romney 206 HAAAA HAAAA HAAAAA LOSERRRRRRS</Title><Msg>You want your country back teabaggers? EAT SHEEEET and DIE! Your pal Monkey</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1352669134420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 16:25:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352669557579-16</Id><Topic><Title>I just increased my Intel holding by 30%. You should too.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1352578642393</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 15:17:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congress has crashed the stock market countless times or have you forgotten. Remember the GOP nutwads and the debt crisis in Congress? BUT--Intel should be trading at a PE of 15:1 instaed of 9:1 but the reason it is not has a lot to do with the political hostage taking the GOP did before now. The Markets are worried they will do it again but of course they cannot so Intel will rally massively in the next 4 months. Do you want your country back? Intel needs to fire paul and replace him with someone who can market. Paul O will be gone before the end of the summer. Intel will benefit from the new CEO and massive increases in phone chip and server chip sales.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1352669557579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 16:32:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352671230820-17</Id><Title>Flumoxed' aliases</Title><Msg>All "cornhole" aliases. All "AMD roadkill" aliases The guy is a total loser, claiming to know stuff about Intel that he can't talk about, claiming to add 30 percent to his share count of Intel, licking Obama's shoes, etc... total waste of bandwidth.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1352671230820</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:00:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352679743267-18</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Paul O., how is business doing??</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1352491108525</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:58:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you just sell it backbay? i'm long and never expected to by the bottom. I do know where to sell though and that appears to be a big problem on this msg board. perma bulls</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1352679743267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 19:22:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352682593030-19</Id><Topic><Title>Flumoxed' aliases</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1352671230820</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:00:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, I know you're wrong about "cornhole" aliases. and I know you'r wrong about "AMD roadkill" aliases, and I also know you're a loser, you're party with it's nutbag notions having gotten drubbed, and I suspect your hangover is just wearing off and you are facing a tough day flipping down at Burger King tomorrow and I therefore proclaim you to know nothing about anything.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352682593030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 20:09:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352682774906-20</Id><Topic><Title>Flumoxed' aliases</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1352671230820</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:00:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for confirming my original post beyond a shadow of a doubt. Your arrogant and baligerant ramblings cannot be mistaken.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1352682774906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 20:12:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352685627574-21</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 332 Romney 206 HAAAA HAAAA HAAAAA LOSERRRRRRS</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1352669134420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 16:25:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh no, it couldn't have been that way,.... Just ask Karl Rove</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1352685627574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:00:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352685668720-22</Id><Title>Lennovo Yoga commercial just on Sunday Night Football</Title><Msg>Looks sweet and has Intel inside. It just looks to me like convertible laptops are a HUGE advancement and Intel's gonna make a ton of money off of these in the coming years. A TON.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1352685668720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:01:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352685782508-23</Id><Title>NOTICE</Title><Msg>to whom it may concern, we haven't made chips recently because we are busy to concentrate on making new 52 week low now, will keep making, regard. short short short</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1352685782508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:03:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352686354107-24</Id><Topic><Title>Flumoxed' aliases</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1352671230820</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:00:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, not mistaken by someone who voted straight republican. Hey, pop another muscatel.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352686354107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:12:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352686494921-25</Id><Topic><Title>Lennovo Yoga commercial just on Sunday Night Football</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1352685668720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:01:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I went to BBuy and talked to sales guys..ultrabooks are hot hot hot...and price points are still high, but beat AAPL. I saw that lenovo Yoga commercial...sweet!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352686494921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:14:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352687881006-26</Id><Topic><Title>4 MORE YEARS OF MISERY AHEAD.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352272744072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 02:19:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no,I do not believe it.</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1352687881006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:38:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352688978959-27</Id><Topic><Title>Lennovo Yoga commercial just on Sunday Night Football</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1352685668720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:01:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dell XPS Convertible commercial just on Sunday Night Football, also. Not only does it look very nice, they present it well in the commercial. The PC is not dying, it's evolving. Intel stock at this price is an absolute long-term steal, IMO. People are now seeing that you can have the laptop AND tablet experience all in one..........Convertibles will do very well in the upcoming years. Exciting!</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1352688978959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:56:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352690069172-28</Id><Topic><Title>4 MORE YEARS OF MISERY AHEAD.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352272744072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 02:19:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The misery is having to listen to you losers whine for four more years. V</Msg><Username>clarrjk</Username><Timestamp>1352690069172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 22:14:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352692631508-29</Id><Title>I don't think INTC will try to bottom until 19.50, but it might not hold this time with AAPL going away from INTC chips</Title><Msg>I don't think INTC will try to bottom until 19.50, but it might not hold this time with AAPL going away from INTC chips</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1352692631508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 22:57:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352693150126-30</Id><Topic><Title>Lennovo Yoga commercial just on Sunday Night Football</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1352685668720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:01:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hot hot babes fondling the new form factor: touchable ultrabook transformers....gotta love it. AAPL doesn't know what#$%$ it.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352693150126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 23:05:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>