<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348546019414-1</Id><Topic><Title>Intel plans to crush ARM beyond 20 nm</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348541567912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:52:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are doing more than making promises, khitchd'uh. They already have 5 factories producing FinFET 22nm chips and are already producing some 14nm. ARM won't have 14nm FinFET for 4 years. It does raise a question, though. Why would anyone invest in ARM when it's clear that their fabrication is coasting to a stop at 20nm and they have nothing after that?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348546019414</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 00:06:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348546588388-2</Id><Topic><Title>Intel plans to crush ARM beyond 20 nm</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348541567912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:52:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What would your report card say on Low Power IA? Still in process after all these years?</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1348546588388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 00:16:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348549585886-3</Id><Topic><Title>Intel plans to crush ARM beyond 20 nm</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348541567912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:52:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel prides themselves on their engineering process. Yet, several years after declaring Low Power IA as the way of the future for low power computing, they're still making promises. Raises questions." I know you just can't wait ....but don't worry....Low power?... ARMs dealer like me will make a fortune while the ARMS buyers will experience declining margins.... and remember there is no switching back and forth among foundries ... Adding the equivalent capacity to start about 10,000 wafers per month costs about $1 billion, Anstice estimated. "I don't know too many people that freely make billion dollar decisions speculatively. It's a high-stakes, high-reward kind of play," he said.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348549585886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 01:06:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348550840926-4</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Illusion</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348512452552</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:47:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Few factors here that need to be considered. 1. A year ago Intel had 0%, yes zero, share of the phone chip market. Intel is poised to enter and gain market share in the largest growth area for chips on the planet. A small share of the market is a hugh gain in sales for Intel. Some analyst are suggesting Intel has limited growth potential. At this stage Intel has more growth potential than say, all or most of the ARM camp. 2. Post PC era. Maybe in the developed world? Yet sales are steady there, and growing in developing countries. Maybe it is better phraised Post Desktop PC era. Mobility is the key to success, be it Notebook,Tablet, netbook, or phone. 3. Next big thing which seems to have limited Intels penetration to the Tablet market is Windows 8. MS's lack of touch screed support has been their biggest failure to date. Best feature of a Tablet that makes people buy it is the touch screen interface. Ie No mouse, keyboard to carry around. Hey, incorporate touch screen technology into a light weight compact notebook, or tablet, with the versatility to run your bussiness and productivity applications, would be, IMO, a better all round appealing product. The argument is that ARM is entering the market with Windows RT OS. MS wont even associate it's name with Win8, with almost No third party application support, and limited MS application support. Too little, to late, already done by google and apple. 4. Apple hype is exactly that...hype. The raving of apple tablet users about how great it is. Most people I know who have apple tablets are women. They like the form factor. Unfortunately in the WIN/X86 the only race that manufacturers seemed to be interested in was the one to make the lowest priced product. That lead to low cost, somewhat unreliable, poor driver products. Bingo, apple makes a fashionable,attractive, reliable, stable, product with limited perifials, with good driver support, charge high prices and win with the IN CROWD. The best product apple produces is their marketing campaign. Remember much of Apples success is due to their adoption of Intel CPU's in their desktop, notebook offerings. 5. Intel has huge manufacturing capability and leed in process, some years advanced to its competitors. Intel has huge R&amp;D capability, my guess is that much emphasis has been put into the next generation mobile SOC. Intels Atom aging mobile offering, at this stage is offering comparable performance and power consumption to ARM's newer offerings. Remember, intels effeorts have basically been just a refinement of an existing design on an ageing 45nm process. Next level will be a complete new SOC, look out ARM, especially if this is released straight to the 22nm process node. 6. Remember that like the the so called post PC era, the commoditisation of the moble platform, be it Tablet, notebook, phone, generally has a 3 year life span. Don't believe me....how old is the device you are reading this on? 7. Intel is dominant in the Server, high end part of the market, cloud is booming. Lower power consumption is attractive forcing server farm upgrades. Is the ARM camp even close yet? yes they are experimenting. Though dont expect them to gain any great market share. All in all the</Msg><Username>gooddigger</Username><Timestamp>1348550840926</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 01:27:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348550879885-5</Id><Topic><Title>Intel plans to crush ARM beyond 20 nm</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348541567912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:52:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel is biding its time." yup... the years are going by... yawn... Now Gatnid61 the question is how to recoupe a $1billion/10 000 waferstarts investment (in a timely matter); don't worry .... don't apply your "defect density model" logic- because it is stupid is as stupid does. your comments about Trigate DD is probably one of the most stupid I've ever seen</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348550879885</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 01:27:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348551940671-6</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL: You are no longer KING</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348533391173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 20:36:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Answer = Absolutely!!!</Msg><Username>eddiematt</Username><Timestamp>1348551940671</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 01:45:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348553293808-7</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL: You are no longer KING</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348533391173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 20:36:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Definitely.</Msg><Username>stok1mom</Username><Timestamp>1348553293808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:08:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348555004028-8</Id><Title>VOTERS RESPONSIBILITY IS TO VOTE FOR A PERSON WHO CAN LEAD US TO THE PROSPERITY.</Title><Msg>We all know it is not obama. You might not be crazy about romney, but we will be better of with him. Obama is just a big talker. We need real action. Romney can deliver it.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348555004028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:36:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348558478630-9</Id><Title>INTEL WILL DROP BELOW $20 SOON!</Title><Msg>I HAVE A BUY ORDER IN AT $19.50</Msg><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1348558478630</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 03:34:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348566921127-10</Id><Topic><Title>Intel......buy on every dip.....for long term....Dividend next....</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348521179270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:12:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, Intel will be around 28$ around Jan 2013, imo</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1348566921127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 05:55:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348570667273-11</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL DROP BELOW $20 SOON!</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1348558478630</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 03:34:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have a nice wait.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1348570667273</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 06:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348578134294-12</Id><Topic><Title>VOTERS RESPONSIBILITY IS TO VOTE FOR A PERSON WHO CAN LEAD US TO THE PROSPERITY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348555004028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmm, that's what people said about Bush and he ruined the country, but, hey, pukes are like Microsoft Windows ... "this new version is better ... really, trust us."</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1348578134294</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 09:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348579031051-13</Id><Topic><Title>VOTERS RESPONSIBILITY IS TO VOTE FOR A PERSON WHO CAN LEAD US TO THE PROSPERITY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348555004028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not sure that's true but is Bush running? or Carter for that matter?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348579031051</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 09:17:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348579271832-14</Id><Topic><Title>Intel plans to crush ARM beyond 20 nm</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348541567912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:52:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>".... don't apply your "defect density model" logic- because it is stupid is as stupid does. your comments about Trigate DD is probably one of the most stupid I've ever seen" Hmmm... please provide any comments of mine about the "defect density model"</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1348579271832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 09:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348580355978-15</Id><Topic><Title>VOTERS RESPONSIBILITY IS TO VOTE FOR A PERSON WHO CAN LEAD US TO THE PROSPERITY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348555004028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfortunately "A PERSON WHO CAN LEAD US TO THE PROSPERITY." is not on the ballot.</Msg><Username>cynicalanddisgusted</Username><Timestamp>1348580355978</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 09:39:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348580582192-16</Id><Topic><Title>Support just may be the 500 MA</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348498194908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:49:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All this action around 22.81 over the last two days is no coincidence. A huge battle is raging as to whether this 500-day moving average remains support or turns into resistance.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348580582192</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 09:43:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348580984828-17</Id><Topic><Title>VOTERS RESPONSIBILITY IS TO VOTE FOR A PERSON WHO CAN LEAD US TO THE PROSPERITY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348555004028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If we don't run Chris Christie, Romney will be the nominee and he will lose to Obama." Ann Coulter Romney CAN DELIVER IT!!!! You just have to tell him what people want to hear for him to win and he will say it!!! Romney delivers it by the truck load!!! Romney will deliver financial pain to you and Romney will deliver your wealth to his friends.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1348580984828</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 09:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348582031973-18</Id><Topic><Title>VOTERS RESPONSIBILITY IS TO VOTE FOR A PERSON WHO CAN LEAD US TO THE PROSPERITY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348555004028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and we all know what should be done is to take from those who earned their money and give it to those who don't work. Redistribute the money. hmmm, I wonder why businesses aren't hiring.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348582031973</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:07:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348582076571-19</Id><Topic><Title>VOTERS RESPONSIBILITY IS TO VOTE FOR A PERSON WHO CAN LEAD US TO THE PROSPERITY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348555004028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>22-Feb-12 05:04 pm Two out of every three people receiving stock dividend payments are rich, many totally, incredibly rich and should be paying more taxes instead of us soaking the middle class. I'm sick of the deadbeat rich who are unwilling to carry their fair share of the load... wallisweaver</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348582076571</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:07:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348582304588-20</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL DROP BELOW $20 SOON!</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1348558478630</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 03:34:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>have to agree with you but I do believe the buck stops there!</Msg><Username>hedgecutter10</Username><Timestamp>1348582304588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348582886257-21</Id><Title>Note to FluMo</Title><Msg>Well, I can't even imagine why you would think that Intel has failed. Stop buying the swill that Wall Street is serving. This is a temporary dip deserving of maybe a buck reduction in price, two at the most. And yet now we are working on seven thanks to Wall Street manipulation and the momentum traders. The dip has been accentuated by the doom and gloom crowd who apparently won't be happy until both the US and world economies collapse. Well, that's not likely to happen but certainly they aren't helping things. If you hype doom and gloom enough, eventually it will happen. Intel has changed all of its priorities to address the mobile market. We have a bit of a lull while this approach gains traction but it is gaining traction. The Motorola Intel smartphone is evidence of this. The LTE roll-out in the US in 2013 will be further proof. Intel is nothing if not methodical in its approach. Intel tablets are now gaining traction. And notebook price points are excellent and an affordable alternative to limited function ARM tablets. The fundamental nature of what is going to happen will of course be determined by fabrication. And Intel is on the verge of a total fabrication win. We will see this in 2013. ARM is in trouble with their fabrication. There is no doubt of this. Because the effects haven't totally hit yet doesn't mean they won#$%$ inevitable. ARM has no answer to 14nm production. No answer. And Intel is already getting some production. Given that 14nm production is on the way, the idea that Intel is not going to be successful is ludicrous. The internet isn't going away. Data centers aren't going away. Big data isn't going away. The Internet of Things is just starting to roll out and it's going to be huge. Huge as in as big as the existing cell phone networks. Intel will benefit from all mobility on the server and data center side. And then benefit directly as smartphone and tablet sales increase. There is nothing in the Intel price for smartphones or tablets. Wall Street isn't just wrong. There screamingly wrong. We saw this when they thought Intel was worth 15. We're seeing it again now. These are not smart people, they are manipulative people - so don't let their temporary success get you freaked out. It's temporary. We'll see 40+ by the end of 2013. I'm extremely confident of this. We currently have a huge disconnect between valuation and performance. Intel would have to have a $6 billion dollar revenue miss to justify the current beat down price. So, we will get a big chunk of the downturn back on earnings when this becomes clear. The Wall Street smoke and mirrors act is coming to an end. In the meantime Intel is doing exactly what it needs to do. It's moving steadily towards 14nm production and total victory in the mobility wars.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348582886257</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:21:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348583326825-22</Id><Title>I will keep INTC under 23.00 today</Title><Msg>Do not buy just sell today. I am the market maker and I am in control. The market up but I am keeping INTC down</Msg><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348583326825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348583561931-23</Id><Topic><Title>Note to FluMo</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348582886257</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:21:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wouldn't get too excited about Apple either. They have an unmitigated disaster with their maps on the iPhone 5 and riots at their FoxConn plant. Headlines today on Fudzilla: Google Maps not coming to iPhone 5 Foxconn reopens rioting plant They are using 32nm on their iPhone 5 and have really no place to go. They are stuck between Samsung and TSMC with only inferior fabrication and technology at both. They continue to push existing products with little new on the horizon. It's not a story one can get excited about. Jobs is gone. He will be greatly missed. Intel on the other hand has a fabulous future. Don't underestimate that WiFi chip that is coming. It's a game changer. And Wall Street doesn't know any more about the Internet of Things than it does fabrication. The future that Wall Street can see doesn't go past this weekend. Mobility, fabrication, The Internet of Things, the WiFi chip all point to huge Intel success. If you build it, they will come. Intel is building it...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348583561931</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348583686311-24</Id><Topic><Title>I will keep INTC under 23.00 today</Title><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348583326825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah, john boy - I see the drug-infused god complex is still driving you forward. I just have one word for you: REHAB</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348583686311</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:34:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348583924214-25</Id><Title>Classic Intel earnings warning</Title><Msg>As a fellow foolish commentator points out, the announcement is classic Intel. The company has a long history of waiting until a few weeks before its earnings announcement – the next one is scheduled for October 16 – and then lowering guidance. When actual earnings results are then reported in line with the original expectations, the company can declare the figures “an earnings beat” and watch shares rise by much more than the lowered guidance cost them. This is a classic game of Wall Street expectation management, and one at which Intel excels</Msg><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1348583924214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:38:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348583959665-26</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>With QE shots fired, the economic and political reality remain unchanged. The market looks unsettled in the near term. The quarter-end window dressing is likely to keep the downside limited. But the pullback in AAPL and selling on good new among the homebuilders yesterday suggests more profit taking is likely to be in the cards. The sideways consolidation during the past few sessions has worked off the short term overbought condition but the major indexes are still very overbought on the intermediate term basis. Technical conditions point to more consolidation/pullbacks. have a nice day.</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1348583959665</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:39:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348584126642-27</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Illusion</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348512452552</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:47:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There were a number of people that rose to senior management positions that needed to be pushed out. Fortunately many of those have left or will soon be leaving. I don't believe Paul O is among those however. Paul O. took Intel's helm after years of atrophy during the Barrett years in which billions were spent on a failed mobile strategy and AMD was allowed to take the performance crown from Intel and get a foothold with top tier PC OEMs. Problems of this magnitude can't be corrected overnight. While I have no difficulty being critical of Intel's management and strategies, and some are really warrant criticism, Paul O. probably deserves probably another 24 months to see if his leadership will deliver the products and results investors will love.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1348584126642</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348584142304-28</Id><Title>The Wall Street Approach</Title><Msg>The Wall Street approach includes no discussion of fundamentals or performance - just wingnuts like john boy saying, "I'm god, I control the markets." Have you had enough yet? Enough of the cockroaches, lucies, analysts, shills, egomaniacs and other assorted #$%$? Enough of the Intel doom and gloom crowd? Enough of the negative media frenzy? Just say no to skumbaggs...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348584142304</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348584662570-29</Id><Topic><Title>The Wall Street Approach</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348584142304</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:42:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And, of course, just say "NO" to perennial pumpers like Wallis who think that stocks only go up. Wallis has NEVER said "take some money off the table" or "wait for a pullback to buy." He relentlessly pumps and recommends buying Intel at ALL levels. He said Intel was a buy at $29. Anyone wh took his advice is now underwater. Wallis is a LOOSE CANNON/CANON with absolutely no conscience or scruples. BEWARE of WALLIS! He is EVIL!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348584662570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>25</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348585440472-30</Id><Topic><Title>Classic Intel earnings warning</Title><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1348583924214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:38:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When actual earnings results are then reported in line with the original expectations, the company can declare the figures “an earnings beat” and watch shares rise by much more than the lowered guidance cost them. ----------- I see that your delusional issues have resurfaced, Pumpwad. I had hoped that your admission that Intel has been dead money for years was an indication that you were improving</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348585440472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:04:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348585619376-31</Id><Topic><Title>Classic Intel earnings warning</Title><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1348583924214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:38:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>armh at 28.5</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348585619376</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:06:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348585702586-32</Id><Topic><Title>Classic Intel earnings warning</Title><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1348583924214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:38:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm going to play 18 today. Wallis is full of crap and Intel is in the toilet. All's right with the world.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348585702586</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:08:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348586472066-33</Id><Title>The various faces of Lucy</Title><Msg>Lucy sold all his Intel at 20 to buy Cisco, but Intel is a cornerstone of his portolio at 29 and he capitulates at 24 as the company is "hitting on all cylinders" and encourages the purcase of Intel shares. Lucy.........a poor little old schizophrenic man with no more than an associates degree. LOL!</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1348586472066</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348586666003-34</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy capitulates, says buy INTEL</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1317740904000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-10-04 11:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO!</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1348586666003</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:24:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348586776821-35</Id><Topic><Title>I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1293550442000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-12-28 10:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So which is it? Intel hitting on all cylinders at 24 and then you sold at 20? Nice buy high sell low strategy, associates degree boy!</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1348586776821</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348586980100-36</Id><Topic><Title>The Wall Street Approach</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348584142304</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:42:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like Mr. Weaver. He strikes me as someone who has his shirt buttoned up all the way to the very top button, a pocket protector with pens galore and a piece of tape holding his glasses together. He may not always be right or know how to trade but at least he stands by his principles.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348586980100</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:29:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348586981527-37</Id><Title>Raise your hands if watching little sissie girl Tiglet cry every day about Intel's stock price bores you</Title><Msg>7777777</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1348586981527</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348587075596-38</Id><Topic><Title>The various faces of Lucy</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1348586472066</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:21:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ cares? thanks for helping to ruin this fianacial board ,congratz you putz.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348587075596</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348587252597-39</Id><Title>LOL</Title><Msg>7'sssssssssssssssssss</Msg><Username>williamdavis_suxwang</Username><Timestamp>1348587252597</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:34:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348587704469-40</Id><Title>Motorola Razr i - Great All-Rounder Smartphone - Gets 4.5 Stars</Title><Msg>The Motorola Razr i is a great all-rounder smartphone. It offers a great combination of design and performance for a reasonable price. It's worth a look for its price and worthy of our recommended award. PCAdvisor(dot)co(dot)uk/reviews/mobile-phone/3400396/motorola-razr-i-review/?tab=verdictTab#top</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1348587704469</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348587774595-41</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola Razr i - Great All-Rounder Smartphone - Gets 4.5 Stars</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1348587704469</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:41:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Motorola Razr i: Battery life We're still testing the Razr i for battery life in the lab but benchmarks aside, we found we got more than a day's use out of the smartphone with varied use. The battery lasted a solid two days before we needed to charge it up which is a good result for a phone with a large Super AMOLED screen.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1348587774595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348587905478-42</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy capitulates, says buy INTEL</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1317740904000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-10-04 11:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, keep posting this to make sure that tampon doesn't fool anybody.</Msg><Username>williamdavis_suxwang</Username><Timestamp>1348587905478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348588348371-43</Id><Topic><Title>Classic Intel earnings warning</Title><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1348583924214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:38:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>except ww, he's left. way left</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348588348371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:52:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348589523092-44</Id><Topic><Title>VOTERS RESPONSIBILITY IS TO VOTE FOR A PERSON WHO CAN LEAD US TO THE PROSPERITY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348555004028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aren't you supposed to call "them" the "job creators"? If you support any form of taxation or collective support of programs for the USA (military, roads, bridges, dams, ...), then you believe in taking from "those who earned their money". I bet you believe in "redistribution" too since those who don't earn money get benefits from those items. A big chunk of those who earn their money but do not pay federal taxes, do so because of tax credit laws put in place by Presidents in the 1970's and 80's. The new tax credits were initated pretty equally between both parties. Even Reagan with the Low-Income Housing Tax Credit. Businesses aren't hiring because they have no need to hire. Their current capacity and workers can support all their customers. The "job creators" have no need to create jobs if those who "don't work" have no salary to spend. You reach a point where you could give the "job creators" zero taxes and it would not create another job. Businesses aren't hiring because they can't find properly trained people. Businesses aren't hiring because Intel and automation has structurally changed the labor market and what part of manufacturing is left in the US has changed. Robots.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1348589523092</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:12:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348589913746-45</Id><Title>no power</Title><Msg>try to go up but no power, will be closed red, lobster red.</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348589913746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:18:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348590089616-46</Id><Title>The defense cuts kick in on Oct 1 big layoffs have started. Sell some or protect you shares in all your stocks</Title><Msg>The defense cuts kick in on Oct 1 big layoffs have started. Sell some or protect you shares in all your stocks</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1348590089616</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:21:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348590250088-47</Id><Title>Why are we up only 2 cents and GOOG is up 11 dollars</Title><Msg>This stinks</Msg><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1348590250088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:24:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348590258507-48</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy capitulates, says buy INTEL</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1317740904000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-10-04 11:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1348590258507</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:24:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348590929780-49</Id><Topic><Title>Why are we up only 2 cents and GOOG is up 11 dollars</Title><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1348590250088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>up 2 cents for this stock that means skyrocketing , but later will be lobster red.</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348590929780</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:35:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348591390877-50</Id><Topic><Title>Why are we up only 2 cents and GOOG is up 11 dollars</Title><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1348590250088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only pink now on the break of .80 nice rally in the SQQQ off .60</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348591390877</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348591580807-51</Id><Topic><Title>VOTERS RESPONSIBILITY IS TO VOTE FOR A PERSON WHO CAN LEAD US TO THE PROSPERITY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348555004028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>then change the tax laws but don't demonize people for being smart. Education + birth control are the answers, do you see the Pope saying this? that fool says breed and have big families. Okay, who's going t o pay for them ? with no incentive to work hard, why would smart people do so? you need to stay in school, you need to think for yourselves, do you count on hiding in a union job as a good future? how'd that work for GM? how'd GM work for the taxpayer? 4 more years will only dig a deeper hole if we don't change directions. Raise some taxes, close some loopholes, but as we are going, it is not a good path imo.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348591580807</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:46:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348591997855-52</Id><Topic><Title>VOTERS RESPONSIBILITY IS TO VOTE FOR A PERSON WHO CAN LEAD US TO THE PROSPERITY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348555004028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is over for Rombo. Quit your crying. It is funny but getting to be pathetic.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1348591997855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348592659673-53</Id><Title>Intel smartphones(mini-computers) will have patented technology, LOT of it. Does ARMH even have 375 million dollars?</Title><Msg>Intel seems to have finally gotten serious about its mobile strategy. No longer willing to let ARM Holdings have its way, Intel is now looking to fight it out in the smartphone and tablet spaces that ARM has dominated for years. In June, Intel paid $375 million for 1,700 patents to "support Intel's strategic investments in the mobile segment." Translation: We're coming for your bread and butter, ARM.</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1348592659673</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:04:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348593251493-54</Id><Topic><Title>Intel smartphones(mini-computers) will have patented technology, LOT of it. Does ARMH even have 375 million dollars?</Title><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1348592659673</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:04:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow, slumbering giant finally waking up</Msg><Username>d186282mps</Username><Timestamp>1348593251493</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:14:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348593716226-55</Id><Topic><Title>INTC may well come to be the stock to see this quarter.</Title><Username>carlsonedward117</Username><Timestamp>1348079498503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:31:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am new , Is intc now a good time to buy?</Msg><Username>david7591</Username><Timestamp>1348593716226</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:21:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348594089045-56</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy capitulates, says buy INTEL</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1317740904000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-10-04 11:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROFL!</Msg><Username>lucyboycots_chickfillet</Username><Timestamp>1348594089045</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:28:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348594160258-57</Id><Topic><Title>Support just may be the 500 MA</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348498194908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:49:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oops, actually I was looking at the 200ma on a weekly basis, I guess that's a 1000ma! Corresponds to the volume/price bars, much stronger support around 20-ish. The 500ma is very pretty, but there's no volume support.</Msg><Username>whowants2be</Username><Timestamp>1348594160258</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348594963119-58</Id><Title>wake up</Title><Msg>up and down, up and down, it couldn't hold the gain, junk</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348594963119</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:42:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348595057082-59</Id><Title>How low did INTC go in 2009? was it $12.09 or did it go lower ?</Title><Msg>How low did INTC go in 2009? was it $12.09 or did it go lower ?</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1348595057082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:44:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348595225809-60</Id><Topic><Title>How low did INTC go in 2009? was it $12.09 or did it go lower ?</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1348595057082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:44:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>11-May-11 10:24 am I must admit that this morning's announcement is nothing short of remarkable. As of today, I officially capitulate and am encouraging the purchase of Intel shares. This company is hitting on all cylinders and the management team is doing everything right. The outlook for the shares is positive, imo. I do, however, reserve the right to take shots at Wallis when he presents an easy target. Rating : lucy_nuff earth View Messages Ignore User Report</Msg><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1348595225809</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:47:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348595251264-61</Id><Title>Big defense cuts, Layoffs have started, Sell some or protect your 401k</Title><Msg>Big defense cuts, Layoffs have started, Sell some or protect your 401k</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1348595251264</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:47:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348595782397-62</Id><Topic><Title>Big defense cuts, Layoffs have started, Sell some or protect your 401k</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1348595251264</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:47:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>11-May-11 10:24 am I must admit that this morning's announcement is nothing short of remarkable. As of today, I officially capitulate and am encouraging the purchase of Intel shares. This company is hitting on all cylinders and the management team is doing everything right. The outlook for the shares is positive, imo. I do, however, reserve the right to take shots at Wallis when he presents an easy target. Rating : (1 Rating)Rate it: lucy_nuff earth ----------------------------------------------------- --------------------------- View Messages Ignore User Report</Msg><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1348595782397</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:56:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348596195367-63</Id><Topic><Title>wake up</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348594963119</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:42:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bear market for sure, QE 3 is useless, up 1 cent and down a dollar, will keep going down day by day, down down down, I'll be a millionaire!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348596195367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:03:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348596836470-64</Id><Title>Extra thin replacement battery for your Smartphone or Tablet --- no more battery issues</Title><Msg>for those who cares.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1348596836470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:13:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348597281866-65</Id><Title>im in order filled monday 22.60 3.9+% div</Title><Msg>they will find their way.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348597281866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:21:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348597283744-66</Id><Topic><Title>Extra thin replacement battery for your Smartphone or Tablet --- no more battery issues</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1348596836470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:13:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where's the link? Is this something Intel has a patent on? Did you know that ARM was priced at 28 and that I'm off to buy some extra-large tampons? - Tigs</Msg><Username>tiglet3l</Username><Timestamp>1348597283744</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:21:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348597540660-67</Id><Topic><Title>im in order filled monday 22.60 3.9+% div</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348597281866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>expecting INTC to rally while the market corrects are we?</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348597540660</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348598856991-68</Id><Topic><Title>Extra thin replacement battery for your Smartphone or Tablet --- no more battery issues</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1348596836470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:13:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>check Dell latitude -- with a dual-core 1.5GHz Clover Trail Atom processor</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1348598856991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348599637623-69</Id><Topic><Title>im in order filled monday 22.60 3.9+% div</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348597281866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Help, I'm long the SQQQ, what should I do? Nice bullish engulfing candle.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348599637623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:00:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348600338727-70</Id><Title>HAY Wdblwgrow, how's that SIRI you pumped no less than 80 to 200 percent higher than it is today, LMAO</Title><Msg>Re: SIRI spike question/Vetmom By wdblawgrow . Jan 15, 2003 9:37 PM . Permalink Go to topic Early yesterday, SIRI was upgraded to an outperform, essentially noting that investors had over reacted to the refinancing, pricing SIRI for bankruptcy. Then XMSR the same pre open announces news on the GM sat radio install options. Those still short run to cover. The idea from my perspective is that one or the other, and possibly both of these companies is going to make it to profitably ability and huge growth. Debt for stock will cause dilution, but significantly less debt. Need a "little" pull back, a breather. Hope that helps somewhat.</Msg><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1348600338727</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348600680260-71</Id><Title>WDBLAWGROW says ZERO percent change Intel goes over 24......right before it goes to 29+</Title><Msg>Re: When Will Intel Reach $24? By wdblawgrow . Sep 18, 2011 9:33 AM . Permalink Go to topic The liklihood of INTC reaching 24.00 is probably zero for the next several years. The liklihood of sub 19.00 far higher.</Msg><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1348600680260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:18:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348600758182-72</Id><Title>When it smells like #$%$, it is</Title><Msg>10 years of the Wall St. pump and dump. Patience is definitely a virtue owning the stock of a company that is perhaps Wall St.'s most loved manipulation and should be trading in triple digits. Intel should go private. Period.</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1348600758182</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:19:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348601778150-73</Id><Title>Cockroaches are Swarming</Title><Msg>You have to laugh at the Wall Street shills. Where do they get people this lame? Oh, that's right. There's only one person. The one man shill show in his never ending preparation to enter the fetal position. This earnings will be memorable...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348601778150</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348601916420-74</Id><Title>$7 Billion Revenue Miss Now Priced In</Title><Msg>Wall Street has now priced in a $7 billion revenue miss. Raise your hands if you think that's actually going to happen. Otherwise it's all manipulation that will end come earnings...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348601916420</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348602172337-75</Id><Title>Setting Up Nicely For Short Slaughter</Title><Msg>Windows 8 release and then earnings a week later. With a $7 billion revenue miss priced in. What was Wall Street thinking?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348602172337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:42:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348602370314-76</Id><Topic><Title>Setting Up Nicely For Short Slaughter</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348602172337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What were you thinking when you had a "strong buy" at $29? What about a letter of apology to the board?</Msg><Username>c757172</Username><Timestamp>1348602370314</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348602714045-77</Id><Topic><Title>VOTERS RESPONSIBILITY IS TO VOTE FOR A PERSON WHO CAN LEAD US TO THE PROSPERITY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348555004028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just touching on the issues you raised ..... I have never demonized anyone for being "smart". I also have never equated being "wealthy" with "being smart". There are many very smart people who are not wealthy (some by choice). Wealth is not a "smart meter". Is Paris Hilton smart? Maybe. I have no respect for those who lack good character and morals. (Note ... I am not pointing any general finger). Bernie Maddoff ? I believe that a woman has the right to decide. (GOOGLE: " freakonomics abortion ") I believe there is always an incentive and benefits to work hard. "Smart" is not the driving force there. There are lazy smart people. There are smart people who make unwise decisions and become poor. Education is good. Staying in school is great if you can afford it and have food and shelter. Having food and shelter is not always a given. There is probably some changes needed with the union structure but it is wrong to demonize them just because their goal should be to protect workers from abuse. GM? Were the unions to blame or the "smart" guys at the top who said "OK" to their demands? The taxpayer so far has made a profit on all their "trades". A large number of GM employees and feeder industries have been paying taxes they would not have if GM had went under. The GM story is not over yet. Raising taxes? Close some loopholes? Republicans have stated that their prime goal is to get rid of Obama. It appears that the will not let anything stand in their way ... including America or its citizens. They stand behind an oath to not raise taxes which makes your first suggestion a problem. They view closing loopholes as tax increases so that has the same problem. Obama would have a hard time since his opponents have taken an obstructionist position. Romney, I don't think really wants to do either but he will have similar problems. You cannot get a bill considered in the Senate without 2/3 vote because there will be some Senator who will put a hold on the legislation because he/she does not agree. 60% of the US citizens are not extreme liberals nor extreme conservatives. The election system and district lines just pressure parties to the extremes.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1348602714045</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:51:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348603658715-78</Id><Topic><Title>VOTERS RESPONSIBILITY IS TO VOTE FOR A PERSON WHO CAN LEAD US TO THE PROSPERITY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348555004028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great post Lucy.spam.. To penma1, This is stock message board, the S&amp;P is up OVER 70% since Oboma took office.. I think I will vote for Him.. I am MUCH BETTER OFF now than I was on Sept 25 2008.... Romney makes George W Bush look smart..</Msg><Username>vuso2000</Username><Timestamp>1348603658715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:07:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348603885628-79</Id><Topic><Title>Setting Up Nicely For Short Slaughter</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348602172337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I expected more shorting to show up in this short interest report. The short interest released just a few minutes ago shows a 4mil share decrease in short interest. 172mil shares short is still high historically but not a big increase in the short position I expected. Settlement Date Short Interest 9/14/2012 172,757,382 8/31/2012 176,103,236 8/15/2012 152,401,318 7/31/2012 146,242,930 7/13/2012 130,114,118 6/29/2012 122,750,721 6/15/2012 118,063,532 5/31/2012 101,516,225 5/15/2012 93,017,070 4/30/2012 93,249,832 4/13/2012 88,608,747 3/30/2012 98,020,476 3/15/2012 101,309,076 2/29/2012 99,542,746 2/15/2012 103,422,076 1/31/2012 110,348,353 1/13/2012 131,784,131 12/30/2011 117,479,241 12/15/2011 120,548,516 11/30/2011 119,714,369 11/15/2011 122,693,269 10/31/2011 131,064,051 10/14/2011 133,211,075 9/30/2011 150,281,860 9/15/2011 141,809,046</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348603885628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348603933286-80</Id><Topic><Title>Setting Up Nicely For Short Slaughter</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348602172337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope so, but I sure hope you aren't General Custer and we're not at Little Bighorn. I do admire your optimisum as mine is waining with my losses that are piling up.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1348603933286</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:12:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348604286413-81</Id><Title>Prosperity</Title><Msg>Prosperity is brought about by the hard work and ingenuity of people trying to get ahead. You give politicians way too much credit and way too much blame.</Msg><Username>clarrjk</Username><Timestamp>1348604286413</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:18:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348604356260-82</Id><Title>Alert: Jabil Circuit TANKING AH !!</Title><Msg>Thoughts ? Comments ?</Msg><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1348604356260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348604673939-83</Id><Topic><Title>im in order filled monday 22.60 3.9+% div</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348597281866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>im in order filled monday 22.60 ---------------------- CONGRATULATIONS! You're underwater. TOOOOO FUNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348604673939</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:24:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>26</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348604895883-84</Id><Topic><Title>Why are we up only 2 cents and GOOG is up 11 dollars</Title><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1348590250088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You posted recently that you had sold all of your INTC to buy Skull Candy, twit.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348604895883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:28:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>26</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348605064283-85</Id><Topic><Title>$7 Billion Revenue Miss Now Priced In</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348601916420</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even a one dollar revenue miss will justify current price, and may also impact profits rather more heavily. The charts all scream that this is going down another buck or two, but in today's markets, who knows. If the price gets below $21 I buy for sure.</Msg><Username>whowants2be</Username><Timestamp>1348605064283</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:31:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348605238051-86</Id><Topic><Title>Setting Up Nicely For Short Slaughter</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348602172337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 Bugs Plaguing Microsoft, Intel CEO Said to Tell Staff at Bloomberg 03:56pm EDT</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348605238051</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:33:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348609005286-87</Id><Topic><Title>im in order filled monday 22.60 3.9+% div</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348597281866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>im not blowing bubbles yet-high 20s 2013</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348609005286</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 17:36:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348610510546-88</Id><Topic><Title>im in order filled monday 22.60 3.9+% div</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348597281866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stupid people. Do you only invest daily? INTC will make a comeback sooner then later and you will be one of the idiots saying wish I bought when it was this cheap.. Watch the charts. INTC is way oversold. Watch if this doesn't rise before next months earnings it will then after earnings. This is how the market works. Even if they miss it will go up. INTC is a great buying spot. Look at the charts last 2 years. I was at it's lowest each of the last 2 years here and made serious gains in OCT and NOV..</Msg><Username>verioinc</Username><Timestamp>1348610510546</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 18:01:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348612712913-89</Id><Topic><Title>im in order filled monday 22.60 3.9+% div</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348597281866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i agree.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348612712913</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 18:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348612894249-90</Id><Title>Paul O. today says PC growth next year</Title><Msg>&amp; he also said no Intel layoffs. Good news. Thinsg are not getting worse &amp; INTC is way oversold on a technical basis.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1348612894249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 18:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348613086530-91</Id><Title>WHAT CRAMER SAID TONIGHT ABOUT INTEL</Title><Msg>He said that owning Intel right now is like "flogging a dead horse."</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348613086530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 18:44:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>25</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348613573246-92</Id><Topic><Title>im in order filled monday 22.60 3.9+% div</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348597281866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC will make a comeback sooner then later --------- Sooner and then later? TOOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348613573246</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 18:52:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348614671011-93</Id><Topic><Title>Classic Intel earnings warning</Title><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1348583924214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:38:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are U nuts dikwad??? I am not delusional!!! I never resurface my issues. You are losing Ur mind. Alzheimer? You forgot to say ... TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOoooooooooooooooo FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY</Msg><Username>pumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1348614671011</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 19:11:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348614852471-94</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT CRAMER SAID TONIGHT ABOUT INTEL</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348613086530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 18:44:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too late to short down here in the 22.50's, could keep getting more oversold, but a bounce is just as possible with the rsi under 30. plenty of overhead resistance, so the elevator better be a brand new model and not simply a repair.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348614852471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 19:14:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348614929761-95</Id><Topic><Title>Classic Intel earnings warning</Title><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1348583924214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:38:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know the game to well. Load up on Oct calls. They are VERY VERY cheap. You can make 10-50X potential. If a stock is depressed going into earnings it will rise. If a stock is pumped weeks before earnings it will fall. Classic WS.</Msg><Username>verioinc</Username><Timestamp>1348614929761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 19:15:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348615481013-96</Id><Title>See interview with Ken Fisher</Title><Msg>Ken Fisher: Bull Market Is Halfway Done The bull run in the stock market has reached its half-life, and large-cap companies are the way to invest from here, CEO Ken Fisher of Fisher Investments told CNBC on Tuesday. “People are optimistic about their own lives, but they’re skeptical about everything else. Therefore, we’re going to move from that skepticism, eventually, to some form of optimism, or lack of skepticism, and that means people who haven’t been in the market will get in, will capitulate and put prices higher,” he said on “Fast Money.” Fisher noted a trend from large-cap stocks. “This year, we started the process where the very largest stocks started outperforming,” he said. “Usually that happens just about 40 to 60 percent of the way through the time of a bull market, so therefore I think we’re probably about halfway through the bull market and we have several years fully to run.” Fisher picked five large-cap stocks that he thought had room to run: Intel [INTC 22.535 -0.26 (-1.14%) ], PepsiCo [PEP 70.35 -0.35 (-0.5%) ], Sanofi [SNY 44.20 -0.16 (-0.36%) ], ExxonMobil [XOM 91.74 -0.14 (-0.15%) ] and BHP Billiton [BHP 68.06 -1.32 (-1.9%) ].</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348615481013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 19:24:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348617810210-97</Id><Topic><Title>See interview with Ken Fisher</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348615481013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 19:24:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CEO Ken Fisher of Fisher Investments told CNBC on Tuesday. ------------------------------------------- I wonder if he has any stake in the game? LOL Another media pumper. herbal_dude of piper hedge funds says this is a totally fake market and the chickens will come home to roost. Trillions of dollars have been pumped into Treasury notes and this fake stock market will come to an end. Only an idiot would keep buying these false hopes. Then again, most that invest in this pig are idiots. What part of the history of INTC don't you understand?</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1348617810210</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:03:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348617823694-98</Id><Title>armh still at</Title><Msg>$28, man intc is weak. can you believe qcom has caugt intel? talk about being asleep for 10 years now, sad.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348617823694</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:03:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348618049844-99</Id><Topic><Title>im in order filled monday 22.60 3.9+% div</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348597281866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I did buy it when it was cheap, now it is coming back to me. I can only look forward to how much fun we are going to have climbing back up to 29, whoopee!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348618049844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348618104248-100</Id><Topic><Title>im in order filled monday 22.60 3.9+% div</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348597281866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now that is TOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNY !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348618104248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:08:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348618120228-101</Id><Topic><Title>Alert: Jabil Circuit TANKING AH !!</Title><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1348604356260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:19:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, ww is an #$%$</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348618120228</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:08:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348618181504-102</Id><Topic><Title>Setting Up Nicely For Short Slaughter</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348602172337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is the $3 eps that you blew about priced in too?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348618181504</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:09:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348618762933-103</Id><Topic><Title>VOTERS RESPONSIBILITY IS TO VOTE FOR A PERSON WHO CAN LEAD US TO THE PROSPERITY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348555004028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you respect Bill Clinton? abortion has no business in ploitics, you want to murderyour baby, sad but her choice. why even bring that up? if your $ is taken, why work hard? work hard for the benefit of others? not gonna happen on a grand scale. staying in high school is hard? a lot of americans can't read, can't do simple math, can't speak proper english, who can hire that? Unins to protect workers from abuse? we have labor laws now, plenty of laws. Unions are pure greed now, you're living in the past. GM may not be over but if the banks were going down a 2nd time as GM is, what would the gov't be saying? they would screaming at them. GM gets a pass because they are unionized. Romney just said he was for means testing on social security, that's a #$%$ idea imo but he isn't as far right as many think. He may not be real great but he has to be better than what we have now. Obama is going to spend and spend and spend.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348618762933</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348618969847-104</Id><Topic><Title>See interview with Ken Fisher</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348615481013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 19:24:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one should buy and hold any semiconductor stock, they are deplorable as "investments", that said, they are fine for trading. one could buy INTC for the yield, short an equal dollar amount of the SMH. A nice hedge with the benefit of the yield. fwiw, INTC started it's slide from the 27's right as the SMH hit rsi 70, and peaked before the overall markets did. Sometimes, they bottom first, ie only a short term dip is seen as in the cards for the overall indexes, ie QQQ, SPY, DIA.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348618969847</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:22:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348619487674-105</Id><Topic><Title>ONE WAY TO GO</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348525464695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:24:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks! keep going down day by day, I'm in control, i'll be a millionaire! short short short, just short, i told you so!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348619487674</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:31:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348619835420-106</Id><Title>Are you long or short?</Title><Msg>Coming to the conclusion that most of the posters on this board don't own any stock. Why comment unless you have skin in the game? Guess most are armchair quarterbacks. Watching Intel as a sport? Or not wanting to admit ownership for fear that someone might find out you're down. Have to keep up the front that you're in control and wise no matter what. If Intel goes down, it's "I told you so" (making a killing on a short position or if it goes up, it's "I bought at the bottom" and held to make a bundle for the heck of it.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348619835420</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:37:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348620026389-107</Id><Title>Everyone Knows</Title><Msg>That President Carter was the worst thing to happen to America since boiled liver and onions. Then our illegal alien President came along! America and the World are collapsing around us and all your illegal alien President wants to do is smile and tell cute little stories on the "View!" I can't believe this is happening! We must be in Toontown!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1348620026389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:40:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348620320516-108</Id><Title>Low was 19 last year. Higher highs, Higher Lows</Title><Msg>Chillax</Msg><Username>baltimoreravens_suck_coggg</Username><Timestamp>1348620320516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:45:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348621190602-109</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy capitulates, says buy INTEL</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1317740904000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-10-04 11:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TOOOFUNNNY</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1348621190602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348621200805-110</Id><Topic><Title>Low was 19 last year. Higher highs, Higher Lows</Title><Username>baltimoreravens_suck_coggg</Username><Timestamp>1348620320516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:45:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In fact, the pattern for INTC since the lofty 29 and change has been lower highs and lower lows.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348621200805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:00:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348621259530-111</Id><Topic><Title>Are you long or short?</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348619835420</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:37:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am long and am down but I dont care. I am in here for the long term, good yield and they have a terrific R&amp;D. Valuations is cheap.........Once the Apple Mania subdues people will come back to Intel........PC is dead is all #$%$........I am loading up Leaps....... Do you think that Intel will die because of Apple iphone and tablet? you must be kidding. Could we ever change the QWERTY pattern on our keyboards on PC which is from typewriter? We couldnt! same way PC is not going to die!</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1348621259530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:00:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348621349243-112</Id><Topic><Title>WDBLAWGROW says ZERO percent change Intel goes over 24......right before it goes to 29+</Title><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1348600680260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:18:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lolzzz</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1348621349243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:02:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348621384252-113</Id><Topic><Title>HAY Wdblwgrow, how's that SIRI you pumped no less than 80 to 200 percent higher than it is today, LMAO</Title><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1348600338727</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:12:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lolzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1348621384252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:03:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348621724200-114</Id><Title>Lazy Muslim President hasn't attended 60 percent of the daily CIA Briefs. Dispicable.</Title><Msg>Just PATHETIC !</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348621724200</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:08:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348623506266-115</Id><Title>Ya shoulda listened to marco :</Title><Msg>Folks, there's two kinds of INTC traders, the ones that listened to marco and shorted @ $28 and the ones who wish to heaven that they had listened to marco and shorted @ $28. I will make this prediction, one day INTC will paint $25 again, but, not before it paints $15. If you sold and/or went short like I told ya, and you want to show your appreciation, just send $25 to marcothegreat[at]paypal. thx in advance</Msg><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1348623506266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:38:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348623604687-116</Id><Topic><Title>Ya shoulda listened to marco :</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1348623506266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:38:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just looked at your posted history. You shorted Intel at 24 and 26........right before it went to 29. Did your wife kill yoiu like she said she was going to? You're a tool-box.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348623604687</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:40:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348623717846-117</Id><Title>Ya should listen to Marcopubio and buy facebook</Title><Msg>I lost so much money on FB By marcopubio.Jun 4, 2012 12:00 AM.Permalink I'm going to kill the wife before she gets a chance to see our brokerage statement. Any suggestions on how to make it look like an accident?</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348623717846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348623804060-118</Id><Topic><Title>Lazy Muslim President hasn't attended 60 percent of the daily CIA Briefs. Dispicable.</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348621724200</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:08:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's, "despicable," not, "dispicable." Spelling is the cornerstone of being listened to. My guess is that you are from the south. Also, your facts are completely wrong. Your "60%," nonsense is something that Rush Limbaugh uttered over the AM hate radio network. It is completely fallacious (look it up.) How is it that people as stupid as you manage to get on the internet? Liberry?</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1348623804060</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:43:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348624384220-119</Id><Topic><Title>Why are we up only 2 cents and GOOG is up 11 dollars</Title><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1348590250088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I told you so, lobster red!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348624384220</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:53:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348624460103-120</Id><Topic><Title>Ya shoulda listened to marco :</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1348623506266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:38:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't anybody listen to intc_inside, he's a paid pumper for INTC IR and gets $3.57 for each pump. They say he's a low level manager of 6 pumper bots. They'll probably fire him for his lousy performance.</Msg><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1348624460103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:54:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348624569524-121</Id><Topic><Title>Ya shoulda listened to marco :</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1348623506266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:38:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never listen to a putz (Marco) that says he's lost so much money on FB that he's going to kill his wife before she sees their DISASTER of a brokerage statement. LOL, get lost wuss.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348624569524</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:56:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348627229905-122</Id><Title>Time to buy</Title><Msg>I'll be buying soon. Probably after end of year/qtr. I have never seen such a bargain price for something so good as shares of INTC.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348627229905</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:40:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348628096056-123</Id><Topic><Title>Time to buy</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348627229905</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can buy it @ the middle of 2013, it will be single digit.</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348628096056</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:54:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348628147786-124</Id><Topic><Title>Time to buy</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348627229905</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like your IQ?</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348628147786</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:55:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348628342459-125</Id><Topic><Title>Lazy Muslim President hasn't attended 60 percent of the daily CIA Briefs. Dispicable.</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348621724200</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:08:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do you people come from and what in the name of Buddah, Allah, God or Shiva does this have to do with INTC?</Msg><Username>prc4me</Username><Timestamp>1348628342459</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:59:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348630296938-126</Id><Title>RSI almost lowest in 2 years.</Title><Msg>Slightly lower one time - aug 8, 2011.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348630296938</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 23:31:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>