<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354427737546-1</Id><Topic><Title>I got a call from SEC regarding my naked short "whistle"</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354393047619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would totally laugh my rear end off if some skumbag got busted for naked shorting. Anxiously awaiting updates...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354427737546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 00:55:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354427977794-2</Id><Topic><Title>I got a call from SEC regarding my naked short "whistle"</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354393047619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PS: Tell them to check the phone records of James Covello and Chris Danely while they are looking for illegal Intel trading...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354427977794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 00:59:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354428927087-3</Id><Topic><Title>IA architecture inside iPhones &amp; iPads = Negotiation NOT talks</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354407935082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:25:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>weak... you got NOTHING !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1354428927087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 01:15:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354433906616-4</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is a $100 stock</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354363260107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 07:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flumoxed flumoxed Stick up the Bummox looks like Wallis on roids! Get a grip</Msg><Username>marrohead</Username><Timestamp>1354433906616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 02:38:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354447645682-5</Id><Title>My insight:</Title><Msg>For some time there have been AAPL-INTC talks/negotiations. Then there was the "break-down" a month and a half back when AAPL said no more INTC chips in their products. Then O "stepped down." Now we are seeing "negotiations". These events are correlated. It's not hard to figure it out. O's politics were not acceptable to AAPL and they had to back-peddle from INTC. There's probably not a single AAPL employee with a measurable IQ who supported Romney (in fact, that is a generally true statement of most people, but most at AAPL have high IQ's). AAPL was offended by O's statements...at very least, for not keeping it to oneself. The INTC board saw a great oppty slipping away. So, out goes O, and we're back in serious "negotiations." In the meantime there is a strong correlation between the politics and intellect displayed on this board. You need only unignore att4glte occasionally to see how drool and republicanism are the same thing. Let the republicans scream and rant all they want. They lost, and of course, they are very bad sports. They are very bad losers...well, hey they are simply losers, period.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354447645682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 06:27:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354450694954-6</Id><Topic><Title>My insight:</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354447645682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 06:27:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is not the republicans who lost, but the American people. It is a tried and true fact that socialism does not work, yet Obama is leading us down that path and everyone is blindly marching to his magic flute. I manage a large factory in China and have 500 Chinese nationals on my team, half of whom are university-educated. They are bewildered by the aggressive moves toward socialism the US is now taking. They heard before in their own country the class warfare rhetoric from the man in charge, the media unable or unwilling to ask the tough questions due to a worship of the leader, and the term "fair share," over and over again. It led them into a multi-decade nightmare. People laugh at Romney and the republicans for not getting elected. People should focus less on who didn't win and more on who did - A man that raised more money from wealthy donors than any candidate in U.S. history. A man who took more money from the taxpayers by force and gave it to rich bankers. A man who was the first president in history to pass a major piece of legislation without a single vote from the opposing party (how's that for bi-partisanship and reaching across the aisle), and finally a man who for the first time passed a law penalizing 100% of Americans for NOT buying something. If you think this guy was dictatorial, legislated by fiat, was divisive and secretive beyond belief during his first term, just wait and see what happens now that he does not have to worry about reelection - assuming he doesn't overturn the 22nd Amendment by executive decree.</Msg><Username>tomjensen1945</Username><Timestamp>1354450694954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 07:18:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354451822077-7</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go read Alexander's post regarding valuation, and how INTC is cheaper today by all measures (besides PPS, which isn't really a measure) than it was in 2009 at 12.41 when the S&amp;P hit a low of 666. Nobody thought INTC should trade below 20 ever again, at least nobody with a brain. I do not post about every trade, but I too was buying all the way down, since the drop defied logic and reason. Who's the bigger idiot, you are the one who thinks ARMH is going to stay up forever with it's 70x P/E ratio. By comparison, INTC would have to trade above 150 to have such a sky high valuation, and has been growing earnings at about the same rate as your beloved ARM.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354451822077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 07:37:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354452369654-8</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's systemic problems</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354374845764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:14:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a systemic problem that you cant just root out which short term fixes. It needs a longer term approach to resurrecting the company which includes paying better for the better engineers, something Intel hasn't culturally been wont to doing. They've traditionally taken the stand that their corporate image is so good that they'll automatically attract the best engineers. Unfortunately, that has changed over time. Their lack of R&amp;D ROI is a symptom of this underlying problem. Also, their lack of being able to deliver on commitment. They make the right speeches, get their ducks lined up the right way, but the forward momentum is just not there.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354452369654</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 07:46:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354453148328-9</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's systemic problems</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354374845764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:14:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you sound like a disgruntled ex-employee.</Msg><Username>gordon939</Username><Timestamp>1354453148328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 07:59:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354453835595-10</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo Laptop - "think pad"</Title><Username>stok1mom</Username><Timestamp>1354245823705</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 22:23:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great job Mom. Kids are born every minute, years later they grow to be adults. The next generation won't know what an Ipad is.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354453835595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 08:10:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354454130161-11</Id><Topic><Title>IA architecture inside iPhones &amp; iPads = Negotiation NOT talks</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354407935082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:25:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Getanid61: Why do do you always shout (with caps) ?? Have you put yourself in an untenable postion or what is the issue...? Suggest you introspect. And just make your point and move on....</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1354454130161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 08:15:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354454356187-12</Id><Topic><Title>My insight:</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354447645682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 06:27:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama said Bush was irresponsible and unpatriotic for adding 4 trillion in 8 years......said this was unsustainable and that he PLEDGED to cut the deficit in half in his first term.................anyone ever heard anything more #$%$ than this? People like me that have no debt, house paid off and worked for every single bit of it have to listen to SKUM like Flumoxed puke all over themselves daily. Google Conservatism is calling, watch the video and you'll be blown away by Obama's own words about the defit as well as Ronald Reagen's take on Government after he switched from Liberal to Conservative.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354454356187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 08:19:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354454687009-13</Id><Title>HP Ditches ARM Server Project</Title><Msg>HP ditches ARM for Intel in Project Moonshot Published on 20th June 2012 by Gareth Halfacree</Msg><Username>ikeclanton_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1354454687009</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 08:24:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354454742347-14</Id><Title>HP Ditches ARM Tablet Efforts</Title><Msg>HP ditches Windows RT tablet plans, Microsoft Surface to blame TabletsJune 29, 2012at 2:45 PM by Dan Graziano</Msg><Username>ikeclanton_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1354454742347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 08:25:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354454831330-15</Id><Title>AMD, ARM's new server partner says ARM servers may be a waste of time</Title><Msg>Google it.</Msg><Username>ikeclanton_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1354454831330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 08:27:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354454898306-16</Id><Title>VMWare CEO says ARM servers not happening anytime soon</Title><Msg>VMware Boss Puts Brakes on ARM Server Revolution By Cade Metz08.30.123:08 PM</Msg><Username>ikeclanton_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1354454898306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 08:28:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354455064910-17</Id><Title>Intel chips REPLACE ARM Holding chips in Europe</Title><Msg>Google-owned Motorola Mobility on Tuesday joined Intel in London to unveil the Razr i, Motorola's first smartphone with an Intel processor.</Msg><Username>ikeclanton_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1354455064910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 08:31:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354457102852-18</Id><Title>Stacy Smith presentation</Title><Msg>Stacy Smith did a lengthy presentation last Tuesday, its on the Intel website, Investor Relations. He didn't sound too down (he's been something of a sad sack the last couple of earnings conferences) so I think the quarter is progressing about as they thought. At about 49 minutes in he's asked about doing foundry work for Apple. (This is a couple days before the latest rumor broke.) He's a little vague, as to be expected, but I took his answer to be essentially "no." He said something about being hopeful of getting Apple's business, but X86 chips "are job one," implying that they'd like the business by convincing Apple to convert because of Intel's superior technology. That's how I read it, someone else listen and see what you think.</Msg><Username>dundarra</Username><Timestamp>1354457102852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:05:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354458841476-19</Id><Topic><Title>My insight:</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354447645682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 06:27:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is not the republicans who lost, but the American people. It is a tried and true fact that socialism does not work, yet Obama is leading us down that path and everyone is blindly marching to his magic flute. I manage a large factory in China and have 500 Chinese nationals on my team, half of whom are university-educated. They are bewildered by the aggressive moves toward socialism the US is now taking. They heard before in their own country the class warfare rhetoric from the man in charge, the media unable or unwilling to ask the tough questions due to a worship of the leader, and the term "fair share," over and over again. It led them into a multi-decade nightmare. People laugh at Romney and the republicans for not getting elected. People should focus less on who didn't win and more on who did - A man that raised more money from wealthy donors than any candidate in U.S. history. A man who took more money from the taxpayers by force and gave it to rich bankers. A man who was the first president in history to pass a major piece of legislation without a single vote from the opposing party (how's that for bi-partisanship and reaching across the aisle), and finally a man who for the first time passed a law penalizing 100% of Americans for NOT buying something. If you think this guy was dictatorial, legislated by fiat, was divisive and secretive beyond belief during his first term, just wait and see what happens now that he does not have to worry about reelection - assuming he doesn't overturn the 22nd Amendment by executive decree. __________ Terrifying and very real. You know we are a mess when outsiders look at us and scratch their heads at us ruining our Freedom. But guys like Flumoxed don't care.........he'll just let future generations worry about the catastrophe he and his ilk are creating. What a tragedy unfolding.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354458841476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:34:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354459380923-20</Id><Title>The best way to make a dividend play on INTC, IMO, is:</Title><Msg>Buy 1,000 shares at 19. This gives you $900/year and total cost of 19,000 Should it go down lower: Buy 1,000 shares at 18 giving you another $900/year for a total of $1,800 and total cost 37,000 Buy 1,000 shares at 17 giving you another $900/year for a total of $2,700 and total cost of 54,000 Buy 1,000 shares at 16 giving you another $900/year for a total of $3,600 and total cost of 70,000 Buy 1,000 shares at 15 giving you another $900/year for a total of 4,500 and total cost of 85,000 Buy 1,000 shares at 14 giving you another $900/year for a total of 5,400 and total cost of 99,000 Buy 1,000 shares at 13 giving you another $900/year for a total of 6,300 and total cost of 112,000 Buy 1,000 shares at 12 giving you another $900/year for a total of 7,200 and total cost of 124,000 I doubt it will go any lower than that, however, if it does just keep cost averaging in. I think it is a good buy at this price, however, you should cost average in to be on the safe side. so should it drop you still make good money on the dividend with only a little invested. lovemedo</Msg><Username>jamespeter255</Username><Timestamp>1354459380923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:43:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354459847129-21</Id><Title>Paul Otellin presentation.</Title><Msg>Intel CEO will be speaking at Sanford Bernstein Conference on Dec. 5 at 9 am PT.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1354459847129</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:50:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354460313818-22</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith presentation</Title><Username>dundarra</Username><Timestamp>1354457102852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:05:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about posting a link. Last presentation from Smith was in October</Msg><Username>kahoutek_44</Username><Timestamp>1354460313818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:58:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354460446346-23</Id><Topic><Title>My insight:</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354447645682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 06:27:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure is and it also makes me ill. We in trouble folks.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1354460446346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 10:00:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354461332819-24</Id><Topic><Title>My insight:</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354447645682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 06:27:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The GOP lost and are losers" ________ Wow, you sound like such an intellectual heavyweight. What did you win again? The right to take money away from those that worked hard for it? Yeah, that'll work...</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1354461332819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 10:15:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354461475970-25</Id><Topic><Title>My insight:</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354447645682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 06:27:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Elections are over,please keep stupid useless tit for tat politics off this financial board TY.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1354461475970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 10:17:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354462296423-26</Id><Topic><Title>My insight:</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354447645682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 06:27:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please. Obama election was a farce, due mainly to better campaign organization than to actual policies. Most Americans want lower taxes &amp; lower spending (except for the lazy). The Repubs will never go for the ridiculous higher taxes for the higher income (i.e., class warfare). Repubs are in the driver seat..Obama doesnt want the fiscal cliff &amp; recession on his watch, so he'll have to compromise.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1354462296423</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 10:31:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354462481322-27</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Inside The Apple iPad? It Makes Sense!</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354406975293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I also called for Paul O's resignation for the past 2 years &amp; it looks like I was very right on that one. What a poor leader he turned out to be. Its a shame because Intel has all the capability to be a $50 stock right now.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1354462481322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 10:34:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354463109678-28</Id><Topic><Title>The best way to make a dividend play on INTC, IMO, is:</Title><Username>jamespeter255</Username><Timestamp>1354459380923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:43:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>an absurd idea. as absurd as believing one can get rich simply buying a holding a semiconductor stock. in addition, when dividend rates go up, there will be far less incentive to pay one or increase one.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1354463109678</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 10:45:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354463794055-29</Id><Topic><Title>The best way to make a dividend play on INTC, IMO, is:</Title><Username>jamespeter255</Username><Timestamp>1354459380923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:43:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How'd the people do that bought at 13 in 2002 and sold at 32 in 2003 do? What about those that bought at 13 in 2008 and sold at 29 this year? Let's not even talk about those that bought in the single digits that now have a Dividend payment that blows their mind. How are those 20 cent trades at the bottom treating you? From the anger in your voice, obviously not too well.</Msg><Username>ikeclanton_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1354463794055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 10:56:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354465084406-30</Id><Topic><Title>The best way to make a dividend play on INTC, IMO, is:</Title><Username>jamespeter255</Username><Timestamp>1354459380923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:43:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>loosy the 2bit daytrader that lives on a chat board 24/7 must be doing great LOL.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1354465084406</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:18:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354465788852-31</Id><Topic><Title>IA architecture inside iPhones &amp; iPads = Negotiation NOT talks</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354407935082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:25:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Getanid61: Why do do you always shout (with caps) ??" For the naive who ignore the obvious... "Have you put yourself in an untenable postion " The opposite... "Suggest you introspect." Evidence dictates otherwise... "And just make your point " Doubt anyone has any trouble understanding my points...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1354465788852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:29:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354466116140-32</Id><Topic><Title>I got a call from SEC regarding my naked short "whistle"</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354393047619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kuddos for your effort Alex. Hope something good comes out for us the ordinary human being investors.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1354466116140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:35:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354467376771-33</Id><Topic><Title>IA architecture inside iPhones &amp; iPads = Negotiation NOT talks</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354407935082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:25:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I understand your point you're an insecure little man that shills over priced over hyped ARMH on the INTC board.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1354467376771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:56:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354467519825-34</Id><Topic><Title>I got a call from SEC regarding my naked short "whistle"</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354393047619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those are the rules of the game, doooshwad. The shares being shorted are in The Street's name. If you don't want your shares to be shorted, request the certificates for "your" shares. Then if you need to get out in a hurry, you can wait 3 days in turn-around time. You people are SOOOOOO STOOOOOOOPID!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354467519825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:58:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354467833745-35</Id><Topic><Title>I got a call from SEC regarding my naked short "whistle"</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354393047619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The more letters you write, the lower the stock goes, Pumpwad. You guys, all of you, are crybabies. And now Alexander has joined Waldo's crybaby parade! TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354467833745</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:03:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354468136809-36</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith presentation</Title><Username>dundarra</Username><Timestamp>1354457102852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:05:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Presentation is at: intcDOTcom Events calendar Credit Suisse conference Concerning foundry work for Apple, he didn't flat out say 'no, we will never manufacture ARM chips' so that tells me there is the possibility and I think the rumors are true and deal will be announced soon. I few things I got from the presentation: - He seems very surprised that INTC stock price has dropped to the point where it is yeilding 4.5% dividend - cost per transistor continues to go down (24 min mark) for Intel but notes that competitors is not able to do this. - Mentions a couple of times a major competitor (i think he means AMD) is about to exit the server market. AMD in deep trouble. - Lenovo yoga selling like hotcakes...convertibles and detachables selling very well...lines between tablet and pc's are blurring. Believes there is pent up refresh coming - Says 14nm manufacturing sites will be ramping up production starting in 2013. Not sure what he means by this? will 14nm products be available in 2013? - expect Intel's phone market share to more than double for each of the next few years - gross margins back to normal by 2nd quarter</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354468136809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:08:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354468473850-37</Id><Topic><Title>I got a call from SEC regarding my naked short "whistle"</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354393047619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am familiar with the rules,my point is little 2bit lowlife douchnozzels like yourself should be made to pay a user fee for using shares they have no vested intrest in IMO.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1354468473850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:14:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354469036765-38</Id><Topic><Title>IA architecture inside iPhones &amp; iPads = Negotiation NOT talks</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354407935082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:25:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I understand your point " Evidence dictates you don't !!!! Compare ARMH vs INTC... on yahoo charts... every option yahoo charts offers: 1D, 5D, 1M, 3M 6M, YTD, 1Y, 2Y, 5Y, MAX keep the faith...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1354469036765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:23:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354469248676-39</Id><Topic><Title>I got a call from SEC regarding my naked short "whistle"</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354393047619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for your efforts and hope you are compensated largely. Naked shorting is one of the many things wrong with the stock market.</Msg><Username>blair.wagner</Username><Timestamp>1354469248676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:27:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354469461903-40</Id><Topic><Title>IA architecture inside iPhones &amp; iPads = Negotiation NOT talks</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354407935082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:25:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You #$%$ always take the bait! I thought you had me on ignore, jackwipe. TOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354469461903</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:31:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354469843296-41</Id><Topic><Title>I got a call from SEC regarding my naked short "whistle"</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354393047619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Investopedia explains 'Naked Shorting' Naked shorting is illegal because it allows manipulators a chance to force stock prices down without regard for normal stock supply/demand patterns. In 2007, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) amended Regulation SHO to further limit possibilities for naked shorting by removing loopholes that existed for some broker/dealers. Regulation SHO requires lists to be published that track stocks with unusually high trends in "fail to deliver" shares. Some analysts point to the fact that naked shorting, albeit inadvertently, may help markets stay in balance by allowing the negative sentiment to be reflected in certain stocks' prices.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1354469843296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:37:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354470957220-42</Id><Title>INTC will be in Apple's iPad soon - here's why</Title><Msg>The lines between tablets and PCs are blurring. With products like the samsung ativ smart pc 500t and Acer iconia w510, hard to differentiate. If windows tablets can run full windows, there is a major competitive advantage over iPads which only run iOS. If Apple wants to respond with a tablet running full MacOS, should it run on ARM or INTEL? I posted earlier that a lot of Mac users install Windows on their Macbook using bootcamp or some emulator program (parallels) so if Apple wants to keep that trend going they need to have to convert to tablets running Intel. By switching, there is also the advantage that they do not have to convert their MacOS to run on ARM. As well, all there won't be any compatibility issues for all current SW running on MacOS ala Windows RT. Finally, the Intel's chip is just heads and shoulders above ARM in terms of performance (power effiency matching soon with Broadwell). BTW, check out the patent Apple has at the below link. MacPad is coming! patentlyappleDOTcom/patently-apple/2010/11/apple-wins-multiple-touch-macbook-tablet-patentsDOThtml</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354470957220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:55:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354471069638-43</Id><Title>Lenovo Yoga reviews on best buy ON FIRE - GREAT point about no longer needing multiple gadgets</Title><Msg>here's just one: I'm really digging this IdeaPad Yoga so far. I've used it like a traditional laptop for typing longer documents, chatting with friends, or casual surfing. I flip it around to the stand mode (keys against my lap, screen closer to me) for games, watching videos, and doing light surfing that doesn't require a keyboard. This is probably my favorite mode. You don't have to hold it, but that big, gorgeous screen is right there close. And I flip it to a tablet when I want to show videos or photos to others. Haven't used tent mode yet, but I probably will for watching movies with my significant other. All in all, this thing rocks! You really need touch for Windows 8 to shine, but this gives you a keyboard when you need to get work done. Much better than carrying both a tablet and a laptop (which I've done). Nice!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354471069638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:57:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354471181003-44</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will be in Apple's iPad soon - here's why</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354470957220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the way, getting a Intel-based tablet to run iOS will not be a problem since iOS share the same kernel as MacOS. Did you know what iOS apps are all compiled using x86 machines?</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354471181003</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:59:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354471574953-45</Id><Title>INTC for true investors!</Title><Msg>I am not concerned about INTC performance in the short term. GS analyst is not stating the fact that INTC servers are the killers not their PC business. INTC could double in a year if they hire a great CEO!.</Msg><Username>sameas55</Username><Timestamp>1354471574953</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:06:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354472278894-46</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith presentation</Title><Username>dundarra</Username><Timestamp>1354457102852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:05:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He also mentioned that the haswell ultrabooks entering the market in the first half of 2013 will run at less than 10 watts and have twice the graphics performance. Also, tablets in the 7 inch range might run on the medifield platform. I also do not think Intel will produce arm chips.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1354472278894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:17:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354472715551-47</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith presentation</Title><Username>dundarra</Username><Timestamp>1354457102852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:05:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I also do not think they will produce arm chips long term. But they might just for Apple for the next iteration of the iPhone but after that I expect the iphone will run Intel going forwards. So if there is agreement, it might result in Intel manufacturing Apple-design arm chips for a temporary basis.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354472715551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:25:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354473089296-48</Id><Title>Intel will manufacture ARM chips for Iphone until the clearly beat the ARM designs</Title><Msg>There is absolutely NOTHING to lose for either company when looked at that way. NOTHING. My older brother, Getanid61 is learning what KARMA is all about. His need to rub the stock price of ARM into the faces of Intel holders is gonna dome full circle on him.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1354473089296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:31:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354474059222-49</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will manufacture ARM chips for Iphone until the clearly beat the ARM designs</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1354473089296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:31:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are saying Intel will agree with Apple to do ARM designs and then switch over to Intel designs only after it's clear that theirs are better, I agree with you and agree that it's a stellar deal for both, and very fair. Apple would agree to this as they'd be assured of the best designs available, whether they be ARM or Intel and Intel would be able to control its own destiny as long as they came up with the best chips.</Msg><Username>blacklabpup2003</Username><Timestamp>1354474059222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:47:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354474282313-50</Id><Title>Can Intel save Apple from its LTE mess?</Title><Msg>Can Intel Save Apple From the LTE Mess? Sascha Segan By Sascha Segan September 15, 2012 11:30am EST iPhone 4 vs. iPhone 4S vs. iPhone 5 Apple couldn't engineer itself out of the global LTE mess, but maybe Intel can. The new iPhone 5 features 4G LTE, which is going to dramatically improve Internet speeds for AT&amp;T and Verizon iPhone owners. (Sprint subscribers are left waiting for LTE to arrive where they live.) But globally, the iPhone LTE picture is a disaster. There are two different iPhone models. The AT&amp;T iPhone will work on LTE on T-Mobile USA and in Canada, but not in the rest of the world. The Verizon/Sprint iPhone will work in some European and Asian countries. No iPhone will work on the existing LTE networks in Austria, Brazil, Columbia, Denmark, Norway, Russia, Saudi Arabia, and Switzerland, as iMore points out. The phones will still roam where they can't get LTE; they'll be on 3G, which isn't fatal, but it's a night-and-day difference in terms of speeds. The incompatibility is because there are way too many frequency bands being used for mobile phone networks right now. Apple's a popularizer and refiner of technologies; they're not introducing any radical new RF breakthroughs here, so they're stuck in the same LTE band whirlwind that everyone else is. Between Apple's two models, it's already supporting seven different LTE bands, known as band 1, 3, 4, 5, 13, 17 and 25. But European operators have three more bands they use: 7, 20 and 38. They may also use band 8 in the future. Some Asian operators appear to be on Band 40. Here at home, Sprint also plans to use band 26, and some smaller US carriers have band 12. It's a mess. It means phone makers have to put together lots of different models for different countries, and those units will have trouble roaming well in other countries if they travel. It also means small carriers on obscure LTE bands, like 12, have trouble getting phones that work well with their networks because there are no huge carriers placing large orders for them. Can Intel Fix Apple's Problems? Fortunately, across the street from the iPhone event, I saw a potential solution. Intel's Developer Forum was going on just across the street from Apple this week. Up on the second floor, the company was showing off the four relatively lackluster Intel phones so far, as well as a modem technology that could really change things. Intel's XMM6260 modem, which has been in the market for a while, uses a single power amplifier for multiple bands, and it can be extended in software to support as many bands as necessary. It doesn't support LTE or CDMA, which is part of why we haven't seen it in many U.S. products. But the point here, an Intel engineer told me, is that the company will be able to put an unlimited number of bands on a single LTE modem, possibly as soon as late next year. Intel's modems will be able to mate with processors from Samsung, Nvidia, TI, and others. Apple used its modems up until 2010, when it switched over to Qualcomm in part to get Verizon and Sprint compatibility. Modems are only half of the solution, though. Dermot O'Shea, co-founder of antenna firm Taoglas, said antenna design gets difficult when you're covering such a wide range of frequencies. Active antennas for smartphones, which have just started to hit the market this year, can adapt to different bands without being huge, although they add to the cost and complexity of smartphones. We're likely to see more of them next year. Between active antennas and multi-frequency power amplifiers, it looks like phone makers are starting to get their hands around the riot of LTE frequencies; they're just not there yet. Maybe we'll see them in the iPhone 7.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1354474282313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:51:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354474287909-51</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith presentation</Title><Username>dundarra</Username><Timestamp>1354457102852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:05:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You could be right. I can not see apple moving all their chip needs to intel. I believe with all the talk about tsmc means the tsmc will make some chips for apple ( probably i phone). If tsmc fails to deliver , intel may be a fall back for arm production. If Intel does get apple tablet chips, this would be an important step in allowing both companies gain experience with x86 chips running the ios system so if or when apple moves the iphone to intel in the future. By moving their tablets to intel, apple would gain a new market for their larger ipad(run the mac os) and relieve some of the supply demand on arm foundries.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1354474287909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:51:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354474592789-52</Id><Title>Intel and Apple Sitting in a Tree: K-I-S-S-I-N-G</Title><Msg>Top four articles today from the message board news section are all on the potential and major expansion of the Apple/Intel relationship. Could the geniuses on Chump Street have totally screwed the pooch???</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354474592789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:56:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354475055228-53</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith presentation</Title><Username>dundarra</Username><Timestamp>1354457102852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:05:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I can not see apple moving all their chip needs to intel. I believe with all the talk about tsmc means the tsmc will make some chips for apple ( probably i phone). If tsmc fails to deliver , intel may be a fall back for arm production. If Intel does get apple tablet chips, this would be an important step in allowing both companies gain experience with x86 chips running the ios system so if or when apple moves the iphone to intel in the future. By moving their tablets to intel, apple would gain a new market for their larger ipad(run the mac os) and relieve some of the supply demand on arm foundries." [The problem is that Apple cannot afford for TSMC to fail to deliver. That would be an economic disaster for them. And it's not so easy for someone else to be a fall back. It takes an enormous amount of time and effort to set up production. I just don't know that Apple can afford the uncertainty or to back two different companies. The reliable solution is clearly Intel. TSMC still doesn't have volume 28nm production. Volume availability of 20nm is a huge unknown...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354475055228</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 14:04:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354475402534-54</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith presentation</Title><Username>dundarra</Username><Timestamp>1354457102852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:05:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I cannot see tsmc doing all iphones. Maybe instead of Intel being a fall back plan, it could be that Intel manufacture chips for use on Verizon say and tsmc manufacture chips for AT&amp;T. But i agree, Intel in future iPads.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354475402534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 14:10:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354476356394-55</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith presentation</Title><Username>dundarra</Username><Timestamp>1354457102852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:05:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually i take it back, if they split the production between intel and tsmc, Intel iPhones will perform better than the ones produced by tsmc and carriers/customers will complain. So I agree with Wallis, Apple will go with Intel for the whole production using more advanced and reliable and better yielding Intel's 22nm process.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354476356394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 14:25:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354476922073-56</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will be in Apple's iPad soon - here's why</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354470957220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You keep a hoping &amp; keep a praying... too bad for you Apple is investing more in the ARM ISA... keep the faith...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1354476922073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 14:35:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354477063915-57</Id><Topic><Title>a gift to get intc below $22</Title><Username>lilies778</Username><Timestamp>1352151206420</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-05 16:33:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>set long term buys for 18's aeaggggg</Msg><Username>weburk</Username><Timestamp>1354477063915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 14:37:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354477920205-58</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will be in Apple's iPad soon - here's why</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354470957220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am long Intel and would like nothing more than MacPad announcement. I am also an IT professional and know that porting iOS to x86 is a very doable task with well defined timeframe. What I am not sure about is what should be a strategy for supporting all existing ARM based applications. Obviously, not supporting existing apps is not an option - no one will upgrade to a new iPad if it's incompatible with all existing Apps. Then what? and before anyone gives an example of Android port which supports most existing applications, 80% of Android apps run under Java VM and could care less about underlying instruction set. With iOs applications are compiled to a native arm instruction set and Intel would have to emulate ARM to support them. Question is how much performance/power hit would this take? Will translation happen one time upon installing an application? What other options are there? Would love to hear intelligent discussion on this topic.</Msg><Username>bubbagumphere</Username><Timestamp>1354477920205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 14:52:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354478264926-59</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will be in Apple's iPad soon - here's why</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354470957220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What I am not sure about is what should be a strategy for supporting all existing ARM based applications." Fab an ARM chip...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1354478264926</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 14:57:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354478847591-60</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will be in Apple's iPad soon - here's why</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354470957220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The iPad wouldn't consider going to an Intel processor until Bay Trail in 2014. A MacPad is possible using Haswell in 2013 but that would require a touch-based Mac operating system. Then the 2013 Mac touch OS could go on the 2014 Bay Trail iPad. Also, does Apple support both a Mac touch OS and a Mac regular OS and do something more than Microsoft ? And then, the iPhone keeps the iOS and so that's three operating systems. Then since that's three different operating systems, the iPad actually keeps the ARM processor but a MacPad with a Haswell processor is added. The iPad is only concerned with being a coffee-shop touch-browser. If something more is wanted that's a MacPad. An iMacPad ?</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1354478847591</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:07:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354479193539-61</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will be in Apple's iPad soon - here's why</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354470957220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read this article: extremetechDOTcom/computing/113123-how-intels-medfield-will-dismantle-arm In the comments section, one knowledgeable commenter states: "Do you not know that iOS is basically a fork of Mac OS X (which runs on x86), and that the "iPhone Simulator" which every iOS developer uses to write their apps is not a CPU emulator, but runs their iOS code directly against the x86 APIs? " The author then replied: "Yep, I'm well aware that iOS and OS X have basically the same kernel. Are you saying that iOS developers, when they test their apps, are building x86 executables? If so, that's pretty cool." Remember ios apps are in a closed enviroment. They all have to be verified by Apple and are all on Apple's app store. It would be easy to convert all apps to run on x86. Another interesting article to read by same author: extremetechDOTcom/computing/130552-intel-dismisses-x86-tax-sees-no-future-for-arm-or-any-of-its-competitors</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354479193539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:13:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354480318548-62</Id><Title>Intel in Lenovo and Dell thinkpads</Title><Msg>I really like these thinkpads and for anyone who wants a combination epad and laptop, they look great. I tend to like the Lenovo better after seeing it at Best Buy. If you want to have the full Windows 8 experience, this is what I would buy.</Msg><Username>stok1mom</Username><Timestamp>1354480318548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:31:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354480375773-63</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will be in Apple's iPad soon - here's why</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354470957220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most importantly, though, ARM must be painfully aware that Intel has matched the latest and greatest Cortex-A9 with its first ever attempt at a real SoC, and at 32nm no less. While competition from Samsung and Qualcomm are pushing out with limited supplies of 32/28nm chips, Intel has already announced that it will be shrinking its ultra-low-power Atom chips to 22nm in 2013 and 14nm in 2014. Say what you like about ARM chips being inherently more efficient, but the shift to 22nm and 14nm will mean that Intels ULV chips simply cannot be beaten. ARM can innovate until its blue in the face, but at the end of the day it will be impossible to compete with Intels far superior manufacturing process  and heck, on top of all that, its not like Intel doesnt know how to make a good CPU. In short, ARM &amp; Co. are in a very unenviable position. Intel now has a beachhead and its terrifying, industry-clobbering, 60%-gross-margin wehrmacht will surely follow. You might only see a few Medfield-powered scouts in 2012, but by the time the 22nm Silvermont tanks roll around in 2013 and x86 is better than ARM across the board, expect to see dozens of Santa Clara design wins. Unless TSMC, IBM, GloFo, or Samsung uncover some kind of ancient scroll that details the magic of 14nm, come 2014 and the Airmont core, I wouldnt be surprised if Intel completely dominates the Android smartphone market. Following the Motorola partnership, I would also be very surprised if Microsoft and Apple arent working on x86 versions of their mobile operating systems, too.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354480375773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:32:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354480400829-64</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo Laptop - "think pad"</Title><Username>stok1mom</Username><Timestamp>1354245823705</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 22:23:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. Not a bomcomputer: a computer. LOL.</Msg><Username>stok1mom</Username><Timestamp>1354480400829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:33:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354480871352-65</Id><Title>Lennovo top end phones with Intel inside will happen, and will make Intel RICH</Title><Msg>Lenovo is on a mission. Check it.</Msg><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1354480871352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:41:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354481511087-66</Id><Title>Latest Barrons (Dec. 3 issue) says BUY INTC! Mid to high $20s on the way.</Title><Msg>Should be good for a rally to mid or high $20s.</Msg><Username>to.josie</Username><Timestamp>1354481511087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:51:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354481663755-67</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Caris Cuts Estimatesat Forbes (Fri 10:22AM EST)</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1354300605387</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:36:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Latest Barrons (Dec. 3 issue) says BUY INTC! Mid to high $20s on the way.</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1354481663755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:54:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354482028723-68</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will be in Apple's iPad soon - here's why</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354470957220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 2014 there will be an iPhone with an ARM processor, an iPad with an ARM processor, a MacPad with a Bay Trail processor, and a MacPad with a Hawell processor. See, the stock market analysts confused a coffee-shop browser ramp-up with a longer PC replacement cycle. The coffee-shop browser ramp-up will top out and at about that same time a PC replacement cycle will begin. But one doesn't really drive the other.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1354482028723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:00:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354483241364-69</Id><Title>With only good news to come and all bad out, this is a VERY dangerous short......</Title><Msg>and I have nothing against shorting! I short myself but going short on the bottom end and potential deals in the works. Geesh, really scary to have to cover this big boy on ANY good news.</Msg><Username>nysstocks</Username><Timestamp>1354483241364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:20:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354483382125-70</Id><Topic><Title>Latest Barrons (Dec. 3 issue) says BUY INTC! Mid to high $20s on the way.</Title><Username>to.josie</Username><Timestamp>1354481511087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:51:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are way too optimistic</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1354483382125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:23:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354483429834-71</Id><Topic><Title>a gift to get intc below $22</Title><Username>lilies778</Username><Timestamp>1352151206420</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-05 16:33:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>might get there but keeps bouncing off support. Left a little powder dry if it creeps under $19. Holding long and strong 3K averaged @ $19.68</Msg><Username>nysstocks</Username><Timestamp>1354483429834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:23:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354484502401-72</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will be in Apple's iPad soon - here's why</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354470957220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:55:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Binary translation for Android enables running of ARM code on x86, and is very fast, little or no difference from running natively on ARM. This is possible because ARM is a RISC based architecture, which by definition has a reduced instruction set. X86 is complex instruction set, so it is able to do much more in a single clock cycle by comparison. The reverse is true if trying to emulate x86 on ARM, the CPU may need to use multiple clock cycles to perform the same instructions. There is no reason why binary translation shouldn't work for iOS, and if things progress as expected for Atom at 14nm and beyond, the iOS applications will likely end up running MUCH better on x86 even though compiled for ARM.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354484502401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:41:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354484692452-73</Id><Title>Stacy Smith for CEO?</Title><Msg>If not Pat Gelsinger or Andy Bryant (but he is a little old) then I like Stacy Smith.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354484692452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:44:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354484843312-74</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith for CEO?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354484692452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:44:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dadi Perlmutter would be my first choice.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354484843312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:47:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354484887712-75</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith for CEO?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354484692452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:44:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's been my preference from day 1. He's a good, honest and well-spoken man. Intel is doing EXACTLY what they need to do. They are targeting Mobile fiercly and evolving the PC at the same time. Intel Radio, Select Foundy business, etc...What else can you ask from them !?</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354484887712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:48:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354484903086-76</Id><Topic><Title>Latest Barrons (Dec. 3 issue) says BUY INTC! Mid to high $20s on the way.</Title><Username>to.josie</Username><Timestamp>1354481511087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:51:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two separate articles on Intel. First, MKM Partners likes On Semiconductor, Fairchild, Qualcomm and three others. "Our framework analyses suggest that, after significant cuts over the course of the last two months, consensus estimates for 2013/2014 for broad-based semiconductors are much more realistic. Unfortunately, valuation for many names suggests that investors expect a sharper (and faster) snapback than seems likely. It has historically paid to own these stocks when numbers are no longer going down, but we struggle to see how the group broadly will be higher a year from now. We view On Semiconductor (ticker: ONNN) and Fairchild Semiconductor International (FCS) as the most attractive cyclical names because we see clear upside to estimates on reasonable valuation. We also remain positive on product stories ( Qualcomm (QCOM), Broadcom (BRCM)), as well as Intel (INTC) (consensus structurally too negative, but the [ Microsoft (MSFT)] Windows 8 data points seem to be getting worse) and catalyst-driven Micron Technology (MU)." Also, an article by Andrew Bary. How to Play the Economic Recovery By ANDREW BARY Ross Margolies says the recovery in auto sales and the housing rebound bode well for the U.S. Why he likes Celanese, Hormel, Intel and JPMorgan. "Margolies spoke with Barron's recently at his Manhattan offices, weighing in on the shale energy revolution and why he is bullish on the U.S. economy and stock market. His current favorites include Hormel Foods; Celanese; Seagate Technology; JPMorgan Chase; AerCap Holdings, an aircraft-leasing firm; and out-of-favor Intel . What do you see in Intel that the market doesn't? The stock is around $19.50 now, and it trades for 10 to 11 times next year's earnings. The consensus for 2013 is around $2 a share, but we are assuming projections come down to between $1.75 and $1.85 because the PC market is very tough. It has a dividend yield of more than 4%. We know that Intel [INTC] is cutting back production, and that process takes about six months, and is detrimental to margins while it's happening. How bad is the situation? The core PC-chip business is weak. Intel has low penetration in the mobile market, and, to top it off, CEO Paul Otellini announced that he is going to retire in six months. So why are we buying it instead of selling it? The answer is that Intel has transformed its business dramatically over the past five years from a manufacturing standpoint and taken out a lot of costs. Technology companies historically have not been disciplined manufacturers. Intel also has a technology lead over other semiconductor makers. What's the key there? Intel has developed a new three-dimensional chip design called Tri-Gate that allows Intel to develop chips with either more processing power or better battery life. The reason Intel missed the mobile market is that it was always focused on speed, not battery life. As the world went mobile, battery life became more important. Intel has addressed that now. In addition, Intel is the dominant company in making chips for servers, which are very profitable. So you think Intel will crack the mobile market? Intel should pick up share in the mobile markets where it has none. People are concerned about Intel losing share in PCs, despite the fact that its main competitor, Advanced Micro Devices, is pulling back. Intel should pick up meaningful market share in phones and tablets over time, and if that happens, it should offset what occurs in PCs. Do you think the dividend is safe? It's very safe. If anything, Intel is going to keep on raising it, although probably not in the next few months. Intel spends an enormous amount each year on capital expenditures. It could easily cut back on a few billion dollars worth of capex, and generate a lot of extra free cash. Intel controls its own fate. As long as Intel keeps its technology lead, it's going to be hard for anyone to keep up.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354484903086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:48:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354484916837-77</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith for CEO?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354484692452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:44:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mark Bohr would be my 2nd...</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354484916837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:48:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354484929394-78</Id><Title>Google "Conservatism is Calling" and watch the video for Obama's debt LIES</Title><Msg>do it!!!!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354484929394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:48:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354484956336-79</Id><Topic><Title>Latest Barrons (Dec. 3 issue) says BUY INTC! Mid to high $20s on the way.</Title><Username>to.josie</Username><Timestamp>1354481511087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:51:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two separate articles on Intel. First, MKM Partners likes On Semiconductor, Fairchild, Qualcomm and three others. "Our framework analyses suggest that, after significant cuts over the course of the last two months, consensus estimates for 2013/2014 for broad-based semiconductors are much more realistic. Unfortunately, valuation for many names suggests that investors expect a sharper (and faster) snapback than seems likely. It has historically paid to own these stocks when numbers are no longer going down, but we struggle to see how the group broadly will be higher a year from now. We view On Semiconductor (ticker: ONNN) and Fairchild Semiconductor International (FCS) as the most attractive cyclical names because we see clear upside to estimates on reasonable valuation. We also remain positive on product stories ( Qualcomm (QCOM), Broadcom (BRCM)), as well as Intel (INTC) (consensus structurally too negative, but the [ Microsoft (MSFT)] Windows 8 data points seem to be getting worse) and catalyst-driven Micron Technology (MU)."</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354484956336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:49:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354485073663-80</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith for CEO?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354484692452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:44:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dadi is not a good communicator...is accent is too strong but i like him.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354485073663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:51:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354485106910-81</Id><Topic><Title>Latest Barrons (Dec. 3 issue) says BUY INTC! Mid to high $20s on the way.</Title><Username>to.josie</Username><Timestamp>1354481511087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:51:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two separate articles on Intel. First, MKM Partners likes On Semiconductor, Fairchild, Qualcomm and three others. "Our framework analyses suggest that, after significant cuts over the course of the last two months, consensus estimates for 2013 / 2014 for broad-based semiconductors are much more realistic. Unfortunately, valuation for many names suggests that investors expect a sharper (and faster) snapback than seems likely. It has historically paid to own these stocks when numbers are no longer going down, but we struggle to see how the group broadly will be higher a year from now. We view On Semiconductor and Fairchild Semiconductor International as the most attractive cyclical names because we see clear upside to estimates on reasonable valuation. We also remain positive on product stories Qualcomm, Broadcom, as well as Intel (consensus structurally too negative, but the .... "</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354485106910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:51:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354485196483-82</Id><Topic><Title>Latest Barrons (Dec. 3 issue) says BUY INTC! Mid to high $20s on the way.</Title><Username>to.josie</Username><Timestamp>1354481511087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:51:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two separate articles on Intel. First, MKM Partners likes On Semiconductor, Fairchild, Qualcomm and three others. Our framework analyses suggest that, after significant cuts over the course of the last two months, consensus estimates for 2013 / 2014 for broad-based semiconductors are much more realistic. Unfortunately, valuation for many names suggests that investors expect a sharper (and faster) snapback than seems likely. It has historically paid to own these stocks when numbers are no longer going down, but we struggle to see how the group broadly will be higher a year from now. We view On Semiconductor and Fairchild Semiconductor International as the most attractive cyclical names because we see clear upside to estimates on reasonable valuation. We also remain positive on product stories Qualcomm, Broadcom, as well as Intel (consensus structurally too negative, but the ....</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354485196483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:53:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354485290365-83</Id><Title>Apple doesn't want to miss out on Intel's 48 core Smartphone Chip</Title><Msg>Intels 48-core supercomputing smartphone CPU is less than a decade away By Grant Brunner on October 31, 2012 at 1:44 pm Cell phones are rapidly growing ever more dominant as computing devices. Not only are they becoming vital parts of our everyday lives in the English-speaking western world, but also in developing nations around the globe. Its clear that dumbphones are on the way out, and our current smartphones will look like dunces in the next decade. Intel has been working hard on an impressive 48-core mobile processor for a few years now, and its looking like it could be ready for prime time in a mere five-to-ten years  and inside of our mobile devices, not just servers. Computerworld has a fantastic story with direct quotes from Intel upper management and the actual research scientists working on making small and power efficient parallel computing a reality. Justin Rattner, Intels CTO, says Its just not practical to just take sound and pictures and send it up to the cloud and expect that some server is going to perform those tasks. So a lot of that will be pushed out to the client devices. That really stands out as an ambitious goal that is worthy of consideration. Siri Immediately, services like Siri and mobile speech-to-text come to mind. Right now, every command you give to Siri involves a lot of interaction with Apples servers. Your voice command is sent via the network, processed by Apples servers, and returned to your device as text. Then, the servers grind and grind in hopes of understanding what you meant. If all of the planets are aligned properly, your command is executed a few seconds later. Sometimes, for whatever reason, Siri just spins and spins until it times out. If your iPhone had a true large-scale parallel processor, instead of few measly cores between the CPU and GPU, all of this could be done locally on your device. It wouldnt even matter if you had cell service or not. Most impressively, these chips being developed are very power efficient. Back in 2009, Intel claimed that the processor uses about the same amount of power as two lightbulbs. In 2010, it was made public that the cores were clocked between 1.66GHz and 1.83Ghz, and are roughly on par with Atom-class chips. The individual cores themselves dont have to be super computers, but the technology that allows them to work together in concert is what has massive potential. Sadly, Intel hasnt given us a name or a specific architecture, but it would be fairly safe to assume that were talking about a mobile variant of the Xeon Phi/Knights Corner MIC. Encoding massive videos, always-on augmented reality, and large-scale multitasking are just some of the benefits well see from technology like this 48-core parallel processor. Not only will our phones be able to power our traditional computing needs, but also tasks were not even dreaming about yet. In combination with an increased number of sensors and receivers in your device and the world around you, your phone could be controlling your HVAC, automatic shifting in your car, and creating a realistic 3D replica of your current environment all while youre looking at cat pictures or composing an email. A decade is a long way away, and this is all still very much in development. This is a big shift in technology that could make our devices even more integrated in our lives, and we need to be on the look out for applications for this awesome amount of power well have. It would seem that Sebastians dream of smartphones replacing every other PC form factor might be rather accurate.</Msg><Username>motorbike_trash</Username><Timestamp>1354485290365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:54:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354485339134-84</Id><Topic><Title>Latest Barrons (Dec. 3 issue) says BUY INTC! Mid to high $20s on the way.</Title><Username>to.josie</Username><Timestamp>1354481511087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:51:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two separate articles on Intel. First, MKM Partners likes On Semiconductor, Fairchild, Qualcomm and three others. "Our framework analyses suggest that, after significant cuts over the course of the last two months, consensus estimates for 2013 / 2014 for broad-based semiconductors are much more realistic. Unfortunately, valuation for many names suggests that investors expect a sharper (and faster) snapback than seems likely. It has historically paid to own these stocks when numbers are no longer going down, but we struggle to see how the group broadly will be higher a year from now. We view On Semiconductor and Fairchild Semiconductor International as the most attractive cyclical names because we see clear upside to estimates on reasonable valuation. We also remain positive on product stories Qualcomm, Broadcom, as well as Intel (consensus structurally too negative, but the .... "</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354485339134</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:55:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354485686604-85</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith for CEO?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354484692452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:44:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dadi is not a bad communicator, but he does have an accent. More important, he is head of the mobility group, and knows the technology better than most. He would have been my #2 behind Sean Maloney, but of course he is out of the running now.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354485686604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:01:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354488393329-86</Id><Title>Who grew more in revenue, QCOM or INTC?</Title><Msg>Analysts keep on pointing to percentage growth. But how about real growth in dollars. Since 2010, Qualcomm's revenue has grown by $8 Billion. This with the huge smartphone excitement that Qualcomm has been talking about. Since 2010, Intel's revenue has grown by $10 Billion. So even with the so called weakness in PC growth in percentage terms, Intel's actual dollar growth has grown more than Qualcomm. Yet analysts justify the higher market cap for Qualcomm by saying that future growth expectations are higher for QCOM. Let's see how that plays out while Intel is breaking into Qualcomm's market share of smartphones and tablets. Mostly smartphones since Intel has just started getting design wins with a much better chipset which is only going to get even better.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1354488393329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:46:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354491581823-87</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith for CEO?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354484692452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:44:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey att4glte, why do you care who runs the company? Anyhow, Smith is a great CFO but this ins't a bank or financial institution, Intel is a semi-conductor and software services company. A leader in this field needs to have vision and creativity when it comes R &amp; D and it is absolutely crucial for the CEO undertand the technology, not be really good at numbers. Another good candidate may be a marketing exec, but I don't know of any who may be in the running at Intel.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354491581823</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:39:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354491939151-88</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL BE SINGLE DIGIT STOCK IN 2013:THIS IS THE REAL PROBLEM FOR INTEL NEXT $30 SoC or $250 CPU?</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1348796337780</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:38:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Challenge for Intel to defeat ARMH Today's silicon wafers are about the size of a dinner plate at 300 mm in diameter. Intel plans to shift production to 450 mm silicon wafers  the size of a small coffee table. That's about 40% more chips per wafer at a fraction of additional production costs. With the massive silicon wafers, and the move to smaller geometries below 22 nm, which squeezes more chips into the same area, Intel's new fabs will be able to make mind blowing numbers of chips. But before Intel spends $7 billion plus on 450 mm fabs it has to ensure that it will have mind blowing demand for its chips. It needs high demand because it has operate its fabs at near full volume and 95% plus yield rate. If Intel were making hundreds of millions of low cost Atom chips, replacing all those ARM chips, it would have the volumes it needs to keep its fabs running smoothly. That means it has the means to manufacture all of its highly profitable server and desktop microprocessors, at the lowest possible production costs. There's another very important element in this story: a high volume chip like Atom is essential in helping to quickly ramp up production of all of its chips. High volume products qualify chip production machinery and fine-tune hundreds of complex chip processes. They are essential to Intel being able to maintain high levels of usable chips per wafer. This is why ARM markets are important to Intel and why it must defeat it with Atom, or something similar -- it needs the numbers. Not because it needs the microscopic revenues that feed ARM. Intel needs those markets for the sheer volume of chips that device makers such as Apple and others buy, so that its hugely expensive future 450 mm fabs will be viable producing its high profit chips.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354491939151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:45:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354492073005-89</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL BE SINGLE DIGIT STOCK IN 2013:THIS IS THE REAL PROBLEM FOR INTEL NEXT $30 SoC or $250 CPU?</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1348796337780</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:38:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>15 billion arms licensed to date 98% of cellphones since 2005 have had arms in them. all ipods, ipads, nintendo ds and gba, most routers and other hardware. once, people did buy 8051 series, now they use arm instead. intel now only have pc and pc server markets. pcs are starting to dwindle due to the rise of tablets, servers will also fall as power becomes more expensive. Intel fabs may be the best at making huge expensive chips, but what if that isn't what people want?</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354492073005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:47:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354492467822-90</Id><Title>Qualcom/Samsung/Apple/Nvidia and Chinese Co's will never abandon ARMH and INtel has to wrestle against these Gorillas</Title><Msg>Hello Intel folks You have to compete with $30 Soc's not $300 processors in the future. Keep trying to Kill ARMH and keep fighting for Intel Inside but defeat is at Door steps.. you have to cave into New price Paradigm ------------------- Android and ARMH runs over 900lbs Gorilla called WinTel</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354492467822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:54:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354492577726-91</Id><Title>Windows on ARM is dead. ARM chips are bad for</Title><Msg>compute intensive tasks. They may be good enough for smartphones now, but in the future, even smartphones will become compute intensive as "voice" and "games" take over.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354492577726</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:56:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354492722401-92</Id><Title>Hey Greggy Girl Lynn</Title><Msg>You trying to call me out? Don't make me laugh. Why do I care who's CEO of Intel? Sorry pal, I'm not like you at all. I don't get scared at 20 and sell and try to buy back 20 cents cheaper. What a two bit scared panty wearing little daytrader.........you aren't in my ballpark, little kid.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354492722401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:58:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354492776003-93</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcom/Samsung/Apple/Nvidia and Chinese Co's will never abandon ARMH and INtel has to wrestle against these Gorillas</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354492467822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:54:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple is already abandoning ARM. ARM's latest A15 is struggling to beat 5 year old ATOM now. Next year's new ATOM will have a significant lead in power and performance. First Tablets will switch from ARM to Atom, after that it will be smartphones.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354492776003</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:59:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354493035425-94</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL BE SINGLE DIGIT STOCK IN 2013:THIS IS THE REAL PROBLEM FOR INTEL NEXT $30 SoC or $250 CPU?</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1348796337780</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:38:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you think they will pay over $1 in dividends in 2013? You could be right.</Msg><Username>jamespeter255</Username><Timestamp>1354493035425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 19:03:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354493577747-95</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcom/Samsung/Apple/Nvidia and Chinese Co's will never abandon ARMH and INtel has to wrestle against these Gorillas</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354492467822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:54:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol ARM Cortex-A15 posts impressive performance, threatens Intel and AMD November 29, 2012 at 3:20 pm amsungs dual-core Exynos 5 broke cover with the launch of a new Chromebook a few weeks ago. Now, a full suite of Ubuntu benchmarks show the chip as a credible threat to Intel and AMDs low-power x86 processors in the tablet and netbook space. Nvidias Tegra 3 was similarly abused, though Tegra 4s imminent ramp should help diffuse the situation. Phoronix tested the Exynos 5250 against Nvidias quad-core Tegra 3, three Intel Atoms (the N270, Z530, and dual-core D525), and a Core i3-330M with a 35W TDP. The Exynos 5250 smokes Tegra 3 and the two single-core Atom processors, racking up wins by margins of up to 50%. The dual-core, Hyper-Threaded D525 is better competition for the Cortex-A15, but the ARM chip still won more tests than it lost to that particular Intel CPU. The Core i3-330M, on the other hand, crushed the Cortex-A15 in every single metric. While the article points out that the i3s TDP is nearly an order of magnitude greater than the Exynos 5250s, it failed to acknowledge that Intel has made substantial strides in this department. The i3-330M was launched in early 2010 as a 2.13GHz chip with 3MB of L3, no Turbo Mode, and no AVX support. The best current, non-embedded match would be the Core i7-3667U (2GHz base, 3.2GHz Turbo, 4MB L3, 17W TDP) or the embedded i7-3517UE (1.7GHz base, 2.8GHz Turbo, 4MB L3, 17W TDP). The point here isnt to diminish the Cortex-A15s accomplishments, but to put its performance in the proper context. The TDP and performance-per-watt gap between Intels Core products and the current low-power Atom, Brazos, and ARM families have shrunk dramatically in just two years. Theyll shrink further in 2013, when Intel launches 10W Haswell hardware. The Cortex-A15 is unlikely to challenge Intels absolute performance lead, but it could form a potent bulwark against Clover Trail. The D525 is a decent stand-in for the Z2760s performance, if not its thermals. I suspect that AMDs Brazos would have put up a better showing  its typically 15-25% faster than Atom  but Brazos is a bit long in the tooth compared to either chip. As for Tegra 3, these benchmarks stress just how badly Nvidias product line needs a refresh. Of the three companies weve mentioned, AMD is easily the most vulnerable to a strong Cortex-A15. Intel has low-power SKUs, high average selling prices (ASPs), and substantial momentum to draw on. Nvidias Tegra 4 is already in the pipe. AMDs Brazos is aging and its replacement is still half a year or more away. If Kabini slips later in 2013, it could end up squeezed between the Cortex-A15 at the low end, and Intels 22nm Valleyview Atom (the first out-of-order Atom architecture) at the top. The next 12 months will determine whether Windows RT will seize a significant percentage of the x86 notebook market or if these devices remain on the periphery. Based on these performance figures, I suspect Cortex-A15 designs will be the first real competitors for x86 tablet and netbook form factors. Tegra 3 may have served as a launch vehicle for the Surface RT, but the dual-core Exynos is dramatically faster than Nvidias quad-core design. Windows RT and Android tablet manufacturers arent going to ignore that.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354493577747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 19:12:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354493686696-96</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcom/Samsung/Apple/Nvidia and Chinese Co's will never abandon ARMH and INtel has to wrestle against these Gorillas</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354492467822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:54:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung is integrating the new ARM Mali 604 graphics into the Exynos 5 to provide the high-resolution support for these activities, which also add support for DirectX 11, indicating that this chip could be used for Windows 8 computers. Even if not, expect advanced 2D and 3D mobile gaming as developers can use graphic engine software once reserved for traditional computers.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354493686696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 19:14:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354494067277-97</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcom/Samsung/Apple/Nvidia and Chinese Co's will never abandon ARMH and INtel has to wrestle against these Gorillas</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354492467822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:54:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC's 20nm process technology can provide 30 percent higher speed, 1.9 times the density, or 25 percent less power than its 28nm technology. TSMC 20nm technology is the manufacturing process behind a wide array of applications that run the gamut from tablets and smartphones to desktops and servers.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354494067277</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 19:21:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354494174729-98</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcom/Samsung/Apple/Nvidia and Chinese Co's will never abandon ARMH and INtel has to wrestle against these Gorillas</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354492467822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:54:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Foundry Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. Ltd. has held a groundbreaking ceremony for a fab module at its Fab 14 gigafab at the South Taiwan Science Park in Tainan, Taiwan. The phase-six module is expected to be TSMC's first fab to mass produce 16-nm FinFET circuits in 2014. Building of the sixth-phase module is being commenced only seven months after TSMC (Hsinchu, Taiwan) broke ground on phase-five. Building work for phase six of the Fab 14 gigafab is not due to start until 2013 as part of a $17 billion capacity expansion scheduled for the next five years, according to a Taipei Times report. "The factory will be the world's first 12-inch factory producing 20-nanometer system-on-chips and the first 16-nanometer FinFET chip manufacturing site for TSMC," the report quoted TSMC co-chief operating officer Chiang Shang-yi, as saying. Fab 14 phases 5 and 6 are expected to approximately double the manufacturing capacity of the first four phases by offering a total cleanroom area of 87,000 square meters  equivalent to more than 11 soccer fields and four times larger than a typical 300-mm fab.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354494174729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 19:22:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354494233755-99</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcom/Samsung/Apple/Nvidia and Chinese Co's will never abandon ARMH and INtel has to wrestle against these Gorillas</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354492467822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:54:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMCs 16nm FinFET process will be substantially similar to its 20nm high-K metal gate SoC process in the back-end, said Cliff Hou, vice president of research and development at TSMC. Recently introduced 14nm-XM offering from Globalfoundries is based on a modular technology architecture that uses a 14nm FinFET device combined with its 20nm-LPM process back-end-of-line (BEOL) interconnect flow. Leveraging the maturity of the 20nm-LPM technology will enable a rapid time-to-market as well as a smooth transition for customers looking to tap the benefits of FinFET system-on-chips, such as lower power consumption and higher performace, as soon as possible.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354494233755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 19:23:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354494511938-100</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcom/Samsung/Apple/Nvidia and Chinese Co's will never abandon ARMH and INtel has to wrestle against these Gorillas</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354492467822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:54:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung Starts Production of 10 nm-Class, Tablet, Smartphone Flash Chips Jason Mick (Blog) - November 15, 2012 7:02 PM New memory recycles last-gen process, but still offers 30 percent performance gains Embedded MultiMediaCard (eMMC) -- tiny chips soldered to smartphone and tablet motherboards via ball-grid arrays -- are a staple of the mobile industry. Samsung Electronics Comp., Ltd. (KSC:005930) offered up some exciting news today, revealing that it had started production of 10 nm-class (10-19 nm) NAND for eMMC, taking mobile storage to new levels of "tiny". The new 64 GB NAND Flash storage chips, which are built on the eMMC 4.5 standard, which Samsung basically wrote itself, offer random writes of 2,000 IOPS (input-output operations per second), random reads of 5,000 IOPS, sequential reads at 260 MB/s, and sequential write speeds of 50 MB/s. Those stats are about 30 percent up from the first-generation eMMC 4.5 devices (mature 20 nm product), which Samsung delivered five months ago. More good news for Samsung is that it was able to repurpose its 20 nm lines to produce the 10 nm-class chips. It says the process compatibility is expected to increase its manufacturing yields around 30 percent.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354494511938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 19:28:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354494753058-101</Id><Title>LOL! singhlion2001 and shorts shaking in their boots!</Title><Msg>What's the matter? scared of an Apple/Intel deal? You should be, because it's going to happen any day from now! Here's a rundown of what might happen in 2013: - When deal is reached, INTC will be manufacturing millions of chips for Apple next year, that's right, next year's iPhone 5s will be manufactured by INTC! - Intel will be in next iPad and new products like the MacPad - How about the iTube coming in 2013? It will have INTC inside as arm cannot handle the processing as the iTube will have game console built in! - end of year and early next year, INTC will be announcing multiple smartphones wins with Motorola, ZTE, Lenovo, Acer, Sharp, HTC, Dell, LG, Huawei, Samsung - the z2580 and newer chip coming in mid-2013 running on 22nm will also be in a couple of 7" tablets - Look at all the Windows 8 convertibles, detachables and tablets coming onto the market now. Things will only get better when Haswell comes out in early 2013. You are going to see all sorts new form factor and products that will blur the lines between tablets and PCs. Consumers will flock to upgrade their 5-year-old bulky laptops - Don't forget about traditional PCs upgrades coming from corporations, it will pick up as there has been pent up demand as companies were waiting for Windows 8 to come - How about the next generation of Xbox 720; there is possibility of MS switching from AMD to INTC Haswell chips with its monster integrated graphics</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354494753058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 19:32:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354495375559-102</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcom/Samsung/Apple/Nvidia and Chinese Co's will never abandon ARMH and INtel has to wrestle against these Gorillas</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354492467822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:54:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple appears to already be abandoning ARM, butkus. Didn't you read all the headlines from this weekend??? Oh, that's right - you did. That's why you are posting up diversions like it's going out of style. ARM is not going to be a threat to anyone with RT. It's already begun the big fade. WOA - DOA</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354495375559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 19:42:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354495668755-103</Id><Topic><Title>LOL! singhlion2001 and shorts shaking in their boots!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354494753058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 19:32:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HEY CLOWNS MY FIRST TARGET IS MET BELOW $20 You all were warned and target was roared .........Bashers can bash on...........Who is right ? NEXT TARGET in 2013 will be below $15 for now flip trades like slot machines Vegas for quarters and dimes is good enough yahooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1354495668755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 19:47:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354496560461-104</Id><Title>INTC will compete with $30 SoC just fine</Title><Msg>- Intel does not have to pay license to ARM - Intel does it's own manufacturing with superior process that have better yields - After making acquisitions in the last 2 years, Intel now have all the components for the SoC and do not have to license from Qualcomm or Samsung - with the above advantages, intel can afford to undercut samsung, qualcomm or nvidia's SoC and still retain good margins - Intel will go after mobile market agressively: 'we will not lose a design win on price' - with Intel's chips being superior in performance, power consumption and price, which phone companies can resist???</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354496560461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:02:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354497250659-105</Id><Topic><Title>LOL! singhlion2001 and shorts shaking in their boots!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354494753058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 19:32:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>singhlion = lucy You can tell by the repetitive key strokes. People without writing skills like to use a lot of repetitive key strokes...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354497250659</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:14:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354497343467-106</Id><Title>Intel to slash power consumption on Ivy Bridge chip</Title><Msg>Chip giant plans to make Ivy Bridge more power efficient than the versions that are currently used in the MacBook Air and Windows 8 ultrabooks.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354497343467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:15:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354497817265-107</Id><Title>Asian shares higher after firm China PMI</Title><Msg>Asian shares edged higher on Monday as further signs of a stabilizing Chinese economy boosted sentiment...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354497817265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:23:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354498454410-108</Id><Title>intel rumors from losing apple business to making more chips for them</Title><Msg>all within 3 weeks. the pps should be 2 bucks up</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1354498454410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:34:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354499010799-109</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Greg Lynn</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354374797281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:13:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Me calling you out?? Seriously, and now name calling.. wow. I'm honored, you seem to only do that to the best of them. I'm not replying to your other post, I'm ashamed for you acting like you are 6, and I figured you woudln't care who the CEO would be since you are so in love with ARM, and so I figured you to be short INTC.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354499010799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:43:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354499235710-110</Id><Title>Hey att4glte</Title><Msg>This is what it looks like to call somebody out, without name calling even. Addressing your alias in a post, not the same.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354499235710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:47:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354499757894-111</Id><Topic><Title>Hey att4glte</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354499235710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:47:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey geek, I told you I thought the CEO should be Stacy Smith, because he's a good decent man unlike yourself. In your other post, I was asking why you were calling me out, asking why I cared who the CEO was. I'm in Intel for life with a staunch Dividend every three months.......I'm an Intel investor, not a two big daytrader and shorter like you. I called you out for your ARM short because you have a very loud mouth and are no more than a tool. You wanna do lunch sometime? We can talk about that gawd-awful Toupet on top of your head. LOL! #$%$ punk.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354499757894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:55:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354500203655-112</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith for CEO?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354484692452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:44:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like Brian Krzanich will likely get the job though.. He is now exec VP and COO, just like Paul Otellini, Craig Barrett and Andy Grove were before taking the job.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354500203655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 21:03:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354500391287-113</Id><Topic><Title>Hey att4glte</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354499235710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:47:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You like to make a lot of assumptions about people don't you, I don't day trade but I do trade, and never once have I ever shorted INTC, the only stocks I have ever shorted are ARMH and RMBS. I effectively bought INTC for $0.50 cheaper by selling and buying back at a discount, this isn't chump change.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354500391287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 21:06:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354503190151-114</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will compete with $30 SoC just fine</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354496560461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:02:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, Intel plans to have an excelerated roadmap for smartphone chips. Current medfield is 32nm, next one will be iteration of it, the z2580 with duo core but it is still 32nm. Next chip, will be in mid 2013 produced using 22nm process. There will probably be an iteration of this chip after a couple of months. Then end of 2013, another new chip using 14nm whereby they will be in line with core process...with every new iteration and process, each chip will have multiple smartphones running it....seriously, arm doesn't have a chance, it is like taking candy from a baby...only reason arm seems so dominate now is because Intel hasn't decided to compete yet. 2013, Intel will seriously compete!</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354503190151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 21:53:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354503362912-115</Id><Title>What Will Happen When The Surface Pro Isnt The Only Flagship Win8 Tablet In Town?</Title><Msg>The Surface Pro launches in January, just after the holiday rush. Its a pricey bauble at $899 plus an extra hundred for the Touch Cover. But everyone is excited. This is the model most of the Surface sympathizers are waiting for. It has the full Windows 8 experience, a capable Intel chipset, and an ecosystem two decades in the making. But heres the problem: come January the Surface Pro could have serious competition from Asus, Samsung, Lenovo and maybe even HP. In short, what happens when the big guys finally catch up to Microsoft? As of this writing, pickings for a Windows 8 tablet are pretty slim. To the rabid Microsoft fan, the Surface Pro looks like the second coming. Its the tablet that will save them from the horrid iPad. But fear not, friend. The Surface Pro will be just one among many options soon. From techcrunch</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354503362912</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 21:56:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354503758811-116</Id><Topic><Title>What Will Happen When The Surface Pro Isnt The Only Flagship Win8 Tablet In Town?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354503362912</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 21:56:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Haswell and Clover Trail+ comes out, there will be SO many more lighter form factors from 7", 10" tablets to 11.6" detachables to convertible ultrabooks like the yoga and dell's xps for consumers to choose from. The Surface Pro will be just one of many Windows touch devices out there. What will happen??? Intel everywhere!!!</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354503758811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 22:02:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354503767680-117</Id><Title>China: Manufacturing sector expands</Title><Msg>China's official manufacturing index increased in November, boosting hopes for a sustained expansion in the crucial sector. China's official purchasing manager's index jumped to 50.6 in November from 50.2 the previous month, the government said. Any reading above 50 indicates that factory conditions are improving in the manufacturing sector. Another measure of manufacturing activity released Monday, HSBC's initial purchasing manager's index, also indicated improvement in the sector. At 50.5, the index is at its highest level in 13 months. "This confirms that Chinese economy continues to recover gradually," said Hongbin Qu, an economist at HSBC.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354503767680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 22:02:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354503799389-118</Id><Title>Does Goldman know somthing we dont know?</Title><Msg>On Nov 21st Goldman downgraded HP to neutral rating with a price target reduced from $16 to $14. Then Goldman downgrades Intel to sell with a price target of $16. HP has so much debt on #$%$ unlike Intel. From every metric perspective Intel is better than HPQ. Doe Goldman know somthing that we all dont know yet? ( well it is obvious that they knew Paul's Retirment hence they had a sell call with $20 price target) Any thoughts? ( I didnt want to take a chance and have hedged my position with Feb puts by then all the uncertainity should be out of our way)</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1354503799389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 22:03:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354503831808-119</Id><Title>AUBURN FIRES COACH</Title><Msg>The rapid fall from a national championship to 3-9 and the Southeastern Conference doormat led to Chizik's firing yesterday, the day after a humbling 49-0 loss to No. 2 Alabama that showed just how far the program has fallen. The Tigers endured the worst slide within two years of winning a national championship of any team since the Associated Press poll started in 1936 and hadn't lost this many games since going 0-10 in 1950</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354503831808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 22:03:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354504408338-120</Id><Topic><Title>Does Goldman know somthing we dont know?</Title><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1354503799389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 22:03:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya they know that Intel will make major push into mobile market in 2013 and also that 2013 will be the year for the resurgence the PCs with touch interface. Intel will grow my leaps and bound and take all hw manufacturers including HPQ with it. It's obvious they want to buys shares of INTC at cheap prices....Goldman et al are S*C*U*M*S...you will see upgrades start to come after 1st quarter earnings.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354504408338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 22:13:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354504691315-121</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will compete with $30 SoC just fine</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354496560461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:02:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>---- intel can afford to undercut samsung, qualcomm or nvidia's SoC and still retain good margins ---- Indeed INTC has a superior process and does not need to pay license fees. But their ability to leverage these advantages to deliver low-cost alternatives at 'good margins' is far from certain.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1354504691315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 22:18:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354504762572-122</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will compete with $30 SoC just fine</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354496560461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:02:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>--- only reason arm seems so dominate now is because Intel hasn't decided to compete yet. ---- OK that's just funny. They haven't DECIDED to compete yet? More like they haven't been ABLE to compete yet</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1354504762572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 22:19:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354504916296-123</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will compete with $30 SoC just fine</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354496560461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:02:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"- Intel does not have to pay license to ARM" INtel does have to pay IMG license for their powerVR GPUs INtel does have to pay NVidia royalties for use of their GPU patents btw, can you tell me how much is the license to Qualcomm on LTE, connectivity, etc... "- with the above advantages, intel can afford to undercut samsung, qualcomm or nvidia's SoC" Samsung has their own fabs, and own phones... margins are low Qualcomm doesn't pay license for connectivity... NVidia doesn't pay license for GPUs...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1354504916296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 22:21:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354504949200-124</Id><Topic><Title>Does Goldman know somthing we dont know?</Title><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1354503799389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 22:03:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Goldman knows just about the same it did when it downgraded Intel to a sell a couple of years ago with a target price of $15, when Intel traded at aroung $19. Goldman never changed its sell rating as Intel went all the way to $29. Goldman's EPS estimate for 2011 was around $1.57 at that time. As we all know, Intel actually came in at an EPS of $2.39. So what does Goldman know? They know how to get it very very wrong.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1354504949200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 22:22:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354505571137-125</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will compete with $30 SoC just fine</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354496560461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:02:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm quite sure it was a decision on the part of Intel not to go into the smartphone market until now. The medfield chip is 5 years old. The could have gone in anytime they wanted to. I think part of the reason they didn't go in earlier was the profit isn't there. Now with 14nm process coming on board and now that they have all the components to make the very best SoC they will go on an all out attack. Also now, the cost per transistor will go down for intel (listen to Stacy Smith's at Credit Suisse conf) while their competitors are going up further upping the margins for Intel.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354505571137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 22:32:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354506110865-126</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will compete with $30 SoC just fine</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354496560461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:02:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has own XMM6260 modem chip which supports LTE other connectivities. They will integrate that and their on GPUs in next interation of chips running on 22nm process.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354506110865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 22:41:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354507442172-127</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL SEE A $18 HANDLE NEXT WEEK</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1354324553680</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:15:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally ,you don't know the dynamics involved in a tech company with 100k employees. Wise up and smell the coffee dude</Msg><Username>ercool</Username><Timestamp>1354507442172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 23:04:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354508059651-128</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will compete with $30 SoC just fine</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354496560461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:02:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see... btw, if you were wondering... in January INtel pays NVIdia $250M per year for GPU royalties... and just doesn't matter what GPU INtel uses...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1354508059651</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 23:14:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354508562050-129</Id><Title>AS OBAMA SAYS "IT'S RIGHT THING TO DO" - ALL OF US SHOULD BE PAYING HIGHER TAXES</Title><Msg>To support obama's takers. It is right thing to do.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354508562050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 23:22:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354508605761-130</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will compete with $30 SoC just fine</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354496560461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:02:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel owns 16% of IMG :-)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1354508605761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 23:23:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354510793325-131</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith presentation</Title><Username>dundarra</Username><Timestamp>1354457102852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:05:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting presentation to listen to. and good discussion too. But I think everything is rumors until announced.</Msg><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354510793325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 23:59:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>