<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349841926698-1</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349835285929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We're good for 30. LOL Seriously, I see Intel easily moving above 30 in 2013. Here's why: Intel is going to have five 22nm plants going. Intel has high end capacity. ARM doesn't. Nvidia, Qualcomm and AMD are all crying out for high end capacity they can't get from the ARM foundries. The situation will get worse as Intel becomes the only place with available high end capacity. Intel will be preparing for volume production of 14nm at the end of the year. It's going to be Intel's 14nm verses ARM's 28nm. ARM is a very long way from volume 20nm production. This just means Intel is going to get huge traction in mobility. There is absolutely no problem with Intel's mobility strategy - it just needs a little time to develop. The recent Motorola release should be a wake-up call for ARM. Intel has drawn even. In 2013 Intel will move ahead. Intel's tablet solutions are going to make a significant move up. Expect both tablet and smartphone solutions to continuously step up with a frequency that ARM can't match. By the end of 2013 it's going to be clear to the Apple's and Qualcomm's of the world that sticking to ARM will be a huge competitive disadvantage. If they don't use Intel, then their competitors will. It's that simple. There are only two ARM foundries that can compete with Intel. In 2013, TSMC is going to drop to the wayside. They just don't have the money, the technology or the manufacturing prowess to keep up with Intel and Samsung. Samsung unfortunately doesn't have the technology. It will be a two-horse race with Intel significantly in the lead due to its superior fabrication. These factors will combine to give Intel the choice of whatever high end business it wants. ARM will be relegated to the lower-end technology and will have to cut prices to do so. ARM is going to be the new AMD by the end of 2013. This trend will accelerate each year thereafter. And while Intel is building traction in both tablets and smartphones, the Internet of Things (wireless devices, sensors, RF tags, ATMs, signs, vending machines, etc.) will be experiencing exponential growth. Intel is extremely well positioned for this growth and its WiFi chip development gives it a serious competitive advantage. The IoT will provide a whole new ocean of processor, server and data center revenues that don't currently exist. In 2013, this trend will become obvious. The current situation is temporary. The internet is not going away. The growth of video is not going away. Wireless connectivity is expanding beyond people to machines and devices. The Cloud is not going away. And Intel because of its fabrication is getting stronger every single day. Sometime during 2013, the executives at Intel will look like geniuses for expanding capacity during a chip market lull. The lull will not and cannot last. The world has an insatiable thirst for connectivity, for communication and for entertainment. Right now inventories are bare-bottom. As soon as the market starts to recover a bit the need to rebuild inventories will accelerate processor revenues. Only Intel can afford to continue building state-of-the-art capacity at the same rate no matter the temporary economic dips. When the market comes back, the advantage will be clear. TSMC is being punished now for underestimating the high-end market and not building enough capacity. Intel will never make that mistake. These factors will combine to push Intel into the 30 to 40 range in 2013. Look for the Intel LTE smartphone push into the US as just one of the catalysts. Look for a conversion of a major ARM customer to Intel in 2013 as another. In 2013 the dam is going to break and Intel will be the only boat to be lifted...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349841926698</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349842005729-2</Id><Topic><Title>This is a $19 stock</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1349793462618</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:37:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, I get you now... INtel claimed SOC and the size was 1.2cm**2... Later it was revealed that INtel didn't have an SOC as claimed, but a PoP and that was the package size... OK now, do you not think MSFT is porting to ARM...?? You think it's a stupid comment... I've yet to hear why ?</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349842005729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:06:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349842066221-3</Id><Title>PETE NAJARIAN WAS POUNDING THE TABLE @ $30 SAYING IT WAS A SCREAMING BUY</Title><Msg>LOLOL, THAT GUYS A BAFFOON</Msg><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1349842066221</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349843376959-4</Id><Topic><Title>Will Intel see 28 again in the next 3 years?</Title><Username>motorbike_trash</Username><Timestamp>1349835503751</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:18:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have be kidding. Intel will be at 10nm in three years. ARM still won't have 14nm. Intel will be two chip cycles ahead by then. Intel will own the fabrication landscape and therefore the mobility landscape. Intel's WiFi chip will be out in two years allowing Intel a huge advantage with the Internet of Things (IoT) and access to a huge new pot of revenues. It's the wrong question. The question should be "Will Intel hit 50 in the next three years?" Once Intel's mobility revenues ramp up and ARM's fabrication problems shoot ARM in the foot, Intel will get the P/E ratio it richly deserves. And this will vault Intel to a 50+ valuation in three years. Don't think so? I've got two $10 billion 14nm fabs in Oregon and Arizona saying there's nothing you can do to stop it from happening. When they open for business at the end of 2013, I'll be happy to swing by and stamp "Game Over" on your forehead in reverse mirror image so you can see it every morning when you get up...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349843376959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349843480278-5</Id><Topic><Title>PETE NAJARIAN WAS POUNDING THE TABLE @ $30 SAYING IT WAS A SCREAMING BUY</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1349842066221</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:07:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"LOLOL, THAT GUYS A BAFFOON" *** Worse than someone still typing in all caps?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349843480278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:31:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349843797174-6</Id><Title>DRAM $0.64 with $6.5M Market Cap is a Potential Multi-bagger......DRAM and AMD signed an agreement to launch an aggressive campaign to market all editions of AMD's AMD Memory modules for desktops......Per the agreement, DRAM will develop a special edition RAMDisk utility, which will be called AMD Radeon RAMDisk...... AMD Radeon RAMDisk loading times are expected to be 525% higher than those offered by conventional products</Title><Msg>Dataram Corporation (NASDAQ: DRAM) has announced a huge deal with AMD on September 8. 2012 that is sure to take it to the next level in terms of revenues and net income. The stock is completely under the radar and a reason why its 0.2 X sales valuation giving it a $6.5 million market cap. The company is already almost break-even even before the upcoming AMD-related windfall. DRAM has a strong balance sheet with ZERO long term debt. Per the agreement, DRAM will develop a special edition RAMDisk utility, which will be called AMD Radeon RAMDisk. AMD Radeon RAMDisk loading times are expected to be 525% higher than those offered by conventional products, increasing performance, eliminating bottlenecks and improving the gaming experience on the PC as well as other applications requiring fast processing like complex engineering simulation models. AMD Radeon RAMDisk utility will be available from October to December this year. DRAM develops, manufactures, and markets large capacity memory products primarily used in high performance network servers and workstations worldwide. The company has more than 70 Fortune 100 customers and it’s been in business since 1967. On September 8, 2012 TechNews Science and Technology published the following article about Advanced Micro Devices (NYSE: AMD) plans to launch an aggressive campaign to encourage all editions of its AMD Memory modules for desktops, and to achieve this has made an agreement with Dataram (NASDAQ: DRAM) known developer of memory modules for servers, workstations and desktops, plus other solutions and associated services; agreement that will develop a special edition RAMDisk utility, which will be called AMD Radeon RAMDisk and come free with AMD Memory memory modules. AMD Radeon RAMDisk loading times offer up to 525% higher in games and applications (better than that offered by SSDs), increasing performance, eliminating bottlenecks and improving the gaming experience on the PC. AMD Radeon RAMDisk utility will be available from October to December this year, and although AMD or Dataram gave more details on its operation, we assume that this utility to create a RAM disk to use by way of a fast disk cache, based on the Game and application profiles present in the Catalyst Control Center utility, which comes bundled with graphics cards, motherboards (chipset) and AMD APUs. On September 14, 2012, DRAM stated the following in its fiscal 1Q 2013 earnings report: During this quarter the Company entered into two agreements which we expect will generate growth and profits for Dataram in 2013 and beyond: - An agreement with AMD provides for Dataram to develop and sell AMD licensed and branded versions of its RAMDisk software. AMD’s Radeon RAMDisk will target the gaming enthusiast community. - An agreement with Shoreline Memory Inc. ("Shoreline") and the other with Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. ("AMD") for the purpose of expanding our customer base and product offerings. The Shoreline Agreement provides for Dataram to fulfill 50% of the orders Shoreline receives from its primary customers. Management believes these agreements will provide new revenue sources and expanded markets for the Company's products. Mr. Freeman concluded, “These recent agreements and other new opportunities we are currently pursuing should provide new sources of revenue, profit and growth for Dataram in 2013 and beyond. The experience, knowledge and assets we have gained from our current RAMDisk product, in the development of caching software and in solid state products are building a strong foundation for growth.” DRAM is also an unrecognized cloud play. DRAM makes the XcelaSAN memory/storage family of products for cloud and all other applications. The company recently received $5 million from a Japanese company to allow the non-exclusive right to manufacture products using the XcelaSAN technology. ABOUT DRAM Dataram Corporation (NASDAQ: DRAM), an independent memory manufacturer, develops, manufactures, and markets large capacity memory products primarily used in high performance network servers and workstations worldwide. It offers customized memory solutions for original equipment manufacturers (OEMs) and compatible memory for computers manufactured by various companies. The company also manufactures a line of memory products for Intel and AMD motherboard based servers. In addition, it develops, manufactures, and markets a line of storage caching products. The company sells its memory products to OEMs, distributors, value-added resellers, and end-users. Dataram Corporation was founded in 1967 and is based in Princeton, New Jersey</Msg><Username>bt.bigten</Username><Timestamp>1349843797174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:36:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349850491337-7</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349835285929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good points, no, great points! If I may add, people forget how Intel came late to the server market against a giant like IBM, and ended up to be the market leader with a 90% market share. Looks like the same will happen with mobile processors for smartphones. Intel will in time have more than 50% of that market. Tablets may do well for Intel, but I think ultrabook hybrids over time will eat into tablet sales overall. Very cheap tablets will still have a noticeable market. Tablets under $300 that is. Again, great points, and thanks for the well thought out response.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349850491337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 02:28:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349850882801-8</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street Continues to Beat Tech Like a Drum</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349833560908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 21:46:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've written to the SEC at least twice. They pretty much expect specific complaints. As for Senators, I've had a really tough time trying to get them to understand any of the complaints. In California for example, the senators seem to be more active in social issues rather than financial ones such as the stock market or deteriorating house prices. But I would encourage the masses to bother the SEC until they feel pressured to pay attention. It will take time and lots of effort though. For the most part, government staff like to be left alone.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349850882801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 02:34:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349851151413-9</Id><Topic><Title>Latest Election Polls</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349379874655</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:44:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope Bush has a strong back. He has had to absorb alot of blame for four years....I do think folks are getting bored hearing that crap. Romney will win big. jmho</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1349851151413</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 02:39:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349854402094-10</Id><Topic><Title>PETE NAJARIAN WAS POUNDING THE TABLE @ $30 SAYING IT WAS A SCREAMING BUY</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1349842066221</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:07:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The irony is wonderful. Say, is he also an idiut? And a moreon?</Msg><Username>kevin_kevin_ghali</Username><Timestamp>1349854402094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 03:33:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349856706350-11</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349835285929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis, thanks for the excellent summary and roadmap as to why we should own INTC stock. I've seen a lot of outrageous things in my life, but this wholesale assault on INTC by analysts, CNBC, and the zombie-featherbrains who post in here is one of the most incredulous. Reason will prevail.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349856706350</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 04:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349865885766-12</Id><Title>I will take INTC to a new year low today</Title><Msg>sell early I am the one who control the share price.</Msg><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1349865885766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349867545268-13</Id><Title>Bush ran up a TOTAL of 5 Trillion in debt in 8 years with 2 Wars !</Title><Msg>Obama has run up almost 6 Trillion in debt in less than 4 years with no wars! LOL! "It's Bush's fault" don't cut it ! The guard is about to be changed.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349867545268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:12:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349867633508-14</Id><Title>Good News $25,St knew 3rd Qtr result,Div 22.5 Cents</Title><Msg>Good News,St knew 3rd Qtr result,Div 22.5 Cents -St knew INTC growth and adding Stocks. -New CPU and Entering into Mobile Mrkt. Good luck - Buy Buy</Msg><Username>bellst25</Username><Timestamp>1349867633508</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349870651421-15</Id><Title>Concerted Beating down of the stock</Title><Msg>for example, i got an email: '3 Tech Giants Traders Should Sell Now The Nasdaq and a handful of overbought stocks are taking the brunt of the selling. Get my take on the markets.' Looks to me as a concerted attempt by wall street to drive down the price so they can buy it cheap. I will be there buying it too............</Msg><Username>sk4543</Username><Timestamp>1349870651421</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:04:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349871096601-16</Id><Topic><Title>Bush ran up a TOTAL of 5 Trillion in debt in 8 years with 2 Wars !</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349867545268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is going to do 6 trillion in 4 years, whats your point?</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349871096601</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:11:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349871399617-17</Id><Topic><Title>Latest Election Polls</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349379874655</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:44:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slick &amp; greenspan had the idea and plan to put people in h omes they couldn't afford. How's that working so far?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349871399617</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:16:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349871530737-18</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street Continues to Beat Tech Like a Drum</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349833560908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 21:46:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if Intel delivered, they wouldn't be beatable. $3 eps ?????????????????</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349871530737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:18:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349871568875-19</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349835285929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is it that no one mensions the billion dollar a year contract with CSCO that they just signed? Thats over 2% of their annual business!</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349871568875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:19:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349871796831-20</Id><Topic><Title>Bush ran up a TOTAL of 5 Trillion in debt in 8 years with 2 Wars !</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349867545268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try reading more than just the subject line next time, idiot.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349871796831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:23:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349871967372-21</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349835285929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it only gets to $24 before then end of this year, I'm good. But if I have to wait till next year I might sell 1/2 my investment and keep half... I only say this cause half mine is on margin and paying interest with no return is silly... silly of me to margin, yes, but I've always heard from the wealthy people that they got wealthy using other people's money, so I figured why not... sorry I really don't have anything of substance to add to this discussion, but everyone's insight has made me feel better about my investment... thank you.</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349871967372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:26:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349872273110-22</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349835285929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I feel your pain wrt margin. The problem is that the wealthy people who got so on other people's money were the brokers who got us to buy on margin. Another thing to be wary of is shorting naked puts. I shorted 40 on INTC from $25 - $30 strikes. I only regret it because I could do so much better at this level. However, I agree with Wallis, in fact, given what I know about INTC (and can't discuss) I think $30 is a low-ball number for 2013. I would like to gleen more public info about the INTC-Google axis.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349872273110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:31:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349872317875-23</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street Continues to Beat Tech Like a Drum</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349833560908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 21:46:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes it's heavily rigged for the wealthy... but the wealthy will lose if the average joes all abandon ship... it will never be "fixed"... and if any of us has a perfect solution, we'd start our own system... but that's just how it is, there is no perfect solution... I don't like the people can short a stock to death because they have the money to do so, then they can ride it back up and make money both ways... but if we disallowed shorters it would hurt an important part of the market... out of curiousity... where do you think it needs fixed?</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349872317875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:31:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349872725713-24</Id><Title>What would a below estimates earnings report do to INTC?</Title><Msg>Anyone care to venture a 'educated' guess at where the price would go to, if that happened?</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349872725713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:38:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349873044065-25</Id><Topic><Title>What would a below estimates earnings report do to INTC?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349872725713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:38:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>on this planet of fools and republicans? probably up $3.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349873044065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:44:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349873171171-26</Id><Topic><Title>Bush ran up a TOTAL of 5 Trillion in debt in 8 years with 2 Wars !</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349867545268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doubt it, unless the conservatives (which Romney and Obama are not, but Romney is closer) come out in full force and vote for Romney, then Obama wins easily. I voted for Obama the first time because I saw McCain as just another Bush, an oil hungry war monger. Since then Obama has shown himself to be a HORRIBLE debt manager. Romney has a background of managing money, some wins, some loses, but he clearly has WAY MORE experience than Obama and debt management IS important to me, so he will likely be my choice... Of course I'd much rather that we stood up for ourselves and started the french style revolution that this country needs, since that's not happening, I guess Romney will have to do...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349873171171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349873282829-27</Id><Topic><Title>What would a below estimates earnings report do to INTC?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349872725713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:38:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you are saying up to $25 a share? Hmmm, that sure would be nice, but I have my doubts...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349873282829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:48:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349873425462-28</Id><Title>Who's this Rocco Pendola ?</Title><Msg>Intel Missed Mobile Worse Than Facebook Did Add Comment By Rocco Pendola (Yahoo news Article)</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1349873425462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:50:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349873531020-29</Id><Topic><Title>What would a below estimates earnings report do to INTC?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349872725713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:38:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1st off, they were in the 25's when they warned. sat around 24's for a short time and then 23's and 22's. only after this stupid bernstein/barrons article did they go from 22.50 closing to under 22. I say if they meet their 50 cents and give guidance that's not that short from expectations, we click upper 22's to 23's in AH's. Just my take. If they warn worse, we could see 20's and 19's but doubt it. We'll see Tuesday at 4PM.</Msg><Username>chevymalibu1966</Username><Timestamp>1349873531020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:52:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349873778047-30</Id><Topic><Title>Who's this Rocco Pendola ?</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1349873425462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:50:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He writes a scathing article about Intel AFTER he sold. Funny how that works. Unbelievable.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349873778047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:56:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349874378561-31</Id><Title>Unbelievable! Never such a buying op.</Title><Msg>Almost every analyst, commentator, Cramer flunkie, CNBS #$%$ Yahoo poster, et.al., is bashing Intel. Never has there been a more evident BUY SIGNAL on Wall Street. NOT EVER!!! And you get a 4+% dividend on top of it all.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349874378561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:06:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349874561168-32</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349835285929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Intel will be preparing for volume production of 14nm at the end of the year. It's going to be Intel's 14nm verses ARM's 28nm. ARM is a very long way from volume 20nm production. This just means Intel is going to get huge traction in mobility. There is absolutely no problem with Intel's mobility strategy - it just needs a little time to develop. The recent Motorola release should be a wake-up call for ARM. Intel has drawn even. In 2013 Intel will move ahead.' There will be no 2013 14nm Intel products only 22nm Haswell and 22nm Silvermont. However as they are both great designs whose advantages will be greater than just doing a shrink of Ivy Bridge/Medfield it won't be a problem Mr Fabrication Obsessed ;-). If 14nm is ready it will be worked on during 2013 to improve yields and build volume inventory for a big 2014 launch.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349874561168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:09:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349874584180-33</Id><Topic><Title>Who's this Rocco Pendola ?</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1349873425462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:50:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what a POS. Must be some high school sophomore.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349874584180</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:09:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349875036360-34</Id><Topic><Title>What would a below estimates earnings report do to INTC?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349872725713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:38:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Acorrding to Wallis weaver math, an 8 billion miss has been priced in.......so if they miss by just 1 billion, expect the stock to move back near 29 over night. Really! That's his math. It's called "Shameless pumper Math."</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349875036360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:17:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349875557334-35</Id><Topic><Title>What would a below estimates earnings report do to INTC?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349872725713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:38:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like his math - hope he's right.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349875557334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:25:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349875961469-36</Id><Topic><Title>What would a below estimates earnings report do to INTC?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349872725713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:38:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would be nice if we got back up to the mid 22's before then, that would be nice...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349875961469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349876101805-37</Id><Topic><Title>Unbelievable! Never such a buying op.</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349874378561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:06:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UNLESS, they are ALL right... that would sure suck wouldn't it???</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349876101805</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:35:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349876194245-38</Id><Title>Breaking a new 52 week low today... hope this ends soon...</Title><Msg>come on people, this is silly...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349876194245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:36:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349877320585-39</Id><Topic><Title>Unbelievable! Never such a buying op.</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349874378561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:06:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just added shares at 21.84. Now go on up intel.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1349877320585</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:55:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349877549589-40</Id><Title>Intel Is Good for 30 AND 50</Title><Msg>I see Intel easily moving above 30 in 2013. Here's why: Intel is going to have five 22nm plants going. Intel has high end capacity. ARM doesn't. Nvidia, Qualcomm and AMD are all crying out for high end capacity they can't get from the ARM foundries. The situation will get worse as Intel becomes the only place with available high end capacity. Intel will be preparing for volume production of 14nm at the end of the year. It's going to be Intel's 14nm verses ARM's 28nm. ARM is a very long way from volume 20nm production. This just means Intel is going to get huge traction in mobility. There is absolutely no problem with Intel's mobility strategy - it just needs a little time to develop. The recent Motorola release should be a wake-up call for ARM. Intel has drawn even. In 2013 Intel will move ahead. Intel's tablet solutions are going to make a significant move up. Expect both tablet and smartphone solutions to continuously step up with a frequency that ARM can't match. By the end of 2013 it's going to be clear to the Apple's and Qualcomm's of the world that sticking to ARM will be a huge competitive disadvantage. If they don't use Intel, then their competitors will. It's that simple. There are only two ARM foundries that can compete with Intel. In 2013, TSMC is going to drop to the wayside. They just don't have the money, the technology or the manufacturing prowess to keep up with Intel and Samsung. Samsung unfortunately doesn't have the technology. It will be a two-horse race with Intel significantly in the lead due to its superior fabrication. These factors will combine to give Intel the choice of whatever high end business it wants. ARM will be relegated to the lower-end technology and will have to cut prices to do so. ARM is going to be the new AMD by the end of 2013. This trend will accelerate each year thereafter. And while Intel is building traction in both tablets and smartphones, the Internet of Things (wireless devices, sensors, RF tags, ATMs, signs, vending machines, etc.) will be experiencing exponential growth. Intel is extremely well positioned for this growth and its WiFi chip development gives it a serious competitive advantage. The IoT will provide a whole new ocean of processor, server and data center revenues that don't currently exist. In 2013, this trend will become obvious. The current situation is temporary. The internet is not going away. The growth of video is not going away. Wireless connectivity is expanding beyond people to machines and devices. The Cloud is not going away. And Intel because of its fabrication is getting stronger every single day. Sometime during 2013, the executives at Intel will look like geniuses for expanding capacity during a chip market lull. The lull will not and cannot last. The world has an insatiable thirst for connectivity, for communication and for entertainment. Right now inventories are bare-bottom. As soon as the market starts to recover a bit the need to rebuild inventories will accelerate processor revenues. Only Intel can afford to continue building state-of-the-art capacity at the same rate no matter the temporary economic dips. When the market comes back, the advantage will be clear. TSMC is being punished now for underestimating the high-end market and not building enough capacity. Intel will never make that mistake. These factors will combine to push Intel into the 30 to 40 range in 2013. Look for the Intel LTE smartphone push into the US as just one of the catalysts. Look for a conversion of a major ARM customer to Intel in 2013 as another. In 2013 the dam is going to break and Intel will be the only boat to be lifted...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349877549589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:59:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349877969045-41</Id><Title>Intel better be buying hand-over-fist</Title><Msg>&amp; retiring the shares at these prices, not giving them to management as options. Shareholders have had enough with the current management team. Grow shareholder wealth should be the only goal.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349877969045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:06:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349877995213-42</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349835285929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel will be preparing for volume production of 14nm at the end of the year. It's going to be Intel's 14nm verses ARM's 28nm. ARM is a very long way from volume 20nm production. ----- TSMC says it's ready for 20-nm designs Peter Clarke 10/9/2012 11:00 AM EDT LONDON – Foundry Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacuturing Co. said this week its has prepared reference design flows in support of 20-nm planar CMOS and chip-on-wafer-on-substrate (CoWoS) assembly within its Open Innovation Platform (OIP). Both technologies are open for design starts. The 20-nm reference flow culminates in double-patterning-aware place and route to allow manufacturing using deep ultraviolet immersion lithography. Leading EDA vendors' tools have been qualified to work with the 20-nm process on timing, physical verification and design-for-manufacturing. In addition, TSMC and its ecosystem partners are developing 20-nm IP for double-patterning compliance to accelerate 20-nm adoption. TSMC did not list specific vendors' 20-nm compatible tools, but the reference design flow provides a direct link with simulators for voltage-dependent design rules. An RF reference design kit provides high-frequency design guidelines, including 60-GHz RF model support, electromagnetic characterization and integrated passive device support. The 20-nm high-k metal gate CMOS planar process is expected to begin volume production in 2013. The CoWoS reference design flow enables multiple die to be integrated on an interposer. It is a heterogeneous approach in the sense that the interposer, or substrate, usually made of silicon, is unlikely to be in a leading-edge process. Similarly, multiple die on the interposer can be made using different processes. The flow has now been validated with silicon runs and could be adopted to support high-bandwidth and lower power connections between chips, TSMC said. It includes: management of placement and routing of bumps, pads, interconnections and C4 bumps; an innovative combo-bump structure; accurate extraction and signal integrity analysis of high-speed interconnects between dies; thermal analysis from chip to package to system; and an integrated testing methodology for die-level and stacking-level tests.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1349877995213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:06:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349877996438-43</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349835285929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Why is it that no one mensions the billion dollar a year contract with CSCO that they just signed? Thats over 2% of their annual business!" *** The Chump Street mob is in its blood lust. No one is going to mention that someone has already called the cops. Earnings next week. The mob is at risk...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349877996438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349878066624-44</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Is Good for 30 AND 50</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349877549589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:59:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is of course assuming that the U.S. economy doesn't crash before then, which, if we have "4 MORE YEARS" it will... I hope you're right, but I think you are hoping beyond hope...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349878066624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349878130124-45</Id><Topic><Title>Unbelievable! Never such a buying op.</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349874378561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:06:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You could probably sell out now for a small profit and buy back in again at the same price later today or tomorrow...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349878130124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:08:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349878178249-46</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Is Good for 30 AND 50</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349877549589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:59:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>must be nice to still believe in the sugar plum fairy hint, the qqq need to hold 57.00, on the move back up buy the QLD or the TQQQ</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349878178249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:09:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349878473882-47</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349835285929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing there says TSMC is anything but a very long way from volume 20nm production. A year ago we heard noise about TSMC being ready for 20nm. TSMC still hasn't mastered 28nm production. 20nm is going to be much harder and much slower. The market assumes that because Intel ramps like a champ that the ARM world can do the same thing. It simply isn't true and the facts in evidence support this conclusion. TSMC's poor ramp on 28nm makes it impossible to provide any reasonable prediction of when 20nm might arrive, when volume production will be attained and when it might be reliable enough for a customer like Apple. 2015 maybe?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349878473882</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:14:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349878753095-48</Id><Title>SEC: Subpoena Gus Richard's Phone Records!!!</Title><Msg>Just look for Stacy Rasgon's phone numbers...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349878753095</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:19:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349878934941-49</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349835285929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing there says TSMC is anything but a very long way from volume 20nm production. ----- Maybe your definition of a very long way is different to mine. TSMC said: "The 20-nm high-k metal gate CMOS planar process is expected to begin volume production in 2013." ----- TSMC still hasn't mastered 28nm production. 20nm is going to be much harder and much slower. The market assumes that because Intel ramps like a champ that the ARM world can do the same thing. It simply isn't true and the facts in evidence support this conclusion. TSMC's poor ramp on 28nm makes it impossible to provide any reasonable prediction of when 20nm might arrive, when volume production will be attained and when it might be reliable enough for a customer like Apple. 2015 maybe? ---- You really need to dig more around TSMC's 28nm process and how the foundry model actually ramps if you want a true picture of how quick (or not) TSMC can ramp it's 20mm node.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1349878934941</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:22:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879244108-50</Id><Topic><Title>SEC: Subpoena Gus Richard's Phone Records!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349878753095</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:19:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are the #$%$ on Wall Street targeting US manufacturing???</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349879244108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:27:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879247616-51</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349835285929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you say a year ago? http://finance.yahoo.com/q/bc?t=1y&amp;s=INTC&amp;l=on&amp;z=l&amp;q=l&amp;c=tsm%2Carmh&amp;ql=1</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349879247616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:27:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879305539-52</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Is Good for 30 AND 50</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349877549589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:59:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i sold some Qs at $70 a coulpe weeks back.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349879305539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:28:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879391437-53</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking a new 52 week low today... hope this ends soon...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349876194245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:36:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you did hear about avnet didn't you?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349879391437</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:29:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879431488-54</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349835285929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You really need to dig more around TSMC's 28nm process and how the foundry model actually ramps if you want a true picture of how quick (or not) TSMC can ramp it's 20mm node." *** And you need to dig more around Nvidia's, Qualcomm's and AMD's comments on TSMC's 28nm ramp. Nobody was impressed and quite a few were furious. 20nm is going to be much more difficult than 28nm. TSMC gets worse with each new cycle...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349879431488</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879433464-55</Id><Topic><Title>What would a below estimates earnings report do to INTC?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349872725713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:38:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and $3 eps and climb back to $29 is going to be fun. Are we having fun yet?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349879433464</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879545107-56</Id><Topic><Title>Who's this Rocco Pendola ?</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1349873425462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:50:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you bet they did. they owned desktop and have been here the whole time. At least FB is run by a snot node kid who came from nowhere. How did Intel miss becoming Google is what I want to know?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349879545107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:32:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879591210-57</Id><Topic><Title>Unbelievable! Never such a buying op.</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349874378561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:06:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry- but its not buy time yet--wait till it goes under 20--and YES- IT WILL</Msg><Username>marrohead</Username><Timestamp>1349879591210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:33:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879645271-58</Id><Topic><Title>What would a below estimates earnings report do to INTC?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349872725713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:38:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>buoyed by dividend, doubt it goes much below where it is now. A knee jerk reaction may cause it to go to $21</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349879645271</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349879655310-59</Id><Title>Blueredmonk pumping TSMC 20nm OR TSMC HEAD MAN telling customers to "make other arrangements"</Title><Msg>Who would you believe? An anonymous message board pumper OR the head man of the company that told ACTUAL customers to find better options than TSMC? lol.</Msg><Username>getsome_nads</Username><Timestamp>1349879655310</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349879790395-60</Id><Title>What the future holds will start to sink in when Intel reports ACTUAL Mobile $$$$ next week</Title><Msg>dffddffddffddfdfdfdfdfd</Msg><Username>getsome_nads</Username><Timestamp>1349879790395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:36:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879799709-61</Id><Topic><Title>Blueredmonk pumping TSMC 20nm OR TSMC HEAD MAN telling customers to "make other arrangements"</Title><Username>getsome_nads</Username><Timestamp>1349879655310</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:34:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Yahoo pumper for sure.</Msg><Username>beenlong2twolong</Username><Timestamp>1349879799709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:36:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879941893-62</Id><Topic><Title>Blueredmonk pumping TSMC 20nm OR TSMC HEAD MAN telling customers to "make other arrangements"</Title><Username>getsome_nads</Username><Timestamp>1349879655310</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:34:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, I'm going to put my money on the pumper... but what the hell does any of this have to do with INTEL?</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349879941893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:39:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349880003724-63</Id><Title>ARMH getting hit hard today. No Dividend, Huge PE.....YUKK</Title><Msg>df fd df fd df fd heheheeeee!</Msg><Username>getsome_nads</Username><Timestamp>1349880003724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:40:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880056510-64</Id><Topic><Title>What would a below estimates earnings report do to INTC?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349872725713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:38:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah... I was hoping for rapid growth back to 22.50s today, but looks like everyone's waiting for earnings report...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349880056510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:40:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880078516-65</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok thanks! I will take a look at this.</Msg><Username>susannahitilg73632</Username><Timestamp>1349880078516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:41:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880332450-66</Id><Topic><Title>What would a below estimates earnings report do to INTC?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349872725713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:38:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Market already factoring in a very cautious forecast. Unless Intel says it will cut the dividend or that there will be a dramatic shift to their business model, all the risk is for those betting on a $20 price point. My guess is we get a relief rally from oversold conditions.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349880332450</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880612423-67</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1349835285929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you need to dig more around Nvidia's, Qualcomm's and AMD's comments on TSMC's 28nm ramp. Nobody was impressed and quite a few were furious. ----- TSMC have a HP and a LP process, one had yield issues and the other capacity issues... Noticed the following link via ee I posted below and you'll have kittens with a few of the comments made by Meurice. ASML: Push is on for 20-nm chip production in 2013 Peter Clarke 4/19/2012 1:14 PM EDT LONDON – Competition within the ARM ecosystem aimed at mobile devices is driving a faster pace of process development and will likely prompt foundry production on the 22-nm/20-nm process node in 2013, according to Eric Meurice, CEO of lithography vendor ASML Holding NV (Veldhoven, The Netherlands). Meurice, speaking to analysts on a conference call to discuss ASML's financial results for the first quarter of 2012, said the industry is competing in the mobile devices space and that is driving the development of a new production node each year. Meurice said that ASML expects to have six to nine months of strong sales in support of ramping production of the 28-nm production node but that by year end there will be the start of demand for equipment for 22-nm production. The leading chip company is already in production on 22-nm with its own FinFET-based process but leading foundry Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. Ltd. is struggling to meet demand for its 28-nm production, according to recent reports. "We have another six to nine months of production and shipment of machines before we have delivered to the market a mature, not high, level of [28-nm] wafers per month. After that there is another engine for 2013, which is to be proven, but we are getting now significant interest. The customers want to go from 28-nm to 22-nm already." Meurice told analysts that competition in the ARM environment around mobile applications is driving the desire for improved products and architectures. Rather than migrating to a new node every two years or 18 months Meurice sees the faster ramping to a new node every year. In a presentation prepared to accompany the companies financial results ASML said: "Demand for 28-nm in logic continues to be large and structural and will be accompanied by the start of pre-production for 20-nm late in 2012. For memory we expect technology demand for sub 20-nm NAND, sub 30-nm DRAM later this year." Meurice said that successful production at 22-nm or 20-nm in 2013 was not automatic. "These are very complicated nodes technology-wise and you could have difficulties; yield, ramp, etc. But this would probably not impact the litho business." In fact, Meurice concluded, such difficulties could provide a business upside for ASML.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1349880612423</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:50:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880644005-68</Id><Topic><Title>What the future holds will start to sink in when Intel reports ACTUAL Mobile $$$$ next week</Title><Username>getsome_nads</Username><Timestamp>1349879790395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:36:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gonna be sweet to see Mobile revenues in this report. Tune out the noise/haters and enjoy the Dividend and what the future will bring.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1349880644005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:50:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880694154-69</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice share, Very informative.</Msg><Username>katrinaulway244105</Username><Timestamp>1349880694154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:51:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349881116558-70</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Is Good for 30 AND 50</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349877549589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:59:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>67.00 on the QQQ, not 57.00 , 58.00 on the QLD</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349881116558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:58:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349881342249-71</Id><Topic><Title>Intel better be buying hand-over-fist</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349877969045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:06:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I absolutely hate it when they give management stock options. These managers are useless. Stock down 25% from only a month or so ago. They don't deserve anything. They need to reduce the number of shares to get the price up. Eventuall, with a low enough share count, the stock has to go up.</Msg><Username>nickster135796</Username><Timestamp>1349881342249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882367947-72</Id><Topic><Title>Romit Shah puts $1.85 2013 earnings for Intel</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349827965704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No- he is not kidding</Msg><Username>marrohead</Username><Timestamp>1349882367947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:19:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882530912-73</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Informative indeed. Thanks!</Msg><Username>tenishaqjcz03936</Username><Timestamp>1349882530912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:22:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349882641474-74</Id><Title>Huge ARM threat to Intel server space????</Title><Msg>10 October 2012 New ARM interconnect technology paves the way for scalable system-on-chip (SoC) solutions for network infrastructure and servers CAMBRIDGE, UK and LINLEY TECH PROCESSOR CONFERENCE, SAN JOSE – October 10, 2012 – To address the significant increase in data over the next 10-15 years, and the demand for more energy-efficient network infrastructure and servers, ARM has announced the ARM® CoreLink™ CCN-504 cache coherent network. This advanced system intellectual property (IP) can deliver up to one terabit of usable system bandwidth per second. It will enable SoC designers to provide high-performance, cache coherent interconnect for ‘many-core’ enterprise solutions built using the ARM Cortex™-A15 MPCore™ processor and next-generation 64-bit processors. LSI, a leading designer of intelligent semiconductors that accelerate storage, mobile networking and client computing, and Calxeda, an innovative supplier of disruptive SoC technology for the server market, are lead licensees for the CoreLink CCN-504 launch. ARM has also unveiled the new ARM CoreLink DMC-520 dynamic memory controller that has been designed and optimized to work with the CoreLink CCN-504. The new dynamic memory controller provides a high-bandwidth interface to shared off-chip memory, such as DDR3, DDR3L and DDR4 DRAM. It is part of an integrated ARM DDR4 interface solution incorporating ARM Artisan® DDR4/3 PHY IP planned for introduction in 2013. “Calxeda and ARM have been working closely to meet the demands of the datacenter since ARM's initial investment in our company in 2008, and we are beginning to see the fruits that relationship,” said Barry Evans, co-founder and CEO, Calxeda. “We are already building our next generation datacenter-class solutions using this new ARM CoreLink technology, and think we will once again send shockwaves across the industry when they are announced.” “To meet the demands of rapidly growing mobile network traffic, LSI and ARM have worked closely to drive a feature-rich on-chip interconnect that can serve as the backbone for industry-leading many-core system-on-chip devices,” said Gene Scuteri, vice president of engineering, LSI. “ARM expertise in processor and interconnect technology, guided by LSI's deep understanding of networking and compute workloads, has delivered a robust, carrier-grade interconnect that will deliver scalable, deterministic performance and quality of service for today’s most advanced networks.” CoreLink CCN-504 is the first in a family of products. It enables a fully-coherent, high-performance many-core solution that supports up to 16 cores on the same silicon die. The CoreLink CCN-504 enables system coherency in heterogeneous multicore and multi-cluster CPU/GPU systems by enabling each processor in the system to access the other processor caches. This reduces the need to access off-chip memory, saving time and energy, which is a key enabler in systems based on ARM big.LITTLE™ processing, a new paradigm that can deliver both high-performance, required for content creation and consumption, and extreme power efficiency for extended battery life. “As the amount of data used increases exponentially over the next 10-15 years, the CoreLink CCN-504 and DMC-520 will play an important role by providing high-performance system IP solutions for many-core applications,” said Tom Cronk, deputy general manager, processor division, ARM. “This ensures quality of service and coherent operation across the system, and enables SoC designers to efficiently prioritize and handle wide data flows with optimum latency.” The CoreLink CCN-504 supports both the current-generation high-end Cortex-A15 processor and future ARMv8 processors and is the first in a family of network-based interconnect products planned by ARM. Building on the success of the AMBA® 4 ACE™ specification the CoreLink CCN-504 also benefits from ARM experience in hardware-based coherency, which enables improved energy-efficiency and lower latency than software coherency. Over 8000 AMBA 4 ACE specifications have been downloaded to date. The CoreLink CCN-504 cache coherent network includes integrated level 3 (L3) cache and snoop filter functions. The L3 cache, which is configurable up to 16MB, extends on-chip caching for demanding workloads and offers low latency on-chip memory for allocation and sharing of data between processors, high-speed IO interfaces and accelerators. The snoop filter removes the need for broadcast coherency messaging, further reducing latency and power. Availability: the ARM CoreLink CCN-504 cache coherent network is available to lead licensees now, and sampling in partner products in 2013.</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1349882641474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:24:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882941246-75</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Is Good for 30 AND 50</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349877549589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:59:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd say $100 is in the bag,</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349882941246</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:29:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349883102450-76</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems legit, thanks for the free info.</Msg><Username>cristalxwhv46591</Username><Timestamp>1349883102450</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349883505236-77</Id><Title>Obama's Policies are tanking the economy!!</Title><Msg>In spite of Obama's awful incompetence, INTC will survive. Go INTC!</Msg><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349883505236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:38:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349883515338-78</Id><Topic><Title>Get your picks early</Title><Username>yokoeswt344899</Username><Timestamp>1349880273249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:44:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure thing. Been receiving good alerts from them</Msg><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1349883515338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:38:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349883623465-79</Id><Topic><Title>Romit Shah puts $1.85 2013 earnings for Intel</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349827965704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4% dividend is safe even at lower earnings. It is a cash cow and still an innovator. It will be a long time till a bank pays you 4% on your money IMHO. Maybe 5 years or more since the Fed is holding at 0-.25% till mid 2014 and will probably push it out even farther especially if O gets elected. They can't afford to raise the rate because of their own debt. I will continue to collect the dividend which is coming up and also sell short term calls for extra income. Between the dividend and selling the calls it is lucrative, of course there is risk but only if the stock market crashes. That may happen but not for a couple years yet. All the above IMHO</Msg><Username>wi_mike</Username><Timestamp>1349883623465</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:40:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349883661469-80</Id><Title>Can Obama fix this? "You break it you fix it..."</Title><Msg>Or, is this too much for a community organizer to take on? INTC will beat expectations from here, and will likely be around $22.50 next Friday EOD. Go INTC!</Msg><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349883661469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349883910291-81</Id><Title>How can things be so BAD after 4 YEARS of Obama?</Title><Msg>I mean, just say the name Obama and you start to feel better. His supporters told us it was important to vote for him - historic because of his skin color! Obama promised us a new world with falling ocean levels and chickens in every pot, etc. INTC will survive, because - unlike Obama - they are good at what they do. The BEST! Go INTC!</Msg><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349883910291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349884212286-82</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Subscribed! Hoping for the best.</Msg><Username>regeniarunmp23502</Username><Timestamp>1349884212286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:50:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349884609357-83</Id><Topic><Title>Romit Shah puts $1.85 2013 earnings for Intel</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349827965704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Expect Romit Shah repeat his past behavior. He takes a punch at Intel before and again after every scheduled event, epecially earnings confernce calls. Since he left the target unchanged, he will release a lowered price target after the call. I expect he will go back to an $18 target. He likes to be the lowest target. I tried to figure out how he got his numbers but I cannot see where he got his data yet. One of his supporting arguments is that Intel share price has tracked gross margin over the past 10 years. That does seem to be true according to the charts. Reducing the share count by 20% like Intel has done should raise the curve by 20%. Romit says that 12 cents per share was added by share buybacks .... 20%. "Intel shares have tracked the direction of gross margin over the last decade. And thus far in 2012 that trend has continued. The stock has declined over 20% over the last six months on lower gross margin guidance, among other things. That said, we would not expect gross margin to bottom until Q2-13, and for the full year come in around 59%, below consensus of 62%," said analyst Romit Shah.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349884609357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:56:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349884680264-84</Id><Topic><Title>Intel better be buying hand-over-fist</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349877969045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:06:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not enough net cash is left for meaningful buybacks. Buying back shares to offset stock awards is a losing proposition.</Msg><Username>c757172</Username><Timestamp>1349884680264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:58:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349885354338-85</Id><Title>Alot of peole that bought Intel between 12-20/share sold</Title><Msg>It's that simple. More will reload between 18 and here for the next run. Chill out.</Msg><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1349885354338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:09:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349885536939-86</Id><Topic><Title>Alot of peole that bought Intel between 12-20/share sold</Title><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1349885354338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:09:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"people". A lot of people that bought between 12 and 20 sold between 25 and 29. Higher Highs and Higher lows since 2009.</Msg><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1349885536939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:12:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349885753424-87</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this.</Msg><Username>danielacuxb471646</Username><Timestamp>1349885753424</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:15:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349885846417-88</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Is Good for 30 AND 50</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349877549589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:59:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice bounce for the QLD off 58.00, qqq 67.01, former breakout levels</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349885846417</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:17:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349885976077-89</Id><Topic><Title>Alot of peole that bought Intel between 12-20/share sold</Title><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1349885354338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:09:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC is a great company because it MANUFACTURES THINGS that the whole world needs. It does not have the glamour of a Facebook or Google, but it is a real entity. My cost basis is in the teens and, yes, I did take some shares off the table between $26 and $27, but the price is getting back into the strike zone. Dividends and covered calls make this a cash cow for some.</Msg><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349885976077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:19:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349886933465-90</Id><Title>Sell Sell Sell all INTC</Title><Msg>think later</Msg><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1349886933465</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349887081852-91</Id><Topic><Title>How can things be so BAD after 4 YEARS of Obama?</Title><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349883910291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:45:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he got in due to all the blacks that voted for him and all they young stupid whites that went along. Should be different in a month. I don't care if they put a green person in the WH. Just one that will fix the debt, bring home our boys, get the DOW over 25K, quit sending our jobs to china and india, lower taxes, and get gas below a buck/gallon. that's it.</Msg><Username>chevymalibu1966</Username><Timestamp>1349887081852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:38:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349887203328-92</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one. I will subscribe now.</Msg><Username>mittieevdf91666</Username><Timestamp>1349887203328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:40:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349887213549-93</Id><Title>Urgent Request to former Obama voters...</Title><Msg>...please please please reconsider your loyalty to an incompetent leader. Everybody makes mistakes, everybody gets emotionally attached to their stock picks and leaders they voted for, but it is important for former Obama supporters to change their minds. Noone can force you to change your mind (at least the Left hasn't been THAT successful yet), and noone wants to force you anyway, but please reconsider your loyalty in view of the FACTS. Go INTC!</Msg><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349887213549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:40:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349887222934-94</Id><Title>INTC very poorly managed company</Title><Msg>look at the chart - it will tell the story</Msg><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1349887222934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:40:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349887408069-95</Id><Topic><Title>Get your picks early</Title><Username>yokoeswt344899</Username><Timestamp>1349880273249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:44:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like these guys, they're really good.</Msg><Username>roseanntylo65933</Username><Timestamp>1349887408069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:43:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349887567507-96</Id><Title>INTC</Title><Msg>Going to be interesting to see how long before they unload Otellini. He has absolutely a zero growth strategy other than adding some additional compressions to their chip line. They need a CEO with a "Vision" for the company--just making new iterations of chips is not growing the company. The stock has been in the doldrums for 10+ years--the price is below the level when Otellini became CEO. Barret and then Otellini have been of the belief a horizontal based company was the answer and they used to scoff at the Apple model of being "Vertically Integrated" was pure nonsense. Yet Apple now has a valuation 5 times that of INTC--in fact Apple's valuation is greater than INTC, MSFT, DELL and HPQ combined! What happened? Otellini has no answer for the rush to Mobile except basically saying more patience is required--our new chip iterations will save us--yada, yada. Somebody at INTC needs to wake up to the new reality that INTC has been shut out and left behind swinging in the wind.</Msg><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1349887567507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:46:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349887817166-97</Id><Title>INTC, DELL and HPQ all holding each other's hands at new found bottoms today...</Title><Msg>52 Week bottoms that is... for Dell and HPQ it's more like 5 year bottoms... Interesting how they seem to follow each other... DELL almost seems like a buy at this point, but after my last burn on it, I shy away from it these days, but it may turn around big time who knows...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349887817166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:50:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349887831913-98</Id><Topic><Title>INTC</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1349887567507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:46:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did INTC purchase McAfee? Now, INTC is laying off employees.</Msg><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1349887831913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:50:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349888079634-99</Id><Topic><Title>Time for Leadership Change</Title><Username>billsuxx</Username><Timestamp>1349803959061</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:32:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel's Chairman is Andy Bryant who is in Otellini's pocket. Andy should have retired a while back but Otellini found him a cushy post as Chairman. Many of the other board members are old timers who just rubber-stamps management's strategies. Intel needs peopel at the board and in management who can shake things up. Intel needs to bring someone from the outside who understands the sea-change of the value moving from the chip-PC-device vendor to the data/content/apps market. Simply chasing mobile/tablet/smartphone with a "better chip" is a losing proposition. By the time Intel gets there, the game has already moved on. Everyone love the iPhone/iPad but that is not Apple's value. Apple OWNS your data (iCloud, iOS, Apps Store) and more to come. That's where the value is!!!</Msg><Username>billsuxx</Username><Timestamp>1349888079634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:54:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349888473943-100</Id><Topic><Title>Time for Leadership Change</Title><Username>billsuxx</Username><Timestamp>1349803959061</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:32:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree for a change. INTC has been trading water during the last 10 years.</Msg><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1349888473943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:01:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349888629768-101</Id><Topic><Title>Huge ARM threat to Intel server space????</Title><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1349882641474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:24:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huge threat ?</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1349888629768</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:03:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349888809429-102</Id><Title>Things will GET WORSE if OBAMA is re-elected</Title><Msg>Because an anti-business leader will get anti-business results. Go INTC!</Msg><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349888809429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349889308889-103</Id><Topic><Title>How can things be so BAD after 4 YEARS of Obama?</Title><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349883910291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:45:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama will never win the old stupid whites vote. they vote 100% Republican. Obama will get still get the black vote and the young stupid whites. women don't have a very tough time with this decision. hispanics don't have a very tough time deciding either. poor won't have a problem deciding the ones with the tough decision are the moderates in middle who have to chose between two bad extremes and having to listen to the #$%$ from both sides. things will be different in a month but not how you expect .... no matter what the election outcome bring the military home (bring the girls home too) ...... no difference in candidates policy. fix the debt .... that can be done with either too .... Obama will compromise ..... Romney solution will ultimately generate the same result the wages in the US and China/India are normalizing and jobs will balance and flow back naturally. buck a gallon gas ... never again unless it is subsidized.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1349889308889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:15:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349889470875-104</Id><Title>This turd will be under $20</Title><Msg>Sell INTC now.</Msg><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1349889470875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:17:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349889614427-105</Id><Topic><Title>Things will GET WORSE if OBAMA is re-elected</Title><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349888809429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too bad Eric Cantor, John Boehner and Mitch McConnell don't work more cooperatively to get the right legislation.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1349889614427</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:20:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349889748781-106</Id><Title>INTC Results</Title><Msg>Either some idiot leaked earnings to some fund(s) or they are pushing this down due to fear. I wish if INTC's earnings were say $0.50 or better and revenue better, that INTC announces before Tuesday 4pm and catch all of these sellers off guard. That would send this to 23 and higher in a heartbeat. Dopes.</Msg><Username>chevymalibu1966</Username><Timestamp>1349889748781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:22:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349889806525-107</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An article that's worth a read.</Msg><Username>thelmaufwm26402</Username><Timestamp>1349889806525</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:23:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349889974755-108</Id><Topic><Title>This turd will be under $20</Title><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1349889470875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:17:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>probably under 19!!</Msg><Username>marrohead</Username><Timestamp>1349889974755</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349890063098-109</Id><Title>Where's Paul?</Title><Msg>Oh thats right, he's in that 6 week quiet period again. Every Qtr. it's the same old thing, we get bashed and the stock tanks because he doesn't want to talk. He can announce that Macaffe is qoing to lay off employees during this period, but can't refute or say anything good during this period. Wonder if the real reason is the analysts run the price down so INTC employees can get a lower price on their options? After all this is great way to milk the company and pad your retirement at the share holders expense.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349890063098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349890072263-110</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Results</Title><Username>chevymalibu1966</Username><Timestamp>1349889748781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:22:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel IR should be ashamed of themselves to let the share price get manipulated like this by analysts &amp; MMs. Enough of this "quiet period" sham. Speak up Mr. CEO &amp; remove the uncertainty.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349890072263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:27:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349890343708-111</Id><Topic><Title>Where's Paul?</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349890063098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:27:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's too busy to talk. What else can he do besides wasting $8B of shareholder wealth on a stupid McAffee acquisition that no one has any clue how Intel will monetize or totally missing the mobile market!! Worse CEO than Craig Barrett &amp; thats saying a lot.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349890343708</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:32:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349890803484-112</Id><Topic><Title>This turd will be under $20</Title><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1349889470875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:17:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it printed $21.71 today!</Msg><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1349890803484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:40:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349891131400-113</Id><Topic><Title>Things will GET WORSE if OBAMA is re-elected</Title><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349888809429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lucy, there is no compromise because OBAMA does not compromise. Remember Obamacare? ZERO votes from the GOP. The bipartisan vote was AGAINST Obamacare. If you are really concerned about compromise, the contact your DEMOCRAT SENATOR and ask them to start working with the GOP to pass an annual budget. Democrats haven't passed an annual budget in THREE YEARS!!! They didn't even manage to pass a simple budget when they had control of all branches of government. Disgusting.</Msg><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349891131400</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:45:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349891244055-114</Id><Title>DEMOCRAT TAX INCREASES TO HIT ECONOMY IN LESS THAN 3 MONTHS...</Title><Msg>...including Obamacare (the largest tax bill in history), Democrat tax increases are going to affect INTC's price. Go INTC!</Msg><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349891244055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349891571082-115</Id><Topic><Title>How can things be so BAD after 4 YEARS of Obama?</Title><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349883910291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:45:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...his record shows him to be an ideologue who will bring the system down rather than admit he's wrong. He failed the economy, he failed to keep our embassies safe, he failed to cut the deficit in half, he failed to close Gitmo, he failed to use public campaign funds ( a MAJOR DEMOCRAT platform issue for decades), his failure in Afghanistan has resulted in military deaths approaching Iraq numbers, etc. He passed Obamacare without ONE SINGLE REPUBLICAN VOTE! (How divisive can you be to do something like that?!?)</Msg><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349891571082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:52:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349891643793-116</Id><Title>Don't worry: Obama has promised to fix things...</Title><Msg>...uh oh... Go INTC!</Msg><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349891643793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:54:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349891997236-117</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Is Good for 30 AND 50</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349877549589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:59:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally's so mind-numbingly ingnorant that he think QE is the way to go and that Intel will get to 50 with 4 more years of QE. Just absolutely amazing to see how dumb this guy is.</Msg><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1349891997236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:59:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349892121993-118</Id><Title>OMG ........ look at PHLX Semiconductor (^SOX)</Title><Msg>my lord</Msg><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1349892121993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:02:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349892373902-119</Id><Topic><Title>Get your picks early</Title><Username>yokoeswt344899</Username><Timestamp>1349880273249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:44:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope this is good. Subscribed!</Msg><Username>quianabbalf331833</Username><Timestamp>1349892373902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:06:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349892544931-120</Id><Topic><Title>Things will GET WORSE if OBAMA is re-elected</Title><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349888809429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For sure, neither do Republicans. Both my Senators are Republican. I have already contacted them several times. too bad Eric Cantor, John Boehner and Mitch McConnell don't work more cooperatively to get a budget passed. the Democrats could have used the Special Appropriations to fund the wars Bush started, the same way he did. OH!! that would have taken some compromise, if funding for the Bush started wars was rolled into the budget. a Republican would put a secret hold on any budget legislation in the Senate that did not match what the Republicans wanted. Obstruct and defeat!</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1349892544931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:09:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349892598838-121</Id><Title>NEWS: OBAMA LIED ABOUT LIBYA</Title><Msg>Turns out "the video" (nobody saw) was NOT the reason for the attack in Libya. Investigations are showing that the Democrat's Administration failed to take adequate measures to protect our ambassadors. Why does this matter to INTC investors? Because Obama is screwing up the economy with the same misguided confidence. Go INTC!</Msg><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349892598838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:09:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349892779386-122</Id><Topic><Title>Things will GET WORSE if OBAMA is re-elected</Title><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349888809429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As more Democrats get on board the fiscal conservative bandwagon, the better off we will be. Unfortunately for Democrats, most of their elected leaders are ADDICTED TO SPENDING.</Msg><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349892779386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349892839000-123</Id><Title>Will Romney repeal ...</Title><Msg>Wallis Weaver Day?</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1349892839000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349892892123-124</Id><Title>HEALTH CARE COSTS UP $2500 INSTEAD OF DOWN $2500 LIKE OBAMA PROMISED...</Title><Msg>...just one more failed promise in a fantastically long list. Go INTC!</Msg><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349892892123</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:14:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349892944933-125</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRAT TAX INCREASES TO HIT ECONOMY IN LESS THAN 3 MONTHS...</Title><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349891244055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$21.80. Go INTC!</Msg><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1349892944933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:15:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349893065544-126</Id><Title>The good news and the bad news of the impending market decline.</Title><Msg>The bad news first, the market is heading lower short term. The good news, smart investors are going to cash, will move back in at lower prices. Most importantly, the correction of the overpriced market should help get Obama unelected and Romney the businessman can get the country anbd the economy moving again.</Msg><Username>ghetto_trash</Username><Timestamp>1349893065544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:17:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349893121243-127</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am looking for.</Msg><Username>toniegpae066109</Username><Timestamp>1349893121243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349893340860-128</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Is Good for 30 AND 50</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349877549589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:59:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He certainly appears to be far more of a tech geek nerd than anything else. nice afternoon bounce off an oversold 5 minute back above 58.00 for the QLD. really prefer buying rising macd and rising rsi's on the daily charts, not there yet with the declines today. Fighting downward pressure can be hazardous.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349893340860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:22:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349893625099-129</Id><Topic><Title>Where's Paul?</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349890063098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:27:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC is in QUIET period before ER.</Msg><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1349893625099</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:27:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349894268079-130</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Is Good for 30 AND 50</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349877549589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:59:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Intel will be preparing for volume production of 14nm at the end of the year. It's going to be Intel's 14nm verses ARM's 28nm.' This is just plain wrong. We are nearing the end of 2012 and Intel's 22nm Atom is nowhere in sight. You think they will just skip it and go straight to the 14nm version in 2013 ?;-) Seriously are you paid to pump this stock with such obvious falsehoods ? There's not even going to be a 14nm Core product either in 2013 as 2013 will be the year of 22nm Haswell. They might be preparing for 14nm at the end of the year but the 14nm products will not be launched until 2014 in the form of Broadwell and Airmont which should both be good. Intel's 14nm will be competing against ARM's 20nm in 2014.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349894268079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:37:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349894642999-131</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Results</Title><Username>chevymalibu1966</Username><Timestamp>1349889748781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:22:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intc bulls should be esctatic if they believe INTC is undervalued here, assuming they were bright enough to have already sold for profits higher.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349894642999</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:44:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349894799399-132</Id><Topic><Title>Get your picks early</Title><Username>yokoeswt344899</Username><Timestamp>1349880273249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:44:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just joined. Heard a lot about these guys</Msg><Username>luanarbhoj06666</Username><Timestamp>1349894799399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349894919382-133</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRAT TAX INCREASES TO HIT ECONOMY IN LESS THAN 3 MONTHS...</Title><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349891244055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obama tax Increases ( obamacare - EPA - Bank Regulartory - etc,etc, ) will effect ALL PRICES - Not just stock prices - ALL PRICES !</Msg><Username>atexeight</Username><Timestamp>1349894919382</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349895237593-134</Id><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Msg>He needs to be escorted off of this board with his misinformation and your efforts are appreciated. Thanks for refuting his false claims in the thread "Intel is good for 30 and 50".</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349895506388-135</Id><Title>Wally says Balancing the Budget is part of of the job for Democrats</Title><Msg>Any further evidence needed that this guy is a lying POS? Re: Out Of The Week wallisweaver.Jul 14, 2009 2:59 AM.PermalinkGo to topic "LOL, you are quite the character, walli. Obviously you can't tell the difference between being a Republican apologist and a devil's advocate towards someone who seemly puts Democrats on a par with God." *** Well I can certainly see why you think balancing a budget puts someone on a par with God. It's proven to be totally impossible for Republican presidents. But we Democrats just happen to think it's part of the job. To Republicans it's just something way down the priority list after starting ill advised wars and giving out ill advised tax cuts. Someday it may be more of a priority. And then Republicans might actually have a chance to return to the White House. Until then you can wrap yourselves in the cold comfort of your ideology...</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895506388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349895751800-136</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Results</Title><Username>chevymalibu1966</Username><Timestamp>1349889748781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:22:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It could go as low as 20 before the earnings annoucement, the only negative I see in that is that I'm already in at 22.60 average and am maxed out... so I just have to wait it out... to the lucky souls that still have funds to play with, you get to make out like bandits...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349895751800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:02:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349896038607-137</Id><Title>Where do you think it will land today? And Higher or Lower tomorrow (what price if you want)?</Title><Msg>I'm guessing 21.85 it lands today... and lower to 21.80 tomorrow...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349896038607</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:07:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349896098264-138</Id><Title>Cockroaches</Title><Msg>This is what you will never ever see on this board. You will never see any of the cockroaches able to refute any analysis like the one below. It's because they are idiots with no knowledge of technology. Well, except for Vinnie BagODonuts. He fixes computers in his garage. He's pretty sure he's going to be the next Michael Dell. Not this week... I see Intel easily moving above 30 in 2013. Here's why: Intel is going to have five 22nm plants going. Intel has high end capacity. ARM doesn't. Nvidia, Qualcomm and AMD are all crying out for high end capacity they can't get from the ARM foundries. The situation will get worse as Intel becomes the only place with available high end capacity. Intel will be preparing for volume production of 14nm at the end of the year. It's going to be Intel's 14nm verses ARM's 28nm. ARM is a very long way from volume 20nm production. This just means Intel is going to get huge traction in mobility. There is absolutely no problem with Intel's mobility strategy - it just needs a little time to develop. The recent Motorola release should be a wake-up call for ARM. Intel has drawn even. In 2013 Intel will move ahead. Intel's tablet solutions are going to make a significant move up. Expect both tablet and smartphone solutions to continuously step up with a frequency that ARM can't match. By the end of 2013 it's going to be clear to the Apple's and Qualcomm's of the world that sticking to ARM will be a huge competitive disadvantage. If they don't use Intel, then their competitors will. It's that simple. There are only two ARM foundries that can compete with Intel. In 2013, TSMC is going to drop to the wayside. They just don't have the money, the technology or the manufacturing prowess to keep up with Intel and Samsung. Samsung unfortunately doesn't have the technology. It will be a two-horse race with Intel significantly in the lead due to its superior fabrication. These factors will combine to give Intel the choice of whatever high end business it wants. ARM will be relegated to the lower-end technology and will have to cut prices to do so. ARM is going to be the new AMD by the end of 2013. This trend will accelerate each year thereafter. And while Intel is building traction in both tablets and smartphones, the Internet of Things (wireless devices, sensors, RF tags, ATMs, signs, vending machines, etc.) will be experiencing exponential growth. Intel is extremely well positioned for this growth and its WiFi chip development gives it a serious competitive advantage. The IoT will provide a whole new ocean of processor, server and data center revenues that don't currently exist. In 2013, this trend will become obvious. The current situation is temporary. The internet is not going away. The growth of video is not going away. Wireless connectivity is expanding beyond people to machines and devices. The Cloud is not going away. And Intel because of its fabrication is getting stronger every single day. Sometime during 2013, the executives at Intel will look like geniuses for expanding capacity during a chip market lull. The lull will not and cannot last. The world has an insatiable thirst for connectivity, for communication and for entertainment. Right now inventories are bare-bottom. As soon as the market starts to recover a bit the need to rebuild inventories will accelerate processor revenues. Only Intel can afford to continue building state-of-the-art capacity at the same rate no matter the temporary economic dips. When the market comes back, the advantage will be clear. TSMC is being punished now for underestimating the high-end market and not building enough capacity. Intel will never make that mistake. These factors will combine to push Intel into the 30 to 40 range in 2013. Look for the Intel LTE smartphone push into the US as just one of the catalysts. Look for a conversion of a major ARM customer to Intel in 2013 as another. In 2013 the dam is going to break and Intel will be the only boat to be lifted...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349896098264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349896174231-139</Id><Title>Watch CRUS</Title><Msg>wonder why is up today ??</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1349896174231</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:09:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349896500135-140</Id><Topic><Title>Cockroaches</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349896098264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:08:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You talk too much but with little credibility. Why didn't you warn us of the large downfall in revenues this quarter? Why did you deceive the unsophisticated with your unrelenting "strong buy" at $28, $29? You are nothing but a low life manipulator.</Msg><Username>c757172</Username><Timestamp>1349896500135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:15:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349896555780-141</Id><Topic><Title>Watch CRUS</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1349896174231</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:09:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You got a point there, NOTHING makes sense except that manipulation is taking place and people like me are getting played hard... sad, but I'll just hang in and wait it out...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349896555780</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349896573715-142</Id><Topic><Title>Cockroaches</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349896098264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:08:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Post an article, just ONE, proving that Intel will be shipping 14nm parts in 2013, ya cockroach.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349896573715</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:16:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349896881116-143</Id><Title>ALERT: PC shipments to fall for first time in 11 years - forecast</Title><Msg>LOOK OUT BELOW!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349896881116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:21:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349896909874-144</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>irenayuzn69850</Username><Timestamp>1349896909874</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:21:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897106461-145</Id><Topic><Title>Cockroaches</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349896098264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:08:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound a little grumpy today, Pumpwad. You must be ridin' the cotton pony. Take some Midol and RELAX! TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349897106461</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:25:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897107823-146</Id><Topic><Title>Cockroaches</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349896098264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:08:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Waldo, pure sugar plum fairy land, the US could easily slip into a recession next year, inventory wasting away on shelves and no demand, fall off a fiscal cliff, you have no clue what the markets will do, zip, zero.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349897107823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:25:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897113633-147</Id><Topic><Title>Cockroaches</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349896098264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:08:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are just destrying the value in technoloy stocks. This is very steep decline in such a short amount of time. Complete nightmare.</Msg><Username>moobyet</Username><Timestamp>1349897113633</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:25:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897257678-148</Id><Topic><Title>NEWS: OBAMA LIED ABOUT LIBYA</Title><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349892598838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:09:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would you think this is "news"......been asleep for the last 4 years?</Msg><Username>ezmony647</Username><Timestamp>1349897257678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:27:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897670604-149</Id><Topic><Title>Cockroaches</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349896098264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:08:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>destroying the value in technology stocks? QQQ from new highs of 70.00ish to 67ish, a mere 4-5 percent drop. hardly destruction of value in "technology stocks".</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349897670604</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:34:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349897884490-150</Id><Title>DELL/INTC/BRCM/HPQ/CSCO will file chapter 11 soon, why???</Title><Msg>DELL/INTC/BRCM/HPQ/CSCO will file chapter 11 soon or later because CEO/BOD/Employees' bonuses and stock options are outrageous and furious...who pay all that? Hope you stay away from those companies!!!!!!!!! Look at the O/S of INTC??? Thanks me later! Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>exposecrooks</Username><Timestamp>1349897884490</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:38:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897921899-151</Id><Topic><Title>I will take INTC to a new year low today</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1349865885766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:44:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"sell early I am the one who control the share price." Yeah right, that is why this idiot is on welfare as he admitted on the NUVA message board where you can read it for yourself.</Msg><Username>jeml5845</Username><Timestamp>1349897921899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:38:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349898142553-152</Id><Topic><Title>I will take INTC to a new year low today</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1349865885766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:44:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul, is that you?</Msg><Username>cray3040</Username><Timestamp>1349898142553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349898332858-153</Id><Topic><Title>Cockroaches</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349896098264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:08:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True, except for CRUS is curiously up today... that one I can't figure out... Anyone?</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349898332858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349898702497-154</Id><Title>Ultrabook sales have disappointed</Title><Msg>Frm CNN MONEY "Ultrabook sales have disappointed. IHS iSuppli slashed its forecast for the thin laptops in half last week, and NPD DisplaySearch recently forecast that Ultrabooks will make up just a quarter of the total mobile PC market by 2015 -- far short of Intel's forecast."</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349898702497</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:51:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349898982409-155</Id><Title>Just picked up a thousand shares....</Title><Msg>For a trade. $21.72... Good luck longs...........ROTFLMAO</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349898982409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:56:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349899823295-156</Id><Topic><Title>Just picked up a thousand shares....</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349898982409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sell tomorrow at 21.82 for a quick $100 profit, then buy back in at 21.65 or lower... Longs WILL win in the end, but the question is how long... I suspect I'll sell out before the end of the year at 23.60, but that will just be break even for me...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349899823295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:10:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349899862566-157</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you shared this to us.</Msg><Username>hyunbbhn73116</Username><Timestamp>1349899862566</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:11:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349899934898-158</Id><Topic><Title>DELL/INTC/BRCM/HPQ/CSCO will file chapter 11 soon, why???</Title><Username>exposecrooks</Username><Timestamp>1349897884490</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:38:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound bitter and jealous... have fun at the funny farm...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1349899934898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:12:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349900006942-159</Id><Topic><Title>Just picked up a thousand shares....</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349898982409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at least someone's up on INTC a recent buy. Nice bounce for the markets in the last 5 minutes.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349900006942</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349900271179-160</Id><Topic><Title>Just picked up a thousand shares....</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349898982409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm looking for $34 by November. :-) Seriously I would like to hold it a quarter or two and collect the dividend. Maybe sell out of the money calls.</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349900271179</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:17:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349900544090-161</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT: PC shipments to fall for first time in 11 years - forecast</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349896881116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well....lets take a look. In early October 2001 INTC was between approx. $19 and $20 By the end of 2001 , it hit a high of $36 And your point?</Msg><Username>wbobeli</Username><Timestamp>1349900544090</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:22:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349900905774-162</Id><Topic><Title>DELL/INTC/BRCM/HPQ/CSCO will file chapter 11 soon, why???</Title><Username>exposecrooks</Username><Timestamp>1349897884490</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:38:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a buy at these levels..........I hope!</Msg><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1349900905774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:28:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349901495452-163</Id><Topic><Title>Just picked up a thousand shares....</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349898982409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I added 10k shares today at 21.71.</Msg><Username>crazy.wally</Username><Timestamp>1349901495452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:38:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349901593776-164</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great. I will check it out.</Msg><Username>lorraineyahul88626</Username><Timestamp>1349901593776</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:39:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349902253297-165</Id><Title>Can some one tie me a noose?</Title><Msg>I'm sick of this. they did not come out and downgrade all at one. It has dragged out for a couple of weeks now. Damn it. Is this the bottom? Just rocket up already. I hope that the earning is good enough to give these short a@@hole a run for their money. Who think that it will start creeping up toward $24 and reach mid $23 or even $24 by earning time?</Msg><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349902253297</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:50:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349902581084-166</Id><Topic><Title>Can some one tie me a noose?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349902253297</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:50:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You will be lucky if it hits 22 before earnings--nothing but bad news lately</Msg><Username>marrohead</Username><Timestamp>1349902581084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349902614279-167</Id><Title>The Link:-- yahoo.it/CUGuy is SPAM</Title><Msg>just wondering if you've got any cheese?</Msg><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1349902614279</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:56:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349902796684-168</Id><Topic><Title>Can some one tie me a noose?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349902253297</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:50:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know. It's just one big bad news that anal-list keep plucking at it. Like I said, they just did not go out and downgrade immediately. They let it rebound a bit and #$%$ of it and just take turn like that. What I'm hoping for is some bounce going into earning. I think it was heavily short (way over sold) and any back to back bounce of 2% or more will send the rest of the shorties covering. That can drive up the price toward earning day.</Msg><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349902796684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:59:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349902900517-169</Id><Title>S &amp; P Just DOWNGRADED SPAIN</Title><Msg>LOOOOOK OUT BELOW!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349902900517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:01:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349903436474-170</Id><Topic><Title>Unbelievable! Never such a buying op.</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349874378561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:06:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am a published author. I intend to write a book about the Great Manipulation, the stealing of small investor's money by the big guys. You are seeing it. Any half-way reasonable and intelligent person sees clearly that this supercompany is going to own the chip space in the future, on a time scale of 2014-2015. Only a handful of people, such as Wallis, are stating the facts, and he has been marginalized by the crooks who post in here, into a ranting fool standing on a soap box in Hyde Park. The big boys want in, and they want large positions. They can only do this by shaking the trees and shaking them very hard. They are acting now because they know the earnings will likely not be as disappointing as they are stating they will be via CNBS, and various Vomit Shills around the country. And Ottelini can't say anything---he knows too much and he doesn't want to tip his hand. The big boys have sucked all yo mom's and dad's into AAPL. But as INTC begins to take off, with the Google axis in play, AAPL becomes seriously challenged...c'mon, Samsung does have better galaxy phones than I5. The BIG BOYS get it all...the decline and crash of AAPL and the whole blithering ARMH world, and the rise of the INTC--Google nexus. Take this wisdom and think about it. Mark this post. Sadly, I can only give you this fish. Most of you are so severely retarded that you will never learn to fish for yourselves.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349903436474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:10:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349903485138-171</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Although he does make up a lot of #$%$ I don't really disagree with his final price targets or his thesis that the stock is manipulated by analysts who want the stock nearer their previous bad price targets to rescue bad positions. You just don't have to make stuff up like he does as the true story is good enough. It's the combination of design and fabrication that will do it but design is the most important and always has been but as he doesn't really understand one computer design from another he has to bleat on about fabrication as that is relatively simple enough for him to understand and regurgitate. Medfield is just the starter but Silvermont will be the main course and will ask questions of Arm chips that they probably won't be able to answer. Haswell is such an awesome design that will be like the second coming of Conroe which struck down Athlon64 with a mighty blow that AMD never recovered from. Haswell will be a similar quantum jump in performance and there will be sub 10W versions. 14nm Broadwall though will get the power down to 5W which is tablet class. At 14nm Intel is going to squeeze ARM from above with Broadwell and below with Airmont, probably only Apple's bespoke processor will still look any good in comparison. Even well before then the 32nm Medfield/Clovertrail generation will spread far and wide in phones and tablets and Windows 8 will give PCs a buying boost. Truly this is going to be a $50 stock sometime within the next 3-5 years . This stock will start recovering as it did before when it starts surprising again on the upside each quarterly earnings. However before then who knows how far it will drop under all this analyst FUD, perhaps next earnings can stop the rut. The last moving average support is around 20.8. There is also chart support at 20, 19, 18, 16, 15 and 12.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349903485138</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349903668947-172</Id><Title>My fish for you:</Title><Msg>Take this fish and chew upon it: I am a published author. I intend to write a book about the Great Manipulation, the stealing of small investor's money by the big guys. You are seeing it. Any half-way reasonable and intelligent person sees clearly that this supercompany is going to own the chip space in the future, on a time scale of 2014-2015. Only a handful of people, such as Wallis, are stating the facts, and he has been marginalized by the crooks who post in here, into a ranting fool standing on a soap box in Hyde Park. The big boys want in, and they want large positions. They can only do this by shaking the trees and shaking them very hard. They are acting now because they know the earnings will likely not be as disappointing as they are stating they will be via CNBS, and various Vomit Shills around the country. And Ottelini can't say anything---he knows too much and he doesn't want to tip his hand. The big boys have sucked all yo mom's and dad's into AAPL. But as INTC begins to take off, with the Google axis in play, AAPL becomes seriously challenged...c'mon, Samsung does have better galaxy phones than I5. The BIG BOYS get it all...the decline and crash of AAPL and the whole blithering ARMH world, and the rise of the INTC--Google nexus. Take this wisdom and think about it. Mark this post. Sadly, I can only give you this fish. Most of you are so severely retarded that you will never learn to fish for yourselves.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349903668947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:14:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349903835685-173</Id><Topic><Title>Get your picks early</Title><Username>yokoeswt344899</Username><Timestamp>1349880273249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:44:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very informative. Thank you</Msg><Username>luanarbhoj06666</Username><Timestamp>1349903835685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:17:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349904035715-174</Id><Topic><Title>DELL/INTC/BRCM/HPQ/CSCO will file chapter 11 soon, why???</Title><Username>exposecrooks</Username><Timestamp>1349897884490</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:38:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>coming from a kid who has never finished Chapter One of any book he ever tried to read.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349904035715</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:20:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349904212803-175</Id><Topic><Title>Just picked up a thousand shares....</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349898982409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not smart. Every PC stock is tanking and Intel will follow them. Mobile chip margins are miniscule compared to PC and server chips.</Msg><Username>bchen2400</Username><Timestamp>1349904212803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:23:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349904289975-176</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm subscribed. Cool</Msg><Username>jolenemfebt73649</Username><Timestamp>1349904289975</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:24:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349904525467-177</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like to do that sort of thing with goats too! Thanks so much for sharing your dirty little secret!</Msg><Username>drensber</Username><Timestamp>1349904525467</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:28:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349904855023-178</Id><Topic><Title>Just picked up a thousand shares....</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349898982409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've traded this stock for almost 20 years. It is what it is. 4+% dividend with a chance for equity appreciation. But just like every time I've ever bought INTC i will be down right off the bat. The way i will look at it is i did buy 1k shares at $12.50 March 2009 and sold sold at $21.90. I'm buying back cheaper 4 years later. Strong balance sheet, nice dividend. I'll be alright at these prices.</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349904855023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349904984726-179</Id><Topic><Title>My fish for you:</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349903668947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:14:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's original, man, but still idiotic.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1349904984726</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:36:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349905032704-180</Id><Title>What the h@ll just happened?</Title><Msg>Why intc down in the after hour? Serious response only please. it's 21.6 now in AF.</Msg><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349905032704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:37:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349905602759-181</Id><Topic><Title>What the h@ll just happened?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349905032704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:37:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seems to drop suddenly ah recently.. its probably concern related to an earnings announcement from another chip/pc co</Msg><Username>d186282mps</Username><Timestamp>1349905602759</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:46:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349905728229-182</Id><Topic><Title>What the h@ll just happened?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349905032704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:37:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spain's credit has just been downgraded and the S&amp;P futures are down. Intel follows the futures.</Msg><Username>c757172</Username><Timestamp>1349905728229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349905848256-183</Id><Topic><Title>Just picked up a thousand shares....</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349898982409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is what it is ------- BRILLIANT!!! TOOOOO FUNNNNNNY!!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349905848256</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:50:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349905896582-184</Id><Topic><Title>What the h@ll just happened?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349905032704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:37:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New just passed on my screen that Gartner said PC shipments dropped 8% in Q3. Based on the semi's action lately I would figure most of this is priced in. Almost everyday a firm comes out and downgrades INTC and other chip companies which tells me we are near a bottom in the semi's. The holidays are still going to come and people will still buy electronics. I think these guys are buying while they are downgrading. At some point the stock will bounce and these guys who downgrade will own these cheap shares. That's how Wall Street works. These firms are short until almost every analyst has downgraded the stock then they cover and buy your cheap shares. They know people can't take the pain anymore and margin calls hit.</Msg><Username>vincent90157</Username><Timestamp>1349905896582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:51:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349905897076-185</Id><Topic><Title>What the h@ll just happened?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349905032704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:37:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No S&amp;P downgrade was right at the market close time. This drop was just within the last 30 min</Msg><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349905897076</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349905931176-186</Id><Topic><Title>What the h@ll just happened?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349905032704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:37:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I checked but did not see any chi company announce any earning. Any info will help. thanks</Msg><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349905931176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:52:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349906515569-187</Id><Title>Someone Knows Something</Title><Msg>IMO, That's why the Intel is getting slammed in after hours trading</Msg><Username>someoneknowssomething</Username><Timestamp>1349906515569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:01:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349906793181-188</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got it for free. Thank you</Msg><Username>dianggis024565</Username><Timestamp>1349906793181</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:06:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349907035468-189</Id><Title>INTEL IS GOING TO $19-20</Title><Msg>by the end of the month</Msg><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1349907035468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:10:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907816565-190</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL IS GOING TO $19-20</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1349907035468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm still buying all the way down!</Msg><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1349907816565</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:23:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907939276-191</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Continue sharing. Thanks!</Msg><Username>adrianaqomt40304</Username><Timestamp>1349907939276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:25:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349908152141-192</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL IS GOING TO $19-20</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1349907035468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Me too. Intel is way too cheap. Great time to buy.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1349908152141</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:29:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349908594962-193</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL IS GOING TO $19-20</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1349907035468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC could skyrocket, I bought priceline back in 05, 1000 shares @ $21.25 and held, there's something about holding out, at the same time I bought RFMD a chip company in Greensboro NC, 1000 shares in 2000 around $42.00 sh and held, sold at $6.00. You just never know, who would have thought PCLN would be at $602.00 / share.......go figure.</Msg><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1349908594962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:36:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349908731253-194</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL IS GOING TO $19-20</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1349907035468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the chart agrees, and probably sooner than that, but the question is where will it be in a year, is all this "death of the PC" stuff serious, can Intel move into new areas fast enough. On all of that, I dunno.</Msg><Username>whowants2be</Username><Timestamp>1349908731253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:38:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349908794997-195</Id><Topic><Title>INTC on fire in AH! Bodes well for tomorrow!</Title><Username>win_dex_it</Username><Timestamp>1342555393000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-17 16:03:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's financial tare uh rism I tell ya!</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1349908794997</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:39:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349909874198-196</Id><Title>[$$] PC Sales Go Into a Tailspin at The Wall Street Journal06:43pm EDT</Title><Msg>see Yahoo news for Intel</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349909874198</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:57:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349910344300-197</Id><Topic><Title>Someone Knows Something</Title><Username>someoneknowssomething</Username><Timestamp>1349906515569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:01:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's the PC sales report thing that came out after hours. Of course, Chump Street will price it in again. And again. And again. And again. And again. They've priced it in eight times before today. So why wouldn't they just do it again? Of course, Chump Street could have attributed the poor report to the wait for Windows 8 but that's way too rational and like real thinking, and it conflicts with the story that Chump Street is pushing that Intel will be out of business in a couple of weeks and that the internet is dead...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349910344300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:05:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349910449403-198</Id><Topic><Title>$19 coming.....</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1349905640216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:47:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Intel goes to 19, then all other stocks will be down 25% so you can also discount every other stock including the ones you own...so what is your post about? Im buying at these fire sale prices.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349910449403</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349910509089-199</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL IS GOING TO $19-20</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1349907035468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the chart agrees" *** Ah, yes - the chart. The almighty all-knowing, never-erring chart. Yeah, the chart is always right. Hmmmm. Except I wonder why it didn't predict the current downturn???</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349910509089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:08:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349910686070-200</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL IS GOING TO $19-20</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1349907035468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"by the end of the month" *** Well, it's impossible to argue with your argument. Because you didn't make any. I guess they don't teach any of that in shill school. Arguments, logic, analysis, facts, assessments, due diligence, research, etc...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349910686070</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:11:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349910691211-201</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL IS GOING TO $19-20</Title><Username>criticaltolerance</Username><Timestamp>1349907035468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah, yes - the Wallis. The almighty all-knowing, never-erring Wallis. Yeah, the Wallis is always right.... except when he screamed "BUY" at 29! TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349910691211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:11:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349910856833-202</Id><Title>$8 Billion Q3 Revenue Miss Now Priced In</Title><Msg>Getting stupid out there...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349910856833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:14:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349911544457-203</Id><Topic><Title>$8 Billion Q3 Revenue Miss Now Priced In</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349910856833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:14:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Getting stupid out there... -------- You want stooooopid? Here's some SOOOOPER STOOOOOPID..... "Intel is good for 30"-wallis weaver january 2012 "This is gonna be fun"-wallis weaver may 2012 More STOOOOOPID.... wallis weaver recommended INTC as a "buy" at 29. TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349911544457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:25:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349911791307-204</Id><Title>ANOTHER NEW 52-WEEK LOW IN AFTER HOURS!</Title><Msg>GOOOOOOOOOO INTEL!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349911791307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:29:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349911880512-205</Id><Topic><Title>What the h@ll just happened?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349905032704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:37:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you look at the current orders in AH, they're all in the 21.80's. The current bid/ask are based on the last price. There was a bunch of panic selling using market orders based on the PC article. What's left is the common sense people with limit orders.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1349911880512</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:31:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349911958566-206</Id><Topic><Title>$8 Billion Q3 Revenue Miss Now Priced In</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349910856833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:14:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Researchers IDC and Gartner Inc. said PC shipments in the third quarter fell more than 8% from a year earlier..." Now that's funny. A lousy 8 percent drop from a year ago. As reported by the people who have made huge mistakes in predictions in the past. And Wall Street has priced in this big 8 percent drop eight times now!!! And on top of this we have a good reason for the drop - the wait for Windows 8. So, it's unlikely that most of this drop is even permanent. Conclusion: A prediction by people really not good at predictions that has already been priced in 8 times and likely isn't even permanent. I need to file this. Let's see, where's my folder labelled "Dogs That Won't Hunt"?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349911958566</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:32:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349912345703-207</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Intel Corporation (INTC)</Title><Username>charolettemawnb81362</Username><Timestamp>1349879444045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got it. Good job mate.</Msg><Username>twanaiqszf80674</Username><Timestamp>1349912345703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:39:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349912450394-208</Id><Topic><Title>$8 Billion Q3 Revenue Miss Now Priced In</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349910856833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:14:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Conclusion: A prediction by people really not good at predictions ---------- That's YOU, Mr. "Intel is good for 30!!!" TOOOO FUNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349912450394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:40:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349912531410-209</Id><Topic><Title>$8 Billion Q3 Revenue Miss Now Priced In</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349910856833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:14:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has no chip inside Waldo ever not had a buy rec on INTC? The man has no trading skills whatsoever. zero. FWIW, not even the analyst, all of whom have been correct, who downgraded INTC yesterday ,predicted a miss this quarter on the reduced figures provided by INTC when they warned. What he didn't like is potential lower asp's, lower margins going forward.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349912531410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:42:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349912894028-210</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>christopherinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1349912576146</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've NEVER seen Waldo say "take a little off the table here" or "wait for a pullback to buy." Waldo is a perennial mindless pumper.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349912894028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:48:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349913162071-211</Id><Title>Time to buy INTC....here is why</Title><Msg>It is not the only attractively-valued semiconductor manufacturer. Intel (NASDAQ: INTC), recently traded near $23 per share after a 4.3% decline in price over the past year. Intel shares are valued at a compelling 9.6 price-to-earnings ratio, a value which is significantly lower than the 14.1 average of the S&amp;P 500. Shares also trade at a 2.33 price-to-book ratio which is near the 2.05 S&amp;P 500 average. As previously stated, investors should consider this number cheap because the price-to-book ratio fails to account for internally-developed intellectual property including patents, brands, and trademarks. If the economic value of these assets were even partially recorded on the balance sheet the firm's price-to-book ratio would be much lower. Intel's 2.08 price-to-sales ratio is in line with today's prevailing market multiples and does not disconfirm how attractive it is. Intel is also attractive because of its strong balance sheet and commitment to shareholder income. The firm's easily manageable 0.15 debt-to-equity ratio demonstrates that the firm is not overleveraged. This stock pays a hefty 3.97% dividend which is more than twice the 1.64% 10-year treasury yield. Future dividend payments are likely because the company pays out 0.34 of earnings as dividends, so earnings could drop considerably before dividends must be cut.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349913162071</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:52:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349913242237-212</Id><Topic><Title>What the h@ll just happened?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349905032704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:37:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In addition to "yet another bleak PC story" from IDC and Gartner, JPM is recommending clients take a bearish stand on INTC before earnings. Derivatives strategists, Amyn Bharwani and Marko Kolanovic wrote a trading advisory. They are saying that it does not matter what Intel says: "The bank is telling clients that Intel's "bull case does not work, or matter." Intel, a major semiconductor maker, reports earnings next Tuesday." THEY ARE RECOMMENDING: JPM derivatives group also recommeded a BEAR PUT SPREAD: BUY NOV $22 PUT option and SELL NOV $19. This cost 50 cents when recommended and was trading about 70 cents at market close. The net result of a NOV bear put spread would be to put shorting pressure on the stock as the option market maker is encouraged to short shares to hedge possition. "To capitalize on this dour assessment, the strategists told clients to consider buying Intel's November $22 put and selling the November $19 put. The combination of the two creates a put spread that will increase in value if Intel's stock, recently at $21.90, declines to $19." THE COLUMN: The Striking Price | WEDNESDAY, OCTOBER 10, 2012 Trading Intel's Short Circuit By STEVEN M. SEARS | MORE ARTICLES BY AUTHOR Use put options to profit from the chip giant's challenges.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349913242237</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349913256963-213</Id><Topic><Title>$19 coming.....</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1349905640216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:47:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Back up the truck at 19...i'm ready !</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1349913256963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:54:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349914410583-214</Id><Topic><Title>$19 coming.....</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1349905640216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:47:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$19.99 = 4.5% div</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349914410583</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:13:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349914452268-215</Id><Topic><Title>$19 coming.....</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1349905640216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:47:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$19.0 = 4.74% div anything is possible I suppose.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349914452268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:14:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349914472077-216</Id><Topic><Title>$19 coming.....</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1349905640216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:47:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>anything but $30 and $3 eps that is.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349914472077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:14:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349914653815-217</Id><Topic><Title>What the h@ll just happened?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349905032704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:37:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you mean you don't think Obama can assign a Czar to it and fix it?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349914653815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349914789118-218</Id><Topic><Title>Just picked up a thousand shares....</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349898982409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A B O U T time, #$%$ have you been doing(upstairs shaviong?). Do you N O T realize how much fun you are going to have when we march back up to $29 !!!!!! and we announce $3 eps.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349914789118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:19:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349914845490-219</Id><Topic><Title>What the h@ll just happened?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349905032704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:37:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Word leaked out that Hairbawl Doooosh bought today.</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1349914845490</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:20:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349914850600-220</Id><Topic><Title>Just picked up a thousand shares....</Title><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349898982409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$34 by November? what company?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349914850600</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:20:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349914985902-221</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>50 is doable and 40 is almost assured. People don't understand that the economy STINKS but there WILL come a day when it's roaring and Intel will be priced much much higher when the economy is doing well. Not just Intel, but many many stocks will be significantly higher than they are today. Anybody that thinks Intel won't be priced MUCH higher in a roaring economy is pulling your leg or is just clueless.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349914985902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:23:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349915163877-222</Id><Topic><Title>How can things be so BAD after 4 YEARS of Obama?</Title><Username>ih8w8n</Username><Timestamp>1349883910291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:45:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sounds like O.J.'s trial.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349915163877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:26:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349915629116-223</Id><Topic><Title>Congrats longs!!!!!!</Title><Username>tonyclitfon2000</Username><Timestamp>1293116311000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2010-12-23 09:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a window fan that I'd like installed. Can you install it or recommend someone in the Titsville area, Mr. Dooooosh? Are you licensed? Thanx</Msg><Username>titsville_fla</Username><Timestamp>1349915629116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:33:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349915874825-224</Id><Title>Vice presidential debate up next, Romney says ‘I’m not going to raise taxes on anyone’</Title><Msg>What is he going to do? He can't cut programs in the current economy without increasing unemployment and throwing the country back into a recession. He can't move towards a balanced budget without increasing taxes somewhere. He is not being realistic and will say anything to become president.</Msg><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1349915874825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:37:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349916046993-225</Id><Topic><Title>Congrats longs!!!!!!</Title><Username>tonyclitfon2000</Username><Timestamp>1293116311000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2010-12-23 09:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I have a window fan that I'd like installed." You need an HVAC ex-spurt for that! Preferably one who knows nothing about pipe.</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1349916046993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:40:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349916361881-226</Id><Topic><Title>What the h@ll just happened?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349905032704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:37:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, Wall Street's biggest firms working in cooperation. Or collusion. #$%$. Why is Wall Street targeting US manufacturing?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349916361881</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:46:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349916522956-227</Id><Topic><Title>Congrats longs!!!!!!</Title><Username>tonyclitfon2000</Username><Timestamp>1293116311000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2010-12-23 09:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>one who knows nothing about pipe</Msg><Username>titsville_fla</Username><Timestamp>1349916522956</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:48:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349916753658-228</Id><Title>Bo Knows Technology</Title><Msg>Shills not so much. Ever shill comment should start with "My unsupported opinion is..." No support, no logic, no facts, no analysis, no research...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349916753658</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:52:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349917029846-229</Id><Topic><Title>Congrats longs!!!!!!</Title><Username>tonyclitfon2000</Username><Timestamp>1293116311000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2010-12-23 09:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"one who knows nothing about pipe" *** Dunno. Most of the shills seem to know how to put their mouths around one. Wall Street's...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349917029846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:57:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349917115996-230</Id><Topic><Title>Vice presidential debate up next, Romney says ‘I’m not going to raise taxes on anyone’</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1349915874825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He said what was going to happen but you chose not to listen. As he said, he's going to create JOBS. LOTS of them. 12 million more people working means a TON of more taxes being paid. Better jobs paying more means a TON of taxes being paid. Business making more money means MORE taxes being paid. What don't you understand about that, son?</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349917115996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:58:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349917702637-231</Id><Topic><Title>Wally says Balancing the Budget is part of of the job for Democrats</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895506388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:58:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally exposed again as a hypocrite. It's getting old hat, lol.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349917702637</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:08:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349918803493-232</Id><Topic><Title>Bo Knows Technology</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349916753658</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:52:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a shill, someone who constantly pumps a stock hoping others will buy.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349918803493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349918865927-233</Id><Title>Intel may report its first sequential third-quarter sales drop in more than two decades</Title><Msg>According to Bloomberg. See Tonight's Yahoo Intel News for complete article</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349918865927</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:27:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349918998960-234</Id><Title>Ivy Bridge to account for 70 percent of Intel shipments</Title><Msg>[TSMC turns green with envy...] Ivy Bridge 22nm entered production in the first half of 2012, weeks ahead of launch, and at this point Sandy Bridge was accounting for some 70 percent of the market. Ivy Bridge was represented by less than five percent of total Intel market for desktop CPUs in Q1 2012. Already in the second half of 2012 Ivy Bridge market presence climbed to around 30 percent taking most of the market share from Sandy Bridge, a previous generation 32nm that is in sharp decline. Still Sandy Bridge takes almost 50 percent of the whole market even in second half of 2012. In the first half of 2013 it is expected that Ivy Bridge will take more than 70 percent of the market, leaving Sandy Bridge at some 10 percent of market share and Atom fixed at some 5 percent of market. Let’s not forget that a few percent, probably close to 2 percent will always belong to Sandy Bridge E high end parts. In the second half of 2013 Sandy Bridge will almost completely vanish while Ivy Bridge will remain at 60 to 70 percent, but Haswell will start its ramp to dominance that is expected in 1H 2014.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349918998960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:29:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349919022419-235</Id><Topic><Title>Intel may report its first sequential third-quarter sales drop in more than two decades</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349918865927</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yabbut, Weenus Weaver says that INTC has a new FORTRAN compiler optimized for the Xeon PHI.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349919022419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:30:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349919148118-236</Id><Topic><Title>Ivy Bridge to account for 70 percent of Intel shipments</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349918998960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:29:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>70% of a much smaller number shipped.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349919148118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:32:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349919277225-237</Id><Title>Lenovo announces IdeaTab Lynx tablet with Intel Inside</Title><Msg>11.6-inch Windows 8 tablet Lenovo has now officially announced its full lineup of Windows 8 based tablets, ultrabooks and convertible notebooks, including the first dual-core Intel Atom based IdeaTab Lynx. The new IdeaPad Lynx is built around a 11.6-inch IPS screen with 1366x768 resolution and it's based on Intel's new CloverView dual-core Atom CPU working at 1.8GHz. The rest of the specs include 2GB or RAM memory and 32 or 64GB of flash storage. Unlike the rest of the lineup, the IdeaPad Lynx is a more of a traditional tablet that will be available with an optional keyboard dock. Although Lenovo did not reveal any details regarding the battery life of the tablet itself, the did not that it will be able to hold out for up to 16 hours when paired up with the keyboard dock. In addition to the extended battery life, the keyboard dock will also add two USB 2.0 ports. The tablet itself has micro USB, micro HDMI and a microSD card slot. The new IdeaTab Lynx will be available as of October 26th with a price tag set at US $599. The keyboard dock, of course, adds US $149 to the price tag. From Fudzilla</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349919277225</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:34:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349919542389-238</Id><Title>More Intel Windows 8 Tablets Unveiled</Title><Msg>Some branded notebook vendors have lowered the prices of their Windows 7-based notebooks sold through channel operators in the US recently in order to pave the way for the launch of Windows 8 models, according to industry sources. For instance, Acer slashed the price of its 11.6-inch Aspire one to US$249, while Asustek cut the price of some of its 14.1-inch models to US$299, the sources revealed. Meanwhile, vendors including Acer, Lenovo, Asustek Computer, Samsung Electronics and Hewlett-Packard (HP), have all revealed their forthcoming Windows 8-based tablets. Acer has announced the Iconia W700 tablet lineup, which will come with an 11.6-inch IPS panel with a resolution of 1,920 by 1,080 pixels, using Intel's Core i3 or Core i5 CPUs. Industry watchers expect the lineup to start from US$799. Meanwhile, Samsung plans to initially release three Windows 8-based tablets, the Ativ Smart PC, Ativ Smart PC Pro and Ativ Tab. The Ativ Smart PC Pro will be powered by an Intel Core i5 CPU, while the Ativ Smart PC will use an Intel's Atom CPU. HP has also unveiled its Windows 8 tablet, the Elitepad 900, which will come with a 10.1-inch display with a resolution of 1,280 by 800 pixels, powered by an Intel Atom Z2760 processor. Industry watchers expect the model will not be available until the first quarter of 2013.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349919542389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:39:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349919588071-239</Id><Topic><Title>Vice presidential debate up next, Romney says ‘I’m not going to raise taxes on anyone’</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1349915874825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You Puke Liberals can thumbs down it all you want.......but you can't debate it because your boy Obama has created NOTHING. Steve Wynn and lots of other job creators have said that they are not going to hire and some large business owners said said they are gonna lay their employees off and go lay on the beach and retire. This country will be a COMPLETE WRECK is this lazy bum gets 4 more years. But hey, Obama will get to schmooze with rich celebrities for four more years (1 percenters that you claim to hate, yet turn your head when Obama parties with them) and Michelle will get 4 more years of lavish nights out and top shelf booze........then Obama will laugh at all of you and go back to his 1 percent life after partying it up for 8 years. He could care less if the country goes broke because he'll never go broke!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349919588071</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349919758794-240</Id><Title>Ware oh ware oh ware is the FORTRAN COMPILER FOR XEON PHI bounce?</Title><Msg>That was a huge PR, especially on the eve of IDF. THARE IS NO JUSTISS!!!!!!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349919758794</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:42:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349919831393-241</Id><Title>Lenovo launches laptop-tablet hybrids</Title><Msg>Lenovo Group Ltd. Tuesday (Oct. 9) launched a family of Windows laptop-tablet hybrids that the PC vendor hopes will address the needs of both businesses and consumers. The devices, which run either Windows 8 or Windows RT and support touchscreen, are the latest attempt by a PC OEM to bring out devices with new form factors and usage models to suit consumers' increasing preference for computers that are more convenient and flexible than traditional PCs. The hybrids designed to convert from a laptop to a tablet in order to let users take advantage of two usage models. "We think these innovative convertibles are the best devices for a groundbreaking touchscreen experience, plus their multi-modes give people even more ways to use their PC," said Peter Hortensius, president of Lenovo's product group, in a statement. Lenovo's latest hybrids will be available in stores this month, with prices starting at between $549 and $1,099. Lenovo says the ThinkPad Twist offers nearly all-day battery life and tablet-like quick resume from standby. The new offerings include a new incarnation of the venerable ThinkPad brand, the ThinkPad Twist. The Twist features a 12.5-inch screen, a third-generation Intel Core i7 processor and an optional solid-state drive featuring either 500 GB or 128 GB of storage. Lenovo also plans to debut this month the ThinkPad Tablet 2, designed for Windows 8 and powered by an Intel processor. Other new models brought out by Lenovo Tuesday include the IdeaPad Yoga 13, billed as one of the first multi-mode Ultrabooks, featuring a 16.9-mm frame, 13-inch screen, Windows 8, a third-generation Intel Core processor and promising eight hours of battery life. Another model, the Yoga 11, offers an 11-6-inch screen, 15.6-inch frame, Windows RT and Nvidia Corp.'s Tegra 3 quad-core processor. The final new model unveiled Tuesday, the IdeaTab Lynx, is among the first Windows 8 tablets to offer Intel's latest dual-core Atom processor. The device boasts up to 16 hours of battery life. From EETimes</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349919831393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349919980048-242</Id><Title>Intel Enlarging Freescale's Tailpipe</Title><Msg>“We still see Freescale doing very well, but they are losing a little bit of share and Intel is really flying up their tail pipes gaining momentum in networking and comms where a few years ago they weren’t very well positioned,” said Gwennap in an interview with EE Times. Intel has gained sockets as a controller for a growing variety of comms systems, especially as its focus on mobile systems has driven its average CPUs down in power consumption from 60W to less than 30W, Gwennap said. Now the PC giant is making an assault on the so-called data plane, going up against specialized processors that handle packet processing. With its Crystal Forest chip set, Intel recently started a new trend of pairing a standard Xeon server CPU with an integrated comms chip to compete with dedicated network processors in wired systems. “Using the same approach, they can create different companion chips for wireless base stations or other apps,” said Gwennap.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349919980048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:46:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349920039581-243</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Enlarging Freescale's Tailpipe</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349919980048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:46:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“ARM has a very powerful ecosystem, but its big problem in this space has been that its processors have been too wimpy,” said Gwennap.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349920039581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:47:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349920119502-244</Id><Topic><Title>Wally says Balancing the Budget is part of of the job for Democrats</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895506388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:58:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol</Msg><Username>wall.spam</Username><Timestamp>1349920119502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349920309924-245</Id><Topic><Title>More Intel Windows 8 Tablets Unveiled</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349919542389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:39:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. So, I understand this techno-babble. What you have just posted means that INTC is going off a cliff. Tablets are useless to begin with, so let's make them power hungry while we're at it. And, let's distribute them through second tier OEMs. Yeah, that'll work. And, since we're on the subject, let's do an announcement where the parts aren't ready. Wow.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349920309924</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:51:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349920532769-246</Id><Topic><Title>Vice presidential debate up next, Romney says ‘I’m not going to raise taxes on anyone’</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1349915874825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously you do not understand economics. It is demand that creates jobs not lower taxes and regulation. You want to go back to the Bush years. Good luck!</Msg><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1349920532769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:55:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349920665609-247</Id><Title>FORTRAN COMPILER OPTIMIZED FOR XEON PHI!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>On the eve of IDF, no less. The last FORTRAN programmer died in his sleep at the age of 356 twenty years ago.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349920665609</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:57:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349921497345-248</Id><Title>The 8% drop in world PC sales is not good....</Title><Msg>Add to that S&amp;P's downgrade of Spain's credit and we will probably have a FLASH CRASH tomorrow...</Msg><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1349921497345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349923116075-249</Id><Topic><Title>Vice presidential debate up next, Romney says ‘I’m not going to raise taxes on anyone’</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1349915874825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously you don't understand business...........and neither does Obama. Just ask Paul Otelini, Jack Welch, Steve Wynn and man more............they all BLASTED Obama. So you know more than they do? Get real.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349923116075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349925034170-250</Id><Topic><Title>The 8% drop in world PC sales is not good....</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1349921497345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:11:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think what is important to notice about the computer market is STABILITY. The units are going to be in use, replaced and so forth. Intel is not a growth stock in my opinion any longer. That market stability is yet to be tested. I think Intel can hold up under any pressure that may arise there, but the realization is forthcoming.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1349925034170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:10:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349926628543-251</Id><Topic><Title>The 8% drop in world PC sales is not good....</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1349921497345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:11:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Researchers IDC and Gartner Inc. said PC shipments in the third quarter fell more than 8% from a year earlier..." Now that's funny. A lousy 8 percent drop from a year ago. As reported by the people who have made huge mistakes in predictions in the past. And Wall Street has priced in this big 8 percent drop eight times now!!! And on top of this we have a good reason for the drop - the wait for Windows 8. So, it's unlikely that most of this drop is even permanent. Conclusion: A prediction by people really not good at predictions that has already been priced in 8 times and likely isn't even permanent. I need to file this. Let's see, where's my folder labelled "Dogs That Won't Hunt"?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349926628543</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:37:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349927177762-252</Id><Topic><Title>Vice presidential debate up next, Romney says ‘I’m not going to raise taxes on anyone’</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1349915874825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rather have the Bush years than the Obama years anytime.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1349927177762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:46:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349927658837-253</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian please do this board a favor and keep debunking Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349895237593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One thing for sure: the days of "cheap" ARM SoCs is history - there will be rude awakening for the fabless guys. Furthermore you will have VIP customers like AAPL and second tier customers like NVDA - when you look at TSMC capex projections you will notice manufacturing is certainly a BIG issue and concern. As an ARMs dealer I love those (capex clueless) Intel bashers - Way,, way back I visited two TI fabs (was still DRAM back than) - I don't tink the ARM fan boys "appreciate" TI's most recent decision - oh yeah TI exited the DRAM business...</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1349927658837</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>