<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343105701000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's 2012 Campaign slogan:</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1343100790000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 23:33:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We're gonna build roads and bridges, America !!!!! The US does not even qualify as a third level country - the US barley matches former Communist East Germany when it comes to infrastructure ...just like healthcare you stupid morons don't know any better because you never made it to Europe... you're thick as a brick... http://www.autobahn-online.de/images/gallerie_e.html</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1343105701000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 00:55:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343105970000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's 2012 Campaign slogan:</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1343100790000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 23:33:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't like Obama. I was being Sarcastic. Self-absorbed geeks like you that never get laid can't understand sarcasm.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1343105970000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 00:59:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343106021000-3</Id><Topic><Title>"we are unlikely to see 20nm phones and tablets anytime soon..."</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1343093231000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 21:27:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are going to have to wait awhile for the smartphone with 24" screen. The screen consumes too much power. Battery life is a no-go.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1343106021000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:00:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343106093000-4</Id><Title>Romney is a COWARD...</Title><Msg>Let's call a spade a spade: Romney is a coward. He's shown it from his youth, and still puts it on display every day. It's not the draft deferments by themselves--lots of people did that. It's that he participated in demonstrations supporting the draft, saying that others should fight and die, but not him. It's the bullying incident with the kid at the prep school. It's his unwillingness to confront and denounce ugly statements made by those within his own party. It's guiding his sons around the military, while encouraging the country to participate in unnecessary military actions. A true chicken hawk in every respect--with the emphasis on CHICKEN. (Comparing him to Obama or Clinton would be silly; Obama came of draft age when there was no longer a draft and we weren't involved in a war, while Romney opted out during the height of hostilities--a war that he openly supported. And at least Clinton wasn't a hypocrite about the war.) Those who believe that our national leader should be a true cringing, yellow-bellied coward should support Romney for president.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343106093000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:01:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343106476000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's 2012 Campaign slogan:</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1343100790000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 23:33:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney's 2012 Campaign Slogan: We're going to build roads and bridges in the Cayman Islands!</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343106476000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:07:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343106818000-6</Id><Title>Romney is a DRAFT DODGER PUSSYBOY...</Title><Msg>Eat this Republiscum: http://www.salon.com/2012/06/07/romney_dodged_the_draft/</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343106818000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:13:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343107362000-7</Id><Title>TSMC's Chang cuts forecast, sees stall coming</Title><Msg>http://eetimes.com/electronics-news/4390786/Morris-Chang-cuts-forecast</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1343107362000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343108352000-8</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC's Chang cuts forecast, sees stall coming</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1343107362000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:22:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yepper! good catch! chang anticipates the tsmc revenue loss when intel designs cannibalize smart phone &amp; tablet sales. expect qcom and nvda to strike back by lowering tdp by 25% by editing their online data sheet specs. visit Lucy, TN for a day or an hour. family fun!!!</Msg><Username>lucyfer_tooofunnny_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343108352000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:39:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343114605000-9</Id><Title>Are you concerned with declining triangle formation?</Title><Msg>Short term problem is a triangle formation that has declining tops since May and base a bit lower than 25 that is about to break any week now the way it is going. The typical theory suggests a drop sub 25 for good. I think if that happens it opens the door for 21 worse case total breakdown in the traditional triangle formation high to base to low sense (29-25-21) but its too cheap in value for intel to drop even sub 24. In any case i dont buy TA patterns very much in general as a lot of it is charlatan bs (eg Elliot wave theory give me a break) but those that indicate declining tops and common base are kind of rational to interpret as reduced ability to rally and improved stress on the support level base until it finally breaks down. Intel is in a bad spot in terms of all the attacks received left and right and global economic stupidity of leaders to create solutions that focus on growth instead of austerity without a future. Intel itself is doing a great job as a company given all the stress. For near term i view the pattern as risk unless we could rally over 26 very soon again to break the pattern. If we rally here and dont even go as high as 26 and then drop again prepare for very bad drop. I dont like how this looks and i am objective, i have hedged sub 25 with puts bought over 26 but i have uncapped core position if we rally and break out. However i remain skeptical here. In any other case the drop sub 25 today would be a buy signal by the way but the triangle stress is putting things in a different perspective near term. Bottom line i am not very happy near term here even if valuation is a steal. Probably a chance to sell puts short if it gets ugly below 25. I still see Intel over 29 later this year.</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1343114605000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 03:23:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343127848000-10</Id><Topic><Title>ARM grabs TSMC's 3D FinFETs for future 64-bit PC brains</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1343075208000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 16:26:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh they got it right on -- from a press release. It is an IT gossip site. Glad you checked your sources. I have read some of your other posts and you are a ding dong. Your time here is brilliantly spent.</Msg><Username>semiconductorguy</Username><Timestamp>1343127848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 07:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343128117000-11</Id><Title>How many people read this group?</Title><Msg>Just curious. Lots of activity but very little content. Post a quick one here for a count.</Msg><Username>semiconductorguy</Username><Timestamp>1343128117000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 07:08:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343130350000-12</Id><Title>intel not trading in the pre market?</Title><Msg>halted maybe? i don't see any news.</Msg><Username>varlabania</Username><Timestamp>1343130350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 07:45:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343133818000-13</Id><Topic><Title>At Last It Makes Sense</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1343102370000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 23:59:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you may be on to something.</Msg><Username>StockJock44</Username><Timestamp>1343133818000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:43:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343134433000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis Weaver Aliases</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1342624283000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-07-18 11:11:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Add "StockJock44" to the list.</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343134433000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:53:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>28</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343136261000-15</Id><Title>Intel vindicated by TSMC/ARM announcement</Title><Msg>ARM and TSMC are teaming up to optimize next-generation 64-bit ARM cores for FinFET process technology. And that must be leaving Intel feeling rather smug. After all, it completely validates what the chip behemoth said at its investor day -- in both Paul Otellini's and Brian Krzanich's presentations – that Intel is a good four years ahead of its closest foundry competition. Indeed, as my colleague Peter Clarke notes over in his article, the collaboration between the Taiwanese manufacturer and ARM isn’t even expected to yield introductory results much before the second half of 2015, and that is probably an optimistic bet. Furthermore, the announcement serves to show just how far behind ARM will be in terms of making any sort of serious impact on the server market. ARM has repeatedly said it would have a serious server market offering by 2014, and would be able to capture meaningful market share within two to three years, but this latest announcement throws a whole lot of cold water on that notion. If ARM’s latest press release represents the current state of things, it means 64-bit V8 architecture on FinFET process tech is roughly three and a half years away at best, giving Intel ample time to work out all its current kinks and remain far out ahead of its competition. The announcement also means TSMC may be re-setting its strategy for FinFet (tri-gate), after it had previously told the market it would target second generation 20nm. Today’s press release reads like the manufacturer has had to adjust the plan to sub-20nm, though whether TSMC jumped or was pushed is easily debatable. “There’s no doubt that based on current plans of record, Intel’s way ahead of any other company with regard to FinFET deployment,” said industry analyst Nathan Brookwood of Insight64. “They’re shipping millions of devices with 3-D transistors today, but TSMC and Globalfoundries don’t plan to introduce the technology until their 14nm nodes, at least four years away with regard to volume production. I hear both companies want to pull that technology in, but that’s where things stand today.” http://www.eetimes.com/electronics-blogs/other/4390922/Intel-vindicated-by-TSMC-ARM-announcement</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1343136261000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:24:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343136504000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Intel vindicated by TSMC/ARM announcement</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1343136261000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:24:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM has repeatedly said it would have a serious server market offering by 2014, and would be able to capture meaningful market share within two to three years, but this latest announcement throws a whole lot of cold water on that notion. If ARM’s latest press release represents the current state of things, it means 64-bit V8 architecture on FinFET process tech is roughly three and a half years away at best, giving Intel ample time to work out all its current kinks and remain far out ahead of its competition. [If only these two paragraphs could be shrunk down to a single phrase that could be tattooed on Wall Street's forehead in mirror image...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1343136504000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:28:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343136731000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a DRAFT DODGER PUSSYBOY...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343106818000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:13:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your meltdown isdisgusting to waTCH. wHAT ARE YOU DOING ON A STOCK THREAD?</Msg><Username>tiderunner3</Username><Timestamp>1343136731000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343136823000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a DRAFT DODGER PUSSYBOY...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343106818000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:13:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please excuse my sloppy post. Your meltdown is disgusting to watch. What are you doing on a stock thread?</Msg><Username>tiderunner3</Username><Timestamp>1343136823000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:33:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343137083000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a DRAFT DODGER PUSSYBOY...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343106818000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:13:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eat it GOP scumbaggg. Romney is a draft dodger. 4 deferments and he was in France. France? That will be funny when the Chicago gang runs their attacks on 30 second spots.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1343137083000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:38:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343137289000-20</Id><Title>ARE YOU READY FOR THE DROP, HAVE SOLD SOME OR PROTECTED YOUR SHARE</Title><Msg>Are you ready for the drop, have sold some or protected your share</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1343137289000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343137426000-21</Id><Title>Wait until they show proof that ROmney draft dodger has tax evasion.</Title><Msg>It is coming. Then there is the problem with the full time girlfriend that will come out. You rightwing idiots should have never run this rich-boy scumbag. He is a liar, but you know that, but the video clips showing his with all his lies the last few weeks of the campaign will take him down. Him sitting in France while the poor working class kids from the midwest were fighting and being killed in Vietnam, it will be funny. 4 deferments for Romney and he lied about it multiple times and those clips are coming too.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1343137426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343137581000-22</Id><Title>TI's earns and outlook not good for INTC</Title><Msg>TI's earns and outlook not good for INTC, Next Q is going to be bad</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1343137581000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343137585000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Wait until they show proof that ROmney draft dodger has tax evasion.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1343137426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:43:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where was obama?</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1343137585000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:46:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343137639000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Wait until they show proof that ROmney draft dodger has tax evasion.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1343137426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:43:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was 10 years old you idiot.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1343137639000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:47:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343137963000-25</Id><Title>of course OB is going to rip Romney some new holes.</Title><Msg>When this thing is over, Romney will move back to France. Draft dodger RomneyBO? YES Tax evader? YES Outsource American jobs to China did Romney? YES Ride with a dog on his roof? YES lie about everything you can imagine? YES I really do think his draft dodging is going to hurt his severly in the Midwest because they do not much like super Richboy Mormon anyhow, so when they see he is a draft dodger sitting in France, that will cost him BIG! Of course--the girlfriend thing should come the last week and that will be the funniest thing for Mormon boy.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1343137963000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:52:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343138508000-26</Id><Topic><Title>At Last It Makes Sense</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1343102370000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 23:59:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Wally, he keeps arguing with Wall Street, thus, he gets no where.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1343138508000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:01:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343138736000-27</Id><Topic><Title>ARM grabs TSMC's 3D FinFETs for future 64-bit PC brains</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1343075208000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 16:26:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DESPERATE !!!! Again you can't comment on anything in the article !!!! Why do you hide behind multiple aliases ?? You've a WEAK constitution dnenni !!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1343138736000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343138892000-28</Id><Topic><Title>At Last It Makes Sense</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1343102370000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 23:59:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the only thing more pathetic is the tail sniffing lucy that follows him around. TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUUUUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYY</Msg><Username>lucyfer_tooofunnny_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343138892000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:08:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343139291000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Wait until they show proof that ROmney draft dodger has tax evasion.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1343137426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:43:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No stupid, where was he during his serving age years? You guys are nuts.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1343139291000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:14:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343139932000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Wait until they show proof that ROmney draft dodger has tax evasion.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1343137426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:43:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical Liberal. Out of control, angry, drool from the lip..........and a total hypocrite. You guys are a complete disgrace to all humans. Meanwhile, Michelle Obama drinks every bottle of top shelf liquor in site and prays for another 4-years of shopping and partying.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1343139932000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:25:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343139967000-31</Id><Topic><Title>TI's earns and outlook not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1343137581000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has made their forecasts and has factored all this into its forecasts. Intel has met or exceeded current quarter forecast for the last two years. What new light does the TI earnings show that Intel was not aware of last week? Q2Q, TI saw increases in Analog divisions but their wireless business evaporated. TI is expecting a -20% impact from buying National Semi to Q3 revenues. They are seeing customer caution and its impact on orders late in the quarter. Intel has a slightly differnt product mix and Intel has no hit to earnings from absorbing a purchase like National Semi. "TI revenue in the second quarter was about as we had expected," said Rich Templeton, TI's chairman, president and CEO. "Our Analog and Embedded Processing segments grew sequentially, while our Wireless segment declined. http://investor.ti.com/releasedetail.cfm?ReleaseID=694362 Embedded revenue was down q2q by -15% Wireless revenue was down q2q by -39% (ARM CPU)</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1343139967000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:26:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343140113000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Intel vindicated by TSMC/ARM announcement</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1343136261000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:24:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome. Server $$$$$ is where it's at. ARMH will be dead before they ever get to 64 bit.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1343140113000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:28:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343141128000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis Weaver Aliases</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1342624283000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-07-18 11:11:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Adding "att4glte" to the list. never forget that wallis is ALWAYS here.</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343141128000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:45:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>59</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343141362000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Wait until they show proof that ROmney draft dodger has tax evasion.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1343137426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:43:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you do not deny the facts. Not too many undecided would like your posts. Romney outsourced american jobs to China He made huge money and is hiding his tax returns. He took 4 draft deferments to avoid service in the Vetnam war. At leadt Kerry went over there. And OB was 10 years old you idiot so do not ask why he was not in Nam. He was for healthcare in Mass but now is against it. He was pro choice and now he is against it. Romney has a plan so tell us 4 points for his plan for turning around the economy. Be specific please. Good luck because he has not given the points.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1343141362000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343141380000-35</Id><Title>Can INTC Hold 25 Today?</Title><Msg>The Magic 8-Ball sez: "NO WAY!"</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343141380000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:49:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>30</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343141500000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Wait until they show proof that ROmney draft dodger has tax evasion.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1343137426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:43:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has lost the undecided vote, and that will be the dagger for him. I can't wait until your idiotic posts stop in November. You are a known whacko that responds to his own posts under different aliases AND has aliases that are CLEARLY gay. You f-ing gay liberal loser. Scum.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1343141500000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343141874000-37</Id><Topic><Title>Five Buck Miss</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1343055551000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 10:59:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is a huge honking $5 miss now priced in, Walldork?</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343141874000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:57:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>28</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343142141000-38</Id><Title>Insiders dumping,They have sold 65% of shares held and still selling</Title><Msg>Insiders dumping,They have sold 65% of shares held and still selling</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1343142141000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:02:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343142270000-39</Id><Title>Insiders dumping looks like they know something</Title><Msg>Insiders dumping looks like they know something</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1343142270000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:04:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343142350000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Alexander --- what is the dollar amount of the ...</Title><Username>win_dex_it</Username><Timestamp>1343058980000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 11:56:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job, Alexander. Perhaps you are actually related to Alexander Hamilton after all, but you acquired your family name through an unfortunate sort of romantic liason somewhere back there in the family tree? So I guess one could say that 832 million is chump change to Intel, but bear in mind that is just the current projection of the unfunded obligations --- that these things tend to get worse over time as the plan administrators either can't meet their projections on portfolio returns or (perhaps worse) they end up chasing yield by getting snookered into buying crap like mortgage backed securities in 2007. (I am not suggesting Intel is or will ever be doing stuff like this, I just think it's interesting that the LIBOR fixing was another part of the scheme to create a market for the "financial innovation" by forcing pension funds to seek higher returns in what later became known as "toxic assets". P.T. Barnum's estimate as to the birth rat of suckers was way too low IMO.)</Msg><Username>win_dex_it</Username><Timestamp>1343142350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:05:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343142380000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Intel vindicated by TSMC/ARM announcement</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1343136261000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:24:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HONK! HONK! RAMP! RAMP! PUMP! PUMP! GOOD FOR $30! GOOD FOR $30! RAH! RAH!</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343142380000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343142648000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Intel vindicated by TSMC/ARM announcement</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1343136261000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:24:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If only these two paragraphs could be shrunk down to a single phrase that could be tattooed on Wall Street's forehead in mirror image...] ---------- Wouldn't it be much more painless to just have them tattoo "GOOD FOR 30" on their foreheads, pumpwad?</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343142648000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:10:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343142751000-43</Id><Title>Insiders selling get ready for the drop</Title><Msg>Insiders selling get ready for the drop</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1343142751000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343143616000-44</Id><Topic><Title>Insiders selling get ready for the drop</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1343142751000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:12:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the little red hen cried "the sky is falling, the sky is falling....." Intel is just fine, and you scare no one.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1343143616000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:26:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343143873000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Insiders selling get ready for the drop</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1343142751000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:12:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There has been some insider selling. One director (Frank Yeary) sold 639 shares to pay taxes on a vesting RSU option and then exercised the option. He holds the shares. 639 shares is not exactly a significant quantity. http://www.secform4.com/insider-trading/50863.htm</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1343143873000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:31:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343144249000-46</Id><Title>Market Way Overpriced</Title><Msg>Mkt is holding up still on the pretext of QE3. It aint gonna help at all. The Fiscal Cliff uncertainity and the tug of war between Obama and the Repubs is gonna f@#k us all in the end.</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1343144249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343144426000-47</Id><Title>RTQ $24.98</Title><Msg>77777777777777777777</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343144426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:40:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343144792000-48</Id><Topic><Title>Insiders selling get ready for the drop</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1343142751000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:12:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Over 4 Mil shares sold in 25 trans, That is over 65% of shares held by insiders and they are still selling big time, Get ready for the the big drop</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1343144792000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:46:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343146100000-49</Id><Topic><Title>New Highs?</Title><Username>brinncie230</Username><Timestamp>1343140377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice Post</Msg><Username>curranppz885</Username><Timestamp>1343146100000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:08:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343146772000-50</Id><Title>TIC,TOC are you ready for the drop, insider selling big time</Title><Msg>TIC,TOC are you ready for the drop, insider selling big time</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1343146772000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343146844000-51</Id><Topic><Title>RTQ $24.98</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343144426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:40:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343146844000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:20:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343147779000-52</Id><Topic><Title>Intel vindicated by TSMC/ARM announcement</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1343136261000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:24:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC plate is more than full: FinFet EUV and 450 mm - 3 major changes pretty much at the same time. They will have to do FinFet and EUV on 300mm but by that time 450 mm might be ready - IOW "shortly" they would be forced to make a move to 450mm. TSMC is reactive and proactive Intel will eventually start using EUV @ 10nm; me thinks Intel will first scale up to 450 mm</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1343147779000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:36:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343147864000-53</Id><Title>Eat your heart out TSMC...</Title><Msg>So, while TSMC and everyone else is sweating out 28/32nm, Intel is actually DEMOLITIONING 32nm fabs!! Not upgradng, not mothballing....Intel is throwing 32nm in the trash can! Amazing. Glen Yeung – Citigroup Inc. Got it. All right, thanks. And as a follow up, maybe for Stacy, looking at the gross margin guidance and looking at your reconciliation in the printed commentary, it sounded like the only negative impact to gross margins in Q3 would be these other cost of sales, and I wonder if you could just explain what’s going on in there? Stacy J. Smith Sure. What’s going on with other cost of sales in Q3 as we are finding some opportunities to take some 32-nanometer capacity offline. They’re relatively small today, but it’s just a result of the lower demand expectations on the year. And so we are taking some of those factories off and so you will see a little bit of demolition costs and some of those things that flows through other cost of sales. And, yeah, it’s not huge, it’s between half a point and a point, but it’s a bit of an offset in gross margin in the third quarter.</Msg><Username>semiwiz2002</Username><Timestamp>1343147864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:37:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343148171000-54</Id><Title>Intel making Apple parts</Title><Msg>Absolutely no discussion/speculation about Intel making the Apple parts recently. That is simply something that must happen. What happens when this is revealed ot the maorket?</Msg><Username>semiwiz2002</Username><Timestamp>1343148171000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:42:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343149671000-55</Id><Title>Wow, this board's cleaned up. Nice</Title><Msg>No Lucy, nobody conversing with Lucy. Very nice.</Msg><Username>lucy_died</Username><Timestamp>1343149671000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343149947000-56</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, this board's cleaned up. Nice</Title><Username>lucy_died</Username><Timestamp>1343149671000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:07:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/businessinsider/~3/-MScqZ0eBFo/harry-dent-baby-bust-dow-3000-2012-7</Msg><Username>loordo</Username><Timestamp>1343149947000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:12:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343150430000-57</Id><Topic><Title>TI's earns and outlook not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1343137581000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wireless revenue was down q2q by -39% (ARM CPU) that's pretty dramatic - I suppose Kindle tablet</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1343150430000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343150603000-58</Id><Topic><Title>RTQ $24.98</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343144426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:40:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$24.98 that's almost 30.</Msg><Username>wallisweiner</Username><Timestamp>1343150603000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:23:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343150939000-59</Id><Title>Summer Swoon in Progress</Title><Msg>Back to 26 in November. TOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343150939000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:28:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343151400000-60</Id><Topic><Title>The Intel Bounce begins tomorrow.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1342141581000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-12 21:06:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After close--Tuesday, Intel 58 cents a share. Intel UP Wednesday, Intel closes over 28.00 Like the idiots who bad mouthed Intel for three months never were there. 30 two weeks later. ------------ Silly pumpwad! TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343151400000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:36:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343151427000-61</Id><Title>Time to sell semi's as growth slows.</Title><Msg>Fallen out of favor and the selling has begun.</Msg><Username>donzi1822</Username><Timestamp>1343151427000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:37:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343151543000-62</Id><Topic><Title>TI's earns and outlook not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1343137581000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazon smoked their but with their new device that apple is coming out with a smaller and cheaper IPAD.</Msg><Username>donzi1822</Username><Timestamp>1343151543000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:39:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343151780000-63</Id><Topic><Title>Can INTC Hold 25 Today?</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343141380000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:49:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Magic 8-Ball is ALWAYS right! The Magic 8-Ball ROOOOOOOOLZ! TOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343151780000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:43:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343152043000-64</Id><Topic><Title>70% of CNBC polled said Obama</Title><Username>liberalsrwacked</Username><Timestamp>1343151839000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:43:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I voted 143 times!!!!</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1343152043000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:47:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343153301000-65</Id><Title>CNBC viewers must have liked the BOOSH market</Title><Msg>and his socialism... guess they do not like the DOW up 100% under the majic negro</Msg><Username>marcymartin23</Username><Timestamp>1343153301000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:08:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343153552000-66</Id><Topic><Title>Time to sell semi's as growth slows.</Title><Username>donzi1822</Username><Timestamp>1343151427000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lillte late dude !</Msg><Username>marcymartin23</Username><Timestamp>1343153552000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:12:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343153621000-67</Id><Title>what is the point in owning INTC ...?</Title><Msg>this stock does nothing</Msg><Username>marcymartin23</Username><Timestamp>1343153621000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343153661000-68</Id><Title>CNBC VIEWERS ARE DUM</Title><Msg>THEY LISTEN TO MARIA AND CRREMER</Msg><Username>marcymartin23</Username><Timestamp>1343153661000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:14:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343154005000-69</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC VIEWERS ARE DUM</Title><Username>marcymartin23</Username><Timestamp>1343153661000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:14:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah Cramer said buy INTC and it dropped the next 3 days. never fear, Wally promised $30-50.00</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1343154005000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:20:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343154344000-70</Id><Topic><Title>Twin Turd Alert!</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1321887477000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-11-21 09:57:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOOK OUT BELOW!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343154344000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:25:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343154470000-71</Id><Topic><Title>Market Way Overpriced</Title><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1343144249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://stockcharts.com/h-sc/ui?s=SPY&amp;p=D&amp;b=5&amp;g=0&amp;id=p69848300965 market's got overbght on the Oscillators at the former highs, a lower high for INTC of course, as INTC acknowledged that it's a slower world out there.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1343154470000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343154760000-72</Id><Title>RTQ 24.89</Title><Msg>A huge honking $5 miss is priced in. Intel will be 30 next week! TOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343154760000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:32:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343155338000-73</Id><Title>sell it all. China slow down 60%.. could lose 50%.. ouch</Title><Msg>yep yep</Msg><Username>hutchpics</Username><Timestamp>1343155338000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:42:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343155788000-74</Id><Title>Rumor Congress Will Support Stopping the Requirement to Use Ethanol in Gasoline</Title><Msg>OMG do they actually have a brain?! Ethanol will use up to 72% of the corn crop if this corruption continues!</Msg><Username>yourbestfriendshelly</Username><Timestamp>1343155788000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:49:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343155946000-75</Id><Title>Intel Porting Android 4.1 to Work on Atom Tablets, Smartphones</Title><Msg>http://www.pcworld.com/article/259737/intel_porting_android_41_to_work_on_atom_tablets_smartphones.html</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1343155946000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:52:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343155997000-76</Id><Topic><Title>Market Way Overpriced</Title><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1343144249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is bs! "way" REALLY??? Markets are not overpriced at all across the board. Valuations are ridiculous for stocks like intel. It may be that it looks uninspiring technically (triangle etc) and we may mini crash with all the bs doom about global economy and moronic Merkel etc but this is just the stupidity that creates unreal entry points not an overvalued market. For real man are you actually paying attention to valuations or just your positions benefit??? Intel is priced as if it has only 10 years of life left. Are you serious you can see intel as overvalued? And after intel you have many others too that are not exactly of stellar PEs that are not going anywhere anytime. I wont be shocked to see intel at 21 due to how moronic people are in their abilities to solve global problems but look at the SP500 PE here and look what it was past 20 years and tell me its overvalued now. Diclosure i am making a nice profit if we drop to 24 or 23 here but really i cannot for a moment claim Intel deserves this bs! http://www.multpl.com/ http://www.multpl.com/table You see it is near a 30 year low area. The risk here is that the market drops 60-70% over 10 years. The upside risk is &gt;1000% if they get it together and save capitalism for another 50 years by doing exactly what it takes to attack corruption and unethical money culture practices under the stress of a revolution any year now. To be out of stocks like intel in core position here is tremendously unacceptable. Only with derivatives you can protect from cash not from selling a core position of such undervalued stock. That said i am always 50% in cash or more. But overpriced?</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1343155997000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343156642000-77</Id><Title>Intel and Google working closely togethere.</Title><Msg>http://www.pcworld.com/article/259737/intel_porting_android_41_to_work_on_atom_tablets_smartphones.html#tk.rss_news This could really push Intel deep into mobile products. I'm especially interested in smartphones using Intel. Tablets are not that interesting to me. An ultrabook will make owning a tablet unnecessary.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1343156642000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:04:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343156716000-78</Id><Title>Wallfart and His Aliases Called for $30</Title><Msg>TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343156716000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:05:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343156934000-79</Id><Topic><Title>Intel and Google working closely togethere.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1343156642000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For Intel a superficial scratch would be deep since they have ZERO presence in mobile now. How did the morons who run the company miss the boat so badly. Derelict management!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343156934000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:08:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343157076000-80</Id><Title>RTQ 24.80</Title><Msg>That's almost 30!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343157076000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:11:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343157188000-81</Id><Topic><Title>RTQ 24.80</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343157076000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:11:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's almost 30 if you add the HUGE HONKING $5 miss that's already priced in!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343157188000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:13:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343157439000-82</Id><Topic><Title>26, 27, 28, 29</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1337952897000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-25 09:34:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You haven't mentioned the "House O Pain" lately, Wallazzzzzzzzzzzzz. Maybe because it's your new address and you don't like it?</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343157439000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343157446000-83</Id><Topic><Title>Intel and Google working closely togethere.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1343156642000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't Google TV supposed to be out soon? Isn't that supposed to be a big "design win" for Intel, Paul?</Msg><Username>win_dex_it</Username><Timestamp>1343157446000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:17:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343157610000-84</Id><Topic><Title>Intel and Google working closely togethere.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1343156642000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google TV --------- Shirley, you jest.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343157610000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:20:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343157733000-85</Id><Topic><Title>Intel and Google working closely togethere.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1343156642000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Shirley, you jest." Not joking, per se. Don't call me Shirley, Percy.</Msg><Username>win_dex_it</Username><Timestamp>1343157733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:22:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343158230000-86</Id><Title>"These are not the droids you were looking for..."</Title><Msg>The mainstream media are becoming laughable. They are shameless as they try to put the shine on the Democrats' shinola: "The economy would be booming if it weren't for Europe..." Go INTC!</Msg><Username>IH8W8N</Username><Timestamp>1343158230000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:30:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343158251000-87</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, this board's cleaned up. Nice</Title><Username>lucy_died</Username><Timestamp>1343149671000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:07:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The same guy in that link that you provided that said we are headed for Dow 3000............wrote a book in 1999 saying the DOW would hit 21-35k by the year 2008...LOL! That is a FACT. The sad part is that CNBC just gave this greedy SOB a platform to sell himself yet again, and didn't even do any research so as to call him out yesterday about his idiotic call back in 1999. Only in America.</Msg><Username>lucy_died</Username><Timestamp>1343158251000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:30:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343158358000-88</Id><Title>Under Obama, bad news IS good news!</Title><Msg>Everything is all upside down because reality is not kind to implemented Leftist policies. Go INTC!</Msg><Username>IH8W8N</Username><Timestamp>1343158358000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:32:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343158887000-89</Id><Title>Obamacare/Tax WILL DESTROY EVEN MORE JOBS...</Title><Msg>...and the zombies among us still chant: "Yes, we can!" Yes, we can be ignorant. Yes, we can blame the "rich" for our own problems. Yes, we can sign up for food stamps. Yes, we can gut welfare reform; Obama recently unilaterally rescinded work requirements. Yes, we can grow the deficit. Five years of $1 Trillion dollar deficits - thank you, Democrat Nancy Pelosi and Democrat-controlled Congress from 2007-2010. Wake up, America! Reality is not kind to societies with implemented Leftist agendas.</Msg><Username>IH8W8N</Username><Timestamp>1343158887000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:41:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343159065000-90</Id><Topic><Title>I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1293550442000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-12-28 10:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cisco down 6% today. LOL Cisco's good for 15.</Msg><Username>lucy_died</Username><Timestamp>1343159065000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:44:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343159083000-91</Id><Topic><Title>Under Obama, bad news IS good news!</Title><Username>IH8W8N</Username><Timestamp>1343158358000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:32:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch the economy come back to life - as it did under Reagan - if common sense conservative fiscal policy is brought back into style. Let's send the whacko Leftist packing in November...or watch this great country turn into a Cuba or a Kenya. Go INTC!</Msg><Username>IH8W8N</Username><Timestamp>1343159083000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:44:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343159147000-92</Id><Title>Cisco down 6% today Lucy, 25% since you bought</Title><Msg>LOL http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_I/threadview?m=tm&amp;bn=9609&amp;tid=1136365&amp;mid=1136365&amp;tof=2&amp;frt=2</Msg><Username>lucy_died</Username><Timestamp>1343159147000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343159714000-93</Id><Title>Lucy's Cisco trade on FIRE! Bodes well....</Title><Msg>...... for anyone that detests him.</Msg><Username>lucy_died</Username><Timestamp>1343159714000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:55:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343159794000-94</Id><Title>New Message Board Test</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/mb/AAPL/</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343159794000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343160199000-95</Id><Title>cnbc perpetuates false rumor of fed stimulus</Title><Msg>Same old same old.</Msg><Username>hiowl123</Username><Timestamp>1343160199000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:03:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343160272000-96</Id><Title>cnbc now admits they premeditated false and misleading rumors</Title><Msg>Same old same old/</Msg><Username>hiowl123</Username><Timestamp>1343160272000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:04:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343160342000-97</Id><Topic><Title>cnbc perpetuates false rumor of fed stimulus</Title><Username>hiowl123</Username><Timestamp>1343160199000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:03:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you perpetuate what may be false rumor about what may be false rumor. Same old, same old.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343160342000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343160349000-98</Id><Topic><Title>Under Obama, bad news IS good news!</Title><Username>IH8W8N</Username><Timestamp>1343158358000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:32:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4 more yrs. with obama, this great country will be in trouble. Got to go with a new approach.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1343160349000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:05:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343160551000-99</Id><Title>Looks Like The New Message Board Format</Title><Msg>will feature a rating system based on popularity or number of views. I LIKE THAT! TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343160551000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:09:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343161387000-100</Id><Topic><Title>Can INTC Hold 25 Today?</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343141380000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:49:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two Cocky Clowns blow another call and try blame it on the Magic 8 Ball...It's called Karma and knowing to never make a promise you can't keep.</Msg><Username>san_warzone</Username><Timestamp>1343161387000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343161426000-101</Id><Topic><Title>Looks Like The New Message Board Format</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343160551000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cisco down 25% since you sold Intel to buy it, Intel up 25% since then. That makes you down a whopping 50% on that fiasco. LOL! Enjoy the popularity...</Msg><Username>lucy_died</Username><Timestamp>1343161426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343161770000-102</Id><Topic><Title>Looks Like The New Message Board Format</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343160551000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like you've been suckin' on Wally's lollipop and some of his dna seeped into your walnut-sized brain. TOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343161770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:29:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343161983000-103</Id><Topic><Title>Looks Like The New Message Board Format</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343160551000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd probably hide behind my "tooofunnny" alias, too, if I got caught pumping Cisco at 20 and dumping Intel at 20. LOL!</Msg><Username>lucy_died</Username><Timestamp>1343161983000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:33:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343162288000-104</Id><Title>INTC TANKING AFTER HOURS ON AAPL REPORT</Title><Msg>TOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343162288000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:38:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343162472000-105</Id><Title>RTQ 24.80</Title><Msg>Please pay attention, lemmings.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343162472000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:41:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343162489000-106</Id><Title>Intel earnings much better than Apple.</Title><Msg>Intel's earnings for Q2 and guidance for Q3 suddenly looking alot better after Apple's report. Expectations just way too high for Apple. Intel continues to have a much better chance of beating long term expectations. Apple's new valuation will seem much higher.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1343162489000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343162933000-107</Id><Topic><Title>Looks Like The New Message Board Format</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1343160551000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Enjoy the popularity... --------- I'll CONTINUE to enjoy the popularity that has been bestowed upon me by the resident lemmings, rookies, and copycats.... LIKE YOU!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343162933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:48:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343162983000-108</Id><Topic><Title>Intel earnings much better than Apple.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1343162489000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:41:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>26% yoy smartphone growth. 84% on tablets. surprising flattening of smartphones. sort of explains TI earnigns too.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1343162983000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:49:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343163088000-109</Id><Title>RTQ 24.70</Title><Msg>INTC is good for 30. Just ask wallis!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343163088000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:51:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343164653000-110</Id><Title>intc getting pummeled in AH</Title><Msg>tomorrow could be brutal. unfortunately, everything could be affected, not just tech.</Msg><Username>bozox88</Username><Timestamp>1343164653000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343165193000-111</Id><Title>Just like I said earlier cnbc spread fake rumors on Fed today</Title><Msg>The street's attempt to save the market. They new apple would miss big time and market heading down. Now wall street has burned more bridges with today's latest lies (that's all they do you know). All cnbc people said get long appl prior to earnings. Wrong again. Cnbs puppets is pretty much wrong on everything these days, heck most days.</Msg><Username>hiowl123</Username><Timestamp>1343165193000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:26:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343165256000-112</Id><Topic><Title>Are you concerned with declining triangle formation?</Title><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1343114605000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 03:23:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok, with Apple news the break seems possible now. Lets see what put selling opportunities this brings. Most definitely its time to make money by shorting puts when markets get ridiculously oversold (and buying them near 1sd-2sd as always). We can play this game for 2-3 months until a safe big event low is made and then we can try again for 30. When the going gets tough intel survives better than everyone. And it positions itself better. So in a way crisis helps intel in relative terms. Do not expect stupid and malicious market to recognize that. Thats for us to know and have our revenge in time. You can bet any put profits made here long or short is going to be used to buy more Intel eventually. So learn to use intel declines to generate money and buy more core shares later lol!!! Be short or long near term depending on signals and long in the core position and let them crash it if the idiots want to. All that matters is that over time you own more shares than last year and have more cash too etc.</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1343165256000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:27:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343165374000-113</Id><Topic><Title>RTQ 24.70</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343163088000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally has never given any indication he knows anything whatsoever about trading stocks. Poor Wally.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1343165374000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:29:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343165428000-114</Id><Topic><Title>Just like I said earlier cnbc spread fake rumors on Fed today</Title><Username>hiowl123</Username><Timestamp>1343165193000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:26:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no they have the fed on deck waiting to save you temporarily... you better get out on the next QE 3 pump because the next time this tanks may be the big one !</Msg><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1343165428000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:30:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343165441000-115</Id><Topic><Title>intc getting pummeled in AH</Title><Username>bozox88</Username><Timestamp>1343164653000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:17:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1.2% . pummel might be too strong, but nonetheless, not good. Guess if you're cool, calm trader, all knowing, even 10% not bothersome. You can undoubtedly weather any storm. Good luck.</Msg><Username>bozox88</Username><Timestamp>1343165441000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343166519000-116</Id><Topic><Title>Intel earnings much better than Apple.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1343162489000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:41:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like it...it will put the fear of God into Apple. They were getting too big for their britches - by dominating their partners, suing everyone over look &amp; feel while they copied inventions from Xerox/PARC and others, buying up components to keep competition out, etc. Apple turned out to be the company they were supposedly fighting against - took them 28 years from 1984 to 2012 - but they got there all the same.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1343166519000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343166897000-117</Id><Topic><Title>Just like I said earlier cnbc spread fake rumors on Fed today</Title><Username>hiowl123</Username><Timestamp>1343165193000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:26:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No I should clairy. Wall street spread the rumors, just made it up to save the 50 day MA. No basis in truth what so ever. The street also knew appl would miss and needed to pump the market to dump befor the closee. Wall street calls cnbc and lets the parrots repeat their made up story. That's how it works.</Msg><Username>hiowl123</Username><Timestamp>1343166897000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:54:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343166923000-118</Id><Topic><Title>Intel earnings much better than Apple.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1343162489000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:41:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"rediculous!"</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343166923000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343167288000-119</Id><Title>$19 by friday.... running scared longy.. oh yeah</Title><Msg>fffff</Msg><Username>hutchpics</Username><Timestamp>1343167288000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:01:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343168938000-120</Id><Topic><Title>Intel earnings much better than Apple.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1343162489000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:41:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like it...it will put the fear of God into Apple In particular when putting Iphone in perspective to Samsung's most recent quarterly results....</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1343168938000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:28:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343169681000-121</Id><Title>Romney is a COWARD!...</Title><Msg>Message from a PATRIOT: I am a Viet Nam vet. My lottery number was 156. I had been deferred before the lottery because I was attending college, not only to get an education, but to stay out of being cannon fodder for the military. I had already lost two good high school buddies to the war, and saw three more come back raging addicts, so I had a great deal of fear and loathing about going to fight a useless war. My name came up on a waiting list for the Air Force Reserve when the lottery was at 154, so I jumped at the chance to join the Reserves. My mom sent me my draft notice while I was at Basic Training in Texas. I still had to fight the war out of a C-130 Herc and a C-141 T-tail Bug Sucker (C-141 Star lifter…both cargo aircraft, one out of MAC; Military Airlift Command, and the 130 out of TAC, Tactical Air Command) Out of TAC, I saw combat. I know of all sorts of tactics used by lots of well connected rich people to make sure their sons got out of the draft, and if I had had the opportunity to avoid going to Nam, I would have jumped at the chance, but I was part of the 99%, so I had to serve. A lot of guys I served with were of the same opinion, but we all served our country, and served it well. I am proud to say I was in the Military today. The resentment I see in the above article about Romney being “privileged” is a correct one. I only saw rich preppies whose fathers were well connected get into “closed” reserve units that were never called to serve, while the majority of us “99%er’s” had to serve and die for a war that everyone knew we were going to lose. What is so disgusting about Romney is his shrilling for a stronger draft knowing he won’t have to serve, that is unforgivable, despicable, vile, and cruel. To call for a war with Iran, not knowing what that really means is to infect our democracy with a cancer of warmongering to line the pockets of the .01% with even more money, greed and control, at the cost of blood and treasure that this county can ill afford. I have watched this country get divided into the “haves”, and “have nots”, and the line is becoming more defined as we progress in this election season. My fear is the election of the GOP with control of both houses of the legislature and the White House. Our doom as a democracy will be sealed if that happens, and Romney is the tip of that spear of doom. His support of a stronger draft, without his own sacrifice or those of his children speaks volumes about his lack of leadership. He is a coward and has no right whatsoever to call himself a patriot, let alone an American. He needs to perform an unnatural sexual act upon himself (instead of the more colorful expression). He is unfit to even serve as dog catcher.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343169681000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:41:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343169766000-122</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a DRAFT DODGER PUSSYBOY...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343106818000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:13:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is having a 'meltdown' LOL!</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343169766000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:42:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343171120000-123</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a COWARD!...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343169681000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:41:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How did you lose your college deferment? Most National Guard units never saw combat during Vietnam. You have no idea whether any proposed draft would include college deferments. Obama has never served in the military, never run a business, never been anything other than a social idealoque.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1343171120000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:05:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343171870000-124</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a COWARD!...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343169681000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:41:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NBC/WSJ poll: Negative campaign takes toll on candidates; Obama up six points Just in I guess those Obama attack adds will continue. Romney draft dodger--tax dodger--Mass LIB--now a rightwing nut--Mormon--I bet he drinks-- Mitt--rules do not apply to rich boy. But this poll is really bad. Wallstreet Journal is a rightwing nut paper owned by Murdoch. Hardly a left paper.NBC/WSJ poll: Negative campaign takes toll on candidates; Obama up six points</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1343171870000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:17:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343172034000-125</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a COWARD!...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343169681000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:41:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The horserace remains tight In the presidential horserace, Obama leads Romney by six percentage points among registered voters, 49 percent to 43 percent. That’s a slight change – within the margin of error – from last month’s poll, which showed Obama ahead by three points, 47 percent to 44 percent. Read the full poll here (.pdf) In a smaller sample of registered voters living in 12 battleground states (Colorado, Florida, Iowa, Michigan, Nevada, New Hampshire, New Mexico, North Carolina, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Virginia and Wisconsin), the incumbent president’s lead over Romney is eight points, 49 to 41, which is essentially unchanged from June.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1343172034000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343172452000-126</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a COWARD!...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343169681000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:41:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you see those Yankee battleground states BOY! The Yankees do not much like rich mormons. They chased them from ohio through Illinos and Iowa all the way to Utah. Now I know that Mitt does not have 5 wives like his grampa had but he does have a French Passport and off shore money in the millions. He did use 4 deferments to get out of the draft during the Vietnam war. He went to France and pretended to be some Holy man--draft dodger. Against all war he said. but now he is all for wars. What an AHOLE Mitt is!!!!!! But he will lose and you will shiiiiet yourself and cry like a little bbbbbtchhhboy.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1343172452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343172610000-127</Id><Title>Slick Willard...</Title><Msg>This despicable man came out of the same mold as GW Bush. Just another lying hypocrite and the GOP love him for it.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343172610000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:30:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343172704000-128</Id><Title>Rupert Murdoch owns the Wallstreet jounal.</Title><Msg>In their poll out today, OB is beating super richboy liar Romney by 6 pts among registerd voters.. You do not like the poll? Complain to Fox news owner--Rupert. He owns the WSJ--it is a rightwing rag.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1343172704000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:31:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343172746000-129</Id><Topic><Title>Imperative Momentum Stepping In</Title><Username>clementiapfv427</Username><Timestamp>1343143070000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:17:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow!!!</Msg><Username>corellaxus301</Username><Timestamp>1343172746000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:32:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343172831000-130</Id><Title>Romney getting CRUSHED in the polls...</Title><Msg>and it's a good thing too. The word is out on this guy being a lying privileged hypocrite. The GOP really needs to find another candidate and fast.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343172831000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:33:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343172853000-131</Id><Topic><Title>investing technicalanalysis</Title><Username>clementiapfv427</Username><Timestamp>1343143400000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:23:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ur timing is simply best</Msg><Username>corellaxus301</Username><Timestamp>1343172853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:34:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343172904000-132</Id><Topic><Title>Slick Willard...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343172610000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:30:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Republicans love draft dodgers who start wars. GW Bush and now Rombo. Of course--Romney is going to go down hard and the little GOP btttccches here will go back to talking stock again after. Personally--I could never be with a woman who voted for the republicans. I would rather phuck a dog. OH--Romney says dogs are for riding on top of the car while he drives.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1343172904000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343172924000-133</Id><Topic><Title>Don't believe the POLES</Title><Username>liberalsrindenial22</Username><Timestamp>1343172780000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:33:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poles? You are truely a GOP moron! Besides, isn't it your bedtime?</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343172924000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:35:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343173303000-134</Id><Topic><Title>Don't believe the POLES</Title><Username>liberalsrindenial22</Username><Timestamp>1343172780000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:33:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The poll was the WSJ POLL. Rupert Murdoch, owner of Fox news, owns the WSJ. idiot. I bet you cry like a little woosey boy after OB wins again. HAAAA HAAAA</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1343173303000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:41:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343173514000-135</Id><Title>And you though t the boys in Chicago would be nice to Romney? HAA</Title><Msg>They are going to go negative and make Romney into a clown. Negative views on the rise But what did change was an increase in negative views about both Obama and Romney. The president’s favorable/unfavorable score in the poll is 49 percent to 43 percent, a slight change from June when it was 47 percent to 38 percent. Moreover, 33 percent view Obama very positively, while 32 percent view him very negatively – which is his highest “very negative” number in poll. By comparison, Romney’s overall favorable/unfavorable score is 35 percent to 40 percent, with 24 percent viewing him “very” negatively – also his highest mark here. Read the full poll here (.pdf) In fact, Romney would be the first GOP presumptive presidential nominee since 1996 to head into his nominating convention with a net-negative favorable/unfavorable score. In 1996, Bob Dole’s score was 39 percent to 36 percent; in 2000, George W. Bush’s was 52 percent to 32 percent; and in 2008, John McCain’s was 42 percent to 30 percent.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1343173514000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:45:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343173648000-136</Id><Title>the Head of the fed, BEN, is a LIB!</Title><Msg>He will do some massive pumping for the economy next week and save his LIb GOD--OB!</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1343173648000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:47:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343173821000-137</Id><Title>CNBC needs to fire Cuntlow. He is an embaressment.</Title><Msg>I think he is back on the drugs again. Coke I believe is his favorite.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1343173821000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:50:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343173992000-138</Id><Title>QCOM QC VS Medfield</Title><Msg>I was shocked to see how well the QC Krait did against Medfield! ARM is starting to look a good bit better to me. I don't expect Intel will have anything close until they redesign Atom in 22nm sometime next year? Info from Endgaget. Orange San Diego Medfield (M) Samsung Galaxy S III Motorola Droid RAZR Quadcore Krait (Q) Quadrant 3,648M 4,454 2,357 7698Q Vellamo 1,279M 1,751 1,021 2538Q AnTuTu 5,712M 11,960 6,027 13826Q SunSpider 0.9.1 (ms) 1,387M 1,460 2,140 1227Q GLBenchmark Egypt Offscreen (fps) 28M 99 28 132Q CF-Bench 2,437M 13,110 6,191 18219Q</Msg><Username>awaytocar123</Username><Timestamp>1343173992000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:53:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343178626000-139</Id><Title>why does INTC suck these days?</Title><Msg>still paying that handsome dividend, isn't it?</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1343178626000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 21:10:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343179165000-140</Id><Topic><Title>RTQ 24.70</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343163088000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And what's the real time quote of Cisco? So for Lucy, a drop from $19 down to $15 is alot better than a rise from $19 to $24.70 "RTQ". Can Lucy get any weirder?</Msg><Username>texanjk99</Username><Timestamp>1343179165000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 21:19:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343179443000-141</Id><Topic><Title>why does INTC suck these days?</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1343178626000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 21:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy Mortimer, buy. Just don't forget to sell, Waldo's flaw, as always, a 61 year old who thinks he has plenty of time to be a long term investor in a cyclical industry.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1343179443000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 21:24:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343180828000-142</Id><Topic><Title>QCOM QC VS Medfield</Title><Username>awaytocar123</Username><Timestamp>1343173992000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would take these numbers with a pinch of salt since these benchmarks favor the quad core Krait. Once Intel comes out with its own dual-core chip targeting tablets, I'm sure it will level up. Medfield's showing is impressive considering that it's doing all this with just one core. (With four cores, the Qualcomm chip would obviously run down its battery in no time in the real world). Slightly later, when Intel comes out with its own architectural revision at 22nm (forget the name) then we'll really get to see how the architectures match up. Krait after all is one generation beyond ARM's A9 so it's unfair to compare it with more or less last generation Medfield. As Intel's Mike Bell himself said, the instruction set has no role to play in this match up so it really does boil down to how well they lay out the gates. Intel's engineers are recognized experts in this.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1343180828000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 21:47:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343182753000-143</Id><Title>Romney's father was born in Mexico...</Title><Msg>I guess that makes Slick Willard an 'Anchor Baby', LOL!</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1343182753000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 22:19:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343183847000-144</Id><Title>SAP</Title><Msg>http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_C/threadview?m=tm&amp;bn=4879&amp;tid=63594&amp;mid=63594&amp;tof=5&amp;frt=2</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1343183847000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 22:37:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343184240000-145</Id><Title>Et tu Apple?</Title><Msg>Every couple months we get some random punk come on here and explain to us the new world order. Intel is dead and tablets and phones are all we'll ever need in the future. It's a zero sum game, every new tablet or phone sold is one less PC sold. Like they exist in a world where they are mutually exclusive. A person can't own a PC and a tablet and/or smartphone. Today, Apple announced a miss on expectations. Yes they sold 17 million tablets, but came up a little light on phones. People are waiting for the iPhone5 they tell us. Just a few short years ago Steve Jobs was the Barry Bonds of home runs for Apple back in the height of juicing. But, even before he died Apple was starting to run out of home runs. As you may recall Steve Jobs died the day after the iPhone 4s. An appropriate time to go in my opinion, the phone didn't bring anything new to the game, unless you consider Siri to be noteworthy. The days of Apple bringing a sense of wonder to the world with a new, innovative product that makes teenagers clean out their bank accounts seem to be over. All they can bank on right now is that there are enough customers with too many apps and song loaded on their phones to want to do a paradigm shift. They are waiting around for something brilliant. This has to be something that can be relevant for one full year, and then slightly modified for the next year like the iPhone 4s. Here's my point, even with 100 billion dollars sitting in a vault and untold thousands of brilliant people on the payroll I don't think Apple can keep the safe distance between them and their competition. In a couple of months we'll know for certain but I'm feeling by looking at the releases of the iPhone 4s and iPad(3) that Apple can't set the bar high enough anymore. My take on what really happened with Apple today is that when someone recently wanted to buy their first Smartphone they went to their local wireless store to look at the 4S that everybody told them to check out. While they were their they noticed a small crowd of people standing around the Samsung phones. "Let me see that!" And there is one less Apple sale. It doesn't have to happen every time, just enough to become a problem. Apple is going to sell an amazing amount of iPhone5's because they have enough loyal customers who want to buy it now matter how good or bad it is. This can help with their numbers for a quarter or two. But this miss you saw today with Apple, expect more in the future as their segment turns generic.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1343184240000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 22:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343187590000-146</Id><Topic><Title>RTQ 24.70</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1343163088000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, Lucy prefers 50 percent losses and telling everyone THEY are dumb instead of 25% gains, dividends and humility. Whatever floats the lil' guy's boat.</Msg><Username>lucy_died</Username><Timestamp>1343187590000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 23:39:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343188545000-147</Id><Topic><Title>SAP</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1343183847000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 22:37:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boy, I love the cryptic messages you always post here.......not.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1343188545000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 23:55:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343188700000-148</Id><Topic><Title>SAP</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1343183847000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 22:37:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SAP is probably the most horrible SW I've ever used.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1343188700000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 23:58:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>