<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346562666679-1</Id><Topic><Title>Applied Micro's X-Gene server chip ARMed to the teeth</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1346486916226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The idea that you can solve everything with architecture is lame. The chips will just keep getting bigger and bigger. Don't believe it? Just look at the thickness of the new iPad. And feel the heat. It's all about the fabrication. Intel has it. ARM doesn't. End of story...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346562666679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 01:11:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346562903152-2</Id><Topic><Title>ARM can't manufacture its own products, so Toshiba scraps ARM tablets, notebooks</Title><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346529335835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:55:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The people who have no clue are your ARM bosses who sent you here to continuously get your head handed to you in a basket. ARM is so poor that have to use shills like you and Nenni instead of having a real marketing budget. At least Nenni has no reason to be here now he can't post his spam. Why are you still here?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346562903152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 01:15:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346568008535-3</Id><Topic><Title>ARM can't manufacture its own products, so Toshiba scraps ARM tablets, notebooks</Title><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346529335835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:55:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel's strategy is to flood the market with cheap atom mobile chips that are vendor independent like their PC chips. If you know anything about computers you would know that armh chips are vendor specific, therefore are not fluid. Being more fluid comes at a cost and are less efficient.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1346568008535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 02:40:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346569130493-4</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft fails to pacify PC vendors about Surface tablets</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346531658605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:34:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The $199 nvidia surface tablets doesn't really make sense. Nvidia or Msft will lose money at that price.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1346569130493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346569523380-5</Id><Topic><Title>ARM can't manufacture its own products, so Toshiba scraps ARM tablets, notebooks</Title><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346529335835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:55:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" If you know anything about computers you would know that armh chips are vendor specific, therefore are not fluid." clear as mud...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346569523380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 03:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346570033919-6</Id><Topic><Title>Getanid16 pumping ARM servers that don't even exist, LOL!</Title><Username>wall.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346527861985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:31:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Might not happen at all. They got the same barrier crossing over like Intel crossing over to mobile as long as Intel can keep up with Moore's law. I actually think Intel has a better chance crossing over to mobile if they can get their chips to become competitive with arm in terms of power and efficiency because they are just concentrating on chip design and not the end product itself. They will eventually flood the market with cheap mobile chips. If phone makers can cut cost using cheap intel mobile chips, they with most definately use them if the supply is constant and dependable, unlike fabless vendors that rely on their fabs that has tons of other customers that are pressuring them.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1346570033919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 03:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346570770546-7</Id><Topic><Title>ARM can't manufacture its own products, so Toshiba scraps ARM tablets, notebooks</Title><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346529335835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:55:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's true. Intel might be the better way to go in the future because the x86 chips are more fluid. ----- Fluid? What does that mean? If you are talking about binary compatibility, ARM CPU's from different vendors for a specific revision of the ISA are binary compatible (much like x86).</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1346570770546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 03:26:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346571233924-8</Id><Topic><Title>Applied Micro's X-Gene server chip ARMed to the teeth</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1346486916226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The idea that you can solve everything with architecture is lame. The chips will just keep getting bigger and bigger. Don't believe it? Just look at the thickness of the new iPad. And feel the heat. It's all about the fabrication. Intel has it. ARM doesn't. End of story... ----- You can't solve everything with architecture, but it can go a long way. If ARM64 is as clean and elegant as some suggest it means that It will be quick to implement and it will reduce the number of transistors needed to implement it (thus reducing the pressure of needing the newest node). As for the iPad, the thickness/heat issue is due to the screen/battery combo.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1346571233924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 03:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346572551410-9</Id><Title>I spit on this message board...</Title><Msg>What else can I say?</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1346572551410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 03:55:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346582213000-10</Id><Topic><Title>This board still functional...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1346458645000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that all you have? What a wimp.</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1346582213000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 06:36:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346589040000-11</Id><Topic><Title>This board still functional...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1346458645000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For you, my spit is way overkill.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1346589040000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:30:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346595145487-12</Id><Title>Any chance of aapl Sept 12 announcement intc chips in new products?</Title><Msg>Just wondering if true or anyone knew</Msg><Username>raygeo2003</Username><Timestamp>1346595145487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:12:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346595329497-13</Id><Title>Dividend Payable Date 9/1/12</Title><Msg>E*Turde hasn't gotten the word yet</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1346595329497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:15:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346597189981-14</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend Payable Date 9/1/12</Title><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1346595329497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:15:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since the 1st was on a saturday, and we have a long holiday weekend we may not see it in our accounts until tuesday</Msg><Username>bull_v_fighter</Username><Timestamp>1346597189981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:46:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346599201263-15</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend Payable Date 9/1/12</Title><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1346595329497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:15:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got mine yesterday. You can see it if you got an online account.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1346599201263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:20:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346599888740-16</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend Payable Date 9/1/12</Title><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1346595329497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:15:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who do you use? Obviously I have an on-line account and it isn't in there. I agree with bull v fighter, may not se until tuesday at E*turde</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1346599888740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:31:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346603015000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Forecast</Title><Username>felisha_keri23</Username><Timestamp>1346590040000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:47:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fantastic. I will check it out.</Msg><Username>shamika_jaclyn14</Username><Timestamp>1346603015000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:23:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346606238482-18</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend Payable Date 9/1/12</Title><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1346595329497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:15:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just bought a NYC apt with my dividend.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1346606238482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 13:17:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346625546180-19</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood absolutely KILLED IT at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346381822113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shouldn't that be everyones goal, to be rich. If you don't want more money, why are you investing in the stock market ? Obama speak = rich is bad, poor is good, Why don't you give everything you own away, and then we'll see if you practice what you preach. Your goal should be to become as poor as the poorest church mouse.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346625546180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:39:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346626198407-20</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood absolutely KILLED IT at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346381822113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it seems that the Democrats will prefer everyone to be poor while making the poor poorer. Now all are equaly poor. lmao. great plan wally</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1346626198407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:49:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346628235016-21</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood absolutely KILLED IT at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346381822113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Shouldn't that be everyones goal, to be rich. If you don't want more money, why are you investing in the stock market ? Obama speak = rich is bad, poor is good, Why don't you give everything you own away, and then we'll see if you practice what you preach. Your goal should be to become as poor as the poorest church mouse." *** Indeed, then why don't we make the tax rate for the rich zero? Your assumptions are absurd. You equate rich being good with making the rich better off and giving them whatever they ask for.. Only a #$%$ thinks those are the same thing. No Democrat thinks rich is bad and poor is good. The problem is that what you want for the rich comes at the expense of the middle class. America's success and economic stability are based on having a healthy middle class. I'm sick of the rich attempting to soak the middle class beyond anything that approaches reasonable. There hasn't been a Republican president since Eisenhower that has balanced a budget. And where did all this excessive spending go? It went to defense spending and tax cuts. Bush by himself engaged us in two wars and then didn't pay for either one. Instead he gave the rich an enormous tax cut. There is no reality in which this isn't irresponsible. The idea that Ryan really cares about cutting spending is a non-starter. He only wants to cut spending so he can generate more tax cuts - for the rich. He favors tax cuts over insurance for little kids, over education - in fact, there is nothing on Ryan's priority list above tax cuts. You guys got a huge tax cut under Bush and here you are with your hand out again. In the worst economic times in decades you want yet another free hand out. Well, guess what? It's time to put something back into the system that allowed you the opportunity to become rich.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346628235016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:23:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346628502315-22</Id><Topic><Title>intc message board sucks........</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1346531403409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:30:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not me. If the message board was so bad I would get off.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1346628502315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:28:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346628669237-23</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood absolutely KILLED IT at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346381822113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are plenty of independent studies that confirm under Republicans the rich get richer and the poor get poorer. Not under Democrats. Don't take my word. Go look it up. Nobody on the planet vaporized more wealth than George Bush. And now you want to go back to the same exact policies: more tax cuts, more defense spending. And you think that will result in economic prosperity this time. Romney and Ryan have promised to create 12 million jobs. The only problem is that when people ask (and a lot have) exactly how that's going to happen the response is complete silence. Let me say it again: Republicans have no plan to restore jobs or create economic prosperity. Go ahead - Make my day. Explain to me what the plan is...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346628669237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:31:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346629119520-24</Id><Title>Bernanke paves the way for more stimulus</Title><Msg>From CNNMoney: Federal Reserve Chairman Ben Bernanke made his strongest case yet for more easing, during a high-profile speech in Jackson Hole, Wyo., Friday. Bernanke staunchly defended the Federal Reserve's two previous rounds of large asset purchases, saying they drove stocks higher, improved financial markets and created more than 2 million jobs. He also refuted several potential risks associated with those policies and talked up their benefits. "The odds are strong that the Fed's asset purchases will make money for the taxpayers, reducing the federal deficit and debt," Bernanke said. "And, of course, to the extent that monetary policy helps strengthen the economy and raise incomes, the benefits for the U.S. fiscal position would be substantial." The chairman also hinted that a third round of asset purchases known as quantitative easing -- or QE3 -- could be coming, by reiterating the Fed's willingness to pull the trigger. "The Federal Reserve will provide additional policy accommodation as needed to promote a stronger economic recovery and sustained improvement in labor market conditions in a context of price stability." Bernanke added that the economy "is obviously far from satisfactory," pointing to 8.3% unemployment and the weak job market as a "grave concern" causing "enormous suffering and waste of human talent." The Fed also sees the fiscal cliff and Europe's debt crisis as major threats to U.S. economic growth, and that gloomy outlook seems to have lowered the bar for the Fed to provide more stimulus. In previous statements, the central bank has pledged to provide stimulus only if the economy weakens further, but more recently that language has changed to say the Fed will act if the economy merely stays the same. Bernanke seemed to back up that view Friday, suggesting that the Fed needs to consider acting preemptively, to "take out insurance against the realization of downside risk" -- a view often expressed by his number two in command, Vice-Chairwoman Janet Yellen. U.S. stocks initially pulled back when Bernanke began speaking, but quickly moved higher after investors digested the speech as an assurance that additional stimulus is likely.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346629119520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:38:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346629561656-25</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke paves the way for more stimulus</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346629119520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallisweaver begging for another handout/more debt? Sounds about right.</Msg><Username>wall.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346629561656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:46:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346629742294-26</Id><Title>Shorts Have a Week (Or Less)</Title><Msg>With IDF starting on the 11th and the Intel/Motorola announcement coming on the 18th, shorts have a short window of opportunity in which to to cover. Or prolly it's already too late...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346629742294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:49:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346629947645-27</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke paves the way for more stimulus</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346629119520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, like you have a solution...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346629947645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346630391528-28</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke paves the way for more stimulus</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346629119520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm pretty sure that racking up a massive debt has never been the answer in any society, anywhere. But your tiny brain only want the stock market to go higher at any costs. F-'n Dweeb.</Msg><Username>wall.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346630391528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:59:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346631765000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Forecast</Title><Username>felisha_keri23</Username><Timestamp>1346590040000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:47:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love your videos.</Msg><Username>maxie_carmela417</Username><Timestamp>1346631765000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:22:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346634450012-30</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood absolutely KILLED IT at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346381822113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, i believe most american will not fall it agian</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1346634450012</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:07:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346634511722-31</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke paves the way for more stimulus</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346629119520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I have to spend money I do not have to keep things going it seems to me that one of these days I will have a big price to pay. Just seems right. But I dont have alot of answers either. Maybe we need to get a new pres. and let him try. This one didnt get er done.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1346634511722</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:08:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346634864000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Forecast</Title><Username>felisha_keri23</Username><Timestamp>1346590040000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:47:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice to be member.</Msg><Username>farrah_beatriz36</Username><Timestamp>1346634864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346635374520-33</Id><Topic><Title>intc message board sucks........</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1346531403409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:30:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>horrible MB format by yahoo all over, not just for INTC</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1346635374520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346639454014-34</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood absolutely KILLED IT at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346381822113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would have been better if he killed himself.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1346639454014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:30:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346639617350-35</Id><Title>Bain Capital subpoenaed for tax fraud in July...</Title><Msg>Now we know why Slick Willard won't release more tax returns.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1346639617350</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:33:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346641630305-36</Id><Topic><Title>Bain Capital subpoenaed for tax fraud in July...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1346639617350</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:33:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>was the Tea Party plan. Karl Rove releases his copies of the Romney returns after they win the election and Romney is impeached. Tea Party outrage will be without limit.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346641630305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:07:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346642429499-37</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy Nuff un-laid for 10 years</Title><Username>lucy_is_my_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1346543580335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:53:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1346642429499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346643746037-38</Id><Topic><Title>intc message board sucks........</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1346531403409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:30:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I liked the old message board a lot better.</Msg><Username>stok1mom</Username><Timestamp>1346643746037</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346644481885-39</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke paves the way for more stimulus</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346629119520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I'm pretty sure that racking up a massive debt has never been the answer in any society, anywhere. But your tiny brain only want the stock market to go higher at any costs. F-'n Dweeb". *** Yeah, just like giving tax cuts and spending massively on defense when you can't afford it has never been the answer in any society. Name the last Republican president who didn't give tax cuts, increase the defense budget and incur massive deficits. And you voted for all of them. So, take your hypocrisy someplace else. Your tiny brain only wants a tax cut and another war at any cost. Well the cost is going to be the collapse of the American economy if you get your way. F-'n Dweeb</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346644481885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:54:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>