<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-27"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348730673115-1</Id><Title>Oracle OpenWorld Keynote - Diane Bryant - Wed</Title><Msg>In addition to the Bryant Keynote, I would expect some ROMLEY announcements by other companies during the week. Wednesday, October 3 8:00 a.m. – 9:45 a.m., Moscone North, Hall D Data Center Imperatives in the New Era An exploding demand for data and connectivity brings both challenges and opportunities to IT organizations of every size. At the same time, IT has become increasingly integral to the success of the enterprise and must become more agile, efficient, and—ultimately—insightful. Diane Bryant, formerly Intel’s CIO and now head of Intel’s Datacenter and Connected Systems Group, will address how Intel is driving intelligence throughout the data center—across servers, storage, and networking—to reduce TCO, increase security, drive agility, and enable business insights. Bryant will also discuss innovations Intel is providing with Oracle to advance the state of IT. Diane M. Bryant, Vice President and General Manager, Datacenter and Connected Systems Group, Intel</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348730673115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 03:24:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348741496326-2</Id><Topic><Title>Serious question, request for help, and commentary</Title><Username>alstanap</Username><Timestamp>1348734005800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 04:20:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Substitute the dots in the link in some way e.g. financeDOTyahooDOTcom/q?s=intc</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348741496326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 06:24:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348745237923-3</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>After five consecutive sessions of decline, the major indexes are now in short term oversold territory. With the quarter end coming and the S&amp;P 500 getting close to its support area (1418-1422), stocks should be able to find support not far from where they closed yesterday. With that said, expect uncertainty to remain high into October and earnings season. Stay nimble and cautious. have a nice day.</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1348745237923</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 07:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348746388078-4</Id><Title>Can things get worse for Intel?</Title><Msg>Aside from the global slowdown, this last stretch has been really rough for shareholders. I sold a bunch of puts down here, looking to get 4% yeild for a short time then sell off some calls. I don't think we get rich with intel, but I think we can get a good return from here. I think we saw the bottom on monday/tues. GLTA</Msg><Username>fishfryer527</Username><Timestamp>1348746388078</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 07:46:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348749428258-5</Id><Title>"Gold Can Turn Pennies Into Dollars" - Breakout Alert!!!</Title><Msg>Penny gold mining stocks can return tremendous profits as the price of gold moves higher. Bonanza Goldfields, BONZ, is one stock to invest in here. The company's new C.E.O. was a director at the U.S. Mint. Gold production is expected to begin soon at the company's Tarantula site. Read the recent Yahoo news. "Penny stock today. Dollar stock tomorrow."</Msg><Username>wcoastguy2008</Username><Timestamp>1348749428258</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 08:37:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348749428748-6</Id><Title>"Gold Can Turn Pennies Into Dollars" - Breakout Alert!!!</Title><Msg>Penny gold mining stocks can return tremendous profits as the price of gold moves higher. Bonanza Goldfields, BONZ, is one stock to invest in here. The company's new C.E.O. was a director at the U.S. Mint. Gold production is expected to begin soon at the company's Tarantula site. Read the recent Yahoo news. "Penny stock today. Dollar stock tomorrow."</Msg><Username>wcoastguy2008</Username><Timestamp>1348749428748</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 08:37:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348751787104-7</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see the write up on this (INTC)</Title><Username>deniceujk5465</Username><Timestamp>1348665517051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got it for free. Thank you</Msg><Username>hildapyi67500</Username><Timestamp>1348751787104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 09:16:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348751902867-8</Id><Title>Oracle's openworld KEYNOTE speaker? Freaking Diane Bryan of INTEL. I thought it would be Viinne donitz aka Lucy Nuff discussuing FORTRAN</Title><Msg>How's all that AMD you bought and pumped at 40k, Vinnie? ROFL............at YOU.</Msg><Username>vinnie_bagofhotwind</Username><Timestamp>1348751902867</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 09:18:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348755177608-9</Id><Title>Letter to SEC (Updated)</Title><Msg>Letter to the Securities and Exchange Commission Dear Sir or Madam: It is with growing concern that I have watched trends within the stock markets move towards perpetuation of an environment in which the larger firms and corporations are enabled to use money, leverage, technology (as in high-speed trading, and access to media in order to disenfranchise or even defraud those without the same level of resources. This manipulation appears to manifest itself in two primary ways. One is what appears to be the use of a cooperative strategy by Wall Street’s largest firms to use a combination of analyst’s reports, reports to the media, timed upgrades/downgrades, and buy/sell strategies by their own trading desks in order to channel the direction of the stock price and to then unethically and perhaps illegally profit from this combination of methodologies. The other is a similar strategy by hedge funds. Hedge funds under current regulations provide little or no visibility of their trading patterns, strategies or activities, essentially allowing them free rein to manipulate stock prices in ways not compatible with the normal trends produced by supply and demand. Both of these situations work to the detriment of the average investor. They tend to drive the smaller or average investor completely out of the stock markets with the conclusion that the “market is rigged”. In fact this certainly appears to be the case in an unfortunate number of circumstances. Let us consider the case of Intel. Intel has been locked in a trading range for years. Even when they recorded five years of 27 percent annual growth, the P/E ratio was continuously and significantly below that of the average S&amp;P 500 company while they performance was hugely better. Every time Intel threatened to move to a higher level, Wall Street’s largest firms would apparently band together with a barrage of downgrades and negative media comments. The result was a continuous valuation under what any reasonable analysis would support as being fair. Whether these firms traded against Intel in addition needs to be determined. Recent trading patterns indicate the present of a collusive force. I therefore ask for consideration of the following: 1.) An investigation of the manner in which Wall Street’s largest firms internally trade, correlated against analyst recommendations, upgrade/downgrade releases, and reports to the media. 2.) An investigation of the manner of trading across Wall Street’s largest firms to determine if there is any pattern of cooperation or collusion in regards to particular stocks. 3.) The development of new regulations resulting in greater transparency of hedge fund trading in order to determine if they are using money and leverage to manipulate the market and stock prices in a manner inconsistent with stock market fairness and stability. 4.) An investigation of large Wall Street firm and hedge fund trading of Intel Corporation to determine if they are engaged in activities which unfairly or illegally deny Intel a fair valuation. 5.) An investigation into naked shorting of Intel. Thank you for your time and efforts in helping to establish a market environment free of fraud, manipulation and methodologies which disenfranchise smaller investors. Sincerely,</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348755177608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:12:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348755618040-10</Id><Topic><Title>Letter to SEC (Updated)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348755177608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:12:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ are obviously still at it and doing everything they can to suppress the stock price. Enough is enough. There is no good reason why Intel shareholders and investors should be continuously abused by the unethical and perhaps illegal techniques constantly employed by Wall Street's largest firms. This is clearly a cooperative effort. We need to find out if it is collusive as well. Intel is one of America's great companies. Wall Street needs to explain its vendetta and be held accountable. Send the letters. Copy the media. E-mail friends, family and business contacts. Stop doing business with the Wall Street #$%$. Support regulation and disclosures of trading activity of hedge funds. Enough is enough. This has to stop...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348755618040</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:20:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348756096216-11</Id><Title>USA Today: High Frequency Trading Insanity</Title><Msg>In today's stock market, there are two types of trader. The other, the high-frequency trader, deploys massive computer capacity and complex algorithms to buy and sell individual stocks multiple times in a fraction of a second, all in search of micro-profits with each trade. This trader cares not a whit about a stock's fundamentals. In a sane world, high-frequency trading would be a minor specialty at best. But in the bizarro world that Wall Street has become, such activity now makes up the majority of all trades. It is manufacturing risk while siphoning money and talent that growth-producing sectors of the economy need. It has also sparked a technological arms race aimed at shaving milliseconds off each trade. New, more direct fiber optic cable routes have been laid between major trading cities, and now there are even serious proposals to position drone aircraft over the Atlantic Ocean to speed transmission times between New York and London. And what does all this mean for conventional investors? Nothing good. Just gobs of needless danger. The biggest problem with high-frequency trading is that it greatly increases the chances of a major market crash. In 2010, the "flash crash" took the Dow Jones average down more than 1,000 points in a matter of minutes. Finding the cause — a single massive computerized trade made in error — took months. Imagine, then, what might happen if the market started falling in response to a sudden event, such as an attack on Iran. The computers, which act on their own, would likely overwhelm the market with sell orders. Similar circumstances in 1987 caused a crash that took the Dow down 22.6% in a day and nearly crippled the entire financial system. Today, the trade volume would be massively larger. Yet the regulatory response has been negligible, even as problems have continued. Just last month, a trading company called Knight Capital Group nearly collapsed after malfunctions in its computers sent the shares of 148 companies on wild rides. Behind these events is a high-tech war fought among computer algorithms challenging each other for supremacy and unmindful of the destabilizing effect they are having. The growing concern they are causing was evident at a Senate hearing last week, and in a report by the Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago. Beyond the crash risk, these practices undermine the core purpose of markets, which is to raise capital in pursuit of enterprise, profit and economic growth. That's not happening the way it used to. Even though the Dow is back above 13,000 and bond yields are low, investors have been pulling money out of stock mutual funds most of this year, according to the Investment Company Institute. And even sophisticated investors such as billionaire Mark Cuban say they're "terrified" about potential flash crashes triggered by high-frequency trading. The traders argue that they add liquidity to markets that lowers transaction costs and eases dealing in thinly traded shares. There is some truth to this. But the negatives far outweigh the positives. Next week, the Securities and Exchange Commission is holding a meeting to solicit ideas about what to do. Here's a simple one: Slap a small transaction tax on rapid trades, impeding the practice and returning markets to their core purpose. That would be a big win for small investors, and the only people harmed would be those now putting everyone else at risk.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348756096216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:28:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348756302573-12</Id><Topic><Title>USA Today: High Frequency Trading Insanity</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348756096216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:28:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Next week, the Securities and Exchange Commission is holding a meeting to solicit ideas about what to do. Here's a simple one: Slap a small transaction tax on rapid trades, impeding the practice and returning markets to their core purpose." This is a great time to send the letters to the SEC. Protect small investors and the integrity of the markets! At the same time we can send a message to Wall Street that they are not going to be allowed to use money, leverage and manipulation to attack good companies like Intel!!!</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348756302573</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348756770757-13</Id><Topic><Title>Letter to SEC (Updated)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348755177608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:12:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WW- "Dear SEC: I'm done. Please come and wipe my butt for me."</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348756770757</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:39:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>28</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348757307326-14</Id><Topic><Title>Letter to SEC (Updated)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348755177608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:12:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps they should investigate the guy who at 29 said it's good for 30.00</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348757307326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348757488894-15</Id><Title>Intel &amp; Samsung To Gain Against Fabless Chip Rivals</Title><Msg>says Jefferies &amp; Co.analyst Mark Kipacis. Wallisweaver and others have been making this point for some time. Now some analysts are beginning to realize how much of an advantage fully integrated chip production will be to the economics of future chip production.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1348757488894</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:51:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348757585325-16</Id><Title>Intel broke the news that a Softie product is buggy</Title><Msg>"Stop the presses! Put that end-of-the-world in two days story on hold and write the Intel/Windows 8 story instead! Special edition, front page, banner headlines.... in fact, use the whole damn paper for it!" What? A Microsoft product is buggy? Shocking! I just cannot believe it!</Msg><Username>bobbobwhite</Username><Timestamp>1348757585325</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:53:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348758568468-17</Id><Topic><Title>Intel &amp; Samsung To Gain Against Fabless Chip Rivals</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1348757488894</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Denni just fell to the floor kicking and screaming</Msg><Username>sanjitkumar23</Username><Timestamp>1348758568468</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:09:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348759112979-18</Id><Topic><Title>Letter to SEC (Updated)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348755177608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:12:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is one of America's great companies.........Send the letters ------ Wave that flag! Send those letters! Maybe you should sit on a flagpole for about 30 days. You are the kind of guy who would buy a set of kitchen knives from a door-to-door salesman! You, and millions of stooooopid people like you, are the reason that thousands of others are wealthy, peanut gallery boy.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348759112979</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>27</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348760036280-19</Id><Topic><Title>Letter to SEC (Updated)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348755177608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:12:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a conspiracy. I'm going to send a letter directly to the President. He'll see that the SEC acts quickly on this matter.</Msg><Username>wallisweiner</Username><Timestamp>1348760036280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348761313513-20</Id><Topic><Title>Intel &amp; Samsung To Gain Against Fabless Chip Rivals</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1348757488894</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jefferies downgraded Altera (ALTR), a fabless firm, to hold from buy, and upgraded Maxim Integrated Products (MXIM), which has manufacturing facilities, to buy from hold. It upped its price target on Maxim to 33 from 29. Analog manufacturing does not require bleeding edge - that's why l Linear, Maxim, Analog Device and TI analog operate fabs in the US - Analog just made the transition to 300mm. In this particular case this upgrade / downgrade based on manufacturing has absolutely no merit - Lipcas is one of those chipmaker analysts that lacks the basic knowledge - FPGA and analog has as much in common as soccer and American football.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348761313513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:55:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348762599794-21</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle OpenWorld Keynote - Diane Bryant - Wed</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348730673115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 03:24:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Server CPU volume wouldn't even fill one fab. Bryant's business is a profit gravy train only so long as the rest of Intel carries the company. Mobile and PC is where INTC needs to succeed, and they haven't figured that out yet, obviously.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1348762599794</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:16:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348762824411-22</Id><Title>INTC is Headed Back to $23.02</Title><Msg>INTC always returns to 23.02.</Msg><Username>wilder_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1348762824411</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:20:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348763687118-23</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see the write up on this (INTC)</Title><Username>deniceujk5465</Username><Timestamp>1348665517051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good move. I will be expecting for more news.</Msg><Username>yeejnq625</Username><Timestamp>1348763687118</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:34:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348763902460-24</Id><Title>What Was the Worst-Performing Tech Stock on the Dow This September?</Title><Msg>Could the answer be "Smelltel?" TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348763902460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:38:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>20</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348763940161-25</Id><Topic><Title>USA Today: High Frequency Trading Insanity</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348756096216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:28:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amen to the transaction tax. Better yet, charge a penny a share on any buy or sell entered. The high frequency traders would go broke with their simultaneous million share buy and sell orders, which most are cancelled but they would be taxed anyway.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1348763940161</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348764566467-26</Id><Topic><Title>The PC Isn't Dying: Don't Sell Into The Sensationalism</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347282877310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:14:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis, you're fired. Your incessant pumping of this stock, which is now down 20% from its high - where you recommended buying - is a pox on this forum. Ultrabook was a flop, and now everyone long the on the stock like you recommended is paying for it. Go away! ---------------- That wally is a real card! Seriously though, he should WRITE AN OPEN LETTER of apology to all on this mesage board. He's led many innocents down the path to the poorhouse. TOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348764566467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:49:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348765127816-27</Id><Title>What happened to the loud mouther Teabagger GOP?</Title><Msg>They are silent now. WOOOSEY LOSERS!</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348765127816</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:58:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348765631991-28</Id><Topic><Title>USA Today: High Frequency Trading Insanity</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348756096216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:28:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amen to the transaction tax 1.) As far as I recall one of the reasons why London (UK) rejcted/quit the Euro Merkel says will campaign for financial transaction tax | Reuters Jun 11, 2012 – ... using the issue as a way to get euro crisis legislation through parliament. ... transaction tax)," Merkel said in Frankfurt, adding that Germany ... EU Ministers Clear Way for Transaction Tax in Some States ... Jun 22, 2012 – Germany and Austria today said a transaction tax needs to move forward in some form so their lawmakers will approve the the 500 billion-euro ... 2.) another "scary" part is that the "financial industry" in US represents significant portion of GDP</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348765631991</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:07:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348765734790-29</Id><Topic><Title>What happened to the loud mouther Teabagger GOP?</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348765127816</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:58:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am pretty sure most of them are drunk. They still want to see Obummer's birth certificate? HEY? If you are born to an American citizen, you are not a naturalized citizen and so by definition you are a Natural citizen. Obummer's mama was natural born American born on American soli to American parents. Thius, Obummer, no matter where the fluck he was born, is a natural born American you ignorant whitttte trash teabaaging nimrods. BUT oh well--when I talk to one of them I say--he is not an american, he is a commi, he hates America--and I am voting for him. That pretty much ends their crying. Speaking of crying--why is it Ricky SUCKTORUM is not yelling his teabaggi8ng sheet nowadays. Nobody likes a loser do they RICKY!</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1348765734790</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:08:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348766021761-30</Id><Title>bought a tablet for fun but it's getting dustty now as i keep going back to my PC and laptop</Title><Msg>i think i'll have to do some travelling and play with it to justify the purchase./</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1348766021761</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348766053557-31</Id><Topic><Title>What happened to the loud mouther Teabagger GOP?</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348765127816</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:58:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look who's talking, loud mouth. The media has set you up for MASSSIVE heart break with their bogus polls. This is going to be hilarious.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348766053557</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:14:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348766193152-32</Id><Topic><Title>bought a tablet for fun but it's getting dustty now as i keep going back to my PC and laptop</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1348766021761</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>use it as a cutting board in the kitchen</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348766193152</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348766355823-33</Id><Topic><Title>What happened to the loud mouther Teabagger GOP?</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348765127816</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:58:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope so.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1348766355823</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:19:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348766620371-34</Id><Topic><Title>What happened to the loud mouther Teabagger GOP?</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348765127816</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:58:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So now the Fuxed up news poll is against you too. HAAAA HAAAA Get over it--you are a L O S E R but REAL Americans are winners as Rombo loses and Obummer wins. Make sure you do not talk to your woman about this Obama hating you have because likely she is voting for him.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348766620371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348766788334-35</Id><Topic><Title>What happened to the loud mouther Teabagger GOP?</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348765127816</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:58:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>uhhhh, yeah..."winners" talk down to others like you do. The joke of life is on you, and even YOU know it. Here's hoping you find someone to talk to other than those you insult on the internet. Typical out of control Liberal is all you are. Par for the course.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348766788334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:26:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348766859605-36</Id><Title>Otellini and other telecom execs have met with Acer on Smartphones</Title><Msg>Not many can argue that Intel Corp. (Nasdaq: INTC) is a world-leader in computer chips and processors. They might, however, be able to argue that it's presence in smartphones and mobile devices puts it much further down the rankings to the likes of Qualcomm (Nasdaq: QCOM) and ARM Holdings (Nasdaq: ARMH). Well, that's something CEO Paul Otellini is fixing to change. According to Digitimes Thursday, Otellini and other telecom execs have met with Acer brass in Taiwan over putting some of Intel's chips into entry-level and mid-range smartphones. Despite the urging from Otellini, sources said that Acer is content on focusing on its core PC business for now. However, Acer might move gradually into smartphones with a focus on China, where it hopes to become a top-10 brand vendor in the region by FY14. China is a challenging market for many smartphone vendors, including locals ZTE, HTC, and ASUStek. Different network standards as well as lack of subsidies makes packing features into a low-cost and appeal device challenging. Intel currently powers devices from Motorola (Nasdaq: GOOG) and Lenovo, and will be in Microsoft's (Nasdaq: MSFT) upcoming Surface Windows 8 Pro tablet, expected to debut next year. Checking out Intel's own website indicates its footprint isn't very large and striking key deals will be a driver for growth...whichever smartphone market they land in. Shares are up about 0.4 percent Thursday morning. News Provided by Acquire Media Corporation</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348766859605</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:27:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348766907956-37</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see the write up on this (INTC)</Title><Username>deniceujk5465</Username><Timestamp>1348665517051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent. I will check it out now.</Msg><Username>brigetterss5338</Username><Timestamp>1348766907956</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:28:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348766910693-38</Id><Topic><Title>USA Today: High Frequency Trading Insanity</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348756096216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:28:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice to see Waldo's foolish frustractions leading to an oversold move up in INTC.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348766910693</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348767286345-39</Id><Title>HFT will soon have to move away from Intel and it WILL fly. SEC Meeting to discuss is GREAT news</Title><Msg>Thankszzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>baltimoreravens_suck_coggg</Username><Timestamp>1348767286345</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:34:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348767697831-40</Id><Topic><Title>Letter to SEC (Updated)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348755177608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:12:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you know if ww ever gets married he may have to slow down his writing of all those market moving letters</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348767697831</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:41:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348767754123-41</Id><Topic><Title>Letter to SEC (Updated)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348755177608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:12:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$3 eps, LOL</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348767754123</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:42:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348768231563-42</Id><Topic><Title>What Was the Worst-Performing Tech Stock on the Dow This September?</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348763902460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:38:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What will be the best in Oct?? Yeah thats right Intel.. Watch and learn NOOB how WS works.</Msg><Username>verioinc</Username><Timestamp>1348768231563</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:50:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348769338631-43</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy capitulates, says buy INTEL</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1317740904000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-10-04 11:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lmaolmao</Msg><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1348769338631</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:08:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348769444312-44</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy capitulates, says buy INTEL</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1317740904000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-10-04 11:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROFLLLLLLLLLLLLLLL</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1348769444312</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:10:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348769621024-45</Id><Topic><Title>Letter to SEC (Updated)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348755177608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:12:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Man, grow up. Investing is gambling. There is no guarantee of making money.</Msg><Username>furball_80110</Username><Timestamp>1348769621024</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348769999472-46</Id><Topic><Title>Letter to SEC (Updated)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348755177608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:12:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Man, grow up. Investing is gambling. There is no guarantee of making money." *** No one is looking for guarantees of making money, dufus. Just that the dice aren't loaded. Apparently you are some Wall Street wingnut who thinks it's okay to stack the deck. It's not...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348769999472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:19:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348770390997-47</Id><Topic><Title>Letter to SEC (Updated)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348755177608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:12:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Furball.. Wallis is the board's resident pumper/crybaby. He's married to Intel and has no clue that other stocks exist. His cries of "manipulation" have echoed across this message board for years. First Rule Here: If you disagree with Wallis YOU ARE WRONG! Are you any relation to Hairball Dude?</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348770390997</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:26:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348771487841-48</Id><Topic><Title>USA Today: High Frequency Trading Insanity</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348756096216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:28:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amen amen amen....and, though I voted for the guy, Obama's lack of attention to this numero uno priority is scandalous. His admin doesn't seem to care, or even understand, the system and economy we have...it would take a mere phone call to the Sleasey Exchange Commission and REINSTATE THE UPTICK RULE!!! MR. PRESIDENT!!! [The indictment that Obama has a "centrally planned economy" philosophy seems in evidence. His admin also steals BASIC RESEARCH funding from such things as Space, Nuclear, Particle physics, and spends it on applied %^&amp;* such as Solyndra and highly efficient gas engines...stuff that never sees a market. I voted for the guy, and I cannot bring myself to vote for the train-wreck called Romney, but Obama is not effective, a mere 4 on the Clinton scale.] If I thought it would do any good, I would write a letter to Obama and try to tutor him in the capitalist equity system, which is collectively all of us and all of America's wealth konw-how and wellbeing...THROW THESE HEDGIES AND HFT BUMS OUT NOW!!!!</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348771487841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348771759733-49</Id><Title>Romney's fanboys now say the Polls are wrong.</Title><Msg>That is what everybody says when the polls show you losing. But wait until Rombo makes an assssh of himself in the first debat. Then he will implode down 10% to Obummer. And he will be a joke in the debates no matter what he says because the videos of him saying just the opposit will be all over the net and the media after the debate. If he goes angry at Obummer, women will hate it and Romney loses by even more. If he does not attack Obummer, then the rightwing teabagging imbreds in his party get angry and simply stay home instead of voting. If you are a GOPtard, you have no one to blame for this disaster but your own party leaders who ran this clown. Rombo is heading into the trash bin of massive losers in elections. Dems will be sitting down on election night with drinks in hand and dinners and parties. They will be laughing as Florida, Virginia, and North Carolina all go to Obum. Before they announce Michigan and Ohio to The Pres, the Repubs will be home crying like little clowns. Then to make it even funnier, South Carolina will shock the KKK nuts of the South by going to OB too. Here is how you will know it is OVER!!!! Film crews all over the nation showing Dem faces in long freaking lines to vote. People in Chicago will even stop shooting each other down for a night of fun. You want your nation back do you KKk Birther rightwing trashballs? HAAA HAA Go watch Fuxed up news and cry. Read the Raspukking polls and wonder why? How could this landslide happen? Just go to work the next day and see all those ladies laughing and smiling and you will know that your own wives and daughters took you down boys. They say Rombo and said HELLLT NOOO! That crazzzy old whiitey dimmmwit is not taking away by doctor care and my birthcontrol. Your own wife voted for Obummer Teaboy. HAAA HAAAA Oh well--at least she will give you could sex after she wins.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348771759733</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:49:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348772802670-50</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's fanboys now say the Polls are wrong.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348771759733</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:49:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiots on the right really thought they were going to win. They thoght the leftwing trash were going to stay home again with their President running? No way. OB is more than a Pres. He is an iconic symbol of all the left has ever hoped for. That night when Clinton told about the Pres and how he deserves our votes, the left held hands and decided to VOTE and to VOTE in record numbers. That is why the POLLS--all of them, are missing how big a blowout this election is going to be. Women will have record turnouts for the president. African Americans and Hispanic voters will break all records as well. The only way a party based upon small thinking and hate could ever hope to win this election was to stop voter turnout. Yes--there will be long lines on election day and those lines will be women and Browns and blacks. College students and Educate white men will hold hand in lines too. They want to send a message to the Citizens united gang. They want to tell the super rich right-wing people that yes WE CAN!</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1348772802670</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:06:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348773357778-51</Id><Title>intc up say 2 percent</Title><Msg>CRUS up about 6 percent. all thanks to AAPL.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348773357778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348774837331-52</Id><Title>Intel and its Partners Unveil Range of Tablet Designs and Experiences Running Windows* 8</Title><Msg>A few minutes ago ..... Intel and its Partners Unveil Range of Tablet Designs and Experiences Running Windows* 8 Acer*, ASUS*, Dell*, Fujitsu*, HP*, Lenovo*, LG Electronics*, Samsung* and ZTE* to Offer Host of New, Full-Featured Intel-Based Tablets NEWS HIGHLIGHTS Intel-powered tablets and tablet convertibles offer users the best Windows* 8 experience and deliver a range of new features from enhanced media capabilities to security built for the enterprise. Intel-based tablets with Windows 8 are optimized for mobility, provide support for the Windows user interface and maintain flexibility to support for the millions of existing applications, and a full range of devices and other full-featured peripherals such as printers. New Intel® Atom™ processor Z2760 architected specifically for Windows 8 offers outstanding battery life, and always-on technology in sleek designs that are lighter, more responsive and enable a multitude of options for mobile users. Intel Corporation and its OEM partners today unveiled the first wave of new tablets and tablet convertible designs based on Intel Core® vPro™, Intel® Core™ and Intel® Atom™ processors, including the new Atom processor Z2760 (formerly codenamed “Clover Trail”). The new Intel Atom processor-based devices provide consumers and business users with a wide choice of innovative, sleek and stylish designs with long battery life and class-leading performance. Additionally, they will be able to experience Windows* 8 while continuing to run all the programs they know and love. “This is just the beginning of Intel’s effort in the tablet market, and our goal is to deliver products that fit the spectrum of evolving needs of both consumers and business users without compromising on compatibility, experience or battery life,” said Erik Reid, general manager, Application Processor Platforms for Intel’s Mobile and Communications Group. “When people or corporations buy a device with Intel Inside®, they’re getting the best of Windows 8 features with a computing experience that just works.” Intel Atom Z2760: Powerful Computing On-the-Go The Intel Atom Processor Z2760 allows for the thinnest, lightest tablets built on Intel® architecture – as thin as 8.5mm and as light as 1.5 pounds – making carrying and storing a powerful tablet less cumbersome and more convenient. As more and more people take their devices on-the-go, such considerations as battery life and size have become increasingly important, and devices using the Intel Atom Z2760 offer a full-featured tablet computing experience that doesn’t compromise its performance over battery life. The dual-core, four-thread SoC provides exceptionally long battery life with more than 3 weeks of connected standby and more than 10 hours of local HD video playback.1 Tablets and tablet convertibles powered by Intel Atom processors and running Windows 8 deliver a highly intuitive and responsive experience using touch, keyboard and mouse or a pen, while providing capabilities such as Intel® Burst Technology, Intel® Hyper-threading Technology. Utilizing the multitasking capability of Intel architecture, people will experience incredibly fast response, allowing them to swiftly load and switch among their favorite applications. Enhanced Security, Collaboration and Software Support in the Enterprise Intel is enabling a choice of innovative mobile designs for the enterprise, including those powered by Intel Atom, Intel Core, and Intel Core vPro processors. Intel architecture provides corporations with the flexibility and compatibility they are used to, resulting in a lower total cost of ownership (TCO) coupled with the personalized productivity that people crave. Intel tablets with Windows 8 support the millions of existing applications, devices and full-featured components used within corporations and include the security and manageability features corporate IT managers demand. Additionally, these devices easily integrate into existing corporate infrastructures, providing the ability to join a domain, access shared network resources and run both new Windows Store apps and familiar Windows desktop applications side by side. The Intel Atom Processor Z2760 tablets deliver the mobility and experience that business users desire and set a new bar for addressing IT demand for built-in security and manageability with Windows 8. The new Intel Atom Processor Z2760 is built to seamlessly integrate into a business computing environment. Intel Atom Z2760 offers Secure Boot and firmware-based Intel Platform Trust Technology (PTT). Intel Core processor-based tablets with Windows 8 will provide the intelligent performance and responsive power for the most productive and personalized employee experience. In addition, tablets based on the Intel Core vPro processors deliver the most comprehensive and flexible enterprise-class hardware-assisted security, manageability and virtualization capabilities for business computing. With Intel vPro technology, Intel Core-based processors provide remote system access and management, regardless of power or OS state, and offer the most robust set of security features including Enhanced Intel® Anti-Theft Technology, Intel® Secure Key, Intel® OS Guard, Enhanced Intel® Identity Protection Technology, and Intel® Trusted Execution Technology. Intel is actively engaged with a broad cross-section of the software ecosystem to provide the best experience possible for applications running on Intel-based devices. With over 7,000 member companies, the Intel® Software Partner program helps support optimization efforts by concentrating resources, references, and tools for software optimization into key Technology Focus Areas. Additionally, through the Intel® Software Network, developers can connect with communities, tools, training and events to help deliver more efficient, higher-performing software to the market more quickly.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348774837331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348775443604-53</Id><Topic><Title>Letter to SEC (Updated)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348755177608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:12:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No relation.</Msg><Username>furball_80110</Username><Timestamp>1348775443604</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348775758014-54</Id><Topic><Title>Letter to SEC (Updated)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348755177608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:12:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course a fund with lots of money can exert some control on the share price. So can the company itself, by dilution or repurchase of shares. Share price is arbitrary for the most part: what people believe it should be. There are also value traps like GLW, that persistently lag the market (and INTC may now be in that category ... but I bought in because I expect a bump from the Windows 8 release). When more people sell, the stock price goes down ... when more people buy, it goes up. Shorting a stock is like selling. Sure, there are naked shorts (persistent "failure to deliver") - there shouldn't be, as the SEC is supposed to police that. But, if you concerned that naked shorts are hurting the stock price, look at the short interest: is it less than 1%? If so, then the short position has no effect on the stock price, naked or not. Anyways ... if you are going to be a cry baby about the investing game, then stop playing. It is gambling pure and simple.</Msg><Username>furball_80110</Username><Timestamp>1348775758014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:55:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348776891689-55</Id><Topic><Title>Intel and its Partners Unveil Range of Tablet Designs and Experiences Running Windows* 8</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348774837331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:40:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows tablets with Intel CPU's is a definite game changer. These products can reset expectations of what a tablet should be for applications compatibility and working with one's network. The pace of Intel's innovation in mobility will increase dramatically from this point forward.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1348776891689</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:14:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348777058774-56</Id><Topic><Title>intc up say 2 percent</Title><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348773357778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hows that crus div working out?</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1348777058774</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:17:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348778830142-57</Id><Title>REPORT: America's lowest earners spent DOUBLE their income in 2011</Title><Msg>Don't worry, Obama will bail us out !!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348778830142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:47:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348779089584-58</Id><Topic><Title>Intel and its Partners Unveil Range of Tablet Designs and Experiences Running Windows* 8</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348774837331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:40:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Samsung tablet is a huge win for Intel. Picked up another 20K shares at $22.45 yesterday.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1348779089584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:51:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348779374496-59</Id><Title>ROMLEY: Oracle Achieves Record TPC-C Benchmark Result on 2 Processor System</Title><Msg>It looks like this Romley system takes the #2 slot in price/performance as well as fastest 2 socket system. Oracle Achieves Record TPC-C Benchmark Result on 2 Processor System Beats IBM DB2 on Performance and Price/Performance REDWOOD SHORES, CA -- (Marketwire) -- 09/27/12 -- Oracle (NASDAQ: ORCL) News Facts -- Showcasing the superior performance and price/performance of Oracle Database 11g Release 2 and Oracle Linux, Oracle announced a new record TPC-C benchmark result for a two-processor system(1). -- Oracle Database 11g Standard Edition One and Oracle Linux with the Unbreakable Enterprise Kernel Release 2, running on a Cisco UCS(TM) C240 M3 Rack Server with two Intel(R) Xeon(R) E5-2690 2.9 GHz processors achieved 1.6 Million transactions per minute (tpmC) with a price/performance of $0.47/tpmC. -- This result delivered 34 percent more performance at 32 percent less cost per transaction than IBM DB2 on a 2 processor POWER7-based system. (2). In addition, this record breaking result outperformed IBM DB2 on a similar Flex System configuration utilizing the same number of identical Intel processors and the same amount of memory capacity (3). -- Oracle Database 11g Standard Edition One is an affordable, full-featured database for servers with up to two processors. It is simple to manage and is upwardly compatible with other Oracle Database editions. -- In addition to this new record result, Oracle Database 11g is the overall performance (4) and price-performance (5) leader with the TPC-C benchmark. Supporting Quotes -- "This outstanding benchmark result is another proof point that Oracle Database 11g delivers the best performance and price-performance for the high-volume two-socket server market. It also demonstrates that Oracle on Intel beats IBM DB2 on Power7 both in performance and price-performance," said Juan Loaiza, senior vice president, Systems Technology, Oracle. -- "This benchmark result is yet another proof point that Cisco UCS is an industry-leading platform for Oracle applications, offering breakthrough performance at lower cost. With its unique management capabilities, Cisco UCS can significantly improve operational efficiencies, reducing the time to deploy new applications compared to traditional server solutions," said Satinder Sethi, Vice President, Data Center Solutions, Cisco.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348779374496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348780908768-60</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see the write up on this (INTC)</Title><Username>deniceujk5465</Username><Timestamp>1348665517051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An article that's worth a read.</Msg><Username>nubiaumh8014</Username><Timestamp>1348780908768</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348781593838-61</Id><Topic><Title>REPORT: America's lowest earners spent DOUBLE their income in 2011</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348778830142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:47:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The actual data if more interesting than the catchy headlines. These white, college educated 50-somethings are receiving some help. It is unclear who they are receiving help from (savings, family, charities, ....) but it does not appear to be all from the government. I am not sure why you are saying "us"? Are you in the lowest quntile? That would surprise me if you said yes. From the BLS data Table 1. Quintiles of income before taxes: Average annual expenditures and characteristics, Consumer Expenditure Survey, 2011 The average income before taxes: $9,805 ($817 per month) income after taxes: $10,074 the pay no income taxes on their $817 per month Average age: 51.7 years average number of people living off the $817 per month is 1.7 people. 37% male, 63% female. 39% are homeowners and 60% have no mortgage 20% black, 80% white, asian and other races 13% are Latino. Education: 9% didn't reach high school 45% reached high school 45% college 1% no school 65% have cars Average annual expenditures: $22, 001 $3,547 Food $8,771 housing $2,284 utilities $850 Apparel and services $3,256 transportation $1,489 health care</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348781593838</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348788097017-62</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see the write up on this (INTC)</Title><Username>deniceujk5465</Username><Timestamp>1348665517051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool picks. I love it.</Msg><Username>trishcak642792</Username><Timestamp>1348788097017</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:21:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348789082749-63</Id><Topic><Title>REPORT: America's lowest earners spent DOUBLE their income in 2011</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348778830142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:47:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alexander, I have always respected your post. I did not rate it this time but I do find the infor hard to believe. You're telling me people that make $817 a month spend $731 a month on rent/mortgage? $296 a month on food. $271 on transportation. $190 on utilities. and $195 on health care and other. $2500 a month total. My question is are they going 8k a year into debt? I find this very hard to believe.</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1348789082749</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:38:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348792048717-64</Id><Topic><Title>What Was the Worst-Performing Tech Stock on the Dow This September?</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348763902460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:38:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doubtful. Unlike stocks that suffer minor setbacks, there are likely plenty of disappointed INTC longs who would love to get out at breakeven, having bought the "dips" that led to a rout. On the good news front, the semis did outperform the qqq today, the bad news, INTC lagged the group, as AAPL related chip stocks outperformed the group.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348792048717</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 20:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348796087424-65</Id><Title>All it takes to end HFT is</Title><Msg>simple phone call from POTUS to Mr. Smegmatic #$%$ Sleaseball III, Chm. of the SEC, with the order "Institute the uptick rule today!" click.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348796087424</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:34:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348796337780-66</Id><Title>INTEL WILL BE SINGLE DIGIT STOCK IN 2013:THIS IS THE REAL PROBLEM FOR INTEL NEXT $30 SoC or $250 CPU?</Title><Msg>On Pricing and ARM Intel claims that there's no reason that Atom based Windows 8 tablets, from a hardware bill of materials perspective, should be any more expensive than their ARM based counterparts. The important takeaway is that Intel is significantly reducing the price of the Atom Z2760 due to competitive pressure from ARM. Most ARM smartphone SoCs seem to be priced in the $15 - $30 range, and I'd expect the Z2760 to fall somewhere in that range. Intel has shipped cheap CPUs in the past, but I don't know that they've ever shipped something this cheap. ARM's impact on Intel is measurable, it is the new AMD.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1348796337780</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:38:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348796481364-67</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL BE SINGLE DIGIT STOCK IN 2013:THIS IS THE REAL PROBLEM FOR INTEL NEXT $30 SoC or $250 CPU?</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1348796337780</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:38:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Volume for hig margin cpu's goes bust and may pick in $30 soc but bottom line for intel takes beating in margin hell and what dividend? what about debt at intel?</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1348796481364</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:41:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348797489083-68</Id><Topic><Title>REPORT: America's lowest earners spent DOUBLE their income in 2011</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348778830142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:47:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5th attempt I took the information from the BLS website that was the source of the original data. I have fat fingers and my calculations and interpretations should be confirmed. I am far from an expert of what sources of tax free income are. Part of the delta is from federal tax credits. The 51.7 year age would lead me to think about non-taxable retirement income. Reverse mortgages are getting a lot of advertisement time. There has to be other sources. I know that when one of my children have a large, unexpected expense, they give me a call. I help out. There is income data for other years but I did not go digging past the 2011. The data is for ANNUAL numbers and I divided some by 12 to get a monthly number. Google the following phrase (if you shorten the URL and go up one directory level, you can see a number of files or you can down from the top): "2011 Quintiles of income before taxes" Consumer Expenditure Survey The Consumer Expenditure Survey (CE) program consists of two surveys, the Quarterly Interview Survey and the Diary Survey, that provide information on the buying habits of American consumers, including data on their expenditures, income, and consumer unit (families and single consumers) characteristics. The survey data are collected for the Bureau of Labor Statistics by the U.S. Census Bureau. The CE is important because it is the only Federal survey to provide information on the complete range of consumers' expenditures and incomes, as well as the characteristics of those consumers. It is used by economic policymakers examining the impact of policy changes on economic groups, by businesses and academic researchers studying consumers' spending habits and trends, by other Federal agencies, and, perhaps most importantly, to regularly revise the Consumer Price Index market basket of goods and services and their relative importance. The most recent data tables are for 2011, and were made available on September 25, 2012. See Featured CE Tables and Economic News Releases sections on the CE home page for current data tables and news release. The 2011 public-use microdata is the most recent and was released on September 25, 2012.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348797489083</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348799104109-69</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL BE SINGLE DIGIT STOCK IN 2013:THIS IS THE REAL PROBLEM FOR INTEL NEXT $30 SoC or $250 CPU?</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1348796337780</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:38:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What price and how many shares are you short at, Fatboy? Put up or shut up.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348799104109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 22:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348800091960-70</Id><Title>Clover Trail</Title><Msg>Intel and its Partners Unveil Range of Tablet Designs and Experiences Running Windows* 8 Acer*, ASUS*, Dell*, Fujitsu*, HP*, Lenovo*, LG Electronics*, Samsung* and ZTE* to Offer Host of New, Full-Featured Intel-Based Tablets NEWS HIGHLIGHTS  Intel-powered tablets and tablet convertibles offer users the full Microsoft Windows* 8 experience and deliver a range of new features from enhanced media capabilities to security built for the enterprise.  Intel-based Windows 8 and Windows 8 Pro tablets are optimized for mobility, provide support for the new Windows user interface and maintain flexibility to support for the millions of existing applications, and a full range of devices and other full-featured peripherals such as printers.  New Intel® Atom™ processor Z2760 architected specifically for Windows 8 offers outstanding battery life, and always-on technology in sleek designs that are lighter, more responsive and enable a multitude of options for mobile users. SANTA CLARA, Calif., Sept. 27, 2012 – Intel Corporation and its OEM partners today unveiled the first wave of new Windows* 8 tablets and tablet convertible designs based on Intel Core® vPro™, Intel® Core™ and Intel® Atom™ processors, including the new Atom processor Z2760 (formerly codenamed “Clover Trail”). The new Intel Atom processor-based devices provide consumers and business users with a wide choice of innovative, sleek and stylish designs with long battery life and class-leading performance. Additionally, they will be able to experience all that is new in Windows 8 while continuing to run all the programs they know and love. “This is just the beginning of Intel’s effort in the tablet market, and our goal is to deliver products that fit the spectrum of evolving needs of both consumers and business users without compromising on compatibility, experience or battery life,” said Erik Reid, general manager, Application Processor Platforms for Intel’s Mobile and Communications Group. “When people or corporations buy a device with Intel Inside®, they’re getting the best of the new Windows 8 features together with a computing experience that just works.” Intel Atom Z2760: Powerful Computing On-the-Go The Intel Atom Processor Z2760 allows for the thinnest, lightest tablets built on Intel® architecture -- as thin as 8.5mm and as light as 1.5 pounds – making carrying and storing a powerful tablet less cumbersome and more convenient. As more and more people take their devices on-the-go, such considerations as battery life and size have become increasingly important, and devices using the Intel Atom Z2760 offer a full-featured tablet computing experience that doesn’t compromise its performance over battery life. The dual-core, four-thread SoC provides exceptionally long battery life with more than 3 weeks of connected standby and more than 10 hours of local HD video playback.1 Tablets and tablet convertibles powered by Intel Atom processors and running Windows 8 deliver a highly intuitive and responsive experience using touch, keyboard and mouse or a pen, while providing capabilities such as Intel® Burst Technology, Intel® Hyper-threading Technology. Utilizing the multitasking capability of Intel architecture, people will experience Intel/Page 2 incredibly fast response, allowing them to swiftly load and switch among their favorite applications. Security, Collaboration and Software Support in the Enterprise Intel is enabling a choice of innovative mobile designs for the enterprise, including those powered by Intel Atom, Intel Core, and Intel Core vPro processors. Intel architecture provides corporations with the flexibility and compatibility they are used to, resulting in a lower total cost of ownership (TCO) coupled with the personalized productivity that people crave. Intel-based Windows 8 and Windows 8 Pro tablets support the millions of existing applications, devices and full-featured components used within corporations and include the security and manageability features corporate IT managers demand. Additionally, these devices easily integrate into existing corporate infrastructures, providing the ability to join a domain, access shared network resources and run both new Windows Store apps and familiar Windows desktop applications side by side. The Intel Atom Processor Z2760 tablets deliver the mobility and experience that business users desire and set a new bar for addressing IT demand for built-in security and manageability with Windows 8 Pro. The new Intel Atom Processor Z2760 is built to seamlessly integrate into a business computing environment. Intel Atom Z2760 offers Secure Boot and firmware-based Intel Platform Trust Technology (PTT). Intel Core processor-based Windows 8 tablets will provide the intelligent performance and responsive power for the most productive and personalized employee experience. In addition, tablets based on the Intel Core vPro processors deliver the most comprehensive and flexible enterprise-class hardware-assisted security, manageability and virtualization capabilities for business computing. With Intel vPro technology, Intel Core-based processors provide remote system access and management, regardless of power or OS state, and offer the most robust set of security features including Enhanced Intel® Anti-Theft Technology, Intel® Secure Key, Intel® OS Guard, Enhanced Intel® Identity Protection Technology, and Intel® Trusted Execution Technology. Intel is actively engaged with a broad cross-section of the software ecosystem to provide the best experience possible for applications running on Intel-based devices. With over 7,000 member companies, the Intel® Software Partner program helps support optimization efforts by concentrating resources, references, and tools for software optimization into key Technology Focus Areas. Additionally, through the Intel® Software Network, developers can connect with communities, tools, training and events to help deliver more efficient, higher-performing software to the market more quickly. 1. Based on power measurements on a 10 inch Intel reference design at 200 nits with WiFi on, 30Wh battery. anandtechDOTcom/show/6340/intel-details-atom-z2760-clovertrail-for-windows-8-tablets Intel Generated SPEC CPU2000 Comparison - Normalized to Snapdragon S4 SPECint SPECint_rate Qualcomm Snapdragon S4 (1.5GHz) 1.00 1.00 Dual-Core 40nm ARM Cortex A9 (1.8GHz) 1.14 1.14 NVIDIA Tegra 3 (1.3GHz) 0.86 1.25 Intel Atom Z2760 (1.8GHz) 1.20 1.54 Intel Generated Power Consumption Comparison Idle Web HD Video (Screen On) Browsing Playback ASUS Transformer Pad Infinity 2.7W 3.4W 3.1W Apple iPad 2 2.5W 2.6W 2.5W Apple iPad (2012) 4.3W 4.5W 5.9W Intel Clovertrail FFRD 2.3W 2.8W 3.0W newsroomDOTintelDOTcom/docs/DOC-3021 downloadDOTintelDOTcom/newsroom/kits/atom/z2760/pdfs/Intel-Atom-Z2760_FactSheet.pdf</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348800091960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 22:41:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348804055851-71</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL BE SINGLE DIGIT STOCK IN 2013:THIS IS THE REAL PROBLEM FOR INTEL NEXT $30 SoC or $250 CPU?</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1348796337780</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:38:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel makes cash-over-fist at $20 a chip because they essentially get paid "twice" owning their fabs. Idiots like you &amp; analysts dont understand that concept versus the failed ARM-fabless model. Also, the millions of tablets/smartphone chips that Intel will be flooding the market will also lead to an exponential increase in $300-$500 Intel server chips, which is now 25% of their business &amp; will double in the next few years.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1348804055851</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:47:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348804680643-72</Id><Title>19-29-22-24-23-23-24-26-29-33</Title><Msg>stock price fluctuation where was is going</Msg><Username>raygeo2003</Username><Timestamp>1348804680643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:58:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>