<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-01"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349064218083-1</Id><Title>INTC Dead - Futures all red!! Short a will!!!!</Title><Msg>Going to drop big tomorrow!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1349064218083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 00:03:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349064244674-2</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will foundry chips for Toyota, too</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349038775169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, you are correct. Rent out the fabs. Don't sell the best process to competitors. Milk the IA until it dies, except keep the server stuff a cut above everyone else. Don't tell anyone you are fabbing for fabless companies. This is a good plan for getting to $40, since they can steal market share from TSMC, UMC, etc. Desktops and laptops are a dying breed. No future there.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349064244674</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 00:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349064418976-3</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Dead - Futures all red!! Short a will!!!!</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1349064218083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 00:03:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't believe this stock is sooooo bad, should drop $1.75 tomorrow and $4.00 over the next month or more. market ready for a big pull back.</Msg><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1349064418976</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 00:06:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349065134753-4</Id><Topic><Title>this is why its going to 40 2013</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1349032454079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:14:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it certainly will.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349065134753</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 00:18:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349065513162-5</Id><Title>INTC will close GREEN!!!</Title><Msg>Begins a new chapter!</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349065513162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 00:25:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349067121552-6</Id><Title>HP aims for business users with ElitePad 900 Windows 8 tablet</Title><Msg>Expect HP's ElitePad 900 tablet to join several other business-focused mobile devices over the next few months. Intel's mobile push, along with that of Microsoft and Windows 8, will ensure no shortage of similar products. Whether HP can differentiate its tablet is another question, but from what we've seen of the ElitePad 900, we can at least say that it's taking the challenge seriously. In terms of hard specs, the ElitePad 900 offers a 10.1-inch, 1,280x800-pixel Gorilla Glass-coated display. HP says the tablet as a whole will weigh around 1.5 pounds, and comes in at just 9.2-millimeters thick. HP isn't offering specific details regarding the CPU (beyond that it uses "next-generation Intel Atom mobile processors). It's safe to assume the new Atom CPUs in question come from Intel's Clover Trail family. For other specs, the ElitePad 900 will have 2GB of onboard memory, up to a 64GB solid state hard drive, and Intel integrated graphics. HP has also mapped out an ecosystem of accessories for the ElitePad 900, including two keyboard "jackets" that also add a few extra connectivity options, as well as a ruggedized case, a full-fledged docking station, and an "HP Executive Tablet Pen." HP says it will reveal pricing for those add-ons and for the tablet itself closer to its January 2013 launch date.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349067121552</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 00:52:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349067532774-7</Id><Title>Cockroaches Go Crazy - Promise to Price in an $8 billion Revenue Miss</Title><Msg>Beware the drooling mob. The Wall Street cockroaches, shills , analysts, shorts and other assorted #$%$ are apparently not satisfied with having priced in a $7 billion revenue miss into Q3 earnings. They now say we must have an $8 billion miss priced in or maybe $10 billion or maybe even a $50 billion revenue miss. Or maybe that the stock will go negative. Yeah, that's the ticket! Watch out - the cockroaches, armed with their new user IDs are swarming...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349067532774</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 00:58:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349068286093-8</Id><Title>TSMC Woes Continue</Title><Msg>TSMC is projecting a decline in 4Q 2012 and 1Q 2013 revenues while saying that demand for 28nm still cannot be met. Just another indication of ARM's fabrication problems as they simply can't ramp the new process up fast enough. Meanwhile Intel is easily ramping 22nm and will have five fabs in production. *** "The low-voltage performance of Intel's 22-nanometer chip-baking process turned out better that the company had predicted, and the development of next year's 14-nanometer process technology is proceeding swimmingly, thankyouverymuch. So said Chipzilla's head of process technology, Mark Bohr, speaking at a tech session during the company's Intel Developer Forum in San Francisco on Wednesday. And he should know. Bohr is a senior fellow in Intel's Technology and Manufacturing Group, and the director of the company's process architecture and integration efforts. In simple terms, he creates the stuff that chips are made of."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349068286093</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 01:11:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349068899116-9</Id><Title>Intel's Strong Advantage in the Enterprise Market</Title><Msg>Intel and its PC partners will move aggressively to win business customers, which Intel claims is a key advantage for Windows 8 running on its chips. "It brings over what you already have...millions of desktop applications," Chris Walker, general manager of Intel's application processors for the mobile and communications group, said in a phone interview. And that makes Windows 8 tablets from Hewlett-Packad, Dell, Lenovo, and Asus immediately usable at corporations. "I can access my back-end ERP [enterprise resource planning] system, updating it in real time, pulling down all of the corporate information I need and managing like I do on a notebook," he said. And this "flexibility" between consumer and corporate worlds is what separates Intel-based Windows 8 tablets and convertibles from Apple's iPad, Walker said. But Intel has another, more long-term ace up its sleeve. It is able to take advantage of in-house chip manufacturing, which is probably the most advanced in the world. Apple, by comparison, must farm out chip manufacturing for its A series processors to outside companies -- that it has no direct control over -- like legal-foe Samsung. "As we move to 22-nanometer [manufacturing tech] and [future] 14-nanometer, we can take increasing advantage of [in-house manufacturing]," added Walker. Intel currently supplies processors to all of Apple's Mac and MacBook lines. And, needless to say, it probably wouldn't mind making chips for future iPhones and iPads.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349068899116</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 01:21:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349069113181-10</Id><Title>A New PC Tablet Era</Title><Msg>[Intel's mobility strategy gains strength...] On Thursday, Intel's hardware partners showed off their mid-range Windows 8 hybrid devices at a Clover Trail coming-out party. Today we reveal the hardware in all its photographic splendor. Each tablet features Intel's Z2760 Atom processor (aka Clover Trail), a dual-core, four-thread system-on-chip running up to 1.8GHz. Clover Trail devices won't pack the performance oomph of Ultrabooks, laptops and hybrids running Core-caliber processors, but the products you see in this gallery should deliver excellent battery life—in excess of 10 hours. Perhaps more importantly, Clover Trail devices could emerge as winning travel PCs: thin, light tablets married to accompanying keyboard docks. Put everything together, and you might be able to leave your iPad and Ultrabook at home, and simply take one of these hybrids on the road. From PC World</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349069113181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 01:25:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349085681943-11</Id><Title>Obama leads Slick Willard by 9% in Ohio...</Title><Msg>GOPers have no reason to got to the polls next month. Mittens already lost.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1349085681943</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 06:01:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349096451027-12</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL BE SINGLE DIGIT STOCK IN 2013:THIS IS THE REAL PROBLEM FOR INTEL NEXT $30 SoC or $250 CPU?</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1348796337780</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:38:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>APU can push Intel to lower prices for Core i3 Monica Chen, Taipei; Joseph Tsai, DIGITIMES [Friday 28 September 2012] AMD has unveiled its desktop Trinity APUs, and Taiwan-based motherboard makers hope that the launch will bring pressure on Intel to decrease prices for its similar-level processors. The sources hope that price competition between Intel and AMD processors can heat up the PC DIY channel and attract consumer demand to return. Since AMD has not launched any product that could seriously threaten Intel's market share during the past year, Intel has been rather tough with its processor prices to maintain high gross margins, and the lack of price competition has weakened demand in the PC DIY market. Adopting the new FM2 socket, AMD has released several Trinity APUs including quad-core A10-5800K, featuring integrated Radeon HD 7660D GPU, A10-5700, A8-5600K, A8-5500 and dual-core A4-5300. Currently, Intel Core i3 series processor prices range from US$117-138, while AMD's new Trinity APUs are priced at US$69-129. AMD new desktop Trinity APU prices, Sep 2012 (US$) CPU model Price A10-5800K 129 A10-5700 129 A8-5600K 109 A8-5500 109 A6-5400K 65 A4-5300 52 Athlon X4 750K 79 Athlon X4 740 69 Source: Upstream supply chain, compiled by Digitimes, September 2012</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349096451027</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:00:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349096519866-13</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL BE SINGLE DIGIT STOCK IN 2013:THIS IS THE REAL PROBLEM FOR INTEL NEXT $30 SoC or $250 CPU?</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1348796337780</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:38:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Price of quad-core smartphones in China may fall to US$100/unit Daniel Shen, Beijing; Jackie Chang, DIGITIMES [Friday 28 September 2012] Qualcomm and MediaTek have been competing over solutions for quad-core entry-level smartphones. China-based handset makers believe that, by the second half of 2013, there will be quad-core handsets priced around US$150/unit in China, and with increasing competition, it is likely the price of quad-core smartphones will fall to US$100/unit by the end of 2013. MediaTek's MT6588 quad-core chip and Qualcomm's recently announced MSM8x25Q will begin shipments in first-half 2013. With quad-core processors, Qualcomm can help customers develop models for various price ranges including models that can be priced at US$100-200/unit. According to Cristiano Amon, senior vice president of product management in the Cellular Products Group of Qualcomm CDMA Technologies (QCT), customers can go from R&amp;D to launch in a short period of time by adopting Qualcomm Reference Designs (QRD). Qualcomm's quad-core QRD is compatible with its current dual-core QRD, hence it is easy for customers to upgrade to the quad-core platform, said Amon. As for the shortage of 28nm process chips, Amon noted that demand growth began exceeding expectations starting in second-half 2012 which has caused the current shortage. Amon hopes that by the end of 2012, supply and demand can reach a balance.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349096519866</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:01:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349097371413-14</Id><Title>Fiscal Cliff Causing Uncertainity</Title><Msg>Corporations have stopped hiring and are again in a firing mode. EK, HP, BAC and many more are going to eliminate thousands of jobs. Europe has taken a toll on the US and China as well and this election #$%$ is not helping any. If Obama is elected its gonna be a lame duck congress, with nothing being acomplished. There is a disconnect between the markets and fundamentals. There is so much cash pumped into the pipeline and it has to find a place somewhere and its ending up in the mkts. But if you look at the Bond funds they are raking in the cash cause the fear is there that the fundamentals are going to catch up pretty soon. Intel is investing heavily for the future, both in New Mexico as well as Ireland and Arizona. Hopefully when and if the economy recovers it will pay off. Until and unless the congress get their act together we the citizens are gonna suffer. We need to get to the polls and get these lame ducks, the dead wood, the corrupt self centered punks in congress out so fresh blood with new ideas and who care for the USA can get in clear the crap that these dumb #$%$ have created and left behind. In these QE's that have been created only the banks are benefitting not the people. Bernanke has destabilized the dollar and created a mess with inflation on the horizon that is gonna take a severe toll. Today mkts will climb being the 1st of Oct as money will flow in from the pension plans, 401K plans etc. Watch out tomorrow. Have a nice day and stay cautious. Sentiment: Strong Buy .0 users liked this posts 0 users disliked this posts ReplyReport Abuse . .....We are in the process of testing our new message boards. Please pro</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1349097371413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:16:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349098311310-15</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff Causing Uncertainity</Title><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1349097371413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:16:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's funny, we've had 4 years of uncertainty.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349098311310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349098458958-16</Id><Topic><Title>TEENS or $30?</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349048419200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:40:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$3 eps and the march back to $29 are going to be fun</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349098458958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:34:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349098516633-17</Id><Topic><Title>FUTURES VERY REDDDDDDDDD!!!!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349045199618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure you can, you can wish for higher taxes. 22-Feb-12 05:04 pm Two out of every three people receiving stock dividend payments are rich, many totally, incredibly rich and should be paying more taxes instead of us soaking the middle class. I'm sick of the deadbeat rich who are unwilling to carry their fair share of the load... wallisweaver</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349098516633</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:35:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349098595238-18</Id><Topic><Title>FUTURES VERY REDDDDDDDDD!!!!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349045199618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>next time consult wit c_w, this was a terrible call</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349098595238</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:36:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349099396807-19</Id><Topic><Title>FUTURES VERY REDDDDDDDDD!!!!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349045199618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is very young or very damaged.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1349099396807</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:49:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349099651915-20</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see the write up on this (INTC)</Title><Username>deeannamvq129047</Username><Timestamp>1348927437277</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:03:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job. Informational article.</Msg><Username>elodiafgo02646</Username><Timestamp>1349099651915</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:54:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349100894522-21</Id><Title>The iPhone 5 Technology Rabbit Hole - PCM</Title><Msg>This SPECULATIVE Seeking Alpha article has some interesting guesses about iPhone 5 delay. He speculates that the iPhone5 was to have PCM memory which would have reduced power consumption substantially. A CLIP FROM THE ARTICLE: The iPhone 5 Technology Rabbit Hole,, September 10, 2012 The base PCM technology is owned by a company called Ovonyx, which was established by Intel (INTC), some ex-Micron employees and Energy Conversion Devices (ECD). ECD was put into bankruptcy this past February and the stock has gone dark as of last week. It is my opinion that this bankruptcy was orchestrated with the sole purpose of quietly extracting ECD's 38.6 percent interest in Ovonyx. This transaction was recently completed - Micron purchased the interest for just $12 million. Ethical (and speculative) rants aside, Micron (MU) is now positioned to capitalize on a hypothetical PCM-enabled iPhone. Even if this speculation proves to be false, the PCM technology is now real and expected to be a foregone conclusion in displacing a broad part of the $70+ billion DRAM and flash markets. IBM, for example, expects PCM to play a role in dramatically reducing the power consumption of data centers. Intel owns 45 percent of Ovonyx with the remaining 16.4 percent being held by private interests. Because Intel's market cap is much higher, the impact on share price will be less dramatic. I do, however, see Intel acquiring Micron, which owns Intel's old flash memory business Numonyx (not to be confused with Ovonyx) at this point since PCM is the solution to Intel's inability to penetrate the mobile markets. A relationship is already in place - with PCM fruit. With PCM, your phone can have an Intel processor just like your laptop or desktop. And so it can run the same operating system. Your PC will always be with you - in your pocket or purse. When you go home, a wireless monitor, keyboard, mouse and speakers will allow you to use it as a regular PC (or Mac, which also leverage Intel processors).</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349100894522</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 10:14:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349101230246-22</Id><Title>Nearly 1 billion users!!! Facebook FB shares are flying $22.42 +0.76 (+3.51%) aumy intc</Title><Msg>.........</Msg><Username>limitedspacecadet</Username><Timestamp>1349101230246</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 10:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349103021247-23</Id><Topic><Title>The iPhone 5 Technology Rabbit Hole - PCM</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349100894522</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 10:14:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PCM memory is not a requirement for Intel to make smartphones run full blown Windows in addition to whatever OS is the primary OS on the device. When a person brings their smartphone to their office or desk they can plug in there for all the power they need or they could use a wireless charging pad for power. WiGiG will handle all the connections to the docking station for keyboard, monitor and mouse and speakers. This product will be built. Intel and AMD are the only companies that can make x86 and Intel is the only x86 manufacturer strong enough to drive the design. Consumers will want mobility without compromises and they can have their portable and desktop environment with them always. Incidentally, this is not a path the ARM camp can even follow.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1349103021247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 10:50:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349104448632-24</Id><Title>Raspuking Rasmussen rightwing poll shows Rombo Romney is screwed.</Title><Msg>Monday, October 01, 2012 The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Monday shows President Obama attracting support from 50% of voters nationwide, while Mitt Romney earns the vote from 47%. Two percent (2%) prefer some other candidate, and two percent (2%) are undecided. See daily tracking history. These results include “leaners,” people who are initially uncommitted to the two leading candidates but lean towards one of them when asked a follow-up question.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349104448632</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:14:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349104748860-25</Id><Title>TSTRQ</Title><Msg>TSTRQ IS ALIVE AGAIN!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bonkp1</Username><Timestamp>1349104748860</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:19:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349105041822-26</Id><Topic><Title>FUTURES VERY REDDDDDDDDD!!!!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349045199618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're giving tooofunnny too much credit. His blathering isn't destroying value, he's just annoying you. As for INTC, if I have to chose between your pumping and tooofunnny's bad-mouthing, at the moment INTC's lack of a viable strategy, other than investing in fab process to cover mediocre design and narrow and short-sighted product vision, gives tooofunnny's position credibility yours doesn't have. The only differences I see is that you're 180 degrees out of phase, and you're articulate and he's a jackass.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1349105041822</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:24:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349105836714-27</Id><Title>Anybody know what that Charlie Dejamaren guy has against Intel?</Title><Msg>??????????????</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349105836714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:37:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349107180954-28</Id><Topic><Title>The iPhone 5 Technology Rabbit Hole - PCM</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349100894522</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 10:14:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He speculates that the iPhone5 was to have PCM memory which would have reduced power consumption substantially.???? Not sure Micron can currently match Samsung - News Samsung begins producing next-gen DRAM for mobile phones, tablets The South Korean electronics giant said it has begin mass producing 2GB DRAM in the new LPDDR3 specification By Jay Alabaster September 18, 2012 08:20 AM ET 1 Comment . IDG News Service - Samsung Electronics said Tuesday it has started mass production of a new type of memory chip for mobile devices, LPDDR3, that will dramatically increase performance in future smartphones and tablets. The new memory, which meets a standard published in May, will allow future devices to play high-definition video in real time on larger mobile screens than is currently possible, Samsung said. The new RAM will allow data rates of 12.8GB/second, much faster than the current generation of mobile RAM, which usually transfers at 8.5GB/second. In modern mobile devices, memory and processor specifications are increasingly driven by requirements for bigger and richer displays, a major point of competition between manufacturers, as opposed to application requirements. For phones and tablets, where battery life is at a premium, devices are usually built with a special type of low-power memory, called LPDDR, which is more efficient and has stand-by modes for idle time, but is slower and more expensive than the traditional RAM used in computers. The time required to read and write from memory has become a major bottleneck to faster gadgets with better graphics. Samsung said it is the first to produce 2GB DRAM for mobile phones under the next-generation LPDDR3 standard, the successor to the current mainstream LPDDR2. It is making the new chips using 30-nanometer technology. The South Korean manufacturer, which is increasingly well-known among consumers for its Galaxy brand, is also one of the world's largest component makers, supplying memory chips, displays, and flash storage to rival device makers such as Apple. Samsung has said it is working toward hardware which will allow 4k resolution displays, the current cutting edge for full-sized TVs, to appear on tablets in 2014, along with the current TV standard of high-definition on mobile phones. The newer 4k, named for its horizontal resolution of almost 4,000 pixels, has about four times the resolution of HD.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1349107180954</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:59:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349107354868-29</Id><Topic><Title>What INTC Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Username>hamiltoncolby837</Username><Timestamp>1349093204190</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 08:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for all your supports and views.It would bring back my confidence i would like to share my money with this organization.</Msg><Username>vargasboris55</Username><Timestamp>1349107354868</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 12:02:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349108022829-30</Id><Title>Where's singhlion? How's that short on INTC treating you, Pal ?</Title><Msg>Only complete and utter IDIOTS are shorting here.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1349108022829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 12:13:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349108818634-31</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>kathrynzxs923045</Username><Timestamp>1349105010049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:23:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An article that's worth a read.</Msg><Username>marcelenetip41963</Username><Timestamp>1349108818634</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 12:26:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349109291158-32</Id><Topic><Title>Where's singhlion? How's that short on INTC treating you, Pal ?</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1349108022829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 12:13:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He only shows up on down days,strange LOL!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1349109291158</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 12:34:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349109688486-33</Id><Title>So I suppose the massive short covering takes Intel over 25 soon.</Title><Msg>The big computer trading nimrod groups have made their money short so not it is time for them to make their money back long Intel. 30 before Christmas and this 22 will look like it never happend to people who were not paying attention. Of course--if the Apple deal with intel into Ipads and Iphones is struck--40 or more.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349109688486</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 12:41:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349110448981-34</Id><Topic><Title>Anybody know what that Charlie Dejamaren guy has against Intel?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349105836714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is a loose cannon and not very consistent for or against Intel or any other company. One of his recent articles (in Intel's favor) mentioned that Intel was going to embed DRAM into the CPU/SoC by way of interposers. Though I don't fully understand the technology, Charlie was extremely confident that he knew how exactly Intel was going to do this. Imagine Intel CPUs subsuming a huge part of the DRAM TAM. Intel's revenue would virtually go up by 50-70%! Another company Charlie has been railing against is nVidia...that they oversell their products by kluging together their graphics boards for demo-ing their launch products. Not sure what I can make out of his articles/rants...</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1349110448981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 12:54:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349110918533-35</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>kathrynzxs923045</Username><Timestamp>1349105010049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:23:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you shared this to us.</Msg><Username>bettezrm54565</Username><Timestamp>1349110918533</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:01:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349111504089-36</Id><Topic><Title>TEENS or $30?</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349048419200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:40:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>26-29 its closer to 26 than the teens at this second.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1349111504089</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349111544668-37</Id><Title>Buffet is buying now and you will learn about it in 2 months! HAHAHA</Title><Msg>Window dressing Friday as usual for the idiot hypocrites that didnt want to have intel in their funds by end of quarter. Well these sobs will love to have it this quarter and you can bet on it a 20% return idea. Buffer is easily buying here and the days before while all the corrupt system was trashing it. And expect intel to net in 2012 probably earnings that will still not be less than 5% from last year moreover getting attacked from all angles and all idiot politicians republicans and merkel #$%$ in Europe that are doing their bets to tank the planet. Notice the $ is 5+% lower this quarter and the last few weeks of the previous ones and it will have a positive impact on earnings making it possible that intel will miss revenue as it predicted from previous quarter estimations but will not miss as much if at all the earnings eventually. Execution means making profit even from less revenue. Watch it happen naysayers. If intel can take a hit and lose only 5-10% earnings wise why should price drop 25%? And by the way since when adding money makes you less valuable??? Any stupid 5-10% earnings differential is still 10-20 times less than the money they put in the bank from these earnings. Hey losers with the futures yesterday and all night , what happened to the 21 plans???? All one has to do here is buy a ton of 22-21 put spread for october that by earnings will have double the volatility anyway and little loss if we stay here or rally. That allows you then to ride a move to 25 in some surprise recovery say without caring if they try to trash things again ala 22 or less. Bring it. Keep explosive long term leap delta and a few puts on big up days liek today that are cheap by 50% and then let the shorts suffer to hell.</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1349111544668</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:12:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349111928153-38</Id><Topic><Title>The iPhone 5 Technology Rabbit Hole - PCM</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349100894522</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 10:14:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And there's another wrinkle to the quest for no-compromise "take it with you" mobility. Not only can the ARM camp NOT make a smartphone that gets native performance on W8, Apple can't do it either. Apple's laptops and desktops use x86 whereas their smartphones are ARM. Apple can't get native performance of both MAC OS and IOS applications on an ARM architecture. In contrast, Intel devices can run Android &amp; W8, or Microsoft Mobile &amp; W8. Anyone that believes mobility is the future of computing has to believe the W8 capable smartphone is just around the corner. Whoever said, "you can't take it with you" didn't envision the Intel hybrid W8 smartphone.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1349111928153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:18:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349113017414-39</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>kathrynzxs923045</Username><Timestamp>1349105010049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:23:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm subscribed. Cool</Msg><Username>jerilynllq668</Username><Timestamp>1349113017414</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:36:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349113427356-40</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is Headed Back to $23.02</Title><Username>wilder_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1348762824411</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good call, dad.</Msg><Username>son_of_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1349113427356</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:43:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349113528920-41</Id><Title>Tic Toc are you ready for the drop, Sell the rips ,Defense cut layoffs have started, They were given there 60 notice today</Title><Msg>Tic Toc are you ready for the drop, Sell the rips ,Defense cut layoffs have started, They were given there 60 notice today</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349113528920</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:45:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349115349161-42</Id><Title>Microsoft-Intel alliance weakens</Title><Msg>Intel Corp. (INTC)’s delayed delivery of software that conserves computer battery life is holding up development of some tablets running the latest version of Microsoft Corp. (MSFT)’s Windows operating system, a person with knowledge of the matter said. Microsoft hasn’t yet approved any tablets featuring an Intel processor code-named Clover Trail because the chipmaker hasn’t produced necessary power-management software, said the person, who asked not to be named since the process is private. The delay, following remarks by Intel Chief Executive Officer Paul Otellini, who told employees in Taiwan that Windows 8 needs improvement, underscores how the Wintel alliance that has dominated the personal computer industry for three decades is struggling to respond to the threat of Apple Inc. (AAPL)’s iPad. At stake is the chance to make up for lackluster PC buying by capturing users who are flocking to mobile devices, snappy applications and elegant design. “The PC channel is in chaos right now,” said Alex Gauna, an analyst at JMP Securities LLC in San Francisco. “They don’t know what to do. They don’t know what to design for, they don’t know what the consumers are going to buy. Tablets have stolen their growth trajectory, plus the macro situation, plus Wintel has made a mess of their ecosystem.” PC makers, including Hewlett-Packard Co. (HPQ), Dell Inc. (DELL) and Lenovo Group Ltd. (992), are counting on the new version of Windows to help them compete in the $63.2 billion tablet market dominated by Apple. Fighting Apple Any software development delay gives manufacturers less time to get their tablets ready for the year-end holiday shopping season, undermining attempts to erode Apple’s 70 percent share of tablets. Tablets featuring Clover Trail are the ones designed by Intel to most closely compete with the iPad. The industry can ill afford a slowdown in getting them into stores with the next iPad due to be released in March or April, said Wes Miller, an analyst at Directions on Microsoft, based in Kirkland, Washington. “It’s bad news for Microsoft and Intel because it’s not going to present the best light on either one and it will hurt the perception of Windows 8,” Miller said. While Windows is fundamentally sound, the operating system lacks a wide range of robust applications and PC makers haven’t had enough time to work out kinks with so-called drivers, which connect software to such hardware as printers, according to Directions on Microsoft. ARM Threat Microsoft has certified some 800 machines with the new software, said Mark Martin, a spokesman for Redmond, Washington- based Microsoft. That includes tablets running low-power chips with technology from ARM Holdings Plc (ARM) on a version of the software called RT. The recent entrant to the Windows family compounds threats to Intel. “Microsoft has worked closely with Intel and our hardware partners,” Martin said in a statement. “We look forward to the new Atom-based offerings from Intel to complement the already strong Windows 8 and Windows RT ecosystem.” Tablets and laptops convertible into tablets built on Clover Trail will be available Oct. 26, said Jon Carvill, a spokesman for Santa Clara, California-based Intel. “We’re excited about the opportunity for Windows 8 tablets with a broad range of” Intel chips, Carvill said. “We’ve collaborated very closely with Microsoft in extensive testing and validation” for chips, he said. China, Brazil Intel held an event last week showcasing Clover Trail-based tablets from Acer Inc. (2353), Asustek Computer Inc. (2357), Dell, Fujitsu Ltd. (6702), Hewlett-Packard, Lenovo and Samsung Electronics Co. (005930) The new devices, many of which featured detachable keyboards, have weeks of standby time and are capable of playing high-definition video for 10 hours. Still, any delays caused by unfinished software or untested hardware in tablets, laptops and desktops would be harmful to an industry already seeing demand faltering in China and Brazil, countries that until recently could be counted on to compensate for weakness in the U.S. and Europe. The refresh of the software that runs more than 90 percent of all personal computers typically leads PC makers to stock up on parts in anticipation of a surge in orders. Microprocessor shipments have risen an average 6.7 percent in the quarter before new Windows PCs go on sale, according to Mercury Research, while PC sales gained by more than 15 percent in each of the past two release quarters, researcher IDC said.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349115349161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:15:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349115356401-43</Id><Title>intc is tanking</Title><Msg>from 23.17</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349115356401</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349115457739-44</Id><Topic><Title>What INTC Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Username>hamiltoncolby837</Username><Timestamp>1349093204190</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 08:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when i came to know about the feature returns of the share's policy,i became more interested to invest my money on this.thanks for letting me know.have a good time ahead.</Msg><Username>v.roman61</Username><Timestamp>1349115457739</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:17:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349115659459-45</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>kathrynzxs923045</Username><Timestamp>1349105010049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:23:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow free of charge. I love it. Thanks</Msg><Username>jeffreyxyu719</Username><Timestamp>1349115659459</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:20:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349116073098-46</Id><Topic><Title>intc is tanking</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349115356401</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:15:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i told u so</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349116073098</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:27:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349116846134-47</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>kathrynzxs923045</Username><Timestamp>1349105010049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:23:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got it for free. Thank you</Msg><Username>anglasrj14019</Username><Timestamp>1349116846134</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:40:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349117126853-48</Id><Title>Coinmaker = will_amd_yu</Title><Msg>So, the tick-tock boy has a new user ID. He still sounds just as lame...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349117126853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:45:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349117361997-49</Id><Topic><Title>intc is tanking</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349115356401</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:15:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"i told u so..." *** You also told us markets would open down. A lucy by any other name is still a lucy. A $7 billion revenue miss priced in with earnings on the way. Shorts prepare to assume the position...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349117361997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349117531511-50</Id><Title>ARM Chips in Servers</Title><Msg>industry sources report that China-based Internet service providers are interested in adopting servers using ARM-based chips. They're "aggressively" trying to escape the dominating Wintel (Microsoft/Intel) server market, and ARM-based solutions appear to be the fastest way for them to become more independent. There's a growing interest in ARM servers as companies look to reduce costs, become more efficient and more environmentally friendly. Although ARM-based chips mainly reside in tablets and smartphones, there's a growing belief that thousands of ARM-based servers could efficiently process fast-moving transactions like social network requests, search queries and more. Hewlett-Packard has already commenced its ARM-based server project called Moonshot, and plans to cooperate with Calxeda to develop related products. Dell has also revealed its Cooper project that includes servers based on ARM chips. Both HP and Dell are currently offering prototype ARM servers for benchmarking and testing, but Dell claims that ARM-based servers just aren't ready for data centers due to software issues and a lack of 64-bit addressing. Earlier this month Ian Ferguson, director of server systems and ecosystem at ARM, said that early prototype 64-bit ARM servers could be available for testing purposes by the end of 2012, or by the middle of 2013 at the very latest. ARM is working to make inexpensive 64-bit hardware available by working in conjunction with Applied Micro Circuits. "With Applied Micro, we'll look to put [out] really low-cost 64-bit hardware," Ferguson said. "Some people want real hardware in their own lab. If we can drive that down to cheap pricing we'll do that with AppliedMicro so people can get ready for 64-bit." As of this writing, ARM has five architectural licensees, including Cavium, Nvidia and AppliedMicro. The two other licensees will be announced at a later date.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349117531511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349117989446-51</Id><Title>Fab equipment spending declining</Title><Msg>Well, we know that Intel continues on its relentless every eight quarter pace. So, any decline has to be on the ARM side. Just another sign of the ARM fabrication crisis. Not enough money, not enough production and not enough technology... *** "Gartner has warned that worldwide wafer fab equipment (WFE) spending is on pace to total $31.4 billion in 2012, a decline of 13.3 percent from 2011 spending of $36.2 billion. Big G warns that while the market will improve in 2013, it will not return to positive growth, with WFE spending projected to total $31.2 billion, a 0.8 percent decline from 2012. Things will not get better until 2014 and when the market returns to growth, as it is projected to increase 15.3 percent to surpass $35.9 billion. Bob Johnson, research vice president at Gartner said that the outlook for semiconductor equipment markets has deteriorated as the macro economy has weakened. "WFE started off the year strong, as foundries and other logic manufacturers ramped up sub-30-nm (nanometer) production."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349117989446</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:59:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349118105350-52</Id><Title>Intel may still surprise with Q3 Results - Notebook shipments increased significantly in September (30-50%)</Title><Msg>Notebook shipments significantly increase sequentially in September (30-50%) Taiwan-based notebook ODMs have indicated that shipments to vendors in September are estimated to increase by 30-50% on month. Notebook shipments to Hewlett-Packard (HP) in September are estimated to increase on month by 70%, and those to Asustek Computer and Acer to go up by 50% and 30% respectively, the ODMs pointed out. The sequential growth was mainly driven by the upcoming launch of Windows 8 notebook models, the ODMs said, adding Microsoft is set to launch Windows 8 on October 26. Shipments in July and August were relatively weak because vendors were clearing inventories of Windows 7 models, ODMs pointed out. ODMs began to stop shipments of Windows 7 notebooks in mid-September, they noted. Check out: dig-i-times, removed hyphens</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1349118105350</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:01:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349118238432-53</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>kathrynzxs923045</Username><Timestamp>1349105010049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:23:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good move. I will be expecting for more news.</Msg><Username>kaneshactx84294</Username><Timestamp>1349118238432</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349119026636-54</Id><Topic><Title>What INTC Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Username>hamiltoncolby837</Username><Timestamp>1349093204190</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 08:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can count on your money by investing in the stock market for better future returns.</Msg><Username>dickersonh73</Username><Timestamp>1349119026636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:17:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349119113358-55</Id><Topic><Title>intc is tanking</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349115356401</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:15:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i told u so, it doesn't have power to hold the gains</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349119113358</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:18:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349119350372-56</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Chips in Servers</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349117531511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice try, Conman........ HP ditches ARM for Intel in Project Moonshot Published on 20th June 2012 by Gareth Halfacree</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349119350372</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:22:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349119373831-57</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>kathrynzxs923045</Username><Timestamp>1349105010049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:23:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fantastic article. Thanks for sharing.</Msg><Username>leoraejf025405</Username><Timestamp>1349119373831</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:22:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349119421885-58</Id><Title>CAN INTEL GAIN A DIME TODAY?</Title><Msg>It doesn't look too promising.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1349119421885</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:23:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>25</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349119541719-59</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Chips in Servers</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349117531511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM processors for servers do not get an endorsement from VMware yet. According to the virtualization power house, ARM's architecture will not be ready anytime soon to compete with x86 processors. The company's soon-to-be-retired CEO, Paul Maritz, said that his company already built ARM servers running virtual machines, but his impression apparently was that the microserver processors are not quite ready yet. According to Wired, the executive said that the "capabilities [of ARM chips] still have a long way to go before they can match what you get from an x86 processor" and added that there "is a fundamental difference between a [handheld] device and the data center." According to the article, Maritz' main concern was that ARM processors are designed to save power and turn themselves off, when they are not needed. Data centers, on the other hand, would have to be always on. Even if Maritz is leaving VMware, the new CEO is unlikely to change the tone: Pat Gelsinger, Intel's former CTO, still has close contact to his former employer and it is no secret that he prefers x86 architecture over ARM.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349119541719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:25:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349119620174-60</Id><Topic><Title>Coinmaker = will_amd_yu</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349117126853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:45:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares? Look at yourself and get a life.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349119620174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:27:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349119652284-61</Id><Topic><Title>CAN INTEL GAIN A DIME TODAY?</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1349119421885</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:23:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>may be up one to few cents today, but tomorrow will be down fifty cents or one dollar.</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349119652284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349119740217-62</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Chips in Servers</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349117531511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ho-hum. Two years out and it will be irrelevant when it arrives. Intel will be in full production on 14nm by then and working on 10nm. Sure, give ARM the really, really low-end where price is important and performance is not. As the new AMD, that's an appropriate role for them...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349119740217</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349119783767-63</Id><Topic><Title>intc is tanking</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349115356401</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:15:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i told u so, no power</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349119783767</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:29:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349120008197-64</Id><Title>#$%$ is happening to NAS?</Title><Msg>Can anyone tell my wy we give ground much faster than DOW or S&amp;P? #$%$? Why this INTC keep spiking and got drag back. Let it fly damn it. should be in $24 range.</Msg><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349120008197</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349120114735-65</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is Headed Back to $23.02</Title><Username>wilder_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1348762824411</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Splain to 'em abowt the rwenny three oh too, Ildur!</Msg><Username>myle_der_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1349120114735</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:35:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349120165270-66</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$ is happening to NAS?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349120008197</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because it is a junk, i told u so, long long long time ago</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349120165270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:36:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349120199117-67</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Chips in Servers</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349117531511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Conmen_brokemen... another Wallis alias going on IGNORE !!!!!! Why do you need to hide behind so many aliases... PATHETIC !!!!! TIll your next alias...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349120199117</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:36:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349120352199-68</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is Headed Back to $23.02</Title><Username>wilder_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1348762824411</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy it under 23.02. Sell it over 23.02. INTC always returns to 23.02. Has for years.</Msg><Username>wilder_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1349120352199</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:39:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349120420576-69</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$ is happening to NAS?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349120008197</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this week will break 22</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349120420576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:40:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349120589340-70</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$ is happening to NAS?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349120008197</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whatever. wait to cover your short</Msg><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349120589340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:43:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349120591889-71</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$ is happening to NAS?</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349120008197</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:33:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no power</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349120591889</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349120687675-72</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Chips in Servers</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349117531511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That can't be wallis because he's busy working 80 hours a week. In addition, according to wallis, real men don't need more than one i.d. wallis thinks he;s a "real man" and that's........ TOOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349120687675</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>20</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349120809721-73</Id><Topic><Title>Tic Toc are you ready for the drop, Sell the rips ,Defense cut layoffs have started, They were given there 60 notice today</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349113528920</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:45:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FED can't stop the layoff wave Sell the rips and don't buy the dips or get run over</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349120809721</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:46:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349121207409-74</Id><Title>Ultrabook Forecast Cut in Half</Title><Msg>PCs: Ultrabook Forecast Cut in Half by iSuppli at Barrons.com03:49pm EDT</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349121207409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:53:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349121230430-75</Id><Topic><Title>What INTC Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Username>hamiltoncolby837</Username><Timestamp>1349093204190</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 08:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's amazing when your dream comes true in the form of money you have spent earlier  and wow! it gets doubled.</Msg><Username>flynnacosta69</Username><Timestamp>1349121230430</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:53:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349121264074-76</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Chips in Servers</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349117531511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"That can't be wallis because he's busy working 80 hours a week." It's Wallis... no one else posts entirely irrelevant info... "In addition, according to wallis, real men don't need more than one i.d." Wallis is a Wuss... and will continue to hide behind multiple ids...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349121264074</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:54:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349121389174-77</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>kathrynzxs923045</Username><Timestamp>1349105010049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:23:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am waiting for. Thanks for giving out this article for free.</Msg><Username>deenafoc6755</Username><Timestamp>1349121389174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:56:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349121500493-78</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Chips in Servers</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349117531511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, a wuss is somebody that posts an article stating that HP is working with ARM on project moonshot.......when in fact HP DITCHED ARM on that project for none other than INTEL. Keep bashing, I'll keep exposing you. Am I Wally? No, he's a dork like Lucy. Both are complete losers.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349121500493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:58:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349121642761-79</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Chips in Servers</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349117531511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>getanid61 Did you pull this article off "Tom's IT Pro" website? The first couple of words that are missing that said the sources were "UNNAMED" are important. The source is important. It tells you how honest the information is. "Unnamed industry sources report that China-based Internet service providers are interested in adopting servers using ARM-based chips. " The other interesting thing is the back ground (qualifications) of the author. "Kevin Parrish is a contributing editor and writer for Tom's Hardware,Tom's Games and Tom's Guide. He's also a graphic artist, CAD operator and network administrator."</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349121642761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:00:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349121725283-80</Id><Title>Something To Think About</Title><Msg>"The fact that the market is not as strong as before in terms of holding up gains, especially on a day like today when the ISM was a pretty good beat, shows that the market is tired and that the positive tone has changed," "I see this as suggesting that we are likely in for a deep correction. We are at a point where even the good news is not good enough." Be Cautious and Nimble</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1349121725283</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:02:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349122188964-81</Id><Title>INTC could not hold the gains, not good for INTC sell the rips</Title><Msg>INTC could not hold the gains, not good for INTC sell the rips</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349122188964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:09:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349122270545-82</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Chips in Servers</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349117531511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! Alexandar#$%$ just took a HUGE dump all over the WUSS, Getanid61's face. What a desperate little LYING ARM pumpchump.</Msg><Username>baltimoreravens_suck_coggg</Username><Timestamp>1349122270545</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:11:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349122457005-83</Id><Topic><Title>Ultrabook Forecast Cut in Half</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349121207409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:53:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They also said for Ultrabooks to succeed that they must have touch screen features. See, that's wrong. An Ultrabook with a touch screen is a tablet. And a touch screen suggests the need for bigger icons and larger graphical details. Also keeping in mind that a tablet has a screen size of 10.1" or less. So a tablet needs a different interface than other computers. MS should have developed a Windows operating system for Intel tablets. They shouldn't be developing Windows 8 for everything. They wasted their time, worked on the wrong thing, and now they bomb. The Intel tablet needs a faster screen refresh, it needs touch screen features, and it needs to run Windows applications. A tablet and an Ultrabook are two different kinds of computers. In fact it's the Ultrabook with 11.6" screen sizes that didn't catch on. They are mostly being offered with larger screen sizes. But the PC tablet has previous PC slates to base on. It's not an unknown form factor.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1349122457005</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:14:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349122500304-84</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Chips in Servers</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349117531511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well that's a new alias... did you make that up just now for me... why do you hide behind so many aliases ??? only a Wuss does that... another alias on IGNORE !!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349122500304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:15:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349122695935-85</Id><Title>Getanid your NVDA is still dropping</Title><Msg>i guess they buy your #$%$ there. lol</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1349122695935</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:18:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349122698076-86</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Chips in Servers</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349117531511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wuss's 1) Post Articles like you did and take out the part that says "unnamed sources". and Wuss's 2) put people on ignore that expose them as Frauds. Watching you get more and more desperate makes me smile. : )</Msg><Username>getanid61_is_a_conman</Username><Timestamp>1349122698076</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:18:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349123195387-87</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Chips in Servers</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349117531511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Watching you get more and more desperate makes me smile. : )" How many ids did you make for this thread alone to get thru to me... another alias on IGNORE !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349123195387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:26:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349123331735-88</Id><Title>tremor preceding a major break-out upside</Title><Msg>If I was a short I'd have my cyanide capsules and glock out on the bedside table ready for rapid deployment. (Please wear a towel wrap on your head when the time comes... it can be so messy for your wife to clean it up, though she'll know her long prayed for liberation has finally come. Getanid, I am talking to you!) INTC is soon to bust out to the upside in a VERY big way... I wish I could share the reason with you boys, but you'll know why when it happens.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349123331735</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:28:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349123428900-89</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Chips in Servers</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349117531511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will be interesting to watch AMD earnings results. When AMD bought SeaMicro, they got a company that built servers using ARM, Intel ATOM and Intel EP/EX CPU. I am not sure if they built AMD servers before but when AMD reports earnings, SeaMicro probably had one in some stage of design completion. Some analyst will ask AMD how the SeaMicro customers are "voting with their money". Which servers are they buying. SeaMicro AMD is in the unique position to answer that question.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349123428900</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:30:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349123579382-90</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>kathrynzxs923045</Username><Timestamp>1349105010049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:23:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am from Chicago. I love your article.</Msg><Username>graciahsx87364</Username><Timestamp>1349123579382</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:32:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349123727001-91</Id><Title>Defense cut layoffs starting 60 day notices going out BIG, BIG layoffs FED can't stop it OBAMA 4 more years, 4 more years of pain are you ready</Title><Msg>Defense cut layoffs starting 60 day notices going out BIG, BIG layoffs FED can't stop it OBAMA 4 more years, 4 more years of pain are you ready, Sell the rips and get some cash for the sell off lower lows to come</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349123727001</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:35:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349123973086-92</Id><Topic><Title>Ultrabook Forecast Cut in Half</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349121207409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:53:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the same article: But IHS also noted that ultrabooks have the chance to take off in 2013 if new Windows 8 devices reach the $600 to $700 level. And Intel's new processor, code-named Haswell and expected in mid-2013, could also help computer markets "reinvent the PC."</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349123973086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:39:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349124150686-93</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Chips in Servers</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349117531511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It will be interesting to watch AMD earnings results." ---------------------------------------------------------------- Exclusive: AMD to Announce Another 5% Employee Reduction? Reported by Theo Valich on Monday, October 1 2012 2:10 pm At approximately the same time last year, AMD management announced Project WIN, which many of the people thought it was a strategy to get the company to its winning ways. Rather than that, it was a purge of around 5% of the company, with many of key executives and engineers being shown the door. Many insiders viewed Project WIN as a mistake, given that some of the engineers that left were at odds with the interim CEO and CFO Thomas Seifert, and the project was actually set in motion before Rory Read joined the company. That headcount reduction triggered syphoning of minds away from AMD, with companies such as Samsung (Austin, TX), Huawei or Qualcomm (Toronto Area) all opening up extra offices or even locations in order to gain talent. As the time went by, new executives joined the company and apparently were met with quite a lot of resistance in terms of projects being realized. While it took for some time, it seems that both the executive team and the Human Resources department came to inevitable conclusion - the company is too big for the amount of projects at hand. According to our sources close to heart of the matter, we heard that "the company has too many VPs and directors who slow things down. New hires cannot fulfill their targets due to amount of bureaucracy." This was supported by the lowered outlook, which is being rumored among the financial institutions and company insiders alike. AMD apparently did not have a "happy third quarter", with the sales coming short of predicted. However, with the launch of AMD Virgo platform (Trinity for Desktops) and refreshed Scorpio with Vishera processors, fourth quarter should look much better. Once the reductions are completed, AMD should be a leaner company, reducing it from the current headcount of approximately 11,000 people to a sub-10,000 company. Rory's vision about turning AMD into an top-to-bottom SoC vendor doesn't have a lot of fans inside the company, but the company needs to learn how to scale from low-power to high-performance parts if its to capture market share and more importantly, increase the mindshare. Future graphics parts such as Volcanic Islands (2014) or Pirate Islands (2015) offer incredible amount of integration with the CPU cores, but the company needs to have products that can feed the monster GPUs of today/tomorrow.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349124150686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349125135689-94</Id><Topic><Title>Ultrabook Forecast Cut in Half</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349121207409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:53:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Notebook shipments significantly increase sequentially in September, say ODMs Aaron Lee, Taipei; Adam Hwang, DIGITIMES [Monday 1 October 2012] Taiwan-based notebook ODMs have indicated that shipments to vendors in September are estimated to increase by 30-50% on month. Notebook shipments to Hewlett-Packard (HP) in September are estimated to increase on month by 70%, and those to Asustek Computer and Acer to go up by 50% and 30% respectively, the ODMs pointed out. The sequential growth was mainly driven by the upcoming launch of Windows 8 notebook models, the ODMs said, adding Microsoft is set to launch Windows 8 on October 26. Shipments in July and August were relatively weak because vendors were clearing inventories of Windows 7 models, ODMs pointed out. ODMs began to stop shipments of Windows 7 notebooks in mid-September, they noted.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1349125135689</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:58:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349126814979-95</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>kathrynzxs923045</Username><Timestamp>1349105010049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:23:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was really looking for some great news. Now I found it.</Msg><Username>maxinepdv548</Username><Timestamp>1349126814979</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:26:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349127908060-96</Id><Topic><Title>Ultrabook Forecast Cut in Half</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349121207409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:53:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So I guess the fact that Otellini of Intel said Windows 8 is not ready is irrelevant?</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349127908060</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349129400749-97</Id><Topic><Title>Ultrabook Forecast Cut in Half</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349121207409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:53:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's "irrelevant" is you, hosehead. TOOOOO FUNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349129400749</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>21</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349129952282-98</Id><Title>CRAMER JUST SLAMMED INTEL</Title><Msg>LOOK OUT BELOW!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349129952282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349130067967-99</Id><Topic><Title>Ultrabook Forecast Cut in Half</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349121207409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:53:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cramer just trashed INTC bigtime. I never know if you're pumping INTC or bashing it lucy. I guess it all depends on what it did that day. Get a job you POS loser before you boy Obama loses his arsr and your Government check is cut or better yet eliminated.</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349130067967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:21:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349130408629-100</Id><Topic><Title>CRAMER JUST SLAMMED INTEL</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349129952282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boy do you sure tell lies.....I don\t know how many times over the years you have proudly proclaimed you don't watch CNBC. hahaha I guess along with that free Obama phone you get free CNBC. TOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNY Get a job you effing POS loser before your free ride comes to an end!</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349130408629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:26:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349130473111-101</Id><Topic><Title>Ultrabook Forecast Cut in Half</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349121207409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:53:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I gave your reply a thumbs up rating because you are such a pitiful creature and I thought it might help tp improve your miserable existance, hoser.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349130473111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:27:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>21</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349130734652-102</Id><Topic><Title>CRAMER JUST SLAMMED INTEL</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349129952282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What Cramer said: "As for the dogs of the Dow, Intel [INTC 22.755 0.10 (+0.44%) ] was the number one loser, down 11% but Cramer said “I have no bull case for it, none.”. "</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349130734652</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349130894798-103</Id><Topic><Title>CRAMER JUST SLAMMED INTEL</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349129952282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You only wish you had my "miserable existance" loser. It'll never happen so you might as well plan on getting a job.</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349130894798</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:34:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349131197540-104</Id><Topic><Title>CRAMER JUST SLAMMED INTEL</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349129952282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You only wish you had my "miserable existance" ------------- You mean I could get drunk and beat my wife every day?</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349131197540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:39:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>20</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349131277998-105</Id><Topic><Title>CRAMER JUST SLAMMED INTEL</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349129952282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll bet if you took a vote on this msg board "who is the biggest loser" based on posting IP addresses (as I suggested to yahoo) you'd be tops by far. The IP address posting requirement would eliminate loser like you in a hurry. Everyone would know who is who. Many other forums require that and it's coming here too. Just a matter of time. Can't come to fast for me.</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349131277998</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:41:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349131364604-106</Id><Topic><Title>CRAMER JUST SLAMMED INTEL</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349129952282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You only wish you had my "miserable existance" ------------- You mean I could get drunk and beat my wife every day?</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349131364604</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349131595532-107</Id><Topic><Title>CRAMER JUST SLAMMED INTEL</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349129952282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One didn't need to be watching CNBC to read the news on Cramer's picks for this quarter. other dislikes, AMD, HPQ, DELL,ie the pc is dead stocks. That said, while an outsized rally in INTC is unlikely, seems to me it's trying to bounce up.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349131595532</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:46:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349131719247-108</Id><Topic><Title>CRAMER JUST SLAMMED INTEL</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349129952282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Losers like him don't have any money. That's why they laugh at stocks when they go through struggling times. Mark. INTC will jump with eranings. Look at RIMM. They downgraded their earnings and came out like roses. It's a WS game. Buy low. wait for it to pop. I just got in recently. I see 30 by end of year. Look at history. These months strong for INTC.</Msg><Username>verioinc</Username><Timestamp>1349131719247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349132582812-109</Id><Title>Cockroaches Continue to Swarm</Title><Msg>Just like last night. What good did it do them today? None. They're nervous. As they should be with a $7 billion revenue miss priced in to the stock and earnings just around the corner...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349132582812</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 19:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349132940634-110</Id><Title>Nokia Up 7% Takeover ready ?</Title><Msg>$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>barronsfanatic</Username><Timestamp>1349132940634</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 19:09:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349134343177-111</Id><Topic><Title>Cockroaches Continue to Swarm</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349132582812</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 19:03:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep pumping Waldo, you may see 24.00 again</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349134343177</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 19:32:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349135094457-112</Id><Topic><Title>Ultrabook Forecast Cut in Half</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349121207409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:53:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I never see students using tablets in libraries. All is see are ultrabooks these days. People buy tablets for entertainment and ultrabooks to do work. They are in a different niche.</Msg><Username>starbauch</Username><Timestamp>1349135094457</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 19:44:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349136537239-113</Id><Title>Tank in the Backyard</Title><Msg>Intel's attitude seems rather strange these days. Nothing seems to bother them. It's like the guy that is getting bullied but he really doesn't care because he's building a tank in his backyard. And he knows that once it's done, then things will be quite different in the neighborhood...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349136537239</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 20:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349141237265-114</Id><Topic><Title>intc is tanking</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349115356401</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:15:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i told u so</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349141237265</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 21:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349142297047-115</Id><Topic><Title>What INTC Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Username>hamiltoncolby837</Username><Timestamp>1349093204190</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 08:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>like a fresh air your post runs into my heart through the window of my PC.Thanks for being so articulate.</Msg><Username>monroenicholson62</Username><Timestamp>1349142297047</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 21:44:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349144171772-116</Id><Topic><Title>Ultrabook Forecast Cut in Half</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349121207409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:53:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not so sure about that, i see plenty of folks on TV doing home remodel shows with their tablets and I see men in sandwich shops using tablets for work as well. I have no use for a tablet but that's because I run a business and need a PC still but I have to admit the tablets are nice and folks do seem to be getting it done with them.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349144171772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 22:16:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349144223371-117</Id><Topic><Title>CRAMER JUST SLAMMED INTEL</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349129952282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he mentioned the 4% div tho</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349144223371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 22:17:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349144272287-118</Id><Topic><Title>CRAMER JUST SLAMMED INTEL</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349129952282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thought he said 15%</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349144272287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 22:17:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349144376424-119</Id><Topic><Title>Ultrabook Forecast Cut in Half</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349121207409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:53:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sweet Windows Tablets with Intel inside are coming and over the next 18 months they will go to 22nm and then 14. Intel will have all bases covered with 22nm and then 14nm Ultrabooks, Tablets/Convertibles and Phones. Who can't see this coming ?</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349144376424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 22:19:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349144531425-120</Id><Title>An Idiot (Lucy Nuff) quotes another Idiot (Cramer)</Title><Msg>Idiots run in packs. I still remember Cramer recommending Oracle at 25 before earnings one time, then saying he was done with it after it dropped to 21 after earnings only to turn around and recommend it again at 30 this year. The guy should be in jail, IMHO.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349144531425</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 22:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349144761383-121</Id><Title>Intel will have all bases covered very soon</Title><Msg>Sweet Windows Tablets with Intel inside are coming and over the next 18 months they will go to 22nm and then 14. Intel will have all bases covered with 22nm and then 14nm Ultrabooks, Tablets/Convertibles and Phones. People will be carrying around and talking on SmartComputers instead of Smartphones in a couple of years. Who can't see this coming ?</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349144761383</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 22:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>