<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346825145463-1</Id><Topic><Title>National Debt</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346794748656</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:39:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see that you are MSL - Math as a second language...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346825145463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 02:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346842425048-2</Id><Title>ARM Warning, IDF, Apple Launch, etc</Title><Msg>ARM warns of slow sales in 2H12 and DB downgrades ARMH. Possibilities: 1. Surprising in view of bulish outlook from nVidia and TSMC. May be a coordinated effort by ARM and DB to drive down stock price in order to issue employee stock option at lower strike price or some other reasons. I can't rule out this possibility. 2. Or ARM is simply teasing Intel. Somebody ridng positive publicity and perceived success gets more ideas to tease rivals. 3. Or Intel is already gaining market share in smartphones in India, China, Europe. ARM camp's manufacturing lag will only pave way for Intel. Otellini not at IDF, will not be at Apple launch event either. Whole lot of speculation is going on which I think is irrelevant. 1. A company executive is unlikely skip important internal event for symbolic presence at another company event. 2. Apple generally doesn't have supplier executives at its launch events, I believe. Also Apple doesn't announce suppliers at launch. So speculation about Otellini not having IDF keynote in favor of attending Apple event is irrelevant. 3. If at all there is reason for Otellini to be present at Apple event, there would still be no conflict with IDF. He could have keynote address on Sept 11 and still attend Apple launch event on Sept 12. Overall, linking Otellini's absence from IDF keynote to his presence at Apple event for major pro-Intel announcement is the height of optimism. Possibilities: 1. Intel wants to give way to new executives including possible CEO candidates. 2. There will possibly be negative announcement from Apple like version of Mac running on ARM chip designs, without discarding Intel altogether. So Intel doesn't want to set too much possitive tone on Sept 11 only to be embarassed on Sept 12. 3. Not much to show as achievements post IDF 2011, particularly in smartphones and tablets. So Intel wants to downplay IDF 2012. Not to say that Intel has not made any progress so far. But the progress does not show off yet, and may show off in coming months. Apple Launch Event, Sept 12: 1. One hope for Intel is Apple reverts back to Infineon for baseband processors, given Intel's process lead and ability to fill demand. But that will not be known from Apple itself on Sept 12. 2. There is unlikely to be any preannouncement of future product.</Msg><Username>stocktrade14</Username><Timestamp>1346842425048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 06:53:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346844621313-3</Id><Topic><Title>Clinton's hate Obama yet gonna speak at the DNC becuase Obama begged</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346793713680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:21:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>better Clinton than Clint</Msg><Username>i_feel_my_pain</Username><Timestamp>1346844621313</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 07:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346849373234-4</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>It appears investors will be buying the dips as they await word from Europe and Bernanke on the extent of future monetary easing. The floor on the market is 1400 on the S&amp;P 500 and 13000 on the Dow. Keep an eye on these levels as a decisive break below these support levels could trigger more aggressive selling. Although traders may get what they want, be leery that they could sell the news. have a nice day.</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1346849373234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:49:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346849547288-5</Id><Title>GDOT upgraded from Neutral to Overweight, Sell INTC &amp; Buy GDOT</Title><Msg>It looks like Piper Jaffray has upgraded GDOT from Neutral to Overweight and the price target is $20/share ... Today looks to be a great BEAR HUNTING day in GDOT ... especially with over 4 million shares in short ... Could GDOT close above $15/share today ... Is it worth hanging on to INTC ... isn't it better to sell INTC and buy GDOT?</Msg><Username>delphioracle2009</Username><Timestamp>1346849547288</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346850466963-6</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Present at Citi Tech Conference Tues 9am</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346261433506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What happened at this meeting? I did not hear of any warning.</Msg><Username>hweich</Username><Timestamp>1346850466963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346851587932-7</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Warning, IDF, Apple Launch, etc</Title><Username>stocktrade14</Username><Timestamp>1346842425048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 06:53:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for starting my day off in a complete depressed state of mind.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1346851587932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346851945483-8</Id><Title>ARMH GREEEN---INTC REDDDDDDD!</Title><Msg>shocking! TOOOOO FUNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346851945483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:32:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346852056007-9</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH GREEEN---INTC REDDDDDDD!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346851945483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:32:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARMH down 8% yesterday....you forgot to mention that oooops. How's that Cisco you bought at 20 after selling Intel at 20 2 years ago? Underwater for 2 years, no wonder you are so bitter.</Msg><Username>lucy_zero</Username><Timestamp>1346852056007</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:34:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346852104540-10</Id><Title>Rombi is so tired. He is taking a week off.</Title><Msg>The poor guy, Romney, is not use to working. Oh well. The Dems will give Obummer a 5% bounce this week and this will put Romney back in the shietbowl again. Rombo and the GOP screwed up their convention. I thought you knew how to run things Rombo? Looks like those Libs know how to run a show a lot better. Clinton will remind the good old boys in the south that Rombo is a mormon toniight and a Yankee mormon at that.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1346852104540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346852311943-11</Id><Title>Wall Street's Largest Firms Continue Attacks on Intel</Title><Msg>Wall Street's largest firms continue their attempts to deny Intel a fair stock price or P/E ratio. Now with a six buck miss priced in where no miss occurred. With a P/E of 10 instead of 15 to 17. With industry-leading fabrication and manufacturing. With manufacturing here in the United States. These firms owe Intel investors and shareholders an explanation. Send the letters...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346852311943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:38:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346852389107-12</Id><Title>INTEL- Former BELLWETHER</Title><Msg>Now a SMELLWETHER! TOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346852389107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346852666285-13</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Present at Citi Tech Conference Tues 9am</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346261433506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The warning would not happen at that conference, if it comes. Boring presentation highlighting Ultrabooks by an exec that runs a different business. No announcements of any note.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1346852666285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:44:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346852688851-14</Id><Title>PC is dead..no one wants INTC: Cramer</Title><Msg>Just 2 mins ago on CNBC as they commented on AMD. Wallis: send your letters to Cramer and CNBC.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1346852688851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346852821101-15</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street's Largest Firms Continue Attacks on Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346852311943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:38:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Waldo. still in denial, only a 5.00 miss priced in. is 6.00 on the way? ie the 23's</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1346852821101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346852832535-16</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street's Largest Firms Continue Attacks on Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346852311943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:38:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now with a six buck miss priced in where no miss occurred. ========== Is that a HUGE HONKING $6 MISS ALREADY PRICED IN!!! or just a six buck miss? Please explain.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346852832535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:47:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346852910208-17</Id><Topic><Title>INTC got hit again today - but over $25 soon</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1346790002197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:20:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're dreaming. Down again today. Intel is down because they are doing the same old thing, making x86 chips smaller and faster. The market wants more - innovative thinking. Their big story is copying a multi-year-old Apple strategy. Boring.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1346852910208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:48:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346853081492-18</Id><Title>TSMC Says Only 4 Years Behind Intel</Title><Msg>TSMC has announced that they expect to have 10nm by 2018. So if anything like 28 and 20nm, we can add a couple of years. Best guess is that they will be six years behind Intel by 2020. Interesting that they would announce 10nm before they have even come close to being able to do 20nm in volume. By 2020 Intel's share of tablet and smartphone business should be what? 70 percent? And Wall Street has valued Intel's mobility business at what today? Zero. Send the letters...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346853081492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:51:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346853272490-19</Id><Topic><Title>PC is dead..no one wants INTC: Cramer</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1346852688851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:44:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point. Copies should go to all the big business media outlets. Send the letters...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346853272490</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:54:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346853420770-20</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Present at Citi Tech Conference Tues 9am</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346261433506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"first of many" is indeed the first of many shill IDs. As if we needed more. Just more of the coinmaker, flashcrash series. The big Wall Street firms apparently have nothing better to do than bash Intel. Send the letters...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346853420770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346853506543-21</Id><Title>democratic convention</Title><Msg>Mostly minorities in audience. Everyone there wanting a hand out. It's like a dog waiting for a treat.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346853506543</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346853669252-22</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC Says Only 4 Years Behind Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346853081492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:51:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Fudzilla: TSMC has finally gotten around to announcing a roadmap for the mass-production of next-generation 10nm wafers. It seems that TSMC will have everything ready by 2018. The chipmaker delayed in making 450mm wafers, which were originally scheduled in 2015. It said that the delay was caused by semiconductor equipment suppliers’ postponement in developing advanced equipment for manufacturing amid the industrial slump. The 450mm wafers would help solve the problem of rising costs in making advanced chips, allowing TSMC to provide affordable 10 nanometer chips with FinFET transistors for customers. J.K. Wang, vice president of TSMC’s operation in charge of 300mm factories, told a media briefing that it was the cost constraints rather than technological constraints for chipmakers to migrate to next-generation chips via shrinking chip geometry, he said. Chipmakers can get 2.5 times more chips from a 450mm wafer than from a 300mm wafer. TSMC planned to build a pilot production line to make 450mm wafers between 2016 and 2017, when semiconductor ASML Holding NV had its key equipment ready in 2015, Wang said. The chipmaker would consider building major 450mm-wafer production lines in Greater Taichung, he said.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346853669252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346853831090-23</Id><Topic><Title>Check this out</Title><Username>luettaeeb193</Username><Timestamp>1346794351309</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:32:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got it for free. Thank you</Msg><Username>sherrellikk1331</Username><Timestamp>1346853831090</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:03:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346853923308-24</Id><Topic><Title>PC is dead..no one wants INTC: Cramer</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1346852688851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:44:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone who listens to Cramer deserves what they get. The man is Mr. Random. Flipping a coin is better than listening to Cramer.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1346853923308</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346854038056-25</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC Says Only 4 Years Behind Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346853081492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:51:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Note: "..it was the cost constraints rather than technological constraints for chipmakers to migrate to next-generation chips via shrinking chip geometry..." So Intel is currently ahead for business reasons. With TSMC and other independent foundries witnessing exploding demand, this business edge is likely going to reduce. Till now, demand for foundry services was really low compared to Intel's chip volume. This has changed.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1346854038056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:07:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346854066055-26</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street's Largest Firms Continue Attacks on Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346852311943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:38:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>asswhipewhere's the $3 per sahre earnings you have been blowing about for years?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1346854066055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346854160743-27</Id><Topic><Title>PC is dead..no one wants INTC: Cramer</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1346852688851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:44:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallwad: You should send a letter to Santa and ask for "Intel $30" for Christmas and while you're dealing in fantasy, send letters to the Easter Bunny, Sasquatch, and The Tooth Fairy.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346854160743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:09:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346854247548-28</Id><Topic><Title>Still no Ottelini at IDF</Title><Username>beddbugg22</Username><Timestamp>1346805302565</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:35:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Otellini is not on the agenda, so he's not MIA. IDFs have become incredibly boring over the past ten years. It's a second-rate corporate conference.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1346854247548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:10:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346854424015-29</Id><Topic><Title>Still no Ottelini at IDF</Title><Username>beddbugg22</Username><Timestamp>1346805302565</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:35:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Otellini is not on the agenda, so he's not MIA. IDFs have become incredibly boring ---------------- and why would he want to attend a boring event???</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346854424015</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:13:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346854555629-30</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL DROPPED BY ACER</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346776629892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 12:37:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Atom-powered notebooks are and always have been a dud. Tablets have blown them away, and Intel's own Pentium CPUs are not all that much more expensive. So-called netbooks were always a dumb idea. The only positive note is that Atoms are a rounding error on Intel's bottom line. All of that said, Intel is still bereft of a real innovation plan. I'm amazed their BoD puts up with their management team.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1346854555629</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346854859759-31</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Present at Citi Tech Conference Tues 9am</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346261433506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can listen to the replay of the webcast on the Intel investor relations web page. There is also a copy of the presentation which is the standard (evolving) Intel tech conference presentation. The presentation ran a little long and there was only time for one question. The question was (my paraphrase): Why does the Intel forecast for server growth differ so much from the analyst estimates? Diane Bryant answer was (my paraphrase): Analysts are basing their forecast on top three companies who used to dominate the server market but their are now 10 to 15 large players like Google, Amazon, Microsoft, Facebook who are building their own servers. The analysts are not weighing the impact of these new players. Intel has previously made the same comment about PC growth and emerging markets. Since the analysts are consistently "surprised" by Intel performance, it would not be hard to figure out who knows more about the market. The analysts seem to phone Digitimes reporters for their information.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346854859759</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:20:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346854910871-32</Id><Title>@1.95 TSYS is way undervalue 2billion contract awarded</Title><Msg>TSYS will be a 5 dollar stock easy. More contracts are coming.</Msg><Username>johnjohn5200</Username><Timestamp>1346854910871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:21:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346855349764-33</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL DROPPED BY ACER</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346776629892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 12:37:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who's Acer? lol</Msg><Username>lucyboycots_chickfillet</Username><Timestamp>1346855349764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:29:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346855549552-34</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL DROPPED BY ACER</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346776629892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 12:37:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The original Digitimes story was talking about the 10-inch "netbooks" manufactured by "notebook players". Other media did not pick up the story accurately and it makes a good negative story on the board. tooooofunnnny and aliases have posted it here several times. Intel would LOVE to have vendors use the Atom for tablet and smartphone products. It is hard to make a profilt on an Atom based netbooks when a Core i3 notebook is the same price. Intel may need to adjust roadmap for PC-use Atom processors Monica Chen, Taipei; Joseph Tsai, DIGITIMES [Monday 3 September 2012] Intel may be forced to adjust its roadmap for PC-use Atom processors as the top-2 netbook vendors – Asustek Computer and Acer – both plan to stop manufacturing related products, according to sources from notebook players. Asustek is already set to halt its Eee PC product line and officially phase out from the IT industry after completely digesting any remaining inventory. As for Acer, so far, the company has not yet made any plans to open new netbook projects, indicating that the vendor may also plan to step out of the market. Although Atom series processors will still be adopted by handset and embedded products, the sources believe the two product lines are unlikely to be able to fill the gap created by the absent netbook products in short term due to weak shipments. Asustek CEO Jerry Shen recently confirmed that the company will stop production of Eee PC netbooks using Atom-based processors such as the N2600 due to impact from tablet PCs and notebooks, as well as a sharp drop in demand in emerging markets. Asustek plans to have its Transformer tablet PCs fill the 10-inch mobile device market, replacing its netbook product line.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346855549552</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:32:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346856857036-35</Id><Title>The yahoo board is a mess</Title><Msg>If we all moved to Investor Village we could say goo-bye to this POS message board. Google Investor Village.....since yahoo no longer allow links. What are they thinking? IV allows links, has blockable private emails and a bunch of other features a message board should have. I posted this message earlier and it was deleted.....Great, just fxxking great!</Msg><Username>semiwiz2002</Username><Timestamp>1346856857036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:54:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346857264342-36</Id><Topic><Title>The yahoo board is a mess</Title><Username>semiwiz2002</Username><Timestamp>1346856857036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:54:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Send us a postcard from Investor Village. I'm sure your leaving Yahoo will drive the company into immediate bankruptcy. Alternatively, you could spend a few minutes familiarizing yourself with the new Yahoo message boards and just quit your whining of "Who moved my gubbermint cheese?"</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1346857264342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:01:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346858334174-37</Id><Title>CAN INTEL SQUEEZE OUT A DIME TODAY?</Title><Msg>The Magic 8-ball sez: "NO CHANCE!"</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346858334174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:18:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346859117207-38</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL DROPPED BY ACER</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346776629892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 12:37:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, the 10.1" screen PC should be a tablet. Then the laptop PC's can begin at an 11.6" screen. The PC product mix should be: Atom tablet for consumers with 10.1" screen, one pound weight, WiFi, no cellular, and I would prefer an ethernet plug instead of a docking station Ivy Bridge tablet for business with 10.1" screen, one pound weight, WiFi, no cellular, encrypted hard drive, fingerprint reader, and I would prefer an ethernet plug instead of a docking station Ultrabook laptops with screen size beginning at 11.6" and weight beginning at two pounds. Then screen size going up to larger sizes and weight going up to 3.5 pounds. (And one PC maker has a carbon fiber Ultrabook.) But: The PC makers are showing hybrid tablet/laptops when an Atom PC. Then they have one-piece tablets when Win RT on ARM. So: It looks like to me that Win 8 on Atom doesn't have the expected screen refresh rate. However: If Acer is not going to have an 10.1" Atom hybrid tablet/laptop then likely they will have an 10.1" Atom one-piece tablet . And Lenovo has a 10.1" Atom tablet announced but they seem confused as they just also announced 10.1" Atom hybrid tablet/laptops and also announced Android on ARM tablets.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1346859117207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346859533803-39</Id><Topic><Title>New Format worthless and nearly impossible to navigate smoothly.</Title><Username>tiderunner3</Username><Timestamp>1346770034805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:47:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How do you know you have figured them out?" You must be very confused as to what the purpose of these boards is. Seems to me, if you can post and read others' posts, that pretty much covers it. Perhaps you think the features of these boards will make you a better trader/investor or otherwise improve your pathetic life? Sorry, there's no app for that. The new boards have some features I really like, like the notifications feature. How do I know I have that figured out? Well, I know because I'm not an effing dumphock like you.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1346859533803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:38:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346859776707-40</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Present at Citi Tech Conference Tues 9am</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346261433506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Diane Bryant does not impress me. She seems to be in way over her head for this critical position. Not only is Paul O. a poor leader, he also is a bad judgement of people with true leadership skills. Intel really needs new leadership.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1346859776707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:42:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346859850425-41</Id><Topic><Title>New Format worthless and nearly impossible to navigate smoothly.</Title><Username>tiderunner3</Username><Timestamp>1346770034805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:47:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was used to the old. Guess they can do what they want. I can conform.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1346859850425</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:44:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346860180661-42</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL DROPPED BY ACER</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346776629892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 12:37:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I forgot to note that the Ultrabook laptops, starting at 11.6" screen size and starting at two pounds weight, are Ivy Bridge processors. This is the one thing that no one is confused about. With 10.1" Atom tablets in doubt, I would have to recommend 11.6" Ivy Bridge Ultrabooks and look for 1.8 pounds weight.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1346860180661</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:49:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346863035382-43</Id><Topic><Title>market may be ready for a move now.</Title><Username>indexit</Username><Timestamp>1143822213000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2006-03-31 11:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope you're right. It's been a really long wait 'in here'.</Msg><Username>myle_der_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1346863035382</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:37:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346863309838-44</Id><Topic><Title>Butta-ss</Title><Username>harlanj1</Username><Timestamp>1196432272000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2007-11-30 09:17:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"My Favorite restaurant is Dixie Crossroads here in Titusville where a fine dinner can be had for 14 bucks, shrimp at that. Add the shrimp is wild ocean caught." Was there any drop off in business at the Dixie Crossroads after the Deep Water Horizon blew up? TIA</Msg><Username>myle_der_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1346863309838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:41:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346863659587-45</Id><Topic><Title>market may be ready for a move now.</Title><Username>indexit</Username><Timestamp>1143822213000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2006-03-31 11:23:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does Karen Finnnnnnnerman say about that?</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346863659587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:47:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346863911926-46</Id><Topic><Title>I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1293550442000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-12-28 10:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol.....</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1346863911926</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346864247756-47</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is too superior to skip right now. Examine why!</Title><Username>irvinroman22</Username><Timestamp>1346854865135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:21:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAM CRAP</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346864247756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346864605151-48</Id><Topic><Title>The yahoo board is a mess</Title><Username>semiwiz2002</Username><Timestamp>1346856857036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:54:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's not about 'familiarizing' with the board. The lacking of this new board are significant and it's horrible UI.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1346864605151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:03:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346864805405-49</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Present at Citi Tech Conference Tues 9am</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346261433506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need a new keyboard. The "stupid lock" key is stuck in the ON position.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346864805405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:06:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346865484029-50</Id><Title>Has Eva Longoroia taken stage yet at the DNC?</Title><Msg>LOL! Probably not, she's busy chasing Mark Sanchez (half her age). What a bunch of losers. Never seen anything match it.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346865484029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:18:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346866660192-51</Id><Topic><Title>Has Eva Longoroia taken stage yet at the DNC?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346865484029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never seen anything match it. -------------- You and your stooooooopid off-topic messages are a match, douche nozzle.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346866660192</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:37:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346866806974-52</Id><Topic><Title>Has Eva Longoroia taken stage yet at the DNC?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346865484029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Lucy, 2 years later and STILL 50% underwater on his Intel for Cisco trade. I'd be mad, too. LOL! Keep venting, it's good for you.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346866806974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346867914257-53</Id><Title>Chips: Evercore, UBS Advise Sitting Out for Now</Title><Msg>September 5, 2012, 1:43 P.M. ET . Chips: Evercore, UBS Advise Sitting Out for Now . Email By Tiernan Ray There were some cautious words today about semiconductors from a number of analysts, as well as some more cuts in outlook for Intel (INTC) specifically.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346867914257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:58:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346868614570-54</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Present at Citi Tech Conference Tues 9am</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346261433506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "stupid lock" key is stuck in the ON position. -------------- "att4glte" is stuck on stoooooooooooooopid.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346868614570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:10:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346869040416-55</Id><Topic><Title>Chips: Evercore, UBS Advise Sitting Out for Now</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346867914257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:58:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All the analyst talk is just semantics now...similar to the vomit you've posted the past two years since trading Intel for Cisco and losing 50% of nothing.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346869040416</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:17:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346869298156-56</Id><Topic><Title>Chips: Evercore, UBS Advise Sitting Out for Now</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346867914257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:58:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol</Msg><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1346869298156</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346869472337-57</Id><Topic><Title>Barclay's raises INTC price target to $30.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1336764783000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-11 15:33:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like "Vomit" Shah got it right and WW and his aliases got it wrong! TOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY! "Vomit Shah's reasoning on Intel investor meeting. It makes no sense at all. Talks about all the positives that came out of the meeting yet maintains a reduce and a $25 target. The question now is not that if he listens to what Intel is say, but does he listen to what he himself is saying?"</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346869472337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346869754670-58</Id><Title>My One-Star Puppy is Frustrated Today</Title><Msg>He can no longer make my messages "disappear" by using his hundreds of aliases to rate them away and that's TOOOOOOOoO FUNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346869754670</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346869873075-59</Id><Title>Intel announces two software development suites</Title><Msg>INtel Claimed it was just a simple directive.... work in the environment you know Now it's a whole suite of tools I told you all.... !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! CHIPMAKER INTEL announced the launch of two software development suites today, Intel Parallel Studio XE and Intel Cluster Studio XE 2013, to help software developers produce more reliable applications. The INQUIRER got the lowdown on Chipzilla's new products from Intel chief software evangelist James Reinders, who told us that the launch comes as the firm tries to "help developers find simpler errors more easily, in a bid to product fast, scalable and more reliable apps". Set to help developers improve application performance on current and next generation processors including the Intel Xeon Phi coprocessors, the development suits include new features such as improved compiler and library performance, decreased CPU power usage and low overhead Java profiling. Intel also told us that its new Parallel and Cluster Studio XE suites will come with an MPI library with improved fault tolerance and extended parallelism to include Linux, Fortan and C#. "Intel Parallel Studio XE provides advanced tools to build superior shared memory applications and Cluster Studio XE adds support for distributed and hybrid applications," the company explained. "Applications built using these tools typically run faster on computers, servers and clusters. The suites enable developers to deliver applications that perform and scale well in computers and clusters while improving productivity to create faster, more reliable applications." Intel Parallel Studio XE is available from today, while Intel Cluster Studio XE 2013 is set to arrive on Windows and Linux later this year. The software suites will fetch $1,599 to $2,299 and $2,949, respectively.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346869873075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:31:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346870319766-60</Id><Topic><Title>My One-Star Puppy is Frustrated Today</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346869754670</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:29:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only frustrated pup here is you...the guy down 50% since getting rid of Intel. LOL. Rant on. It's been fun to watch you come undone the last 2 years.</Msg><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1346870319766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:38:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346870621699-61</Id><Title>FORBES- INTEL ESTIMATES KEEP RATCHETING LOWER</Title><Msg>9/05/2012 @ 2:35PM Intel: Estimates Keep Ratcheting Lower Amid PC Worries</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346870621699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:43:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346870856962-62</Id><Topic><Title>FORBES- INTEL ESTIMATES KEEP RATCHETING LOWER</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346870621699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:43:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep spewing. The stock went from 19 to 29 the last time you started rapid-firing negative articles. here. Intel Longs love you.</Msg><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1346870856962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346870973507-63</Id><Title>FHF About to Begin-</Title><Msg>FINAL HOUR FADE</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346870973507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:49:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346871276781-64</Id><Topic><Title>Intel announces two software development suites</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346869873075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The simple directive support has been incorporated into the Intel C compiler, Fortran compiler, library products (IPP, MKL, ...) and they released a new version of Vtune supporting Ivy Bridge. The Intel marketing guys packaged tools and called them a "suite". Is that what you told everyone? Intel was going to add support to both C and Fortran?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346871276781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:54:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346871405481-65</Id><Topic><Title>INtel's HD-4000</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346361370473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 17:16:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What's it feel like to be a man" GREAT !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ""who's been put on ignore by everyone?" Thanks for the response... LMAO !!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346871405481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346871504410-66</Id><Topic><Title>FORBES- INTEL ESTIMATES KEEP RATCHETING LOWER</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346870621699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:43:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis loves me? That's pretty scary!!! Ya don't wanna bend over to tee up your ball if that guy's on the golf course! TOOOOO FUNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346871504410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:58:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346871613061-67</Id><Topic><Title>Barclay's raises INTC price target to $30.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1336764783000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-11 15:33:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3 months ago, Intel was trading at $25.xx and Romit Shah had a $25 target and a reduce rating. He missed the run up to $29 and back. The inconsistency is a target that is at the current price and a reduce rating. My question was always: why the reduce rating when the price was at the target? His target says that he expects that Intel is fairly valued.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346871613061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:00:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346871942071-68</Id><Topic><Title>Intel announces two software development suites</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346869873075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I told you all it will be more than a simple directive... INtel is now releasing suits of tools for developers to tune their code... !!!!!!! How do developers tune their code.... with directives !!!!!!! gonna be far more than a simple directive... !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346871942071</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346872435512-69</Id><Topic><Title>Intel announces two software development suites</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346869873075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"INtel Claimed it was just a simple directive.... work in the environment you know Now it's a whole suite of tools I told you all.... !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!" *** This is what happens when the ARM marketing department sends one of their own out to shill on the Intel Message Boards: Lunatic fringe disjointed meaningless rants. I laughed especially hard at the lucy-style string of exclamations points. Nothing says one has no communication skills better than a long string of repeated keystrokes...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346872435512</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:13:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346872805863-70</Id><Topic><Title>Intel announces two software development suites</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346869873075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All of that PLUS the stock is up 3 cents! What a GLORIOUS DAY for Intel! Are ya havin' fun yet Wallwad? WHEEEEEEEEEEEE!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346872805863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:20:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346872991072-71</Id><Title>Mayor of San Antonio caught LYING about job creating at the DNC</Title><Msg>LOL! He said we created 4 million jobs! The FACT are that we've created 300k but also lost 300k so we've created NONE. What's worse, lying about job creating in a depression or forgetting how fast you could run a marathon when you were 20 years old? LOL! #$%$ lying LIberals.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346872991072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:23:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346873372911-72</Id><Topic><Title>Barclay's raises INTC price target to $30.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1336764783000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-11 15:33:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>logic says that if a stock is at the target, nothing more to be gained, therefore sell. many a long would love to see 25.00 again</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1346873372911</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:29:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346873406453-73</Id><Title>A politician caught lying? Not exactly breaking news.</Title><Msg>A politician caught lying? Not exactly breaking news.</Msg><Username>clarrjk</Username><Timestamp>1346873406453</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:30:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346873586281-74</Id><Topic><Title>Intel announces two software development suites</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346869873075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel released a new C and Fortran compiler for all their CPU, Like they regularly do. Is this an issue with new features for MIC? Atom? Ivy Bridge features? Haswell features? There is a compile time option to chose the target CPU and then other options to further optimize the generated code. That is true on all compilers. Sorry, I don't see the problem.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346873586281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:33:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346873804134-75</Id><Topic><Title>Intel announces two software development suites</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346869873075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NVDA and ARMH got hammered yesterday, so naturally Getanid61 is hopping mad and taking it out on the Intel board. He always screams and yells when those stocks get crushed. Poor little loser.</Msg><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1346873804134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:36:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346874272690-76</Id><Topic><Title>FHF About to Begin-</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346870973507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:49:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A CLASSIC FHF IS IN PROGRESS!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346874272690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346874564391-77</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor of San Antonio caught LYING about job creating at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346872991072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:23:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A LIE is a LIE. If you want to invest a few minutes, there are a number of Democrats citing the 4.5m jobs number. You can post this for each one that uses the 4.5m number. However, CNN concludes the figure of 4.5m is accurate if you set the start date after the Bush freefall ended like the Democrats did. I don't think that Ryan indicated that he was timing from the 10-mile mark. From FACT CHECK: When Democrats use the 4.5 million jobs number, they're referring to jobs created after the economy bottomed out in January 2010, one year after Obama took office. That time frame excludes the worst job losses, which took place in 2009, and which many Democrats argue were the result of Bush policies. CNN concludes: "The figure of 4.5 million jobs is accurate if you look at the most favorable period and category for the administration. But overall, there are still fewer people working now than when Obama took office at the height of the recession."</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346874564391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:49:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346874635950-78</Id><Title>WHAT FUN!!!</Title><Msg>This Is Gonna Be Fun By wallisweaver . 3 months ago . Permalink I really enjoyed plowing through 27, 28 and 29. Now we get to do it again. Just a lot faster this time...</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346874635950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:50:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346875320822-79</Id><Title>SPECTACULAR DAY FOR INTC SHARES!!!</Title><Msg>REDDDDDDDDD but REAL and SPECTACULAR!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346875320822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346876338109-80</Id><Topic><Title>Intel announces two software development suites</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346869873075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude, how many aliases you got ??? Why do you hide behind so many aliases ???</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346876338109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346879164124-81</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC Says Only 4 Years Behind Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346853081492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:51:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple, Qualcomm Bids Spurned for Exclusive TSMC Supplies Apple Inc. (AAPL) and Qualcomm Inc. (QCOM) were rebuffed in separate attempts to invest cash with Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. (2330) in a bid to secure exclusive access to smartphone chips, people with knowledge of the matter said. Both proposals included investments, each of more than $1 billion, for the world’s largest custom maker of chips to set aside production dedicated to making chips exclusively for them, said the people, who declined to be identified because the details are not public. Enlarge image TSMC Chairman and CEO Morris Chang Morris Chang, chairman and chief executive officer of Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. (TSMC). Photographer: Ashley Pon/Bloomberg Apple Patent Win Won't Reap Benefits in Long Run 5:42 Aug. 28 (Bloomberg) -- Per Lindberg, an analyst at ABG Sundal Collier Partners LLP, discusses the copyright infringement dispute between Samsung Electronics Co. and Apple Inc., and its possible impact on Nokia Oyj. He speaks with Guy Johnson on Bloomberg Television's "The Pulse." (Source: Bloomberg) The two companies are trying to satisfy booming demand for smartphones, a market estimated by to be worth $219.1 billion, according to data compiled by Bloomberg Industries. Any deal would give Apple an alternate supplier to Samsung Electronics Co. (005930), which builds the main chip used in the iPhone and iPad and is also its biggest rival in smartphones. Qualcomm needs to boost supply, since shortages are starting to limit earnings. As a supplier to Qualcomm, Broadcom Corp. (BRCM), Nvidia Corp. (NVDA) and other companies that no longer operate their own factories, TSMC wants to keep the flexibility to switch its production between customers and products. TSMC Chairman Morris Chang told investors last month that he was willing to devote one or even two factories to a single customer. “Currently we believe we still can fund it,” Chief Financial Officer Lora Ho said in an interview on July 19. TSMC wants to retain control of its plants, doesn’t want to sell part of itself and doesn’t need cash for investments, Ho said in the interview. Dedicated Fabrication Qualcomm Chief Executive Officer Paul Jacobs said in June that he was willing to write ‘big checks’ to improve supply shortages that have held back earnings growth this year. The San Diego-based company is working with multiple suppliers to improve output, he said. TSMC doesn’t comment on negotiations with customers or potential customers, spokeswoman Elizabeth Sun said. Apple spokesman Steve Dowling declined to comment on whether the company had offered cash. Clare Conley, a Qualcomm spokeswoman, declined to comment. Apple and Qualcomm are trying to improve their position in a supply chain where a shrinking number of companies are capable of churning out the millions of parts needed to meet surging smartphone demand. As they become more like computers, the advanced mobile phones need more sophisticated processors made with the latest production technology. While TSMC is Qualcomm’s biggest supplier, according to data compiled by Bloomberg, it has been successful because it has worked with multiple customers. Dedicating one facility to a single product or customer creates the risk of a fabrication plant becoming a burden if the product, client or technology changes, said Ho. “You have to be careful. Once that product migrates, what are going to do with that dedicated fab?” said Ho. “We would like to keep the flexibility.”</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1346879164124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:06:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346879718297-82</Id><Topic><Title>Intel announces two software development suites</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346869873075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Is this an issue with new features for MIC?" Yes, Their advanced tools will have developers more involved than INtel marketing has advertised. Allocating resources, sharing &amp; passing data, scheduling, performance tuning, etc... "Sorry, I don't see the problem." No problem... INtel doing exactly what they need to do... I would've been shocked to the core if such tools weren't available... Just contrary to INtel's advertised simpleness...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346879718297</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:15:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346880747141-83</Id><Title>INTEL IS A....</Title><Msg>COILED TURD! TOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346880747141</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:32:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346882252510-84</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL IS A....</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346880747141</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:32:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>armh is 25.37, a buck higher. Are you worried if gayboy gets married, he'll not be around as much?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1346882252510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:57:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346882394421-85</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT FUN!!!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346874635950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:50:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh hell yes, I am having a blast watching my INTC, aren't you ?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1346882394421</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:59:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346882494749-86</Id><Topic><Title>FORBES- INTEL ESTIMATES KEEP RATCHETING LOWER</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346870621699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:43:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he may ask you to get married, any chance? then neither of you will be around much. LOL!!!!</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1346882494749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:01:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346882608510-87</Id><Topic><Title>I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1293550442000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-12-28 10:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>..............</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1346882608510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:03:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346883491614-88</Id><Topic><Title>Intel announces two software development suites</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346869873075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good move, supporting FORTRAN. I think both engineers who still use it will be impressed. BTW, this kind of software is about 2,000 years old. NU-Mega introduced it in 1989 or thereabouts.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1346883491614</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:18:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346885530836-89</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor of San Antonio caught LYING about job creating at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346872991072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:23:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe he was counting illegal alien jobs?</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1346885530836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346893709772-90</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor of San Antonio caught LYING about job creating at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346872991072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:23:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If FACT CHECK and CNN also counted the same way that the Mayor did, then I would say you are right. They didn't count the undocumented alien jobs. If the state, local and federal government employee jobs tracked up the same way they did under the Regan and Bush recessions, it would probably be 6.0 million jobs. Government jobs increased during both of those recessions.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346893709772</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:08:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346893788159-91</Id><Title>Black and White</Title><Msg>In its recent report, "The Lost Decade of the Middle Class," the Pew Research Center found that in 1971, 62% of the country's income was earned by the middle class, which at that time represented 61% of the population. In 1991, the middle class took in 54% of the income and represented 56% of the country. In 2011, the middle class represented 51% of the population, but its earning was down to 45%. None of this would be a problem if the percentage of Americans who became rich was in line with the amount of money the rich were taking in. Unfortunately, that is not the case. In 1971, the rich represented 14% of the country and took in 29% of the income. In 2011, the rich represented 20% of the country but took in a whopping 46% of the money. [And yet the rich are still not satisfied...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346893788159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:09:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346894139573-92</Id><Topic><Title>Black and White</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346893788159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:09:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Normal people are watching the football game.........while you stare at the walls of your tiny apartment and fume about how much you hate rich people..........what a pathetic existence.</Msg><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1346894139573</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:15:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346894145069-93</Id><Topic><Title>New Format worthless and nearly impossible to navigate smoothly.</Title><Username>tiderunner3</Username><Timestamp>1346770034805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:47:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Well, I know because I'm not an effing dumphock like you." Wow!! You are using the same confused source that you did the last time. Your source is still confused and gets frustrated too easily. You should have him take anger management counciling.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346894145069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:15:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346894725079-94</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor of San Antonio caught LYING about job creating at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346872991072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:23:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently the 'G' in GOP doesn't stand for 'genius'. Have you considered population growth in your unemployment rate calculations?</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1346894725079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:25:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346896410078-95</Id><Title>46 million on Food Stamps, up 50% under Obongo, lol</Title><Msg>Unrealio</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346896410078</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:53:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346896895404-96</Id><Title>DNC a total disaster so far, LOL !</Title><Msg>2/3rd affirmative my #$%$ !</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346896895404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346896922266-97</Id><Title>Sandra Flue the best ya got !??</Title><Msg>lmao ! FLUKE, so ironic.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346896922266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:02:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346897065220-98</Id><Title>DNC taken over by towel heads</Title><Msg>That's what America will look like by 2016 if you #$%$ get your wish. Wow.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346897065220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:04:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346897587221-99</Id><Topic><Title>Barclay's raises INTC price target to $30.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1336764783000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-11 15:33:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The analyst thinks there is nothing to be gained but also nothing to be lost, and therefore a NEUTRAL rating would be more in line. You could buy at $24.40 and then sell call options that generate $0.25 per month while collecting the quarterly $0.225 dividend. SEPT $0.25 OCT $0.62 NOV $0.76 DEC $0.95 JAN13 $1.15 1% per month call premium plus 3% dividend = 12% + 3% or 15% annual. Seems like a NEUTRAL since he is saying low downside and 3% dividend.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346897587221</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:13:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346900185455-100</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Present at Citi Tech Conference Tues 9am</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346261433506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"att4glte's" keyboard "POLITICAL EXTREMIST KEY" is stuck in the ON position. tooofunnny's "VACANCY SIGN" is still stapled to his forehead. Everytime he opens his mouth, lots of nothing comes out.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346900185455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:56:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346900415766-101</Id><Title>Slick Willy (the Adulterer) on fire tonight!</Title><Msg>He lied and cheated on his wife, great dude! The DNC's finest.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346900415766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:00:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346902212210-102</Id><Title>Clinton's speach littered with snake oil - Brit Hume</Title><Msg>LOLOLOLOLOLOL..............................OL</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346902212210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346902355737-103</Id><Title>At least Slick Willy wasn't booed off the stage like last time....</Title><Msg>......Time heals all adulterers.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346902355737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:32:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346903142050-104</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>The market wants to hear something concrete from ECB President Mario Draghi. Earlier in the summer his positive comments sparked a triple digit rally. This time traders want to see action. Technically the DJ Transportation Index broke the bottom trend line of a triangle pattern which is a negative for stocks. If stocks are unable to rally on comments tomorrow keep an eye on the transports. If they are unable to reverse their recent negative momentum and move back into their triangle pattern it could be an indication that the summer rally has gone as far as it can on the stimulus talk. have a nice evening</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1346903142050</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:45:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346903772827-105</Id><Title>Searchin for a bottom</Title><Msg>This market is a Bill Clinton market. It's searching for a bottom!</Msg><Username>buyrightone</Username><Timestamp>1346903772827</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:56:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>