<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345348819000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rule of thumb: you get what you pay for. If you pay $199 for a tablet you got yourself a $199 POS --------------------------- $199 doing wonders for Google Nexus 7 !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345348819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 00:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345353472000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffett Dumps All Shares of Intel</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345331963000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:19:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NVDA and QCOM begging for TriGate ...LOL.... enjoy the ride.... certainly ASML will provide the equipment .... sucker</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1345353472000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 01:17:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345383105000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would be more like a toy as in windows ce version 8. Good luke watching videos from youtube off that.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1345383105000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 09:31:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345386840000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what wonders ?? losing money on it or breaking even??</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345386840000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 10:34:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345387751000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The $199 news has wallis scared crapless. He has his aliases out in full force on this subject in an effort to defeat the original message.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1345387751000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 10:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345388564000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I actually agree with the notion that cheaper tablets is what we need. Right now people are programmed to spend $500 on an iPad. A few years from now they will know that when their tablet breaks or gets lost or stolen they can find a replacement for under $300. I even think ten inch tablets may eventually be under $200 and 7" under $100. When you have less cash invested you have less emotions invested as well. The market will be commodity driven. Google isn't trying to make it's own gear long term. They just wanted to show what a little kick butt under $200 tablet could be with a stock OS (no shells like other manufactures put over to cheapen the experience). Where does this leave Intel? I'll put it this way, if Google really thought that ARM could have taken the industry where it needed to go and Intel would never get mobile they wouldn't have bothered. When Intel started mentioning 22nm and 14nm production on 450mm wafers eventually which meant tens of millions of units being created non-stop Google could have bought into this vision. Now, what to do when you are Apple? TSMC made a strong and convincing argument last year at your corporate HQ about their production capabilities. Then 28nm fired up this year around the same time that Intel fired up 22nm. Intel had product in the streets while TSMC had problems. They still have Samsung for now, but the allure of ARM probably doesn't look that sweet as it did a few years ago. Somehow some people here think that Intel can't sell a processor for $20 and not make 60 margins. Not only do I think they can but they can also position themselves to sell for $30 when ARM is at $20 and having people gladly fork over the extra 50% because the Intel processor is worth it. That's the part that probably scares ARM the most. Pound for pound AMD was usually the least expensive processor, and year after year it got them nowhere. Then there was a day when AMD had a superior processor for a time, and Intel still grew. History never repeats, the whole world only wants ARM. There will never be a day when consumers demand their tablets with Intel processors. The Intel brand name means nothing to consumers thought it's one of the worlds most recognizable logos.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345388564000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:02:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345388952000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>also unfortunately Nexus has quality issues as well.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345388952000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345389035000-8</Id><Title>Does the Nexus 7 Have Quality Problems?</Title><Msg>well yeh Specifically, there's not just one bad batch of Nexus 7 tablets out there - there may multiple bad batches with different problems. Few reviewers got the bad units, of course, because one of the basic jobs of tech product PR is to make sure the gadget works before you send it out. Some of this is luck, of course; we have three tablets and no problems here. Here's what we're seeing reported so far. None of these problems seem to be solvable by software; they're just cases of bad components, manufacturing, and assembly: Screen separation and creaking Android Authority discovered that some Nexus 7 screens don't appear to be attached very securely, causing the case to make a creaking sound. The geeks at Android Authroity and XDA Forums have a DIY fix, but we'd advise ordinary consumers to just return their tablets. Backlight bleeding Pocketnow found a Twitter report with a photo of the Nexus 7's backlight bleeding horribly, which makes the lighting on the screen look very uneven. This might be related to the screen assembly issue mentioned above. I've seen backlight bleeding problems on plenty of "cheapo" sub-$100 tablets; it's one of the things that doesn't get checked for when you're cutting corners. Charging problems Chris Ziegler at The Verge, one of the foremost mobile experts in the U.S., had this problem: his Nexus 7 wouldn't charge off of various wall chargers. It turns out it shipped with a broken MicroUSB port. Search through forums and you'll find other people with the same problem. ... "</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345389035000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:10:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345392126000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The market will be commodity driven" Is the Ipad3 commodity ? iPhone 5 ? Ultrabook ?? " Then 28nm fired up this year around the same time that Intel fired up 22nm. Intel had product in the streets while TSMC had problems. " Naive... FPGA companies were selling TSMC 28nm products for a year... "the allure of ARM probably doesn't look that sweet as it did a few years ago." Naive...ARM is now the test vehicle for foundries new nodes... The world's R&amp;D $$ will go into ARM devices... It's just starting !!!! "Somehow some people here think that Intel can't sell a processor for $20 and not make 60 margins. Not only do I think they can but they can also position themselves to sell for $30 when ARM is at $20" Medfield $17 http://www.fudzilla.com/home/item/25514-intel-reveals-medfield-specs-deals "Pound for pound AMD was usually the least expensive processor, and year after year it got them nowhere." x86 market, INtel monopoly practices... have you already forgotten the law suits... "History never repeats," And ARM isn't AMD... "There will never be a day when consumers demand their tablets with Intel processors. The Intel brand name means nothing to consumers" less every year that goes by...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345392126000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:02:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345392475000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>re:Naive...ARM is now the test vehicle for foundries new nodes... The world's R&amp;D $$ will go into ARM devices... It's just starting !!!! Ya. Thats why HP just dumped ARM for all Intel products, from tablets to servers. $$ invested in an ARM platform versus an Intel platform is just $$ thrown down the drain. Companies are starting to realize that. Software/hardware players know that Intel will be stronger than ever in 5 years..ARM...not so much. They are placing their "bets".</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1345392475000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:07:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345392697000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Thats why HP just dumped ARM for all Intel products, from tablets to servers." Already answered in this thread !!!!! Qualcomm ARM SOCs were MIA for HP... servers are for ARM64 "Software/hardware players know that Intel will be stronger than ever in 5 years..ARM...not so much." links ?? Again, your make-up self-serving claims...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345392697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345393629000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Somehow some people here think that Intel can't sell a processor for $20 and not make 60 margins." Probably the most important statement on this thread. All of the Intel Bear analysts dont understand this concept. The $20 can go even lower as Intel increases its server ASP mix going forward. Yet, idiots think that a splintered outsourcing ARM ecosystem can compete with Intel's business model. LOL.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1345393629000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:27:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345393856000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The $20 can go even lower as Intel increases its server ASP mix going forward. " INtel lock on the server market will be under attack from ARM64... The first real competition INtel has had in decades !!! INtel ASPs will be forced down, Down, DOWN !!!! "a splintered outsourcing ARM ecosystem can compete with Intel's business model." The world's R&amp;D $$ vs INtel R&amp;D $$ who's got more $$..</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345393856000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:30:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345394796000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Again, your make-up self-serving claims... " coming from it's pretty funny</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345394796000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345397197000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;INtel lock on the server market will be under attack from ARM64... The first real competition INtel has had in decades !!! I'm glad you brought up the concept of decades because the last time that RISC was on top they had Microsoft behind it powering NT. At that time RISC processors were 15 to 30 percent faster than Intel. Microsoft couldn't wait to get these truly superior processors on its team. NT was designed specifically for these RISC processors. And for YEARS they ran with dual platforms of NT only to fold it into XP which was X86 only. So, without the "The entire wold is investing in ARM" hyperbole, what is different this time? Honestly, what company is going to take on Intel with ARM64 behind it? Perhaps IBM? Maybe? They have other RISC technologies they are pushing as well. Without a strong champion behind ARM64 how will it rip through the server market to gain market share? I don't see the world in dogmatic points of view. I don't think it's an all Intel world or an all ARM world. Both will survive. Intel cannot supply the world with all the processors it needs. The capital expansion means that Intel sees a very bright future. I don't see Intel's margins getting pushed out of existence. I do see a huge commodity market where tablets will be commodities like PC's. For $100 to $200 a tablet you aren't going to get the best and brightest technology, but a lot of the older and slower future technology will be ARM based and "good enough." For those who demand more there will be Intel. For those who want Intel processors (sorry to disagree but consumers will pay for the Intel name for many years to come) they will be available for a higher price. Both Apple and Microsoft want one version of an OS. It's more likely to be X86 than ARM, but with Apple, I am not saying that being all ARM isn't out of the question. Then there is Google with Android. Can you imagine running Windows as an app on your Android device? For consumers, an Android interface along with Windows programs running native on their X86 devices may become a reality. There will be Microsost, Google, and Apple in the future. Microsoft is hedging it's bets with ARM, but is secure with Intel. Google doesn't believe it can win it's future exclusively with ARM. Apple is paralyzed now from the death of Steve Jobs. Nothing will change very soon (thought I would love to see a iPhone5 with Intel). But the point remains that Apple dumped RISC for it's computers. Intel is still doing well despite the poor economy. I don't see how Intel is failing.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345397197000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 13:26:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345398162000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I'm glad you brought up the concept of decades because the last time that RISC was on top " RISC, CISC... irrelevant "So, without the "The entire wold is investing in ARM" hyperbole, what is different this time?" What is different this time is that the entire world is investing in ARM... World support !!!!!!!!!!!!! NOt a single RISC company... "Without a strong champion behind ARM64 how will it rip through the server market to gain market share?" See above... The entire world behind it... " I don't think it's an all Intel world or an all ARM world. Both will survive. Intel cannot supply the world with all the processors it needs." Congrats on your updated view !!!!!!!! "Both Apple and Microsoft want one version of an OS. It's more likely to be X86 than ARM," Entirely wishful &amp; hopeful thinking... Apple designs their own ARM SOCs... Microsoft is porting to ARM with 'multiple' SOCs !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! "But the point remains that Apple dumped RISC for it's computers." Apple dumped another CISC for its computers...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345398162000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 13:42:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345399081000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more nexus issues http://www.zdnet.com/nexus-7-touchscreen-problem-caught-on-video-7000001325/</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345399081000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 13:58:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345400642000-18</Id><Topic><Title>INtel Xeon Phi</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345331485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:11:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Checked out the link....so now we have a first name for Getanid61 - Bob (the only guy who takes the trouble of religiously spelling Intel as INtel) has commented on the article. Seems in addition to being a fervent nVidia admirer, he also badly wants Intel/x86 to hurt. I would guess Bob is ex-Intel. And has been slighted by Intel in some way, shape, or form. No offense...just a bit of psychoanalysis for fun. Bob, give it a rest...the big guys, especially those with 80-90% of the market, always win - either organically (which would be their preference) or by acquisition. They don't die or fade off easily.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1345400642000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 14:24:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345401238000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Going Higher!</Title><Username>barnebasevz893</Username><Timestamp>1345391417000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great return</Msg><Username>fabianohia644</Username><Timestamp>1345401238000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 14:33:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345401825000-20</Id><Topic><Title>INtel Xeon Phi</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345331485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:11:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>".so now we have a first name for Getanid61 - Bob" LOL !! ltisteve and Dnenni have desperately tried to track me down... Good Luck !! "I would guess Bob is ex-Intel" Never worked at INtel, NVidia, or AMD " And has been slighted by Intel in some way, shape, or form." Me personally...NO But I've seen companies get contracts cancelled due to INtel threats...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345401825000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 14:43:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345402000000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Does the Nexus 7 Have Quality Problems?</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345389035000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol...ol</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1345402000000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 14:46:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345402514000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Does the Nexus 7 Have Quality Problems?</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345389035000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wait a few months before buying one.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345402514000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 14:55:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345403588000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;entire world is investing in ARM... World support !!!!!!!!!!!!! NOt a single RISC company... This implies that the entire world has weighed the decision between ARM and Intel carefully and has opted for ARM. Is it really this way, or is it more likely that people buy what they want without worrying about which processor is powering it? With that being said, just because they are buying ARM based products today doesn't mean that they have a strong preference for ARM. And that reminds me of the time that a famous restaurant was closing in Los Angles. They had the news reporters out there and they had a man on the street interview. "Oh, this restaurant is part of our community, part of our culture, it's our heritage" was what they heard. And then the reporter asked a left field question "if you feel that way, when was the last time you ate here?" Deer in the headlights "Well, ah, it's been a few years." Even if there is a love affair with ARM held worldwide (which I highly doubt) it doesn't mean that consumers will continue to support it on principle alone. Its no longer a question of "What have you done for me lately?" It's going to be more of a question of "What can you do for me today?" Brand name will get Intel a little traction, but its going to be processors on the streets that will make or break their futures.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345403588000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:13:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345403680000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra 3 is a piece of garbage. Cant wait until dooped consumers start asking for recalls. This is supposed to be ARM's "high-end" chip of the future? LOL.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1345403680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345404064000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This implies that the entire world has weighed the decision between ARM and Intel carefully and has opted for ARM." Nothing for the world to decide... INtel has successfully kept the rest of the world off x86... Needed AMD for dual-source issues... and for a time, VIA for chipsets... "just because they are buying ARM based products today doesn't mean that they have a strong preference for ARM." no preference... in fact they don't care !! "It's going to be more of a question of "What can you do for me today?"" Congrats on your updated view... "Brand name will get Intel a little traction" subsidizing $$ will get them more !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345404064000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:21:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345406104000-26</Id><Title>Nvidia Tegra 3 processor problems</Title><Msg>http://www.zdnet.com/nexus-7-touchscreen-problem-caught-on-video-7000001325/</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345406104000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:55:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345407598000-27</Id><Title>Ryan and Religion</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney expects his running mate to help deliver the Catholic vote and smooth over any discomfort among Catholics about Mormonism. (This is the first major-party ticket to go Protestant-less.) Yet after Ryan claimed his budget was shaped by his faith, the United States Conference of Catholic Bishops deemed it immoral. “A just spending bill cannot rely on disproportionate cuts in essential services to poor and vulnerable persons,” the bishops wrote in a letter to Congress. The Jesuits were even more tart, with one group writing to Ryan that “Your budget appears to reflect the values of your favorite philosopher, Ayn Rand, rather than the Gospel of Jesus Christ.” http://www.nytimes.com/2012/08/19/opinion/sunday/dowd-beware-a-beautiful-calm.html?_r=1&amp;ref=todayspaper</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345407598000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:19:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345407951000-28</Id><Title>Toshiba halting development of Windows RT tablet PCs may cause chain reaction</Title><Msg>[Before everyone gets too excited about RT...] [WOA-&gt;DOA...] With Toshiba recently announcing it will halt development plans for Windows RT tablet PCs due to component supply delays, sources from notebook players believe the action could trigger other brand vendors to follow suit. The sources believe that problems such as Windows RT having issues with software compatibility, weaker than expected performance, and price competition for Android and Microsoft's own Surface tablets, could be the reasons that Toshiba has decided to back down from Windows RT development and is using the delays in component supply as an excuse. Toshiba will be able avoid rashly launching devices that have not yet reached expectations, and if other players also decide to follow suit and delay their Windows RT tablet PC launches, Microsoft and Nvidia may be the only two players left to promote the market. The sources also pointed out that PC players are having a lot of difficulties developing Windows RT products and in addition to software driver issues, the operating system also performs rather weak compared to Windows 8 running on standard PC hardware. http://www.digitimes.com/news/a20120815PD208.html</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345407951000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:25:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345407993000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba halting development of Windows RT tablet PCs may cause chain reaction</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345407951000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:25:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The sources also pointed out that PC players are having a lot of difficulties developing Windows RT products and in addition to software driver issues, the operating system also performs rather weak compared to Windows 8 running on standard PC hardware."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345407993000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:26:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345408352000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan and Religion</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345407598000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Must be true if it is the ny times. lol</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1345408352000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345408625000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba halting development of Windows RT tablet PCs may cause chain reaction</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345407951000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:25:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol...</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1345408625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:37:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345409126000-32</Id><Title>Sweet Lenovo Ultrabooks under 800 bucks</Title><Msg>http://www.lenovo.com/products/us/laptop/ultrabook/book-of-do?cid=us|semd|se|google|lenovousindirect|z18E1C|s</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1345409126000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:45:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345409305000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Toshiba halting development of Windows RT tablet PCs may cause chain reaction</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345407951000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:25:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Expect Dell to be the next shoe to drop. First HP bailed on RT, now Toshiba (a low-end brand which says a lot!!). Once Dell bails, its game over for RT before the game has even begun LOL.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1345409305000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:48:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345409617000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan and Religion</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345407598000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Latest polls have Romney pulling ahead. Ryan has made a huge difference.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1345409617000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345410287000-35</Id><Title>Wally in full political scramble mode now, LOL!</Title><Msg>Not a peep from Wally about Politics while Obama was way in the lead, but now that most polls show the lead drastically shrinking or even gone, Wally, just like the DNC, is engaging in a pathetic and obsessive smear campaign daily. Funny Stuff!</Msg><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1345410287000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:04:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345410455000-36</Id><Title>Ultrabook commercials vs. RT commercials</Title><Msg>LOL A million to........none. ARMH's marketing budget consists of some guy (getanid61) trashing Intel on the yahoo board 7 days a week.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1345410455000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:07:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345411396000-37</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan and Religion</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345407598000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NY time blows this non-issue out of proportion using FUD tactics.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345411396000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:23:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345412875000-38</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, without the "The entire wold is investing in ARM" hyperbole, what is different this time? Honestly, what company is going to take on Intel with ARM64 behind it? Perhaps IBM? Maybe? They have other RISC technologies they are pushing as well. Without a strong champion behind ARM64 how will it rip through the server market to gain market share? ----- "what is different this time?" One ISA to rule them all...Perhaps. Maybe. Don't confuse ARM the company and ARM the ISA. As for ARM64, who knows? The latest firm to design it's own CPU's on the ARM 64 bit ISA is Cavium. None of (announced) firms will be targeting Intel's market directly, but will be nibbling round the edges.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1345412875000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:47:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345414615000-39</Id><Title>THE Ultrabook Message</Title><Msg>This message is very, very clear...Ultrabooks and Intel Windows 8 Tablets will catch on fire. This is just the start of a huge wave... Check it out and see for yourself. http://www.lenovo.com/products/us/laptop/ultrabook/book-of-do?showVideo=true</Msg><Username>san_warzone</Username><Timestamp>1345414615000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 18:16:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345416832000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Wally in full political scramble mode now, LOL!</Title><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1345410287000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:04:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a liar or at least illinformed. Polls? Even fuxed up news poll has Obummer ahead. Raspuking polls too. http://realclearpolitics.com/epolls/2012/president/us/general_election_romney_vs_obama-1171.html</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1345416832000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 18:53:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345417649000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan and Religion</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345407598000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Catholic church also finds it immoral that we have borders and don't let in everybody in the world and take care of them. But, hey, I am glad you've move on past Romney's tax returns. Sooner or later we need to evaluate Obama on the job he's currently doing, instead of spinning the Catholic church's POV on his VP's budget. Obama sold us all on hope and change. Well, I 'hoped' for more from him, but now I see it's time to make a 'change.'</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345417649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 19:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345420064000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan and Religion</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345407598000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also in the NY Times is the secret private memo from Romney that consistent with his religion would restart prohibition and allow more than one wife if he is elected president. come on man LOL</Msg><Username>sanjitkumar23</Username><Timestamp>1345420064000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 19:47:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345420354000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nibbling around the edges is something Intel can handle. They are used to full front assaults.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345420354000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 19:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345420866000-44</Id><Topic><Title>THE Ultrabook Message</Title><Username>san_warzone</Username><Timestamp>1345414615000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 18:16:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just liked the part where people were passing along the Ultrabook like a sexually transmitted disease. It's a cute little movie.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1345420866000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:01:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345424508000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Wally in full political scramble mode now, LOL!</Title><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1345410287000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:04:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RED ALERT</Msg><Username>wallisweavergayalias_alert</Username><Timestamp>1345424508000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 21:01:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345427087000-46</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Windows RT Surface $199</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345334041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hard to believe anyone would fork over 200 bucks just to check email and surf the web and play a few games, but nothing else. They could already do that with their smartphones.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1345427087000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 21:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>