<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348459658832-1</Id><Topic><Title>No way INTC can sustain a $20+ stock price</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1348372994711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 00:03:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm going to ruin you sir. I'm going to sue you for everything you're worth. I shall destroy you and push your face in the mud. And thems are the good things I'm going to do to you.</Msg><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1348459658832</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 00:07:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348468198851-2</Id><Title>KICKING OBAMA OUT IN NOVEMBER IS THE RIGHT THING TO DO.</Title><Msg>HOPE YOU ARE WITH US.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348468198851</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 02:29:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348475401826-3</Id><Topic><Title>KICKING OBAMA OUT IN NOVEMBER IS THE RIGHT THING TO DO.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348468198851</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 02:29:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It looks like "LOSING" is going to be the "RIGHT" thing to do this year for the GOP. “If the Republican Party nominates Mitt Romney, we will lose.” Ann Coulter</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1348475401826</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 04:30:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348485969614-4</Id><Topic><Title>Intel keep the powder dry.....</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348480838041</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 06:00:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" six products have now been publicly announced" yippee...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1348485969614</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 07:26:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348488657515-5</Id><Topic><Title>Intel keep the powder dry.....</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348480838041</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 06:00:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Getanid61 is clearly still SEETHING about Intel chips replacing his beloved ARM chips in his own country. LOL. To recap: ARM chips DITCHED for Intel chips in the new Motorola Razr i in London.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1348488657515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 08:10:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348490136501-6</Id><Title>Smartphone Processor Branding</Title><Msg>Globally Intel has one of the most recongized logos and consumers associate that brand promise with performance. Now that Intel is sporting the "Intel Inside" logos on its smartphones, ARM manufacturers want to promote their brand. However the problem for the ARM camp is that ARM manufacturers are too fragmented with no single brand name to promote. It's pretty much the same situation with tablets. There will be Intel branded smartphones and tablets that everyone will recognize and trust and there will be everything else that no one will recognize.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1348490136501</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 08:35:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348490170474-7</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>Stocks spent last week consolidating their gains from previous week's rally. The lack of volume and choppy trades (thursday's upside reversal followed by friday's downside reversal) suggested continuing indecision among investors. No one wants to fight the Fed, while few consider it a good entry point with economic fundamentals showing little sign of improvement. Technically, short term bullish momentum has weakened, but the uptrend stays firm. As we head in to quarter end this week, watch near term support at yesterday's low (1450 for the S&amp;P 500) and resistance at last Friday's high (1475 for the S&amp;P 500). Breaking out of those levels would likely start a new leg of down (breaking support) or up (breaking resistance) moves. Besides watching the near term support and resistance, keep an eye on the DJ Transportation index which broke below its lows in each of the prior three months. Its 2012 low was at 4847 on a closing basis (4795 on the intraday basis) on June 4. Should the transits break its June low, it could have significantly negative implication for the overall market. However, should the DJ transportation index hold above 4873, its closing low in May, it could potentially set up an inverse head and shoulders bottom which would be a bullish sign on an intermediate term basis. have a nice day.</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1348490170474</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 08:36:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348491681186-8</Id><Topic><Title>30 Billion</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1348445538328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:12:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually it was when Fast Money Pete Najarian said were going to -30 Gitty Up. Just goes to show you any time these clowns say something - do the opposite!</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1348491681186</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:01:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348492022735-9</Id><Title>Dividend declared way in advance of pay date,</Title><Msg>Intel Corporation's board of directors has declared a 22.5 cents per share (90 cents per share on an annual basis) quarterly dividend on the company's common stock. The dividend will be payable on Dec. 1, 2012 to stockholders of record on Nov. 7, 2012.</Msg><Username>hd_lowrider_stormy</Username><Timestamp>1348492022735</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:07:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348492327032-10</Id><Title>I will be taking INTC down today</Title><Msg>sell early or lose more money</Msg><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348492327032</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:12:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348492379773-11</Id><Topic><Title>Will INTC squeeze shorts soon?</Title><Username>veqasfletch2001</Username><Timestamp>1348445793113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:16:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not yet apparantly, have to work off an overbght overall market.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348492379773</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348492725794-12</Id><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Msg>1.) The revenue miss has been priced in. Six times! 2.) Intel is in control of its own destiny. 3.) Intel's fabrication lead is significant and growing larger day by day. 4.) Intel will pass ARM in power efficiency in 2013. 5.) Intel's WiFi chip will insure a dominant role in the IoT (Internet of Things) - a huge market as large as the existing cellular market. 6.) Windows 8 release coming up shortly. 7.) Intel has reached parity in cell phone performance and will soon take the lead. 8.) Intel will aggressively roll out smartphones in the US in 2013 when LTE capability becomes available. 9.) Laptop and Ultrabook pricing will begin to significantly affect ARM tablet sales. 10.) New Intel tablets will gain traction in enterprise use - a place where due to their limitations ARM tablets can't go. Yet in spite of all of this, Wall Street's biggest firms continue their attacks on Intel. Intel shareholders and investors need to fight back. Demand answers and accountability.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348492725794</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:18:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348492854757-13</Id><Topic><Title>$22 TOMORROW?</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348444737940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:58:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can U say "Gap down at the open?" TOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348492854757</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:20:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348492930671-14</Id><Title>Intel to host Capital Global Summit on October 1</Title><Msg>[A good time for Intel to fight back against the Wall Street #$%$...] Intel Capital Global Summit will be held from October 1-3, in California, the US with Intel CEO Paul Otellini and Intel executive vice president and president of Intel Capital Arvind Sodhani to disclose information about the company's future roadmap and investment planning. Intel will invite its invested companies, global partners and professionals from IT related industries and the financial segment to exchange thoughts on future innovations and development. The meeting is also expected to help partners learn about the latest ideas that ​​Intel Capital has for further analysis on the technological direction of Intel, according to sources from the upstream supply chain.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348492930671</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:22:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348493073913-15</Id><Title>Collaboration with Lenovo on the upcoming Intel Atom processor-based mobile platform</Title><Msg>Phoenix Technologies announces collaboration with Lenovo on the upcoming Intel Atom processor-based mobile platform Phoenix Technologies Ltd., the global leader in UEFI firmware technology, products and tools, is pleased to announce its collaboration with Lenovo on its new ThinkPad Tablet 2. Powered by Windows 8 and Phoenix SecureCore Technology BIOS, the ThinkPad Tablet 2 is based on the new Intel Atom processor-based mobile platform. The ThinkPad Tablet 2 is a versatile mobile device that combines notebook functionality and tablet mobility, making it ideal for use in the office, home or when traveling. Phoenix SecureCore Technology BIOS boasts a feature set that is robust enough to optimize Lenovo's ThinkPad Tablet 2 design, supporting mobility and connectivity features that include USB and I2C touch, a virtual keyboard, touch hotzone, Connected Standby, fTPM/TPM 2.0 and Windows UEFI Firmware Update (WUFU). Tablets are primarily mobility and connectivity devices, yet, it is extremely important to make sure they are highly secure and manageable. "We chose Phoenix SecureCore Technology because it supports Intel Platform Trust Technology, providing compatibility with Windows 8 security features and offering comprehensive flash updates," said Thomas Butler, Director, Worldwide ThinkPad Product Marketing, Lenovo.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348493073913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:24:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348493142082-16</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348492725794</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The revenue miss has been priced in. Six times! -------------- Is that the same "Huge honking $6 miss" you've been talking about for some time, Pumpwad? Is Intel still "good for 30" like you said it was in May or have you retracted that prediction?</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348493142082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:25:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348493330891-17</Id><Topic><Title>I will be taking INTC down today</Title><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348492327032</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:12:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel longs need to show some backbone in standing up to the cockroaches, shills, analysts, fanbois, lucies and other associated parasites on the US economy before they crash the country a second time...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348493330891</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:28:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348493547094-18</Id><Title>Intel just announced another 22.5 cent Dividend, payable December 1st.</Title><Msg>Buy more now and collect the divvy.</Msg><Username>lucy_zero</Username><Timestamp>1348493547094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:32:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348493570288-19</Id><Title>Apple tries to buy Google staff</Title><Msg>Need a way out of the map fiasco Apple is trying to buy its way out of the map fiasco by hiring Google experts. Jobs' Mob made a big thing of cancelling its map software on iOS 6 and forcing users to use its own “superior” system. The only problem was that it was complete rubbish and could not even direct a fanboy to one of its own stores. In short, it should never have been released, let alone be made a marketing reason to buy the new iPhone5. Now it seems that Apple has realised that it is not going to get away with running the shonky product for long and is desperate to make it go. Unfortunately the only place that such expertise exists is with its rival Google, which it famously fired. Using recruiters, Apple is pursuing a strategy of luring away Google Maps employees who helped develop the search giant’s product on contract. It might just get away with it because most of them might want to accept due in part to the opportunity Apple represents to build new product, instead of just doing “tedious updates” on a largely complete platform. According to Techcrunch, when attention at Google turned to indoor mapping, things started to become less interesting and a lot of staff began looking around for other opportunities. Google probably is not losing much sleep over it. The recent Apple Maps fiasco has shown that Apple is light years behind Google when it comes to mapping. It is only taking contractors, and Google has to get rid of them every year anyway. From Fudzilla</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348493570288</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:32:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348493751168-20</Id><Title>Wow, this Seeking Alpha guy just did a 180 on Intel</Title><Msg>He's been pumping the crap out of Intel and now writes this? Apple's iPhone 5 Chip Design Seriously Impresses - Is The Competition Asleep? September 24, 2012 | 2 commentsby: Ashraf Eassa | about: AAPL, includes: ARMH, INTC, NVDA, QCOM, SSNLF.PK Disclosure: I am long INTC, AMD, NVDA. I wrote this article myself, and it expresses my own opinions. I am not receiving compensation for it (other than from Seeking Alpha). I have no business relationship with any company whose stock is mentioned in this article. (More...) Apple (AAPL) has not failed to impress with its A6 system-on-chip in its latest iPhone 5. A couple of days ago, it was revealed that Apple took its chip design to the next level by actually designing its own custom ARM-compatible (ARMH) cores rather than using off-the-shelf ARM designs as it has done in the past. This level of customization gives Apple much more control over the performance and power consumption profile of the chip for the intended workloads. According to Anandtech, the Apple A6 is 2.13x faster than the iPhone 4S on average. While this in itself is a nontrivial improvement, the more shocking point is that in both CPU power as well as GPU power, the latest Apple chip leaves competition from Nvidia (NVDA), Qualcomm (QCOM), Intel (INTC), and Samsung (SSNLF.PK) in the dust. Graphics: A Very Significant Lead According to the Anandtech benchmarks, the graphics processor in the Apple A6 system-on-chip is just as fast as the graphics available in the latest iPad. More importantly, none of the other graphics chips in currently shipping competing solutions even comes close to matching Apple's performance. This is extremely significant. First and foremost, this will be yet another reason that game developers will be attracted to the Apple platform over Google's (GOOG) Android platform or even Microsoft's (MSFT) Windows Phone 8. With developer support stemming from both a fairly closed ecosystem (making it easier for developers) as well as class-leading graphics hardware, phone buyers will be particularly attracted to the notion of high quality mobile gaming unavailable on any of the other platforms. Interestingly enough, Apple didn't even design its own graphics chip here, but it was smart enough to use the latest-and-greatest from Imagination Technologies and not treat graphics as a second-class citizen. Other system-on-chip vendors need to start caring about graphics performance since gaming is a non-trivial addition to the "user experience." In-House CPU Design Is World-Beating The CPU portion of the Apple A6 looks modest on the surface: a 1GHz dual core chip. With "quad core" phones using the Nvidia Tegra 3 and Samsung Exynos, one would initially be led to believe that Apple's CPU performance is trailing and not leading-edge. And they would be dead wrong. Apple's dual-core 1GHz design is highly efficient and is optimized to get as much work done per clock-cycle as possible, and its performance speaks volumes. In BrowserMark, SunSpider, and Google's Octane and V8 benchmarks, Apple's custom CPU cores prove to be faster core-for-core and clock-for-clock than even Qualcomm's Snapdragon S4, the previous mobile CPU champion. Don't be fooled by "gigahertz" and "core counts," as these metrics do not tell the full story. Competition: Time To Really Push Apple's leap-frogging of the entirety of the smartphone system-on-chip industry is something that all of the players should take serious notice of. Apple's first attempt at its own CPU design has been a rousing success, and the dedicated chip players will need to really push hard if they are to enable performance on competing smartphone platforms that are comparable to or even exceed what Apple's now provides Qualcomm is fine because its dual-core Snapdragon S4, within a similar power envelope to the Apple A6, is able to keep up with the A6 on the CPU side (and the quad-core iteration in a similar power envelope will be significantly faster). The higher-end Snapdragon S4 Pro is faster than the Apple A6 on the CPU front and competitive on the graphics front. Nvidia needs to get its ARM Cortex A15 based designs with an updated graphics processor sooner than later. As a company whose core competency is graphics, it is embarrassing that Imagination Technologies, with its much more limited resources, is able to essentially dominate the field. Intel is in a very tough spot right now. While its "Medfield" chips based on a four-year-old micro-architecture are actually competitive with (but slower than) Qualcomm's dual core Snapdragon S4 in a number of tests, its next generation "Merrifield" needs to absolutely "wow" on a performance/watt basis. And by "wow", I mean, it can't afford to be #2 in any metric: CPU performance, GPU performance, or battery life. Intel needs to offer a fundamentally better piece of silicon than anybody else if it is to be taken seriously in the low-power space. Conclusion Apple has really outdone itself here. It owns its own software/operating system, its own retail stores, and is now succeeding against giants in the semiconductor space at their own game. Only Qualcomm has a competitive solution at the moment, and it's starting to look increasingly likely that for non-Apple devices Qualcomm will be the vendor of choice for quite some time.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1348493751168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:35:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348493957592-21</Id><Title>Intel shows us Clover Trail performance on a tablet</Title><Msg>Windows 8 looks good on Acer W510 Last week at IDF 2012 we had a chance to sit down with the guys from Intel performance labs and a chap called Francois Piednoel, a well-known figure in Intel’s technical PR used the opportunity to show off Windows 8 on an Acer W510, a Clover Trail tablet with 10.1-inch screen that works just great. Many people are still skeptical about Microsoft’s ability to do something big on the tablet market, but this video might actually help to change some minds. Microsoft did a great job on multitasking enabling you to jump through applications including games in the blink of an eye. Our video clearly demonstrates that the tablet, powered by a dual-core Clover Trail chip, handles Windows 8 quite nicely and the whole user experience looks quite impressive. The Acer W510 weighs around 500 grams tablet and it can play very popular DivX HD content without necessity to transcode, which many pirates will find attractive. The tablet feels good in hand and the build quality is really great. We tried it ourselves and it felt and worked great. Enough talking, you can simply play the video to get an idea how fast it is. From Fudzilla [The beginning of the end for the ARM tablet run. And yet the Wall Street ignorance and attacks go on and on and on. Earnings is going to be fun. Shorts are going down...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348493957592</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:39:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348493981451-22</Id><Topic><Title>$22 TOMORROW?</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348444737940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:58:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RTQ $22.72 The Magic 8-Ball is always correct!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348493981451</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:39:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348494014931-23</Id><Title>NTWK $6.75...Up again.......Hottest NASDAQ stock….Up every day since record earnings......Fundamentals can support $16 per analysts with $21 max target......In 2010 it went from $8 to $24 in 4 weeks with 50% lower revenues…..Cloud Division is growing exponentially.....Only 6 PE and 1 times sales is 30% of sector average......Strong 2013 guidance calls for over 30% revenue growth and $1/share net income due to strong global demand for its Legacy and Cloud software solutions</Title><Msg>Short-term Target: $16 per Upgrade………Take a look at incredible NTWK chart. In 2010 NTWK went from $8 to $24 in a few weeks. Today NTWK is a much stronger company with far more revenue sources including new Cloud Divisions. Unlike 2010, NTWK today has the flexibility to deliver reliable software products and services not only from Pakistan but also from excellence centers located in Bangkok, Beijing, the US, and the UK. The float today is 1/10 of what it was then and 2013 revenues are expected to breakaway into the mid $40 million for the first time in company history. During 2010 (and 2007) NTWK's market cap reached over $100 million on 50% lower revenues of what is projected for 2013. During the September 4Q CC NTWK officials stated that revenues are expected to reach $100 Million in 2015 up significantly from the $38 Million reported in 2012. They also expect margins to continue to go up as the high-margin Cloud divisions keep continuing exponentially to revenues. MUST READ ……This Week’s Analysts Comments on Upgrade: We project 13% annual growth to FY14 from FY10 reflecting 80 significant NFS legacy customers in FY14, up from 52, 37, and 28 in FY12, FY11, and FY10, respectively. The new Vroozi Cloud Division contributed $1.3 million in FY12. We expect at least $4 million in FY13 and $6 million to FY14 Our price target is based on the average forward 2013 P/E multiple of 13.2X (up from 12.8X in August 2012). NTWK is trading at 6.4X our FY13 projections. We are forecasting EPS of $0.85 per share. We applied an 11X multiple to our FY13 EPS forecast. We anticipate a richer multiple as earnings momentum builds in FY13. The company guidance calls for $1/share net income in 2013. NTWK is entering FY13 with a $25 million backlog and approximately $100 million in qualified leads. One quarter of the backlog is from four new NFS platform customer implementations that began in 4Q12. In August 2011, NetSol launched its Cloud Vroozi Division, an e-procurement search tool for SAP supplier relationship management (SRM) users. SAP AG is a global vendor of enterprise management systems that has the largest market share (24%) based on a worldwide Gartner survey. Vroozi should provide sales diversification and a higher margin recurring revenue stream. The Vroozi division contributed $1.3 million in FY12 sales and is expected to grow to $4 million in revenues in 2013 NTWK announced its 2nd Cloud Division last week offering an array of products and services to capture a greater % of the cloud applications in North America. The company is implementing this division using their significant software development capabilities and infrastructure. === MORE NTWWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Company projects Doubling/Tripling revenues and net income by 2015 - Significant Institutional investor ownership and growing - Insiders bought over 5% of the Outstanding shares the last 2 years and never sold a single share - Total share count is only 7.5 million shares. The float is only 3 million shares - Trading at forward PE of 5 - Strong balance sheet with $1.5/share cash - Has global agreement with Mercedes Benz - Already 7 countries with NTWK software for leasing and financing Mercedes Benz/Daimler including China, India, Japan, and others…and a few more coming in quarters/years ahead. - No.1 in China and APAC in leasing/financing software products and services. NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Volvo, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc. About NTWK: NetSol Technologies, Inc. ((NASDAQ: NTWK) is a worldwide provider of global IT and enterprise application solutions that include credit and finance portfolio management systems, SAP consulting and services, custom development, systems integration, and technical services for the global Financial, Leasing, Insurance, Energy, and Technology markets. Headquartered in Calabasas, Calif., NetSol's product and services offerings have achieved ISO 9001, ISO 20000, ISO 27001, and SEI (Software Engineering Institute) CMMI (Capability Maturity Model) Maturity Level 5 assessments, a distinction shared by only 178 companies worldwide. The company's clients include Fortune 500 manufacturers, global automakers, financial institutions, utilities, technology providers, and government agencies. NetSol has delivery and support locations in San Francisco, London, Beijing, Bangkok, Lahore, Adelaide, Rio de Janeiro, and Riyadh</Msg><Username>d.malkkey</Username><Timestamp>1348494014931</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:40:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348494056890-24</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348492725794</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1.) The revenue miss has been priced in. Six times! Yeah, that explains the initial collapse. 2.) Intel is in control of its own destiny. This is too weird to answer. They have good fabs. 3.) Intel's fabrication lead is significant and growing larger day by day. Yes and no. TSMC isn't far behind but Intel is the clear leader for now. 4.) Intel will pass ARM in power efficiency in 2013. Maybe, maybe not. ARM people aren't exactly sleeping on the job. 5.) Intel's WiFi chip will insure a dominant role in the IoT (Internet of Things) - a huge market as large as the existing cellular market. Nope. It will ensure that they participate. 6.) Windows 8 release coming up shortly. Nobody cares. IT people dread new versions of Windows and users have lost track. Lots of people still running XP because it works. 7.) Intel has reached parity in cell phone performance and will soon take the lead. Wallis, please. That is beyond exaggeration. They have a couple design wins. 8.) Intel will aggressively roll out smartphones in the US in 2013 when LTE capability becomes available. We'll see. Nobody can predict the future. 9.) Laptop and Ultrabook pricing will begin to significantly affect ARM tablet sales. Nobody cares about tablets. 10.) New Intel tablets will gain traction in enterprise use - a place where due to their limitations ARM tablets can't go. See #9. Nobody cares about tablets.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1348494056890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:40:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348494215291-25</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, this Seeking Alpha guy just did a 180 on Intel</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1348493751168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do his words offend your Intel-centric ears, Pumpwad? Why don't you write him a letter? TOOOOO FUNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348494215291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:43:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348494811319-26</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, this Seeking Alpha guy just did a 180 on Intel</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1348493751168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This just illustrates the normal media ignorance of fabrication. Doesn't matter how great Apple's chip design is (and it's not even a quad core), someone has to make it. Apple is only on 32nm and is pretty much stuck there. Did you hear any "nm" reference in any place anywhere in this article? Intel is not in a tough spot. They are exactly where they want to be. In 2013 they will pass ARM forever in power efficiency. And be way ahead in performance. Bottom line, Apple is stuck at 32nm. Intel is at 22nm and soon to be at 14nm. ARM won't have 14nm for 4 years. Whoever has the best fabrication wins. That's Intel. Forget all the design mumbo jumbo. 14nm. Game over. We're just waiting for it to play out...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348494811319</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:53:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348495123420-27</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348492725794</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What we know that you are an idiot. "strong buy" is at $20, not at $29.</Msg><Username>c757172</Username><Timestamp>1348495123420</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348495129729-28</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, this Seeking Alpha guy just did a 180 on Intel</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1348493751168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First of all, Intel did fall asleep at the wheel and now has to play catch up. That said, I pay no attention to Seeking Alpha...it's just a bunch of longs and shorts writing articles to suit their own self-interests.</Msg><Username>cray3040</Username><Timestamp>1348495129729</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348495316033-29</Id><Topic><Title>I will be taking INTC down today</Title><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348492327032</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:12:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You were warn and you sold as I told you too.</Msg><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348495316033</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:01:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348495538632-30</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, this Seeking Alpha guy just did a 180 on Intel</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1348493751168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That said, I pay no attention to Seeking Alpha...it's just a bunch of longs and shorts writing articles to suit their own self-interests. --------- Much like this message board?</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348495538632</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348495956297-31</Id><Title>Intel plans to crush ARM beyond 20 nm</Title><Msg>From EETimes Speaking to the firm’s executive vice president and head of architecture David (Dadi) Perlmutter recently, EE Times learned that Intel is pushing ahead with its sub 20-nm and 14-nm plans, while the ARM ecosystem struggles to find a business model beyond 22 nm. Intel is biding its time. The semi giant appears quite prepared to wait a couple of generations until sub 20-nm nodes are breached before bringing the battle of low power processing to ARM and its mobile partners. Indeed, Intel claims to have line of sight all the way to a 7-nm process, with all the firm’s CPUs becoming SoCs as of next year. Haswell will be Intel’s 22-nm SoC for tablets and Ultrabooks, while Merrifield will be the company’s SoC for tablets and smartphones. After that, 14nm is expected to be Intel's killer node with the most dramatic power improvements and integrated baseband - although the firm has yet to officially announce it. Meanwhile, the ARM ecosystem has a rather more challenging road ahead of it, with low cost continuing to present a challenge for foundry supply, yield and materials science. ARM is seeing Moore's Law slowing down in its foundries, due to a lack of investment and also to a deficit in R&amp;D capabilities. Even at its current 28-nm, the ARM ecosystem is feeling the squeeze. Today only one foundry (TSMC) can yield 28-nm chips and the entire industry is under-supplied. With Intel pushing ahead to introduce FinFET to foundries and EUV at 14nm and under, ARM faces an even bigger crisis of competition. Meanwhile, Intel’s design teams work hand in hand with the foundries, in one unified effort. “We always work very closely with the fab,” said Perlmutter. “Each time we put a new big challenge in front of the giant team,” he said, adding that every time the focus centered on new and different aspects of the technology. “If you develop technology, every day you bounce into a problem which may seem to be a showstopper,” he explained, discussing the various challenges the teams had overcome hitting the targets for Haswell’s design. “What looked to be hugely complicated 10 years ago looks like a piece of cake now. We have to overcome new things every time around, so we have an ‘aha’ moment every day, every minute in every single Intel product,” he said.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348495956297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348496077433-32</Id><Topic><Title>Intel plans to crush ARM beyond 20 nm</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348495956297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:12:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Experience enabled by performance It’s not just the technology Intel strives to better with every generation, but also its human taskforce. “[The engineers] had better be better these days, way better than when I was an engineer,” said Permutter, adding that today’s engineers came at things “with a different mindset.” This, he said, meant the new generation was used to products with much broader market capabilities. “In some ways that helps a lot, in other ways it makes it harder,” he said. Despite the seeming solidity of Intel’s roadmap, however, Perlmutter is well aware that the road ahead may not be entirely bump free. “I always worry. I was worried when we moved to 1 micron, I was worried when we went below 100, I’m worried about going below 10, but my colleagues running the technology side tell me they are worried too, and the moment they are worried, I’m no longer worried, because they do their job,” he said. Having said that, ARM and its partners might do well to worry a bit more about Intel’s progress, with the firm’s 14-nm node already in “extremely advanced stages of design.” Perlmutter said his firm was holding firm to its schedule of putting its first products on 14nm in production later next year . “We will launch many products on 14nm. Our plans are advancing and we believe that we will grow the gap and it will give us more advantage,” said Perlmutter. “Experience is enabled by performance. The better performance you have the better you are. It’s all about performance,” he said, adding “high performance computing in a small form factor.”</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348496077433</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:14:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348496289858-33</Id><Topic><Title>We like the 4% dividends and we are buying shares now</Title><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348246253924</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:50:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lol, GE has more than tripled since then...you should be thrilled you bought GE instead of INTC unless you dont like money. INTC missed the boat on too many new technologies and will pay the price in the near term. The 4% dividend is nice, but I wouldnt buy it just for that since the PC market is continuing to deteriorate.</Msg><Username>tkell31</Username><Timestamp>1348496289858</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348497006487-34</Id><Topic><Title>We're Good for 30</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1327420596000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-01-24 10:56:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Write more letters, Pumpwad! TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348497006487</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:30:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348497499882-35</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, this Seeking Alpha guy just did a 180 on Intel</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1348493751168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, no. This board is only filled with unbiased opinions for the greater good of the investment community ;)</Msg><Username>cray3040</Username><Timestamp>1348497499882</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348497673958-36</Id><Title>Tremendous buy chance</Title><Msg>I Suggest entering with a#$%$olute complete conviction 2 positions depending on risk preference. Jan 2013 25 calls at 0.34 or jan 2014 25 calls at 1.44. In fact personalty i enter both, most money used for the jan 2014 call position as a long term entry and i use the jan 2013 speculative calls as a near term super oversold buy signal entry. I will sell the jan 2013 calls on the next rally that touches +2sd for the first time and i will sell covered calls on the 2014 25s when this happens as well (either novermber or jan ones even the same sold there if lucky to see it this way). I am prepared to wait as long as needed for this to happen and able to add to both positions if needed lower. Neither TXN nor Qualcom deserve to have a pe 100% larger than intel's. The thesis that the world is ending PCs and going to smart phones/ipads etc is a false one. It is a parallel transition and the PC and the home core electronics eventually will experience a Renaissance when the #$%$ cocaine bing party of the smart phone idiocy is over. You will never be able to do more computing in your hand than in your desktop. Both will improve dramatically but you cant have the hand devices eliminate the need for a real computer. If this happens we have moved into a totalitarian society like the apple 1984 commercial with apple and the wireless providers in the tyrant position a#$%$olutely knowing everything about you and your computer habits and having no genuine freedom under your control. Buy here or miss a once a year entry. This entry here is identical in leverage opportunity to the one at 19+ last year. Shares entry is fine too but i really see the options as extreme opportunity. Intel is as much if not more oversold here than last fall. Intel will be inside all smart phone eventually because it has now been tremendously challenged and will respond with massive vengeance. Watch it happen. .</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1348497673958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348498194908-37</Id><Title>Support just may be the 500 MA</Title><Msg>currently at 22.81 This moving average was also support earlier this month and also in Oct 2011 stockcharts[dotcom]/c-sc/sc?s=INTC&amp;p=D&amp;yr=1&amp;mn=0&amp;dy=0&amp;i=t67132712229&amp;r=1348492895596</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348498194908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:49:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348499926939-38</Id><Topic><Title>I will be taking INTC down today</Title><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348492327032</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:12:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reason I am taking INTC dow is to get you all to sell real cheap.</Msg><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348499926939</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:18:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348500476280-39</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, this Seeking Alpha guy just did a 180 on Intel</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1348493751168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Whoever has the best fabrication wins. That's Intel. Forget all the design mumbo jumbo." If only it was that simple. Fabrication wins if two designs are roughly equal, but the semiconductor industry has proven over and over again that a better design can be a win greater than one fab generation. By trying to win with x86 in SoC Intel is trying to use technology to make a truck competitive with a race car. Dumb. Not that ARM is so great, but agile instruction set design, special functions in Si, greater integration, and custom SoC readiness are the real win factors. I'd rather be a generation behind in fab technology and have the better design. Also, Intel's model of insisting on selling only discrete chips is going to make for tough going in this market. These guys are still a short. The management team needs a refresh.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1348500476280</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:27:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348500901852-40</Id><Title>WOW CNBC PETE the con man wanted you to buy INTC at $29.25 now going under $22</Title><Msg>WOW CNBC PETE the con man wanted you to buy INTC at $29.25 now going under $22</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1348500901852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:35:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348500929057-41</Id><Title>when I post sell everyone listen and are selling now</Title><Msg>I use mind control to get the stockholders to sell</Msg><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348500929057</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:35:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348501681363-42</Id><Title>Check out ALXA</Title><Msg>FDA approval coming soon. Don't miss the ride up</Msg><Username>i_play_fun</Username><Timestamp>1348501681363</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:48:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348502420033-43</Id><Topic><Title>strong sell</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348251479242</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I told you so, after earning under 20</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348502420033</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:00:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348503721343-44</Id><Title>From Last Time</Title><Msg>From the last time Intel warned we know a billion bucks shaved off of revenue is about a buck on the stock price. Since we have now shaved off six or seven bucks on the stock price, it means Intel has to have a miss of five or six billion dollars come earnings to justify the drop in the stock price. Go ahead - those who think Intel is going to have a five or six billion dollar revenue miss raise your hands. Go on, don't be bashful. All of you dimwits on Wall Street should have your hands up unless you are incapable of basic arithmetic...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348503721343</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:22:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348503952244-45</Id><Topic><Title>From Last Time</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348503721343</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:22:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey dimwit. What was the revenue last time when Intel dropped below $20?</Msg><Username>c757172</Username><Timestamp>1348503952244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348504687897-46</Id><Title>Below $20 this earning reports call</Title><Msg>INTC = CSCO in next 3 weeks...Be patient shortie!!!</Msg><Username>bigk95133</Username><Timestamp>1348504687897</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:38:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348504821348-47</Id><Topic><Title>From Last Time</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348503721343</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:22:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Several issues concern me. First, we are way oversold. Second, we are a leader in fabrication by several years and are treated like we are the losers. Third, the competition (ARM manufactures) are not able to get 28nm silicon much less anything better. Fourth, we are approaching a PE that is very conducive to a buyout either friendly or hostile. Fifth, how long can Apple keep buying from Samsung before they screw them over and not supply them. Last, what happens when the BOD tells Paul to start making ARM chips. Whoever buys all the ARM chips that INTC can make will put all the others out of business. I.E. a haswell ARM 22 or 14 nm chip vs a 32 or 28 nm TSMC chip. don't expect much this week as all the funds are finishing their window dressing, but next wek could get very interesting. Thoughts?</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1348504821348</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348505140184-48</Id><Title>WALLIS or LUCY?</Title><Msg>Who has been consistently correct? Who said "buy" at 29? Wallis is a CLOWN LUCY IS THE REAL DEAL! I hope you listened to Lucy?</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348505140184</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:45:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>26</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348505547020-49</Id><Topic><Title>WALLIS or LUCY?</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348505140184</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you bought at 24.00, you'll be fine in six months.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348505547020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506028224-50</Id><Topic><Title>From Last Time</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348503721343</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:22:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This time it's different" You'd better keep writing those letters, Pumperboy! TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348506028224</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506040800-51</Id><Topic><Title>From Last Time</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348503721343</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:22:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speculating that Intel might be bought out is just plain crazy talk. Stupid.</Msg><Username>baltimoreravens_suck_coggg</Username><Timestamp>1348506040800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:00:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348506099486-52</Id><Title>Dual-Core, LTE Compatible Medfied Chips On The Way</Title><Msg>Engadget reports that Intel is readying a dual core version of Medfied that is LTE compatible. Engadet says a quad-core Medfield has been revealed but they could be referring to a dual-core with hyperthreading vs four separate cores.Either way, that's progress.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1348506099486</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:01:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506442309-53</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, this Seeking Alpha guy just did a 180 on Intel</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1348493751168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eassa writes great stuff. It's really unclear about Intel. I too worship the fab technology, but yes they have to DO something with it! My question about the iPhone 5, btw, is battery life. Apple spends WAY too much power on graphics.</Msg><Username>whowants2be</Username><Timestamp>1348506442309</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:07:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506498036-54</Id><Topic><Title>Support just may be the 500 MA</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348498194908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:49:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why 500ma? I'd settle for 200ma.</Msg><Username>whowants2be</Username><Timestamp>1348506498036</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348507738275-55</Id><Title>it is very very weak</Title><Msg>no power to go up</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348507738275</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:28:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348508517766-56</Id><Title>don't renew intc optoins.. loadup amd calls instead</Title><Msg>loadup now amd</Msg><Username>jameswalfosd</Username><Timestamp>1348508517766</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348508921179-57</Id><Title>Recommend that ...</Title><Msg>everyone buy all they can at this price. This price is ridiculous. Even clowns like "too funny" and "lucy nuff". You guys know you really should.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348508921179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:48:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348509175620-58</Id><Title>All the filthiest people in the world want to steal your shares then ride them up on Windows 8 and the winter Tech Rise.</Title><Msg>Shameful.</Msg><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1348509175620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:52:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348509509584-59</Id><Topic><Title>All the filthiest people in the world want to steal your shares then ride them up on Windows 8 and the winter Tech Rise.</Title><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1348509175620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:52:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't be such a DRAMA QUEEN, Wallis.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348509509584</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:58:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>26</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348509899398-60</Id><Topic><Title>Recommend that ...</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348508921179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:48:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>am honestly not a paid shill or pumpwad. Just looking out for the "little" investor.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348509899398</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:04:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348510556164-61</Id><Title>PETE NAJARIAN WAS PUMPING THIS AT $30.00</Title><Msg>NEVER TRUST THAT PUMPER SCAMMER</Msg><Username>fjprz</Username><Timestamp>1348510556164</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348510603369-62</Id><Topic><Title>strong sell</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348251479242</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nothing to hold it up.</Msg><Username>lt1warrior</Username><Timestamp>1348510603369</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:16:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348511019822-63</Id><Topic><Title>Recommend that ...</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348508921179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:48:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stock is being had by the fistful.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348511019822</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348511677626-64</Id><Topic><Title>30 Billion</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1348445538328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:12:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Several issues concern me. First, we are way oversold. Second, we are a leader in fabrication by several years and are treated like we are the losers. Third, the competition (ARM manufactures) are not able to get 28nm silicon much less anything better. Fourth, we are approaching a PE that is very conducive to a buyout either friendly or hostile. Fifth, how long can Apple keep buying from Samsung before they screw them over and not supply them. Last, what happens when the BOD tells Paul to start making ARM chips. Whoever buys all the ARM chips that INTC can make will put all the others out of business. I.E. a haswell ARM 22 or 14 nm chip vs a 32 or 28 nm TSMC chip. don't expect much this week as all the funds are finishing their window dressing, but next week could get very interesting. Thoughts?</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1348511677626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:34:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348511813597-65</Id><Title>Intel announces dividend.</Title><Msg>If things were as bad as some of these crooked analysts want you to believe, Intel would consider lowering the dividend or holding out paying it for a while. That's not the case so far. Intel is obviously confident about delivering decent earnings number in the future. These analysts are creating an atmosphere that is causing investors to be overly cautious and nervous.</Msg><Username>texanjk99</Username><Timestamp>1348511813597</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:36:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348512452552-66</Id><Title>The Great Illusion</Title><Msg>The great illusion is that there is a reason for more than a buck change in the stock price. There isn't. This was done with the usual big Wall Street firm manipulation using money, leverage, and the media. These are the means that the #$%$ use to transfer wealth from those that have earned it to themselves. The only real question is how much cooperation (collusion?) takes place in an effort like this. Judging from what happened today, I'd say a lot...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348512452552</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:47:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348513398033-67</Id><Title>I will not let INTC go over 22.88 betwen now and the close</Title><Msg>I will use my mind control to make sure that doesn't happen. As you all know I am never wrong.</Msg><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348513398033</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348513491503-68</Id><Title>Dont ever listen to Pete.</Title><Msg>He is a worse bet than cramer. I think he meant to buy INTC at $20.</Msg><Username>hedgecutter10</Username><Timestamp>1348513491503</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:04:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348513597878-69</Id><Topic><Title>Intel plans to crush ARM beyond 20 nm</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348495956297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:12:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTEL needs it's stock to stop gettiing crushed! This is a good company but a very bad stock to hold.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1348513597878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348515076031-70</Id><Title>How am I doing keeping INTC down today?</Title><Msg>I told you I would take INTC down today in a up market.I am the only one that has the power to control the stock market. That why all my fro=iends call me the market maker. I will be right again INTC will close under 22.88 today. If it goes over that I will never post again. That how sure I am</Msg><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348515076031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:31:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348515148088-71</Id><Topic><Title>Support just may be the 500 MA</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348498194908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:49:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You just can't pick the moving average you want ;-). The 200 MA is at 25.86 and is clearly Resistance now whereas the 500 MA at 22.81 has just proven it is Support not only on those previous times I mentioned but more importantly today !!</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348515148088</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:32:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348515151379-72</Id><Topic><Title>Intel plans to crush ARM beyond 20 nm</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348495956297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:12:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is biding its time. The semi giant appears quite prepared to wait a couple of generations until sub 20-nm nodes are breached before bringing the battle of low power processing to ARM and its mobile partners.</Msg><Username>tesoro2day</Username><Timestamp>1348515151379</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:32:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348515510297-73</Id><Title>NTWK $6.8 Up 2%.......Hottest NASDAQ stock….Price and Volume up every day......Short-term Target: $10++…...Fundamentals can support $16 per analysts with $21 max target. …..Strong 2013 guidance calls for over 30% revenue growth and $1/share net income due to strong global demand for its Legacy and Cloud software solutions…….Cloud Division is growing exponentially.....Only 6 PE and 1 times sales is 30% of sector average...... In 2010 it went from $8 to $24 in 4 weeks with 50% lower revenues</Title><Msg>Analyst Target: $16 per Upgrade………Take a look at incredible NTWK chart.....3M share float In 2010 NTWK went from $8 to $24 in a few weeks. Today NTWK is a much stronger company with far more revenue sources including new Cloud Divisions. Unlike 2010, NTWK today has the flexibility to deliver reliable software products and services not only from Pakistan but also from excellence centers located in Bangkok, Beijing, the US, and the UK. The float today is 1/10 of what it was then and 2013 revenues are expected to breakaway into the mid $40 million for the first time in company history. During 2010 (and 2007) NTWK's market cap reached over $100 million on 50% lower revenues of what is projected for 2013. During the September 4Q CC NTWK officials stated that revenues are expected to reach $100 Million in 2015 up significantly from the $38 Million reported in 2012. They also expect margins to continue to go up as the high-margin Cloud divisions keep continuing exponentially to revenues. MUST READ ……This Week’s Analysts Comments on Upgrade: We project 13% annual growth to FY14 from FY10 reflecting 80 significant NFS legacy customers in FY14, up from 52, 37, and 28 in FY12, FY11, and FY10, respectively. The new Vroozi Cloud Division contributed $1.3 million in FY12. We expect at least $4 million in FY13 and $6 million to FY14 Our price target is based on the average forward 2013 P/E multiple of 13.2X (up from 12.8X in August 2012). NTWK is trading at 6.4X our FY13 projections. We are forecasting EPS of $0.85 per share. We applied an 11X multiple to our FY13 EPS forecast. We anticipate a richer multiple as earnings momentum builds in FY13. The company guidance calls for $1/share net income in 2013. NTWK is entering FY13 with a $25 million backlog and approximately $100 million in qualified leads. One quarter of the backlog is from four new NFS platform customer implementations that began in 4Q12. In August 2011, NetSol launched its Cloud Vroozi Division, an e-procurement search tool for SAP supplier relationship management (SRM) users. SAP AG is a global vendor of enterprise management systems that has the largest market share (24%) based on a worldwide Gartner survey. Vroozi should provide sales diversification and a higher margin recurring revenue stream. The Vroozi division contributed $1.3 million in FY12 sales and is expected to grow to $4 million in revenues in 2013 NTWK announced its 2nd Cloud Division last week offering an array of products and services to capture a greater % of the cloud applications in North America. The company is implementing this division using their significant software development capabilities and infrastructure. === MORE NTWWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Company projects Doubling/Tripling revenues and net income by 2015 - Significant Institutional investor ownership and growing - Insiders bought over 5% of the Outstanding shares the last 2 years and never sold a single share - Total share count is only 7.5 million shares. The float is only 3 million shares - Trading at forward PE of 5 - Strong balance sheet with $1.5/share cash - Has global agreement with Mercedes Benz - Already 7 countries with NTWK software for leasing and financing Mercedes Benz/Daimler including China, India, Japan, and others…and a few more coming in quarters/years ahead. - No.1 in China and APAC in leasing/financing software products and services. NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Volvo, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc. About NTWK: NetSol Technologies, Inc. ((NASDAQ: NTWK) is a worldwide provider of global IT and enterprise application solutions that include credit and finance portfolio management systems, SAP consulting and services, custom development, systems integration, and technical services for the global Financial, Leasing, Insurance, Energy, and Technology markets. Headquartered in Calabasas, Calif., NetSol's product and services offerings have achieved ISO 9001, ISO 20000, ISO 27001, and SEI (Software Engineering Institute) CMMI (Capability Maturity Model) Maturity Level 5 assessments, a distinction shared by only 178 companies worldwide. The company's clients include Fortune 500 manufacturers, global automakers, financial institutions, utilities, technology providers, and government agencies. NetSol has delivery and support locations in San Francisco, London, Beijing, Bangkok, Lahore, Adelaide, Rio de Janeiro, and Riyadh</Msg><Username>d.malkkey</Username><Timestamp>1348515510297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:38:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348516223491-74</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and th ARM ecosystem</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348289259160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 00:47:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 28nm ramp was actually was smooth from a LP perspective (especially compared to 40nm). I am not sure what your statement is based on. All I can tell you I am watching closely companies like ASML , KLAC, LRCX, NVLS - they are the ones that enable (leading edge) technology and based on their input (CC) your claim has no merit. You see few chipmaker analysts can make a connection to the manufacturing aspect - that applies in Particular to analysts that cover fabless companies - they just "extrapolate" from the past ... two things: 1.) supposedly Apple and QCOM both offered capital to TSMC to obtain "special" treatment. I can see manufacturability/time to market becoming a differentiator among ARM players - and since they compete with each other I don't see why they should share specific knowledge - the IP ownership can become a huge can of worm - if TSMC and QCOM develop mutually a process who has the ownership of that IP. There is a very good reason for the foundries to stay as much as independent from companies like AAPL and QCOM because APPL could sue TSMC in case AAPL believes certain process technology would be AAPL IP. 2.) Samsung is the ONLY ARM player that can develop an ARM SOC (for its on products) just like an IDM which could be an advantage compared to the rest of ARM world that depends on the foundries / foundry process</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348516223491</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348516224815-75</Id><Topic><Title>Tremendous buy chance</Title><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1348497673958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>+0.25 already and decent volume. Chase intel leaps 2014,2015 like a precious metal on any bad day from these levels now. You will not get a bargain as good as this very often. Its less than 1 in 2 years roughly that you get the stock to behave so badly and be trashed by everyone. Pretty soon you will hear as well that Buffet bought close to 22. Of course the stock will be at 24 when you hear that for the first time. Learn to play the game better than the sobs that are manipulating it for you and disclose their true moves months later. Not only intel will feel no stress in earnings eventually as dollar has declined this quarter and their ability to squeeze profits even at reduced revenue is established but also you will see that things will pick up massively after Obama is re-elected and republicans are forced to cooperate with him for tax reform leading to an impressive global rally even before 2013 starts. Miss the chance now and try to chase intel at 25 by December. By all means miss the chance by lstening to those that want the worse for you. I put my money where my mouth says always. Today i entered a massive entry as promised at the 22.55-22.60 levels. I will double it down if we go sub 22 even. I will keep buying until i am fully invested if needed and use the last 10% of account to buy hedging puts if needed. But then the explosion upwards to 30 will take place.</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1348516224815</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348516422529-76</Id><Topic><Title>Tremendous buy chance</Title><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1348497673958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's only gonna crawl back up to 25 by DECEMBER? Yikes.</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1348516422529</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348516520347-77</Id><Topic><Title>Dont ever listen to Pete.</Title><Username>hedgecutter10</Username><Timestamp>1348513491503</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:04:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>outside of RIMM, I don't think there is a tech stock that Pete doesn't like. He and his brother is always recommended the big cap techs, like there is no end to the upside.</Msg><Username>idbtc</Username><Timestamp>1348516520347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:55:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348516911896-78</Id><Title>Intel pumpers are worn out, no mojo left</Title><Msg>Stock down almost 25% in the blink of an eye. STAGGERING.</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1348516911896</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:01:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348516991396-79</Id><Topic><Title>IBM and th ARM ecosystem</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348289259160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 00:47:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 28nm ramp was actually was smooth ------------------ Has the pre-earnings ramp up begun yet, Pumpwad? Are ya wearin' your rally cap, Wallazzzzzzzz! RAMP! RAMP! RAMP! PUMP! PUMP! PUMP! TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348516991396</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>25</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348517074464-80</Id><Topic><Title>How am I doing keeping INTC down today?</Title><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348515076031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:31:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I told you I would take INTC down today in a up market.I am the only one that has the power to control the stock market. That why all my fro=iends call me the market maker. I will be right again INTC will close under 22.88 today. If it goes over that I will never post again. That how sure I am" *** But it wasn't an up market, so you are a dimwit. Or maybe an idiot savant. At least the idiot part...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348517074464</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:04:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348517505104-81</Id><Title>Intel will creep up just prior to earnings</Title><Msg>earnings are 10/16 and then if they are reasonable, expect another climb until div. Overall market weighing on this stock right now not helping.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348517505104</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:11:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348517622659-82</Id><Topic><Title>CAN INTEL SQUEEZE OUT A DIME TODAY?</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346858334174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:18:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Magic 8-Ball RUUUUUUUULES!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348517622659</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:13:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>25</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348517793668-83</Id><Title>up big in after hours</Title><Msg>hedge funds accumulating like there's no tomorrow.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348517793668</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348518011083-84</Id><Topic><Title>strong sell</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348251479242</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>next week will be under 22, after earning under 20, at the end of this year under 15</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348518011083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:20:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348519752602-85</Id><Title>CAT WARNS ON WEAK WORLD ECONOMY - RED HAT DISAPPOINTS</Title><Msg>The INTEL PAIN-TRAIN ROLLS ON TOMORROW!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348519752602</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:49:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>25</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348520000386-86</Id><Topic><Title>How am I doing keeping INTC down today?</Title><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348515076031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:31:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ditto</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1348520000386</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:53:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348522254300-87</Id><Topic><Title>Intel......buy on every dip.....for long term....Dividend next....</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348521179270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:12:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>really? C_W buys 10k quite often. You need bigger goals.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348522254300</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:30:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348522418510-88</Id><Topic><Title>I will not let INTC go over 22.88 betwen now and the close</Title><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348513398033</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:03:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>my gf used to tell me just think about baseball, didn't work too well.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348522418510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:33:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348522458514-89</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Illusion</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348512452552</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:47:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$3 eps wouls shut up wallstreet but not you.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348522458514</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:34:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348522525705-90</Id><Title>WHAT FAST MONEY SAID ABOUT INTEL TONIGHT</Title><Msg>.......It's one of those stocks that you don't want to touch.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348522525705</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:35:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348522747755-91</Id><Topic><Title>Intel......buy on every dip.....for long term....Dividend next....</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348521179270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:12:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i added 10k shares today.</Msg><Username>crazy.wally</Username><Timestamp>1348522747755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:39:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348524417137-92</Id><Topic><Title>CAT WARNS ON WEAK WORLD ECONOMY - RED HAT DISAPPOINTS</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348519752602</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:49:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what is your incentive for trying to torment people holding Intel? Did you get fired from the company and hence have a hatred for anyone or anything associated with it? Hope whatever you're holding goes to zero or even below.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348524417137</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:06:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348524665575-93</Id><Topic><Title>Intel......buy on every dip.....for long term....Dividend next....</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348521179270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:12:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ain't no one gonna get rich holding a semiconductor stock as a long term investment.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348524665575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:11:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348524864243-94</Id><Title>Way to stand up for your shareholders Paul O.</Title><Msg>Gutless leader. Day-after-day, analysts trashing PC as dead. Hey Paul, why dont you go on CNBC once in a while &amp; talk about server growth or something. Wall Street now putting INTC in the same category as RIMM, HP &amp; Dell thanks to the invisible Paul O.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1348524864243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348524893638-95</Id><Topic><Title>CAN INTEL SQUEEZE OUT A DIME TODAY?</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346858334174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:18:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, how about someone squeezing out a loaf on your head? (hopefully with your head tilted up and your mouth open)</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348524893638</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:14:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348525221008-96</Id><Topic><Title>Way to stand up for your shareholders Paul O.</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1348524864243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:14:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>P.O. could go on CNBC and talk about the huge honking $6 miss that is already priced in and that the stock is good for $30. TOOO FUNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1348525221008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:20:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348525464695-97</Id><Title>ONE WAY TO GO</Title><Msg>DOWN TO SOUTH !</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348525464695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:24:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348526421011-98</Id><Topic><Title>Romney releases 2011 Tax Return. Donate THIRTY Percent of his income to charity......Obama only donated 21 percent. No shock, cheap Liberals</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348271068781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 19:44:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>to follow up you might want to check out tyler charitable foundation tax returns.Romneys have been using this Ann Romney trust to stash millions since 2005. 2010 they took a total of 2,983974.00 for charitable donations.1,458807.00 was donated?, to Tyler. Their returns show that amount added to the fund. The total charitable donationsTyler made in 2010 was $647500.00. the balance went in to the fund of non-charitable use, that has a balance of $8,855825.00.How can you take $2,983974.00 for charity donations and only pay $2,172667.00?,$811307.00 goes into Ann's investment fund of non-charitable moneys.That is about as low as you can go.Everyone respects the kind of people who donate to help others.Someone who takes credit for donating money and then doesn't,should be shamed to tears.Some donations like their kids high school and the Equestrian team makes a person wonder how bad those gifts were needed.</Msg><Username>billbaker46</Username><Timestamp>1348526421011</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348527474971-99</Id><Topic><Title>How am I doing keeping INTC down today?</Title><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348515076031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:31:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I warn you friday that I was going to take INTC down today. I am the market controller and what I say goes.</Msg><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348527474971</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:57:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348527893302-100</Id><Topic><Title>Way to stand up for your shareholders Paul O.</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1348524864243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:14:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is pretty pathetic. I no longer have so much animosity toward this company since they have great fabs and retain lots of high paying American jobs, but, M'God, to miss the mobile revolution 100% and then talk about FORTRAN compilers ... that's pretty weak. I might actually buy some of this if it gets to twenty. Now, that's newsworthy.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1348527893302</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:04:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348529491942-101</Id><Topic><Title>How am I doing keeping INTC down today?</Title><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348515076031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:31:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I warn you friday that I was going to take INTC down today. I am the market controller and what I say goes." *** [You must be one of the "cocaine nose jobs of Wall Street" that Fudzilla commented on. I think you are overdoing it a bit, bro. The development of the god complex should have been your warning sign. Hopefully your big Wall Street firm has a detox program. It would be surprising if they didn't have an entire floor of the building dedicated to it. I think it's the floor just above the Sex Party Planning offices. Oh, wait - maybe that's just the hedge funds...] From detoxfromdrugs: "Crack cocaine has become one of the most addictive drugs in today's society. Once smoked, Crack goes straight to the pleasure center of the brain producing a euphoric like state making the user feel superior, in control, psychic, and a king of the hill complex." From Fudzilla: "The cocaine nose jobs of Wall Street have been spluttering into their espressos after Texas Instruments announced that it is set to beat their low end estimates. Wall Street had smuggly declared that since TI was operating in a weaker economy it must be suffering from poor orders. However it seems that TI didn't get the memo."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348529491942</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:31:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348529552593-102</Id><Topic><Title>ONE WAY TO GO</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348525464695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:24:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no more good news in the world, now is the BEAR market for sure, so many stocks are @ 52 weeks low, and new low will keep coming, up 1 cent and down a dollar, wake up!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348529552593</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348529848352-103</Id><Topic><Title>Way to stand up for your shareholders Paul O.</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1348524864243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:14:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seems he was too busy buying back shares at lofty levels. fwiw, only a modest pullback in the indexes anticipated, 2-4 percent to work off overbght levels. If INTC were in the same category entirely as HPQ, DELL, it'd be even lower than it is.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348529848352</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:37:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348530028917-104</Id><Topic><Title>ONE WAY TO GO</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348525464695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:24:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe everyone did not get your sell, sell, sell message. I think you should fire off a couple dozen more threads. Spam up the board real good. Force feed the board your terrific analysis.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1348530028917</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348530134837-105</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will creep up just prior to earnings</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348517505104</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:11:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Earnings a week after the Windows 8 release. I love the way shorts are setting themselves up to get whacked. The one thing we know we won't hear about is the $6 billion revenue miss that is needed to justify the six buck drop in the stock price. Wall Street has gotten totally moronic about the momentum play. Reminds me of the good ole days when the one man shill show used to make predictions and then spend the six weeks after earnings in the fetal position. What goes around, comes around. Here it comes. Shorts get ready to assume the position...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348530134837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348530311934-106</Id><Topic><Title>ONE WAY TO GO</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348525464695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:24:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they did, because the prices keep going down in a up or down market.</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348530311934</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:45:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348531164719-107</Id><Topic><Title>ONE WAY TO GO</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348525464695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:24:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your detailed analysis is "flawless". Your "ONE WAY TO GO" opinion is a perfect opinion.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1348531164719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:59:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348533281848-108</Id><Topic><Title>Way to stand up for your shareholders Paul O.</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1348524864243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:14:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It does suck.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348533281848</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 20:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348533391173-109</Id><Title>INTEL: You are no longer KING</Title><Msg>You've fallen to the back of the line and you have some sweating work to do to get back up front. Can you do it? I don't know.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348533391173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 20:36:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348533604480-110</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Illusion</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348512452552</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:47:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis, at what point do you think INTEL has failed? And at what point do you think that maybe you/me are missing the point? I happen to agree with everything you've posted. But a couple of old men does not make a market. All I hear is raves and excitement from AAPL customers. PC better than tablet? ... No, she says, cause I have a plug in keyboard.... Maybe we are the walking dead, Wallis. Like Paul.O. poster says...maybe this company needs new management. The GAME OVER sign maybe flashing. I am under water in Intel, something I never thought possible.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348533604480</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 20:40:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348535770576-111</Id><Title>Is Intel a company that can fall to 10 or 15 and never recover like Dell?</Title><Msg>I'm not being sarcastic, I'm just wondering. I'd buy right here and hold for the next 30 years if I knew it would at least be worth 20 for that time period. But can it end up like Dell? Is there a floor on this stock ?</Msg><Username>baltimoreravens_suck_coggg</Username><Timestamp>1348535770576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:16:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348536895899-112</Id><Topic><Title>I will not let INTC go over 22.88 betwen now and the close</Title><Username>johnboy2680</Username><Timestamp>1348513398033</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:03:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now you know why we call Raystock, currently hiding behind his Johnboy alias, the sissy boy.</Msg><Username>wowsm1th32</Username><Timestamp>1348536895899</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348537439235-113</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Illusion</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348512452552</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:47:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just hang inthere and collect the dividend .Fab 42 is coming on line next year and thats the game changer.</Msg><Username>kravcleve</Username><Timestamp>1348537439235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:43:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348539391772-114</Id><Title>Obama had time to meet Jay Z and Beyonce and pick up 40 grand of donations but didn't have time to meet with Netanyahu. Calls Killings of our Soldiers a "bump in the road" LOL, you can't make this stuff up!</Title><Msg>Obama is a dirtbag politician, no more NO LESS.</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1348539391772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348539900640-115</Id><Topic><Title>Obama had time to meet Jay Z and Beyonce and pick up 40 grand of donations but didn't have time to meet with Netanyahu. Calls Killings of our Soldiers a "bump in the road" LOL, you can't make this stuff up!</Title><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1348539391772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sure CAN make this stuff up. It has been going on for the last 4 years. To think that Romney forced Ryan to expose his tax cheating. Romney should have the courage or Ryan and file the amendmended taxes and take his medicine. If Romney had 10x the integrity that he currently has, Obama would still look like a saint. Ann Coulter knew this years ago. Flashback Coulter: "If you don't run Chris Christie, Romney will be the nominee and we'll lose."</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1348539900640</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:25:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348543427911-116</Id><Topic><Title>Intel plans to crush ARM beyond 20 nm</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348541567912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:52:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel prides themselves on their engineering process. Yet, several years after declaring Low Power IA as the way of the future for low power computing, they're still making promises. Raises questions.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1348543427911</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:23:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348545020135-117</Id><Topic><Title>Intel plans to crush ARM beyond 20 nm</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348541567912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:52:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel is biding its time." yup... the years are going by... yawn...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1348545020135</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:50:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348545238006-118</Id><Title>There are two kinds of INTC investors</Title><Msg>Thems that listened to marco, shorted at $28 and are now rich, and, thems that didn't listen to marco, but, should have. If you are a should have, there's still time. INTC headed to $15. Trust me on this.</Msg><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1348545238006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>