<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347509020022-1</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts will cover or get crushed as Earnings approach</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347490183202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 18:49:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Short interest increased by 24mil shares to a total of 176mil shares. That level is: 1. the highest short interest in the last year, AND 2. this high number was totaled BEFORE the last dozen or so downgrades and target reductions. 8/31/2012 176,103,236 37,391,822 4.709673 From NASDAQ site.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347509020022</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:03:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347509357326-2</Id><Title>@IDF: you can see INTC is NOT doing well: @least this Q: 18$ coming</Title><Msg>soooon................</Msg><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1347509357326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:09:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347509400784-3</Id><Title>iPhone 5 Has 32nm A6 Chip</Title><Msg>Wow, golly, gee whiz that's amazing. A 32nm chip in the new iPhone. Hey, wait a second!!! 32nm isn't state-of-the-art. Except maybe compared to the A5X 45nm over-heating fatness. Oh, that's right. This is ARM. This is the best they can do. Never mind...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347509400784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347509593381-4</Id><Title>ngmike18</Title><Msg>Your message history identifies you as just another bottom-feeding one man shill show cockroach...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347509593381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:13:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347510090697-5</Id><Title>Intel 14 nm Broadwell chip works</Title><Msg>[Broadwell - or as it will become known: ARM Slayer...] From: Fudzilla Intel has decided not to show off a really tricky step in its tick-tock strategy, the migration from Haswell to 14nm Broadwell. However, sources close to Intel have confirmed that the Broadwell chip has been taped out and that it works. It was actually done a few months ago and it was Intel’s decision not to show it at the IDF keynote, but from what we know chip is able to run Windows and could be a good glimpse into the company's future future. Most of the competition still has to get to 22nm and Intel is getting ready for the 2nd generation 22nm archutecture, better known as Broadwell. In the current schedule Haswell comes in 2013, from what we know from our sources it is expected in Q2 2013 and Broadwell should follow a year after, 2014. At this time Intel doesn’t seem to be facing any major issues in shrinking the Haswell architecture from 22nm to 14nm Broadwell. We are almost certain that the chip might be behind some NDA doors and that Intel will show more to its key customers who need to know. [Who really needs to know? Apple, that's who. They are using 32nm in the new iPhone. D'oh...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347510090697</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:21:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347511340923-6</Id><Topic><Title>Never seen people hate each other in America as much as now</Title><Username>tiglet3l</Username><Timestamp>1347497791493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:56:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To me it's clear that Republiscum like you, who hate gays, woman, minorities and muslims, are creating an atmosphere of hate. Now why don't you and tiglet31 get together and cornhole eachother.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1347511340923</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347511385488-7</Id><Title>So Intel stock still is dead after 12 years. At least Romney is funny. Fuxed news poll shows him losing by 5%.</Title><Msg>Fuxed up news poll shows Rombo losing now by 5%. Intel has got to shrink the chip one more freaking time before it can ram jam its chips into phones and thus destroy its chip competitors.</Msg><Username>gopmeltdown2012</Username><Timestamp>1347511385488</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:43:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347511933114-8</Id><Topic><Title>So Intel stock still is dead after 12 years. At least Romney is funny. Fuxed news poll shows him losing by 5%.</Title><Username>gopmeltdown2012</Username><Timestamp>1347511385488</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:43:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The more Slick Willard talks, the worse it will get for him. This is precisely why doesn't like talking to the news media. It will be pretty entertaining when he has no choice but to answer questions during the presidential debates, LOL! Does anyone know when the first debate will be?</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1347511933114</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:52:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347513004033-9</Id><Title>Obama dispatches war ships to Libya...</Title><Msg>Uh oh!</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1347513004033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 01:10:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347525564623-10</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone 5 Has 32nm A6 Chip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347509400784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:10:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, wait a second!!! 32nm isn't state-of-the-art. Except maybe compared to the A5X 45nm over-heating fatness. Oh, that's right. This is ARM. This is the best they can do. Never mind... ----- Intel's state-of-the-art LP process is also 32nm...</Msg><Username>jezjezwhite</Username><Timestamp>1347525564623</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 04:39:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347528845438-11</Id><Title>Chaos in the Middle East...</Title><Msg>Thanks to a crazy right winger posting a slanderous video on YouTube. The markets are going down.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1347528845438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 05:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347535840914-12</Id><Title>$26,cpu use less power and better performance</Title><Msg>Intel has released early details of its Haswell computer chips, due for release in the middle of next year. One version of the processors will run at 10 watts, about half as much as its current Ivy Bridge design. It said the improvement would mean devices could become thinner, faster and offer extended battery life. In addition it said the chips were designed to better support "perceptual" tasks such as voice recognition, facial analysis and depth tracking.</Msg><Username>cpureview2013</Username><Timestamp>1347535840914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 07:30:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347537758073-13</Id><Title>INTEL'S FUTURE TALK</Title><Msg>Why does INTEL always talk about what's coming down the road and when it comes out it is no longer a big deal? They need to come out with immediate surprises in order to get recognition. Investors don't have patience anymore. They just don't get it! This is a good solid company being poorly managed as far as the stock price goes. They definitely seem to be consistent in the wrong way.</Msg><Username>hweich</Username><Timestamp>1347537758073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:02:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347540161992-14</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL'S FUTURE TALK</Title><Username>hweich</Username><Timestamp>1347537758073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gotta agree. All this gee whiz stuff and the stock just keeps sagging. Two-bit novelties from the Apple novelty shop create shareholder value, while 14nm 10nm that is real value just doesn't seem to help bottom line and pps. What's wrong with this picture, you ask? I dunnoh...somehow dumber seems to win.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347540161992</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:42:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347540429159-15</Id><Title>Wall Street Prices in Miss (Again and Again and Again and Again)</Title><Msg>We know from last year's revenue warning that a miss of the level Intel has declared is worth about a buck off the stock price. So, now we have priced the miss in seven times and I guess today we start work on eight. Here's what the people at Fudzilla had to say: "The cocaine nose jobs of Wall Street have been spluttering into their espressos after Texas Instruments announced that it is set to beat their low end estimates". God bless those wonderful people on Wall Street (scumbags actually) but they are really better at greed than they are at math. Not to mention the question of why Wall Street is continuously trying to destroy one of America's best companies. We need some answers from the "The cocaine nose jobs of Wall Street"...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347540429159</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:47:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347540461416-16</Id><Title>Downgraded? Jeez</Title><Msg>Im averaged in for mid 22s but this sucks! How much will we head down today?</Msg><Username>ibrear</Username><Timestamp>1347540461416</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:47:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347540830550-17</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street Prices in Miss (Again and Again and Again and Again)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347540429159</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis, you have no credibility around here. You were pumping INTC at $29+, predicting $30. Now $20 is more likely. You're wasting electrons with your silly posts.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1347540830550</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:53:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347541387793-18</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone 5 Has 32nm A6 Chip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347509400784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:10:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when's Intel gonna get into the 20th centurly with LTE?</Msg><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1347541387793</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:03:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347541415452-19</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL'S FUTURE TALK</Title><Username>hweich</Username><Timestamp>1347537758073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's wrong with this picture is that Intel doesn't do anything but discrete x86 chips, mostly to run Windows, and that's not where the growth is. And while the pumpers tout servers, server volume probably isn't enough to fill even one fab. For the time being, no PCs = no Intel. Intel needs a new management team. The team running the fabs is fine, but the top leadership is lost. Intel reminds me of Kodak.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1347541415452</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:03:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347541504554-20</Id><Title>What Kind of People</Title><Msg>You have to wonder what kind of people make a living on destroying things. People who get out of bed and attempt to destroy the efforts of other people, who attempt to destroy value created by other people and people who attempt to destroy even the stability of the society in which they live. And if not successful, they get up again the next day and try it again. Well, when it comes to Intel here are some of those who meet that definition: 1.) Clearly the lucies and other shills on this board. Well, there actually may only be a few: the one man shill show and the fanbois from ARM. 2.) Wall Street's largest firms and analysts who have been in Intel attack mode for years. 3.) Hedge funds who are clearly in need of more regulation and monitoring. Please allow me to express my contempt for all of those above. You are morally-corrupt parasites upon America and our society. You are destroying the markets by driving out the small investors with your manipulation of supply and demand. And I hope I'm not alone when I say that Intel investors and shareholders are not just going to roll over in the face of your miserable, misguided and short-sighted efforts...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347541504554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:05:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347541788842-21</Id><Title>Paul O. refuses to stand up for Intel shareholders</Title><Msg>No-show at Intel's main product event &amp; he allows Intel to get showed-up by Apple no less. Poor leader, almost as bad as Craig Bryant &amp; thats saying a lot.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1347541788842</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:09:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347541894794-22</Id><Topic><Title>What Kind of People</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347541504554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:05:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Waldo, new highs for the indexes as INTC drops to new yearly lows in spite of his never ending pumping.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1347541894794</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347541917962-23</Id><Title>Coming Up</Title><Msg>Smartphone announcements Maybe QE3 (65 percent of economists think it will happen) Windows 8 A very slight chance that the #$%$ on Wall Street will recognize Intel's huge market advantages as highlighted clearly at IDF this week. Did I mention the #$%$ on Wall Street? Oh, yeah - I did...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347541917962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:11:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347542002062-24</Id><Topic><Title>What Kind of People</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347541504554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:05:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another DOWNGRADE! INTC trading at 23.02! SOOOOOO, WHO'S YOUR DADDY, PUMPWAD! TOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347542002062</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>26</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347542145091-25</Id><Topic><Title>Coming Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347541917962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:11:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now that's hilarious. Yahoo thinks the word that starts with mo and ends with ron is too rude for message boards significantly inhabited by those who would sell their sisters into the sex trade if they made an extra fifty cents...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347542145091</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:15:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347542186270-26</Id><Topic><Title>Paul O. refuses to stand up for Intel shareholders</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1347541788842</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:09:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much do you think we go down today? I've got shares in the low 22s average ( not including dividends)... Should I grab some weekly puts to hedge? Weekly 23 seems cheap at .11...</Msg><Username>ibrear</Username><Timestamp>1347542186270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:16:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347542193992-27</Id><Topic><Title>Coming Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347541917962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:11:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My goodness you've been reduced to nothing but a crier and constant moaner who pumps Intel at any and all prices. Intel will be fine long-term, but your constant need to comment on every tick of the price is just flat insane. You and Lucy are both complete wierdos.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347542193992</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347542626427-28</Id><Topic><Title>The PC Isn't Dying: Don't Sell Into The Sensationalism</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347282877310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:14:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Wallis, you're fired. Your incessant pumping of this stock, which is now down 20% from its high - where you recommended buying - is a pox on this forum. Ultrabook was a flop, and now everyone long the on the stock like you recommended is paying for it. Go away" --------------- "firstofmany" Your above post is the best of the year! Thanks!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347542626427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347543094729-29</Id><Topic><Title>NTWK $5.3 UP 33c....BREAKING OUT!! NEW TARGET $16...GUIDES FOR 40% 2013 REVENUE GROWTH &amp; $1/SHARE NET INCOME. NEW CLOUD DIVISION ANNOUNCEMENT IS HUGE!!..September 6, 2012. NTWK created a new division, NetSolCloudVM, that will offer infrastructure-as-a-service (IaaS), initially targeting the North American market. Set to launch in September as a division of NetSol North America, NetSolCloudVM will provide clients with IT infrastructure on a monthly tiered subscription basis</Title><Username>nick.jr40</Username><Timestamp>1347292114601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:48:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>up again today?</Msg><Username>joeyggrecco</Username><Timestamp>1347543094729</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:31:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347543356843-30</Id><Topic><Title>What Kind of People</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347541504554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:05:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Walrus, do you have ANY IDEA how many companies Intel destroyed?</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347543356843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:35:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347544007861-31</Id><Topic><Title>GDOT upgraded from Neutral to Overweight, Sell INTC &amp; Buy GDOT</Title><Username>delphioracle2009</Username><Timestamp>1346849547288</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:52:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Piper Jaffray has upgraded GDOT from Neutral to Overweight and the price target is $20/share ... Now Citi has downgraded INTC ... Is it worth hanging on to INTC ... isn't it better to sell INTC and buy GDOT? GDOT is presenting at Goldman Sachs Financial Technology Conference at the Goldman Sachs Conference Center in New York, NY</Msg><Username>delphioracle2009</Username><Timestamp>1347544007861</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:46:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347544106526-32</Id><Title>Don't let Wallisweaver scam you</Title><Msg>If he cared about Intel, he wouldn't freak out about short-term price fluctuations. He cares about one thing and one thing only: his finances..........that and piling on more debt to future generations with QE.</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1347544106526</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:48:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347544465087-33</Id><Topic><Title>What Kind of People</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347541504554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:05:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis, the people on this board mostly likely have no effect on the stock price whatsoever. They only affect your psyche. As for the investment banks, I generally agree with you. I have unflattering nicknames for all of them. On the other hand, Intel's management has not communicated a compelling vision other than doing mostly what they've been doing, and that has just excited no one. This is not a case of a visionary Intel being discounted by the dumb financial people. This is a case of in-bred management being overly conservative and refusing to operate outside of their comfort zone. They remind me of Kodak.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1347544465087</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347545490304-34</Id><Topic><Title>Don't let Wallisweaver scam you</Title><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1347544106526</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:48:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your advice is very good but applies to EVERY anonymous user on this board .... including me and .... you. You have agenda too. Your scam (position) is just different that Wallisweaver. "Pay no attention to that man behind the curtain." EVERYONE should do their own due diligence and make their own best investment decisions.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347545490304</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:11:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347545721115-35</Id><Topic><Title>Obama dispatches war ships to Libya...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1347513004033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 01:10:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet they are quaking in thier boots, especially after obamas apology.</Msg><Username>akrinn</Username><Timestamp>1347545721115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347545939700-36</Id><Topic><Title>What's Wrong With This Picture?</Title><Username>jceandthegirls</Username><Timestamp>1347402877728</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:34:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At what point will this insanity end? The analysts continue to beat INTC into the ground while their is a shortage of ARMH chips at 28nm. QCOM needs chips despirately for their snapdragon. They said they would open their check book and write big checks to insure adequate supply of chips. Their PE is 19 and INTC with state of the art 22nm is a PE of 10. With all the bashing, how long before they make a buy out offer? I know as a share holder, they would probably get my shares if the offer was over 31.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1347545939700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:18:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347545994379-37</Id><Title>There's something wrong with INTEL</Title><Msg>The pps of this stock is absurdly low. The invisibility of the CEO is also absurd. Where is the vision? Where is the blitzkrieg on the iphone?</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347545994379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:19:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347546240767-38</Id><Topic><Title>Never seen people hate each other in America as much as now</Title><Username>tiglet3l</Username><Timestamp>1347497791493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:56:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do you come off saying half the country hates gays, woman, minorities, #$%$ sexuals? I don't hate anyone except those who try to speak for me or harm my family. I do hate war, our debt, unemployment, and divisive inflammatory rhetoric. I love my wife, sisters, daughter, and mother. Do you love anything? Or just hate half the country?</Msg><Username>akrinn</Username><Timestamp>1347546240767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347547103828-39</Id><Title>You think TSM is a better play ?</Title><Msg>What you think ?</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1347547103828</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:38:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347547496800-40</Id><Title>Intel's Bohr sees path to 10-nm chips</Title><Msg>SAN FRANCISCO – Intel Corp. has found a way to create a 10-nm process technology using immersion lithography. In addition, the processor giant is on track to start making chips in a 14-nm process technology before the end of next year, an Intel fellow said in a talk here. The 10-nm process would debut in 2015 or later. It would require quadruple patterning for some mask layers but “it’s still economical,” said Mark Bohr, director of Intel’s technology and manufacturing group, speaking to EE Times after a talk at the Intel Developer Forum here. Bohr did not reveal details of either Intel’s 14- or 10-nm process plans. His comments focused only on technical feasibility. The company has long worked to develop extreme ultraviolet (EUV) lithography and recently agreed to invest $4.1 billion in tool maker ASML to drive it forward. “EUV is very important to us, and that’s why we invested in ASML, but we have multiple paths that we pursue such as immersion with multiple patterning,” Bohr said. Intel expects to use at least double patterning in some layers of some chips at 14 nm. If immersion is used at 10 nm, more layers will require double patterning, and some will even require quadruple patterning, he said. At 14 nm, Bohr said, "the increased wafer costs [associated with double patterning] is still being offset by improved density, so our cost per transistor continues to go down with each generation on a very steady trend." That trend would continue, he suggested, even if immersion is used at 10 nm. As of today, “EUV is later than I would like, and I can’t count on it for sure,” he said. “We are probably the last company continuing to stay on a pace of having a new process technology every two years or so,” Bohr said in his talk.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347547496800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:44:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347548961274-41</Id><Title>First Xeon Phi Supercomputer to Launch on January 7th, 2013, Tesla K20 Inside too</Title><Msg>First Xeon Phi Supercomputer to Launch on January 7th, 2013, Tesla K20 Inside too During the technical session on designing the future of supercomputing, presenters from TACC (Texas Advanced Computing Center) went into detail on creating the Stampede supercomputer, world's first supercomputer powered by the Xeon Phi coprocessors. The system targets compute power of almost 10 PFLOPS, with the majority of compute power coming from Xeon Phi. The system originally targeted 10 PFLOPS, but it seems they might miss the mark by a few dozen/hundred TFLOPS. According to information given, the Stampede deploys 2 PFLOPS of compute power through Sandy Bridge-EP based Xeon CPUs and no less than 7 PFLOPS using Xeon Phi "coprocessors". Even though TACC did not disclose how many thousands of Dell servers are being deloyed, we know that the supercomputer has 272TB of DDR3 memory and 14PB of total storage. The Xeon processor is E5-2680 (Sandy Bridge-EP), while TACC is using special versions of pre-production Xeon Phi processors in order to make the launch. When it comes to the actual Xeon Phi card, Intel still hasn't disclosed the performance and features. However, we can reveal that the first Xeon Phi cards will feature 62 cores, 8GB of GDDR5 memory (connected to a 512-bit bus), using PCIe Gen2 (FirePro and Tesla utilize PCIe Gen3). The TDP is set at 300W, Furthermore, Center decided to pack 128 Tesla K20 (GK110-based) for visualization purposes. While this deal represents a major loss to NVIDIA, it is telling that Xeon Phi cards need Tesla in order to visualize data. Will this be the case with all future Xeon Phi supercomputer wins - time will tell, but NV and probably AMD (FirePro is finally available in server variants) could end up riding Intel's co-tail and achieve some revenue (albeit in percentile figures)</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347548961274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:09:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347551158305-42</Id><Title>rare chance to load up so far below 200DMA</Title><Msg>jumping in here. Though INTC needs to get serious (MORE!) about mobile. Desktops and laptops are in permanent decline.</Msg><Username>futuresrnow</Username><Timestamp>1347551158305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:45:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347553068024-43</Id><Topic><Title>What Kind of People</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347541504554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:05:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$23.02 Did you listen to lucy or did you listen to pumpwad???</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1347553068024</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:17:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>36</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347553285488-44</Id><Topic><Title>You think TSM is a better play ?</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1347547103828</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:38:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Short term, maybe, long term, no way.</Msg><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1347553285488</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347555178789-45</Id><Topic><Title>What Kind of People</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347541504554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:05:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps you should add the Intel insiders who are constantly awarding themselves stock options with ZERO strikes then immdiately dumping their shares upon option exercise while using the company cash to support the stock price in a fixed range for years and years and years. Lather, rinse, repeat.</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1347555178789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:52:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347555574673-46</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone 5 Has 32nm A6 Chip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347509400784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:10:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was at a concern last night and the lady sitting next to me had the iPhone3. She kept trying to take pictures and they came out HORRIBLE. I was effortlessly working my Samsung Galaxy 2 and she was getting disturbed with her phone. I told her to get the new iPhone5 and never look back. Apple has a bit of a problem with this new iPhone, but it's subtle. It's on par with the industry's best. That doesn't sound like a problem? It is! Apple is used to setting the bar so high that the industry has a problem catching up in the two years it takes to get to a new generation of iPhone. But, when the bar has been set by someone other than Apple, what does that mean? It means that the iPhone5 will be a hit by this Christmas and by next Christmas a follow up version of the 5 with a few more bells and whistles will come out. That means the iPhone six will come out sometime before 2015. I know someone said that Apple will be using TSMC 20nm next year. I don't see it happening. I see them doing what they normally do which is to run with the same processor for two years . By the time two years is up, Intel will be at 22nm and just getting into 14nm. If TSMC can't deliver on 20nm and they stick with ARM the iPhone6 can very easily be 28nm or another round of 32nm. Going from 32nm to 28nm isn't going to be that big of a jump. If 20nm isn't ready by the iPhone six you will see Apple failing to keep up with the industry. Apple is stuck in a belief that their logo and user experience is greater than the sum of their parts. They are losing ground as of now, and if they choose the wrong side of the processor battle they can end up loosing a lot more ground.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1347555574673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347555599740-47</Id><Topic><Title>Active Stocks INTC</Title><Username>preston.tina32</Username><Timestamp>1347543394338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:36:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well it looks like we are finally going to see some profits from our investment.</Msg><Username>stephenson.diana85</Username><Timestamp>1347555599740</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347555734819-48</Id><Title>Filthy Weaver gets an 8 cent bump on QE3</Title><Msg>Laughable.</Msg><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1347555734819</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347555742445-49</Id><Title>Filthy Weaver gets an 8 cent bump on QE3</Title><Msg>Laughable.</Msg><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1347555742445</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:02:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347555751222-50</Id><Title>Filthy Weaver gets an 8 cent bump on QE3</Title><Msg>Laughable.</Msg><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1347555751222</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:02:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347555840353-51</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone 5 Has 32nm A6 Chip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347509400784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:10:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I had a buddy yesterday that was playing with his Iphone and I asked him about Siri and he said "he hated Siri."</Msg><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1347555840353</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:04:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347557437332-52</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is poor. This is exactly why.</Title><Username>kennethleyva125</Username><Timestamp>1347471588870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wonderful</Msg><Username>johnniewhaley707</Username><Timestamp>1347557437332</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:30:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347558354665-53</Id><Title>QE3 is targeting housing, it will get us out of this mess guys</Title><Msg>Housing is crucial to any recovery.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1347558354665</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:45:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347559259505-54</Id><Topic><Title>Filthy Weaver gets an 8 cent bump on QE3</Title><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1347555734819</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:02:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Make that .02 good thing the markets aren't a tad overbght. lol</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1347559259505</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:00:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347559777261-55</Id><Topic><Title>QE3 is targeting housing, it will get us out of this mess guys</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1347558354665</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:45:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How come the first two didnt help? Why would a third time do it....</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1347559777261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347561730827-56</Id><Title>IDF???</Title><Msg>Anybody else disappointed by IDF. Low power? CEO?</Msg><Username>aliasyhoo99</Username><Timestamp>1347561730827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:42:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347561789372-57</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is poor. This is exactly why.</Title><Username>kennethleyva125</Username><Timestamp>1347471588870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ya i thing.....</Msg><Username>stanleyanthony36</Username><Timestamp>1347561789372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:43:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347563077588-58</Id><Title>IDF- Intel Disappointment Forum</Title><Msg>The stock was trading higher last week than it is now. is "Intel good for $30" or was Wallis just blowin' smoke??? TOOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347563077588</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:04:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347563367115-59</Id><Title>No new stuff for INTC @IDF + losing market share to ARM for mobile: 18$ coming</Title><Msg>Sell the pop and short the pop.... Exactly what is happening for Intel stock =============eom =======================</Msg><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1347563367115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:09:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347563767119-60</Id><Topic><Title>No new stuff for INTC @IDF + losing market share to ARM for mobile: 18$ coming</Title><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1347563367115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:09:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>get back to the burger flipping, paddy.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347563767119</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:16:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347564488009-61</Id><Topic><Title>QE3 is targeting housing, it will get us out of this mess guys</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1347558354665</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:45:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing is getting fixed until Washington gives businesses the optimism to hire and grow. Obama is anti-business, is gonna win and we are doomed beyond belief. Stock up on Army food and the like.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1347564488009</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347564655247-62</Id><Topic><Title>QE3 is targeting housing, it will get us out of this mess guys</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1347558354665</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:45:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And learn Spanish if you don't know it already.</Msg><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1347564655247</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347564753806-63</Id><Title>The Health of INTC</Title><Msg>Not Bashing, Not Pumping. Have owned Intel for sometime and took some profits last spring with the idea that I would get back in at a lower price, and try to catch the next upswing. Right now I am a looking at doing that but concerned about the direction things are going with INTC. After having dropped from 29 last spring into the 22's earlier today, it is a wonder where the bottom is on this downswing. Believe me I know it is not possilbe to time the market, but with all of the positives I keep hearing about INTC and where things are headed lately, there is legitimate concern. What seems to be the driving force into the drop off since May? I had thought that we might level at something about 26 or so, but this drop has come as a surprise! Any sentiments?</Msg><Username>koroundiii</Username><Timestamp>1347564753806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347564974958-64</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone 5 Has 32nm A6 Chip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347509400784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:10:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you know that they are replacing Google Maps with Waze? Talk about a miss. I read an interesting article about how stupid it was to not have a micro USB on it and got to yet another new proprietary interface.</Msg><Username>intel_4ever</Username><Timestamp>1347564974958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:36:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347565136586-65</Id><Title>Dirty game. Analsyts will pump Intel once Windows 8 comes out</Title><Msg>Wash and rinse.</Msg><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1347565136586</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:38:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347565354961-66</Id><Topic><Title>The Health of INTC</Title><Username>koroundiii</Username><Timestamp>1347564753806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dividend yield at 22.5 cents is 3.9%. Coverage is 30% and Intel has a target of a higher target. Intel sold off from $29 based on expectations of weak PC sales, Then .... Intel dropped when HPQ warned. Intel dropped when Dell warned. Intel dropped again when Intel warned. Intel dropped farther as all the analysts lowered their targets and possibly rating, each day. Seems like an overreaction to me but I suspect that there will be value investor interest at these yields.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347565354961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:42:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347565388427-67</Id><Topic><Title>Dirty game. Analsyts will pump Intel once Windows 8 comes out</Title><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1347565136586</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:38:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Analshits? Nice spelling.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347565388427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347565466284-68</Id><Topic><Title>The Health of INTC</Title><Username>koroundiii</Username><Timestamp>1347564753806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry ... ....Intel has a target of 40% dividend which is 10% higher percentage of profits than current.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347565466284</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:44:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347565690140-69</Id><Title>Doom and Gloom Crowd Ignores QE3 Warnings - Gets Thumped Up</Title><Msg>Great to see the doom and gloom crowd getting their heads handed to them. Of course, they still are sitting on Intel thinking there is more to come. They always think there is more to come. My only regret about today is that the Intel shorts didn't get thumped up worse. Scumbags...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347565690140</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347566089153-70</Id><Title>Note to Intel Investors</Title><Msg>Longs: Show a little backbone. Stop selling on every market fluctuation. You're just playing into the hands of the scumbags. You helped to turn a dollar adjustment into a seven dollar adjustment. Wall Street keeps playing you like a fiddle. Cut it out. Shorts: Good job of hanging in and getting thumped today. Hang in there. We've got smartphone announcements coming up. A lot better if you cover at higher prices. Don't let your common sense overwhelm your greed...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347566089153</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:54:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347566232927-71</Id><Title>Only one poster on this entire board who's posts are worth reading</Title><Msg>Alexander.dumbaXXXX Only ONE !</Msg><Username>lucyboycots_chickfillet</Username><Timestamp>1347566232927</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347566563541-72</Id><Topic><Title>No new stuff for INTC @IDF + losing market share to ARM for mobile: 18$ coming</Title><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1347563367115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:09:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean no new stuff you can understand. The idea that Intel is losing market share to ARM in mobility is the kind of conclusion a shill with no knowledge of communications might post up. Dunno why the financial terrorists hire shills with such limited skills. Maybe their relatives...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347566563541</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:02:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347566723361-73</Id><Title>PC sales predicted to rebound big-time in 2013 (Intel postition well in 2013)</Title><Msg>IDC predicted the global PC market will grow by 1% this year and 6.5% next year thanks to a rebound in PC spending, especially in China. Thailand's PC market is expected to grow by 8% this year and 11% next year.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1347566723361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347566803511-74</Id><Topic><Title>Note to Intel Investors</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347566089153</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:54:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm long INTC, but am looking for a pullback to the 22.50 range to add more.</Msg><Username>csecomm</Username><Timestamp>1347566803511</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347566944517-75</Id><Title>QE3 will prevent crash, Dividends is where it's at</Title><Msg>Seriously....</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1347566944517</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:09:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347568483745-76</Id><Topic><Title>QE3 will prevent crash, Dividends is where it's at</Title><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1347566944517</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:09:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What the Fed did today was announce that its policy was not based on a forecast of things getting worse—but on a desire for things to improve faster. In short, it announced that the central bank intended to change the pace of recovery.</Msg><Username>stormy_nomore</Username><Timestamp>1347568483745</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347569310641-77</Id><Topic><Title>Bernake just said:"WE CAN'T SOLVE IT" !!!..QE3: Won't create Jobs</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1347568559115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:35:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Viewers, put the original poster on ignore. He's a scorched and scorned daytrader. He sold Intel at 20 and has been beating on his cage to get out ever since. Here are just a fraction of his aliases - he's one pitiful, sorry excuse for a man. flashcrashcoming vinny_baguhdonutz wallisweiner nj_maverick tooofunnny lucy_nuff lucifer_nuff DOWFACE GOLFCOMANION49 MED_INVESTOR wilder_blitch win_dexit coinmaker wallisschmallis stupidstewie gordon.greco kored65 obamaloveswallst kohighbloodpressure Jimbohomegamedyou CrazyWally Foxnewzzz(with three z's) maximumwalrus winteldead think5pm pedroexressway walldexit trixeee777777 jessejames_blitch wallywiththereddress_nuff No less than 100 others</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1347569310641</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:48:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347569854590-78</Id><Title>How low do we go????</Title><Msg>Missing earnings kills stock in this market. Just heard a trader say he thought we had another leg down. Where do you thin that would be and it a safe investment at that point?</Msg><Username>hedgecutter10</Username><Timestamp>1347569854590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:57:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347570465175-79</Id><Title>Bernanke: Fed OKd new stimulus because unemployment is 'grave concern'</Title><Msg>Federal Reserve Chairman Ben S. Bernanke said "grave concern" about the nation's high unemployment rate led the central bank to launch another round of stimulus, and that the aggressive open-ended program underscores a commitment to the economic recovery. "We've seen not enough jobs growth to bring down the unemployment rate, and what we need to see is more progress," Bernanke said. The Fed would continue with its stimulus "until we do," he said. "We're just trying to get the economy moving in the right direction, so we don't stagnate at high levels of unemployment," Bernanke said Thursday at his quarterly news conference, which followed the Fed's announcement of its new stimulus effort. The Fed said Thursday it would buy $40 billion a month in mortgage-backed securities until the outlook for the labor market improves substantially. Bernanke said the program "should increase downward pressure on interest rates," particularly mortgage rates, which would encourage more home sales and refinancing. He would not give a specific level of unemployment the Fed was aiming for, but said the goal was not to continue the purchases until the labor market was at a full employment rate of about 6%. The unemployment rate in August was 8.1%. "There's not a specific number we have in mind, but what we've seen in the last six months isn't it," he said. "We're looking for something that involves unemployment coming down in a sustained way." Responding to criticism that the Fed's actions were hurting savers by keeping interest rates low, Bernanke said there are benefits to the rates. Low interest rates help the value of homes and business, he said. And though the rates do harm people with certificates of deposit and other savings, Bernanke said, "It's difficult to save for retirement and other goals without the income from a job." From: LA Times</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347570465175</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:07:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347570622834-80</Id><Topic><Title>Bernake just said:"WE CAN'T SOLVE IT" !!!..QE3: Won't create Jobs</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1347568559115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:35:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What he said was "QE3 can't solve the economy's problems ON ITS OWN." Nice distortion, shill boy...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347570622834</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:10:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347570788319-81</Id><Title>silly fed games</Title><Msg>i bet markets crash. Just games by FEd trying to give false confidence to markets. Same game last 4 years. All a.hoax. Games never end. Thats my view. Last time back fired .Rates too low too long look out below.Cant mess with natural order of things.</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1347570788319</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:13:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347573222091-82</Id><Topic><Title>silly fed games</Title><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1347570788319</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:13:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Viewers, put the original poster on ignore. He's a scorched and scorned daytrader. He sold Intel at 20 and has been beating on his cage to get out ever since. Here are just a fraction of his aliases - he's one pitiful, sorry excuse for a man. kopach flashcrashcoming vinny_baguhdonutz wallisweiner nj_maverick tooofunnny lucy_nuff lucifer_nuff dowface golfcompanion49 med_investor wilder_blitch win_dexit coinmaker wallisschmallis stupidstewie gordon.greco kored65 obamaloveswallst kohighbloodpressure Jimbohomegamedyou CrazyWally Foxnewzzz(with three z's) maximumwalrus winteldead think5pm pedroexressway walldexit trixeee777777 jessejames_blitch wallywiththereddress_nuff No less than 100 others</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1347573222091</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347574889912-83</Id><Topic><Title>QE3 will prevent crash, Dividends is where it's at</Title><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1347566944517</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:09:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder why they are in a hurry for things to improve? Could it be a political move to save the pres. butt? Naw, they would not do that.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1347574889912</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:21:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347574943534-84</Id><Title>Intel has successfully gained 80% of the CPU market</Title><Msg>Intel has successfully gained 80% of the CPU market share since 2006 others have 20% market share . CPU leader : Intel</Msg><Username>techviewmarket</Username><Timestamp>1347574943534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347577837544-85</Id><Title>Was Otelini too embarrassed to speak?</Title><Msg>Did he feel stupid with is 23 dollar stock price speaking about laptops when Apple was right down the road pushing 700 a share and everything non-Intel?</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1347577837544</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:10:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347578141047-86</Id><Topic><Title>silly fed games</Title><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1347570788319</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:13:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"i bet markets crash. Just games by FEd trying to give false confidence to markets. Same game last 4 years. All a.hoax. Games never end. Thats my view. Last time back fired .Rates too low too long look out below.Cant mess with natural order of things." *** You always bet markets crash...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347578141047</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:15:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347578145153-87</Id><Topic><Title>Intel has successfully gained 80% of the CPU market</Title><Username>techviewmarket</Username><Timestamp>1347574943534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:22:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right, this is the kiss of death. They cannot grow and they still have competition. Same position they've been in for 20 years.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347578145153</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:15:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347578670366-88</Id><Topic><Title>Intel has successfully gained 80% of the CPU market</Title><Username>techviewmarket</Username><Timestamp>1347574943534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:22:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Viewers, put the original poster on ignore. He's a scorched and scorned daytrader. He sold Intel at 20 and has been beating on his cage to get out ever since. Here are just a fraction of his aliases - he's one pitiful, sorry excuse for a man. vinny_baguhdonutz kopach flashcrashcoming wallisweiner nj_maverick tooofunnny lucy_nuff lucifer_nuff dowface golfcompanion49 med_investor wilder_blitch win_dexit coinmaker wallisschmallis stupidstewie gordon.greco kored65 obamaloveswallst kohighbloodpressure Jimbohomegamedyou CrazyWally Foxnewzzz(with three z's) maximumwalrus winteldead think5pm pedroexressway walldexit trixeee777777 jessejames_blitch wallywiththereddress_nuff</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1347578670366</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:24:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347580118988-89</Id><Title>It is devastating for the shorts. Bernenke is re-electing Obama.</Title><Msg>He will lose the job he loves has head of the fed if Romney wins. SO--he has taken sides and is running the stock market up huge before the November election. Romney is screwed.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1347580118988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:48:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347582273196-90</Id><Topic><Title>Intel has successfully gained 80% of the CPU market</Title><Username>techviewmarket</Username><Timestamp>1347574943534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:22:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's pretty funny. I am none of those. I am my own person. I have more experience working for and at Intel than probably most people on this board. But, keep screeching. You seem to enjoy it.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347582273196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:24:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347583149856-91</Id><Topic><Title>Intel has successfully gained 80% of the CPU market</Title><Username>techviewmarket</Username><Timestamp>1347574943534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:22:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've searched your posts. You're the same tool, and you just never got over getting fired by Intel. Funny stuff. Keep chirping.</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1347583149856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:39:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347583740124-92</Id><Title>Intel Seeks to Eliminate Computer Passwords With Wave of Hand...BIG RALLY TOMORROW</Title><Msg>INTEL innovating sensor product will be a blast for margins and the value of its stocks. Everyone hates typing passwords...i hope more news about this sensor start leaking I have 90K to buy tomorrow at the opening. Intel is underpriced here.</Msg><Username>herculesmovers</Username><Timestamp>1347583740124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347584199102-93</Id><Title>Poor little Vinnie (LUCY), couldn't cut it at Intel</Title><Msg>Re: AMD Longs, Please Read By vinnie_baggadonitz . 4 years 9 months ago . Permalink Go to topic Douchebag, I am not an AMD long. No surprise you didn't respond to the numerous occasions on which INTC has been CONVICTED of stealing technology. Hard to argue with the truth. As for your other baseless contention, I was offered 50K options to stay at INTC and I went elsewhere. Do you want me to name the group, the facility and the hiring manager?</Msg><Username>vinnie_bagofhotwind</Username><Timestamp>1347584199102</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:56:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347584288375-94</Id><Topic><Title>Intel has successfully gained 80% of the CPU market</Title><Username>techviewmarket</Username><Timestamp>1347574943534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:22:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was offered 25K options to stay at Intel and turned it down. Best move I ever made. My guess is the other guy was in a similar situation. INTC is great unless you work there. Buncha fat white guys with hazelnut groves who screw the NCG's into working 7 days a week. Their roadmap is as stale as it was in 98 when I left. Fight with Microsoft, slow roll the MHz, kill off partners and vendors. Big time yawn. They will never ever ever recover.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347584288375</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:58:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347584395328-95</Id><Title>Vinnie must just be SICK watching AMD DIE</Title><Msg>Re: Well Well Well By vinnie_baggadonitz . 8 years 7 months ago . Permalink Go to topic There's one difference .. Dell can switch to AMD processors if things get desperate; Intel can't.</Msg><Username>vinnie_bagofhotwind</Username><Timestamp>1347584395328</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:59:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347584590952-96</Id><Topic><Title>Intel has successfully gained 80% of the CPU market</Title><Username>techviewmarket</Username><Timestamp>1347574943534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:22:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel was rated THE number 1 best place to work. You are a loser that never got a raise, got fired, and talks big on the Internet because you can't do it/prove anything in real life. Keep programming the only language you know: Cobol. LOL! F'n loser.</Msg><Username>vinnie_bagofhotwind</Username><Timestamp>1347584590952</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:03:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347585477968-97</Id><Title>AMD was over 40 when little Vinnie pumped it 8 years ago. LOL!</Title><Msg>Nice job, buddy! How are all those AMD options you have these days?</Msg><Username>vinnie_bagofhotwind</Username><Timestamp>1347585477968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:17:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347585965149-98</Id><Title>I see I have a troll following me.</Title><Msg>Check my posts if you want the truth, or listen to the Supreme Dilrod of Earth if you want cheesy sound bytes. I worked for AMD and Intel. Wouldn't touch either one. AMD served its purpose, which was to save the consumer from the INTC borg. Now, both are just dying shadows.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347585965149</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:26:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347587289517-99</Id><Topic><Title>It is devastating for the shorts. Bernenke is re-electing Obama.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1347580118988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:48:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you're blaming the head guy keeping our financial system from falling apart completely. Who has been more transparent than any one before him. While nothing is done by the rest of the our system. For doing what his job description says he's supposed to do?</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1347587289517</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:48:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347587717985-100</Id><Topic><Title>How low do we go????</Title><Username>hedgecutter10</Username><Timestamp>1347569854590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:57:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We don't have anything new from Intel for another ~9 months or so. Lots and lots of new performance info on new ARM chips between now and then. Info from Nvidia, QCOM, AAPL, TI, and many others will damage Intel, I suspect. Quad core A15s at 2.5GHZ will be plenty for laptops, and throw in Nvidia's graphics and we got lots of problems. They ain't going out of business, but we could go significantly lower, depending on perceptions of the tablet and PC markets.</Msg><Username>awaytocar123</Username><Timestamp>1347587717985</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:55:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347588979827-101</Id><Topic><Title>How low do we go????</Title><Username>hedgecutter10</Username><Timestamp>1347569854590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:57:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, stock market is more based on perceptions than reality. Otherwise 10 times earnings would be considered too low for a company like this. I'm OK with waiting with the nice near 4% dividend though. Banks pay out a crappy interest rate and I think we will see at least 25$ again at some point in the future. So better than the bank as far as I'm concerned.</Msg><Username>x1x4x1x13</Username><Timestamp>1347588979827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347589897490-102</Id><Topic><Title>How low do we go????</Title><Username>hedgecutter10</Username><Timestamp>1347569854590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:57:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tech does well inf from November through April. I wouldn't place a big bet on Intel dropping "signifacantly" from here. Come on man.</Msg><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1347589897490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:31:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347590813449-103</Id><Title>What happened to INTC @ $30?</Title><Msg>Hey Wallis you shameless pumper when will we see $30? I was at IDF this week. Intel has NO mobile story. 22nm mobile chips are expected in late 2013? That's not what you said Wallis. Ride it down and double up? :-o</Msg><Username>semiconductorguy</Username><Timestamp>1347590813449</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:46:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347591725450-104</Id><Title>Would this market rally have legs?</Title><Msg>1. Fiscal cliff looming 2. Unemployment still a big issue 3. Corporate earnings would be hit and miss 4. NASDAQ at the highest point since 2000 (that's 12 years) Thoughts?</Msg><Username>pricelinelong</Username><Timestamp>1347591725450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:02:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347592670869-105</Id><Topic><Title>What happened to INTC @ $30?</Title><Username>semiconductorguy</Username><Timestamp>1347590813449</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You proved you weren't at IDF this week by saying that Intel has no Mobile story. lol. Hey, can I get your number? Motorola wants to call you and pick your brain...</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1347592670869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:17:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>