<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351830576077-1</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for a bad jobs number tomorrow</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351825442336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We've wasted 4 years on zero-growth socialist economic policies. Most MBA students have a better understanding of how to grow an economy than our Chicago political machine-product Mr. Obama. Thats not the "change" Americans signed up for 4 years ago.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351830576077</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 00:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351831866501-2</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL IS TOO CHEAP TO PASS UP ! =BACKING UP THE TRUCK !</Title><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1351821920436</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 22:05:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>22.40 range few days then breakthrough 23 to touch 28 December rally</Msg><Username>raygeo2003</Username><Timestamp>1351831866501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 00:51:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351832805770-3</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for a bad jobs number tomorrow</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351825442336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, it is not the change that Americans signed up for 4 years ago. There was no "Tea Party". The Republican Party was not completely crazy yet. We were not expecting the Republican and Tea Party wackos to become obstructionist at any cost to America just to make Obama a one term President. "Zero-growth socialistic policies" have two sources: 1. Republican race to the right and refusal to negotiate moderate solutions to problems. 2. Democratic response to the left in order to replace the moderate Republican part of the moderate middle. Thank you Mitch McConnell. Thank you Eric Cantor Thank you John Boehner. Thank you Republican Party for the slow recovery. Yes BUSH and the dregs he left when he disappeared. Now what whe have to chose from is MORE OF THE SAME (D) and WHO THE HELL KNOWS (R).</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351832805770</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 01:06:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351833586114-4</Id><Title>It is over for Romney and that idiuot Ryan. ROADKILL</Title><Msg>I am pretty sure the rah rah cheerleading on fuxed up news for #$%$, is going to soon switch from saying it is a sure thing that Romney wins to the new--Impeach Obummer for the cover up nonsense soon. I could have sworn I saw the idiots on the 5--fuxed up news show, say it was over and Ryan was going to win BIG just last Friday. Now? They look angry and about ready to cry. Of course Fuxed up news will keep pumping a win for Romney to keep viewership up. Because the minute the rightwing nimnuts who watch Fuxed News know Rombo has lost, they will turn off the TV and Fuxed ratings will drop. SO let me get this? Florida? Obummer will win. You rightwing trash will be shocked because you heard no chance of that happening. Why would you watching only Fuxed up news. HAAA HAAA Virginia--No chance for Rombo there. Obummer wins Virginia and then you BARFFFF and cry like little rightwing teabagging losers. Ohio? GONE to OB too. Colorado to OB also. If you teabagging dddimwits are still watching by then, you could be crying like little woooseys by then. How could you be so so stupid as to think Romney was going to win? Have you shheeeet for brains? HAAA HAAA</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1351833586114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 01:19:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351833629808-5</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg Backs Obama, Citing Fallout From Storm</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351828220385</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:50:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Our climate is changing,” he wrote. “And while the increase in extreme weather we have experienced in New York City and around the world may or may not be the result of it, the risk that it may be — given the devastation it is wreaking — should be enough to compel all elected leaders to take immediate action.” Too late - too little the saltwater will have longterm effects on every piece of steel embedded in concrete... The clean coal dummies coalition is still brainwashing you but now the time is coming to pay for it - you (US) fools have the technology to move to renewable energy but capitalism will strangle it....irreverisble The Kyoto Protocol is a protocol to the United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change put a dumbpuck like Ryan second in command</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1351833629808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 01:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351856208925-6</Id><Title>FEMA,get generators to gas stations so they can pump gas in NJ!!!!</Title><Msg>80% of gas stations offline. My brother lives there and can't get gas.</Msg><Username>tfmvance</Username><Timestamp>1351856208925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 07:36:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351856581033-7</Id><Topic><Title>It is over for Romney and that idiuot Ryan. ROADKILL</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1351833586114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 01:19:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm a welfare rat &amp; couldn't be happier with an Obama win. Ya see, I don't work &amp; I get 10 (count 'em 10) different handout programs because I'm in the PC class. I am not a troll. I'm real, and happy that BO will keep spending ad nauseum. I could care less about a balanced budget or paying a damn dime toward trhe national debt. At 71, I have more annuities coming in than I can keep track of. I file a 1040 only to get credits back. Life is very sweet now &amp; BO will keep it so. And Hector, if you are a taxpayer, I want to thank you for paying taxes so I can stay on this gravy train. Also, I want to thank the Fed for helping BO win. And finally I want to thank God for Sandy. The timing was perfect.</Msg><Username>sdansker2002</Username><Timestamp>1351856581033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 07:43:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351857858518-8</Id><Topic><Title>FEMA,get generators to gas stations so they can pump gas in NJ!!!!</Title><Username>tfmvance</Username><Timestamp>1351856208925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 07:36:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try Legumes. They always work for me.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351857858518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 08:04:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351858510806-9</Id><Topic><Title>FEMA,get generators to gas stations so they can pump gas in NJ!!!!</Title><Username>tfmvance</Username><Timestamp>1351856208925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 07:36:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh no, we don't want guvmint getting into the affairs of private business...the market will take care of it!</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1351858510806</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 08:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351859340507-10</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg Backs Obama, Citing Fallout From Storm</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351828220385</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:50:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, your little food stamp/QE Machine Barck Obama zoomed over to Jersey for a few photo opporunities and then quickly flew to Wisconsin, Las Vegas, Florida and Ohio to campaign. I heard he tipped the local media to make sure the pictures of his brief time in Jersey were splattered all over the air ways. Meanwhile, the families of dead soldiers still wants answers. What a disgrace.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351859340507</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 08:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351859517851-11</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg Backs Obama, Citing Fallout From Storm</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351828220385</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:50:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jobs report looks good. Unemployment number 7.9%.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351859517851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 08:31:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351859954638-12</Id><Title>Remember - Real Quality of Life Determined By State's Rights - Romney</Title><Msg>Federal control is the alternative</Msg><Username>mackgreene33</Username><Timestamp>1351859954638</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 08:39:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351860547939-13</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg Backs Obama, Citing Fallout From Storm</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351828220385</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:50:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup, yup, yup! The little food stamp machine/QE machine flew over NJ with one of the Republican INSULT MACHINES. The Republican Insult machine kept bowing to the little food stamp/ QE machine. A giant (literally) sucking sound coming from NJ. If there were any "tips" they were offered by Christie. The ROMNEYwad STONEWALL machine still cranking out the lies and disinformation on ALL FRONTS. 34 days since the last time the ROMNEYwad opened his PIEHOLE to answer any question from ANY reporter. EVEN the FAIR AND BALANCED FOX cannot get ROMNEYwad to talk. Teach ROMNEY sign language since he has lost his voice along with his MORALITY.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351860547939</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 08:49:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351861071816-14</Id><Topic><Title>Let's hope for a really great jobs number tomorrow.</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351826204707</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:16:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great jobs number. Guess what you can do with it, att4?</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351861071816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 08:57:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351862618186-15</Id><Title>Sadly, liberal puke wouldn't trade that natural disaster for the world</Title><Msg>They fall to their knees every night, thankful for the natural disaster that came along and made people forget that Obama has no record to run on.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351862618186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:23:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351862748127-16</Id><Title>Real employment 11% and Obama just can't trick them into thinking they are employed</Title><Msg>LANDSLIDE Real unemployment rate is 11% By cspanosmwc.18 minutes ago.Permalink . 3% of Americans have given up and are just gonna live off food stamps and the nanny state, they officially have given up till Obama is gone.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351862748127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:25:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351862854885-17</Id><Title>Shorters... Get Ready???</Title><Msg>Get ready to take a nap, while you wait for the downside... we are on an up swing till maybe Monday... another day of gains today? $23+ by some point today... sure do hope so!</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351862854885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:27:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351862926657-18</Id><Topic><Title>Real employment 11% and Obama just can't trick them into thinking they are employed</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351862748127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:25:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pray it is in five days.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1351862926657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351863041020-19</Id><Topic><Title>Sadly, liberal puke wouldn't trade that natural disaster for the world</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351862618186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:23:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HAPPILY, the CONSERVATIVE PUKE don't need a natural disaster to fall to their knees every night. They fall to their knees every time they are in the airport restroom. They fall to their knees every time they walk through the hotel lobby. They fall to their knees every time they see a good looking guy. The CONSERVATIVE PUKE forget that they can take large for the "Obama record". Their obstructionist policies forced him to the left to pick up the votes. The CONSERVATIVE PUKE are just UPSET that they have to vote for a liberal, shape-shifting Republican.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351863041020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351863300931-20</Id><Topic><Title>Real employment 11% and Obama just can't trick them into thinking they are employed</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351862748127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:25:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TIE popular vote. ELECTORAL LANDSLIDE for OBAMA. REAL unemployment rate is probably higher than 11% Thank you Mitch McConnell Thank you Eric Cantor Thank you John Boehner. Thank you Mitch Romney .... shake your booty and take a new position.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351863300931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:35:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351863379700-21</Id><Topic><Title>Shorters... Get Ready???</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351862854885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:27:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey, btw, what are you plannig to do with the puts you purchased? sell or better hold ?</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351863379700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:36:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351865148350-22</Id><Topic><Title>If it stays up today, ya think we should prepare for a HUGE drop tommorow...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351779966087</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:26:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next hurdle is the dropping 50 MA at 22.99, if it can break above that that would be a bullish sign.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351865148350</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:05:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351865502278-23</Id><Topic><Title>Shorters... Get Ready???</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351862854885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:27:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I never bought puts... I bought 1000 at 22.70 and 1000 at 22.50 on Margin.. NO options.. I don't mess with options as I'm not knowledgeable enough on them...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351865502278</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351865519999-24</Id><Title>Bloomberg's 'Warm Hug' Boosts Obama</Title><Msg>President Obama and New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg talk with participants at the New York City Science and Engineering Fair on March 29, 2011, at the American Museum of Natural History in New York. New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg’s surprise endorsement of President Obama is the latest warm hug that the president has gotten from some famously independent Republican types in the closing days of the 2012 campaign, and it couldn’t have arrived at a more opportune time for him. Now comes Bloomberg -- close on the heels of former GOP Secretary of State Colin Powell and New Jersey’s notoriously gruff GOP Gov. Chris Christie -- with a bouquet for the Democratic president and a cuff for the Republican standard-bearer. “In the past,” said Bloomberg, Romney has “taken sensible positions on immigration, illegal guns, abortion rights, and health care. But he has reversed course on all of them.” Indeed, Bloomberg cited Obama’s work during the hurricane, and the “major steps” taken by the president to combat global warming and its effect on violent weather, in his unexpected endorsement. It came just days after the mayor declared that he would probably not declare a preference. It’s difficult to say how much Bloomberg’s blessing will matter. The Northeast, of course, is already reliably Democratic. And in many rural areas of the country, the mayor is best known -- and not too fondly, either -- as the nation’s leading elected proponent of gun control, and as the man who’s waged war on Big Gulp sodas, cigarettes, and fattening food. But for third-party types, environmentalists, Jewish voters in Florida, and undecided independents in the suburbs of states like New Hampshire and Pennsylvania, the Bloomberg brand may shore up Obama’s support. At the very least, the mayor’s endorsement sent a message to business, and to business-minded voters worried about the economy, that at least this one pragmatic billionaire has confidence in Obama and harbors doubts about Romney’s character and capability. The endorsement said something, as well, about Bloomberg. It is the second big step on the national stage the mayor has taken in the waning days of the 2012 election. Last month, he announced that his new super PAC, the “Independence USA PAC,” will spend up to $15 million on behalf of candidates who have the guts to support gun control, gay rights, education reform, and other tough issues. “I like to take on those things that other people either are unwilling to take on for political reasons, or unwilling to take on because it’s just too complex, or they just don’t care,” Bloomberg told James Bennet, editor in chief of The Atlantic magazine, in an interview in its latest issue. “Leadership is about doing what you think is right, and then building a constituency behind it,” Bloomberg said. “It is not doing a poll and following from the back.”</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351865519999</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:11:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351865719786-25</Id><Title>Short-Sellers of Europe Set to Be Unmasked</Title><Msg>[About GD time. Now let's do the same thing to the scumbags in the US...] Short-sellers around the globe will be unmasked starting on Friday as new European rules come into effect. The European Securities and Markets Authority (ESMA), the EU regulator, has issued new rules on the short-selling of securities indicating that anyone with short positions of greater than 0.2 percent in an EU company’s shares must report it to regulators. Positions of more than 0.5 percent will be publicly released, naming both the company and the short-seller. Public disclosure is triggered any time that level is hit with each 0.1 percent increase or decrease after that. Teams of lawyers were working into the night to help banks, hedge funds and other investors comply with the rules with the deadline due at 3:30 p.m. local time in each jurisdiction. And disclosures need to be filed separately to each national regulator which has introduced plenty of headaches, given that in some countries, like Hungary, the paperwork is largely written in the local language. Sources from the finance industry have indicated to CNBC that the disclosure rules will hurt overall market activity in Europe, potentially driving investors to other markets like Hong Kong Others have told CNBC that a version of the rule already in place in Spain and Portugal hasn’t had a major impact. Still, it is a major step towards unmasking the short positions of hedge funds which are typically one of their most closely guarded secrets.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351865719786</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:15:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351865734895-26</Id><Topic><Title>If it stays up today, ya think we should prepare for a HUGE drop tommorow...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351779966087</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:26:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does the 22.5 cent drop happen at market close today (4pm EST)? And if yes, is after hours and Monday pre-market trading still allowed on the stock?</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351865734895</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:15:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351866144396-27</Id><Title>Added 171k jobs, lost 170k.......LOL!</Title><Msg>Musical chairs you can believe in.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351866144396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:22:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351866355008-28</Id><Title>Alexander.dumb.... aka "aholewad"</Title><Msg>Just another liberal slimeball, slithering around under the tables.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351866355008</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:25:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351866374899-29</Id><Topic><Title>Short-Sellers of Europe Set to Be Unmasked</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351865719786</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:15:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm all for it IF it solves naked short selling. but other than making more paper work will it deter any hedge fund from shorting?</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351866374899</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351866487702-30</Id><Title>Fund selling late October</Title><Msg>As per the slide at the end of October, it looks like many funds dumped INTC so they didn't show a massive loser in their reports. But, now that it's November they're buying it back because of the low price, low p/e and high dividend. Could be a good sign that the stock can recover somewhat this quarter.</Msg><Username>nickster135796</Username><Timestamp>1351866487702</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:28:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351866609185-31</Id><Topic><Title>If it stays up today, ya think we should prepare for a HUGE drop tommorow...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351779966087</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:26:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After hours trading happens normally today and Monday. If you buy in the after hours today, it appears that you get the dividend. The price that Intel trades is ALWAYS determined by an agreement between a BUYER-SELLER. Trades today will happen at that point. The "adjustment" in the price happens when the various organizations incorporate the dividend adjustment into their numbers. If Intel closes today at $22.50, and opens on Monday at $22.50, the "tape" will show "green" with Intel up 22 cents. If Intel opens on Monday at $22.00, the "tape" will show "red" by 23 cents. If Intel opens on Monday at $22.23, the "tape" will show "unchanged". You will see some organization take longer to purcolate the "adjustment" into their numbers and they will show unadjusted change. "Extended Hours Trading Another area of confusion about dividend dates is how extended hours trading affects dividend rules. The answer to that question is a simple one: extended hours trading (both pre-market trading and after hours trading) does not affect dividend rules. Buy before the ex-date (no matter if in pre-market trading, regular hours trading or after hours trading) you qualify for the dividend; buy on or after the ex-date (whether in pre-market trading, regular hours trading, or after hours trading) you don't qualify for the dividend."</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351866609185</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:30:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351866834579-32</Id><Topic><Title>Short-Sellers of Europe Set to Be Unmasked</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351865719786</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:15:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think shining a bright light on the #$%$ will be useful. They like to operate in the dark for a reason...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351866834579</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:33:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351866934537-33</Id><Title>It is falling</Title><Msg>Short 15k this baby @ 22.53, it will keep falling, keep falling, keep falling! short short Short, easy money! I told you so!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351866934537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351866983820-34</Id><Title>If I Buy Today Will I Get the Divident?</Title><Msg>Thanks in advance DM</Msg><Username>divident_man</Username><Timestamp>1351866983820</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:36:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351867042524-35</Id><Topic><Title>If I Buy Today Will I Get the Divident?</Title><Username>divident_man</Username><Timestamp>1351866983820</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:36:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that is affirmative</Msg><Username>joespada282</Username><Timestamp>1351867042524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:37:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351867304734-36</Id><Title>Send him home to chicago</Title><Msg>nobody is buying his bull, this time around, he is finished.</Msg><Username>joespada282</Username><Timestamp>1351867304734</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351867883157-37</Id><Topic><Title>It is falling</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351866934537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said the same thing at 21.60, dufus. How are your supposed shorts from that level doing? You kissed your easy money good-bye. And still you run your mouth and get paid by the post. You ego runneth over...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351867883157</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351867883421-38</Id><Topic><Title>If it stays up today, ya think we should prepare for a HUGE drop tommorow...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351779966087</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:26:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alex, i agree with your comments regarding the price adjustment of INTC after divy. A naive question is if the pps drops by the same amount of the divy given, what's the point of buying divy stocks as after that the pps suffers? on a different note: what tools are good to evaluate if a specific option (call or put) is too expensive? I understand it's suplly/demand but anomaly happens and one need to evaluate it the asked price is not too high. second when selecting an option strike price, do you use a tool or a method to decide which strik price has the best risk/reward? Thankx</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351867883421</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351867938950-39</Id><Topic><Title>It is falling</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351866934537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will be totally lobster red very soon, because I'm shorting this junk!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351867938950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351867973126-40</Id><Topic><Title>Send him home to chicago</Title><Username>joespada282</Username><Timestamp>1351867304734</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:41:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, you think the American people are buying the bull about Romney being a moderate?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351867973126</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:52:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351868108599-41</Id><Topic><Title>It is falling</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351866934537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It will be totally lobster red very soon, because I'm shorting this junk!" [Your face is lobster red because you swam into the upsurge, shill boy. Cut back on the drugs today and maybe your god complex will recede too...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351868108599</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:55:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351868213323-42</Id><Topic><Title>It is falling</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351866934537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>15k shorted at 22.53 and then bought back at 22.38 seems like a $2250 profit... I'd call that good money... If I had the money to do that I would too....</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351868213323</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351868594135-43</Id><Title>Teabag Goes Silent</Title><Msg>He must be looking for more drugs...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351868594135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351868807644-44</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg's 'Warm Hug' Boosts Obama</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351865519999</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New Yorkers think Bloomberg's an idiot for going foward with the NYC Marathon........the picture of the two MASSIVE generators being used for the Marathon has made many LIVID. Good old Liberal New York. No clue.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351868807644</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:06:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351868927574-45</Id><Topic><Title>Teabag Goes Silent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351868594135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:03:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sad to see you use the Lord's name in vein earlier this morning. You are someone we all strive to be just like, single, never married, in your 60's, and saying G.D. 50 times a day to vent your anger. What a guy....</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351868927574</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:08:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351869194843-46</Id><Topic><Title>Send him home to chicago</Title><Username>joespada282</Username><Timestamp>1351867304734</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:41:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If OBOMNEY wins, we all lose...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351869194843</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:13:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351869539509-47</Id><Topic><Title>Send him home to chicago</Title><Username>joespada282</Username><Timestamp>1351867304734</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:41:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he is a better choice because he has business experience with a proven record,obama knows nothing about business, 4yrs of his bull is proof enough, now lets give the other guy a shot at it</Msg><Username>joespada282</Username><Timestamp>1351869539509</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:18:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351869580764-48</Id><Topic><Title>Teabag Goes Silent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351868594135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:03:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sad to see you use the Lord's name in vein earlier this morning -------------------- vein/vain Lord's name may be taken in VAIN...but you take drugs in VEIN U R SOOOOOOO STOOOOOOPID. U must have gone to school with herbal dooooooosh!</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1351869580764</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:19:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351869674123-49</Id><Topic><Title>Teabag Goes Silent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351868594135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:03:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intravenous gets it to your system quicker.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351869674123</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:21:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351869747312-50</Id><Title>Otellini endorses Romney...duh Obama is pro-foodstamp and anti-business</Title><Msg>Intel's Otellini endorses Mitt Romney Portland Business Journal Date: Friday, November 2, 2012, 8:08am PDT Intel CEO Paul Otellini has endorsed Mitt Romney for president. Intel CEO Paul Otellini has received a lot of face time with Pres. Barack Obama, hosting the President at a huge Intel expansion announcement in Oregon and serving on his jobs council. Still, when it came time to endorse a candidate for president, Otellini pledged his support for Mitt Romney. As the Wall Street Journal reports, Otellini's endorsement is one of several executive endorsements Romney is touting in the final days of the campaign. Pres. Obama received his own high-profile endorsement on Thursday, when New York City Mayor Mike Bloomberg announced his support for the President.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351869747312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:22:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351869805475-51</Id><Title>SPIN THIS HEADLINE, WALLIZZZZZZZZZZ.......</Title><Msg>"Intel's Otellini Endorses Mitt Romney"</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1351869805475</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:23:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351869962976-52</Id><Topic><Title>If it stays up today, ya think we should prepare for a HUGE drop tommorow...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351779966087</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:26:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stocks should be bought/sold based on whether or not the stock matches your investment goals and whether it is priced at a value you feel comfortable with. There are many types of investors/traders with a wide range of risk tolerances. The investment goals/tolerances for pension plans, hedge funds, trader are all different. There is a discontinuity in value that happens at the ex-dividend instant. 22.5 cents will change hands at that instant. The option market maker has to price the options after that instant normally. Just before that ex-dividend instant, the option market maker must protect himself from those who would exercise early and take the dividend and those who would not. IMO, the option market maker has a very regular and rigid pricing mechanism that uses something like the Black and Scholes Option Pricing Model. Option pricing deviates from these pricing models because of expected news (uncertainty). Any pricing deviation from that model is driven by expectation of news and the option market maker passing the uncertainty through. There are a number of methods of finding overprice/underpriced options but I don't have any leads for you there. Sorry. Intel is a low beta stock that generally tracks the market. I feel comfortable selling put options at the money on Intel. I sell them and keep enough premium on them to prevent them being put. I usually sell them 60 to 90 days out in the $1 per share range and then either cover or roll them. I usually close them out when they drop below 25 cents. I roll them out for credit (usually in 30 cents per month credit) when the premium drops below 10 cents. I have option level 3 qualification so I can sell the naked puts and they reserve cash for the option face value and margin cash to cover the exercise if it were to happen. I usually trade 10 to 20 contracts per transaction so I am a small fish. I sell to open after Intel has dropped and becomes oversold. When most people buy shares, I sell put options which allows me to take a position and the premium time value is my friend.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351869962976</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:26:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351870048971-53</Id><Title>Worthless 2014 release of ARM/AMD server chips</Title><Msg>Gotta hand it to Rory over at AMD. He knows how to buy time and keep that massive payday coming into his personal account. _______________________________ But once you ponder on the time factor, AMD sure seems to be on slippery turf. In fact, some of the very companies, such as Dell and Hewlett Packard, that it may be targeting to market the new chips are themselves trying to build similar products or servers based on the ARM technology platform. And if you are only bothered about Intel, that doesn’t help much either. Although Intel probably will never make ARM-based chips mainly because they don’t want to shell out royalties to the latter, the company has ramped up its efforts to launch low-power chips by itself, and one such product may be out as early as the end of this year. If that happens, the only distinguishing edge AMD might have over cash-rich Intel will be its own ‘Freedom Fabric’ – a technology that integrates a lot of servers as part of a cluster and a legacy of the SeaMicro acquisition. But then, the question remains – will the edge still remain till 2014? I think not. This is one stock I would be watching from a distance, just to see if it does rise from the ashes. Till now, the chances are really slim.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351870048971</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351870178797-54</Id><Title>Obama got his photo OP, then raced off to campaign/brag about getting Bin Laden</Title><Msg>. Isolated NYC borough says help is slow after Sandy By EILEEN AJ CONNELLY and MEGHAN BARR | Associated Press – 3 hrs ago.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351870178797</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:29:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351870363472-55</Id><Topic><Title>Alexander.dumb.... aka "aholewad"</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351866355008</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no way. You're wrong on this one. it's lucy, he and ww aren't as different as they seem</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351870363472</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351870443037-56</Id><Topic><Title>Real employment 11% and Obama just can't trick them into thinking they are employed</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351862748127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:25:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Under Obama's jobs bill, unemployment would drop and debt would rise. That's a #$%$ plan and you know it.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351870443037</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:34:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351870546102-57</Id><Topic><Title>Real employment 11% and Obama just can't trick them into thinking they are employed</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351862748127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:25:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>or moved to disability.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351870546102</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:35:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351870826375-58</Id><Title>Obama said he would cut deficit in half......instead he's doubled it</Title><Msg>I mean WTF? LOL (shaking head at you Liberals) -Unemployment rate HIGHER now than when he took office...He said he was going to cut it to 5.2%. - Average family paying 2000 more per year for gas. - Promised to be post-partisan (LOL).........he's the most partisan president in history. - Said he was going to work across the isle......yet hasn't met on the economy, budget or jobs with either the republican leader of the house or senate since JULY. Think about that.....WOW. Of course, he had to campaign instead of step across the aisle. Just unreal. UN-FREAKING-REAL. Those supporting him are miserable, jealous, backboneless humans that want their misery spread to others. It's that simple.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351870826375</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:40:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351870918478-59</Id><Topic><Title>Alexander.dumb.... aka "aholewad"</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351866355008</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no way. You're wrong on this one. I am a. dumbazz AND attHole, lucy and ww!! i use my attHole alias for ROMNEY POLITICAL HUMOR!! i use my lucy alias for NEGATIVE SPAM!!! i use my ww alias for INTEL HELIUM!!! slithering slithering slithering slithering slithering slithering slithering TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYY!!!</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351870918478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:41:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351871072785-60</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for a bad jobs number tomorrow</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351825442336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing plant. Pipeline. Healthcare bill, unread and shoved down the right's throat, and you want to negotiate. 2 way street.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351871072785</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351871092147-61</Id><Topic><Title>Obama said he would cut deficit in half......instead he's doubled it</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351870826375</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:40:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(shaking head at you Liberals) (moving attHole's head lower) AHHHHHHHHHHHHHh!! Oooooooooooooooooooo!!! That's it!!! Right there!!! The miserable people are the ones who have not had your head in their lap but have had to listen to your polydrivel.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351871092147</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:44:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351871152896-62</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for a bad jobs number tomorrow</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351825442336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you blame Paul? Europe is a glaring example but those in line and getting those handouts do not care. They are bought votes.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351871152896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:45:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351871329792-63</Id><Topic><Title>Viewers, put this scorched trader Lucy on IGNORE</Title><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1339260364000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-06-09 12:46:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>aholewad tooofunnny lucy_nuff lucifer_nuff vinnie_baggadonitz wilder_blitch win_dexit coinmaker wallisschmallis stupidstewie gordon.greco kored65 obamaloveswallst kohighbloodpressure Jimbohomegamedyou CrazyWally Foxnewzzz(with three z's) maximumwalrus winteldead think5pm pedroexressway wallisweiner walldexit trixeee777777 jessejames_blitch wallywiththereddress_nuff No less than 100 others Rating :</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1351871329792</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:48:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351871536494-64</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for a bad jobs number tomorrow</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351825442336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hahaha, sounds like the drop from 8.1 to 7.8 :) or lets talk about inflation if you want to talk about bogus numbers.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351871536494</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:52:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351871572506-65</Id><Topic><Title>Let's hope for a really great jobs number tomorrow.</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351826204707</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:16:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah and if you can't change it, blame GWB.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351871572506</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351871577630-66</Id><Title>People LIVID about Bloomberg going forward with NYC Marathon</Title><Msg>Marathon goers are even livid that it's going on. 2 MASSIVE Generators from where.............LONG ISLAND brought in for the Marathon while the cleanup on Long Island hasn't even started and they have NO power there. It does NOT get any dumber than the Liberal mindset. It just does not.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351871577630</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351871592462-67</Id><Topic><Title>Viewers, put this scorched trader Lucy on IGNORE</Title><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1339260364000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-06-09 12:46:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Viewers -------------- You must think this is the Bijou or a wide-screen television format! TOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1351871592462</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:53:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351871659805-68</Id><Topic><Title>Reverend that inducted Obama back in 2009 now throwing out racial slurs</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351820957151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:49:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suppose you backed Slick.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351871659805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:54:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351871673759-69</Id><Topic><Title>If it stays up today, ya think we should prepare for a HUGE drop tommorow...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351779966087</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:26:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for your informative view!</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351871673759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:54:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351871852489-70</Id><Title>Just dawned on me that none of you losers deserved 1 second of my time</Title><Msg>Thanks for the dividend and goodbye.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351871852489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:57:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351871902109-71</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for a bad jobs number tomorrow</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351825442336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Creating a new Boeing Plant in SC should have been allowed. Pipeline will be built. It will carry the Canadian oil to Houston so it can be exported. It will not change gasoline prices. Health care bill, unread (it was all read but not by one person) and shoved down the right's throat (yes). The Republican choice was to simply say NO and obstruct OR to participate and influence. They chose to obstruct which forced legislation hard left where there were enough votes. The Republican obstruct was an influence whether they want to admit it or not.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351871902109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351871925267-72</Id><Topic><Title>Alexander.dumb.... aka "aholewad"</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351866355008</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>keep C_W away from aholewad. aholewad has spent too much time with ww in the hot tub I fear.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351871925267</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:58:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351872042624-73</Id><Topic><Title>Just dawned on me that none of you losers deserved 1 second of my time</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351871852489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:57:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats 1 second more than anyone wanted and more than enough time for you to share all you know (and have time left over).</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351872042624</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:00:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351872168328-74</Id><Title>sip starbucks best coffee,be fresh and.......</Title><Msg>sip starbucks fresh coffee,be fresh and be prepared to vote for president OBAMA on tuesday,nov 6,2012. buy intc as it is very good dividend stock for a long term.</Msg><Username>goreric51</Username><Timestamp>1351872168328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351872315385-75</Id><Title>Paul O proves he is an idiot.</Title><Msg>Never back a loser. Romney loses and you get fired now Paul you moron.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1351872315385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:05:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351872417013-76</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for a bad jobs number tomorrow</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351825442336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So the bottomline is.....both sides are the same with regards to working with one another. Dims lead uneducated and simpler people around by the nose telling them how good they will take care of them by basically higher taxes or extortion via unions. Repubs like less taxes, more business, and expect people to become self sufficient. How is Obama going to help his followers if they have to do what they are NOT capable of doing? That would mean becoming self sufficient. Handouts baby, that's all they know. It is like they say, at some point you will run out of other people's money to spend. Of course in the USA we just print more and run up the debt until we reach the breaking point(see Europe). Obama's jobs bill just continues that line of thinking(more debt). And yes, again I say GWB was awful, and yes I know the wars were expensive. I agree but we are headed down the wrong path.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351872417013</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:06:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351872573138-77</Id><Topic><Title>Paul O proves he is an idiot.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1351872315385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Friday, November 02, 2012 The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Friday shows the race tied, with President Obama and Mitt Romney each attracting support from 48% of voters nationwide. One percent (1%) prefers some other candidate, and three percent (3%) remain undecided. See daily tracking history.</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1351872573138</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:09:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351872806610-78</Id><Topic><Title>Paul O proves he is an idiot.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1351872315385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney may just win this thing. Beyond me why he is not far ahead.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1351872806610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351872942201-79</Id><Topic><Title>Paul O proves he is an idiot.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1351872315385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ouch--the trend is not good for Rombo Romney. I think Romney loses by 2% Nationally and loses Florida early causing Rushdrugbaugh to take some Oxi and go to a make prostitution house. Ricky suckateli in Chicago will likely be laughed at for years after he cries on CNBC. Grow some nuggetts you wwooosey teabagging loser. Fuxed up news will have to put a suicide watch out for Teabaggers who believed the idiots on FOx who predicted an easy Romney win. LOSSSSSSSERRRRS!</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1351872942201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351873171338-80</Id><Topic><Title>Paul O proves he is an idiot.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1351872315385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul has the right to his own opinion, that being said I see no advantage for CEO to get involved in politics at this point</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351873171338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:19:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351873680967-81</Id><Topic><Title>Real employment 11% and Obama just can't trick them into thinking they are employed</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351862748127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:25:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reducing unemployment is the goal of a jobs bill. Debt control is not. There is wide disagreement about what will work or not. A jobs bill could be produced and will be produced when the Republicans (PARTY OF NO) divorces Grover. NONPARTISAN .... NONPARTISAN .... NONPARTISAN .... NONPARTISAN .... NONPARTISAN .... NONPARTISAN .... Nonpartisan Tax Report Withdrawn After GOP Protest Published: Friday, 2 Nov 2012 | 8:53 AM ET Text Size By: Jonathan Weisman The New York Times The Congressional Research Service has withdrawn an economic report that found no correlation between top tax rates and economic growth, a central tenet of conservative economic theory, after Senate Republicans raised concerns about the paper’s findings and wording. The decision, made in late September against the advice of the agency’s economic team leadership, drew almost no notice at the time. Senator Charles E. Schumer, Democrat of New York, cited the study a week and a half after it was withdrawn in a speech on tax policy at the National Press Club. But it could actually draw new attention to the report, which questions the premise that lowering the top marginal tax rate stimulates economic growth and job creation. “This has hues of a banana republic,” Mr. Schumer said. “They didn’t like a report, and instead of rebutting it, they had them take it down.” Republicans did not say whether they had asked the research service, a nonpartisan arm of the Library of Congress, to take the report out of circulation, but they were clear that they protested its tone and findings. Don Stewart, a spokesman for the Senate Republican leader, Mitch McConnell of Kentucky, said Mr. McConnell and other senators “raised concerns about the methodology and other flaws.” Mr. Stewart added that people outside of Congress had also criticized the study and that officials at the research service “decided, on their own, to pull the study pending further review.” Senate Republican aides said they had protested both the tone of the report and its findings. Aides to Mr. McConnell presented a bill of particulars to the research service that included objections to the use of the term “Bush tax cuts” and the report’s reference to “tax cuts for the rich,” which Republicans contended was politically freighted. They also protested on economic grounds, saying that the author, Thomas L. Hungerford, was looking for a macroeconomic response to tax cuts within the first year of the policy change without sufficiently taking into account the time lag of economic policies. Further, they complained that his analysis had not taken into account other policies affecting growth, such as the Federal Reserve’s decisions on interest rates.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351873680967</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351873742090-82</Id><Title>Medfield vs A6 vs A15 vs S4</Title><Msg>anandtechDOTcom/print/6425 Medfield/A6 beat A15 on Sunspider/Browsermark but lose on Kraken/Octane.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351873742090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:29:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351874000978-83</Id><Title>Acer expects 10 % PC growth in 2013</Title><Msg>Acer Greater China president expects 10% growth in 2013 notebook shipments Ocean Chen, Taipei; Joseph Tsai, DIGITIMES [Thursday 1 November 2012] President of Acer Greater China Scott Lin, commenting on the touchscreen and convertible notebook trends brought on by Windows 8, pointed out that he believes these trends can resurrect the PC industry. He expects notebook shipments to enjoy a more than 10% on-year growth to 230 million units in 2013 with Windows 8-based touchscreen ultrabooks to account for 30-40% of the shipments.</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1351874000978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351874179412-84</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for a bad jobs number tomorrow</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351825442336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INFLATION???? OK. Would you use the current method for your calculations? Would you use the pre-Clinton method for your calculations? Would you use the pre-Reagan method for your calculations? Would you use some other method for your calculations? and why?</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351874179412</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:36:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351874337479-85</Id><Topic><Title>Reverend that inducted Obama back in 2009 now throwing out racial slurs</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351820957151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:49:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You talking about John Travolta ???</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351874337479</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:38:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351874762494-86</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for a bad jobs number tomorrow</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351825442336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tax me to death so someone can sit around all day smoking cigarettes and drinking coke, get cancer, have me pay for their medical bills... then tell me I need to Pay my fair share... yeah that makes sense... ALL politicians are worthless, lying thieves, we need to have a violent revolution in the country to get things back on track... Death of the value of the dollar is coming... both major political parties are accelerating its death... then the revolution will come... off with their heads!</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351874762494</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351874920155-87</Id><Topic><Title>If it stays up today, ya think we should prepare for a HUGE drop tommorow...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351779966087</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:26:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing to hold it up. fundamentals for pcs, tech are BAD. TECH IS A WRECK. long term..low teens IMO</Msg><Username>lt1warrior</Username><Timestamp>1351874920155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:48:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351875614071-88</Id><Topic><Title>It is falling</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351866934537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I keep wondering how low it's going to go, then it goes lower... as I suspected ex-div doesn't mean anything... I should have sold at 22.50 and bought back in lower or sold and shorted, that would have been a mean play... oh well... I lose some, then I lose some more...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351875614071</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 13:00:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351876495958-89</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for a bad jobs number tomorrow</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351825442336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds good to me!!! smoking cigarettes? increase food stamps so they can sell them for smokes. drinking coke? sooooooooooooo dumb!! COLT45's isa betta cancer? you pay for their medical bills whether you like it or not. you pay for prevention (health care) or you pay for their unpaid emergency medical attention (higher medical fees &amp; insurance cost) ..... you can support the method that you pay. you get to chose. I am glad you don't mind sharing the cost of my diabetes, gout, and related complications from me being grossly overweight. OH!!! And thanks for the Viagra. All politicians are worthless ....?? the Citizen's United decision will help that. violent revolution? haven't you noticed ..... Tea Party and Republican "just say no" politics dollar death? world wide part of globalization and rebalancing of currencies ... check RACE TO THE BOTTOM</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351876495958</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 13:14:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351877213016-90</Id><Title>Question</Title><Msg>who is your favorite poster here who do you most dislike here who is the smartest poster here who is the dumbest poster here</Msg><Username>yodeling_pig</Username><Timestamp>1351877213016</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351877399014-91</Id><Topic><Title>Medfield vs A6 vs A15 vs S4</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351873742090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is your take from this, O.P.? Solid progress from Intel or no?</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1351877399014</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 13:29:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351877422129-92</Id><Topic><Title>Question</Title><Username>yodeling_pig</Username><Timestamp>1351877213016</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Favorite: wallisweaver Dislike: anyone with nuff at the end of their name Smartest: alexander.dumbass Dumbest: ME</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351877422129</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 13:30:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351877495921-93</Id><Topic><Title>Acer expects 10 % PC growth in 2013</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1351874000978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:33:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next year looks great for Intel, as Stacy Smith said especially with Intel placing so much emphasis on 14nm production.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1351877495921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 13:31:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351878074239-94</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for a bad jobs number tomorrow</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351825442336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The unemployment number is bogus because it doesn't report reality. The real situation is far, far worse. There are over 23 million citizens unemployed and the real unemployment number is not 7.9% as reported. The true number is about 18% when one counts the long-term unemployed, those that have given up looking and the under-employed that want full time jobs but can only get temporary or part-time jobs with no benefits. More of the same is terrible for the tech industry, Intel included.</Msg><Username>publicservice100</Username><Timestamp>1351878074239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 13:41:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351878739120-95</Id><Topic><Title>Reverend that inducted Obama back in 2009 now throwing out racial slurs</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351820957151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:49:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No I am talking about Monica's boyfriend. That #$%$ should have just swallowed like I am sure old shut up and just sing Barbara did and your boy wouldn't have been impeached.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351878739120</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 13:52:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351878837897-96</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for a bad jobs number tomorrow</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351825442336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it was my job performance being covered up, I'd do it just the same way the pack of deceitful liars are doing it now, if I wanted to stay in office.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351878837897</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 13:53:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351879008878-97</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for a bad jobs number tomorrow</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351825442336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are over 23 million citizens unemployed and the real unemployment number is not 7.9% as reported. _____________ If this is the case, that's 23 million votes for Romney as I'm sure they aren't thrilled to hear that everything is so honky dorry.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1351879008878</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 13:56:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351879590845-98</Id><Topic><Title>Real employment 11% and Obama just can't trick them into thinking they are employed</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351862748127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:25:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Reducing unemployment is the goal of a jobs bill. Debt control is not. There is wide disagreement about what will work or not." ------------------------------------------------------------------ LOL, well sh*t then get more ink and fire up the gov't money printing press, run up that debt and hire all the people who want jobs. Then what do we do about the millions who are happy coasting on the Obama giveaway plan? unemployment, disability, food stamps, cell phones, okay what else do you need from the muslim santa clause. does it snow in kenya? Did you know that Obama so loves the poor, he's created millions more? By: Jonathan Weisman The New York Times Jewish(99% Dims)? member of the press...shocking. Next you'll tell me the Pope is Catholic. Chuckie Schumer.....Biden's plugs buddy? What an ahole Chuckie is btw. Can you find out about Jon Corzine next? Has Edwards endorsed Obama yet?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351879590845</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:06:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351879817648-99</Id><Topic><Title>Medfield vs A6 vs A15 vs S4</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351873742090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course, Medfield is a faster browsing chip than Qualcomm's Krait and lasts longer doing it. It can beat both A6 and A15 in some benchmarks but also loses to them in others so it's in the high performance mix as well as being in the long endurance mix. Intel have produced a competitive phone chip at 32nm contrary to the myth x86 couldn't do it. It's a start of what no doubt will be a continuous flow of better future phone chips to come. Everybody will not suddenly switch to Intel phone chips but more will in time and hey the starting point is 0% so the only way is up ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351879817648</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:10:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351880143479-100</Id><Topic><Title>It is falling</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351866934537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>does the truth hurt Waldo, 22.50 ish was short term resistance from the lofty pre earnings run up that resulted in a drop to 21.20, as opposed to soaring post earnings as you predicted. one would expect a pullback given the run up yesterday.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1351880143479</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:15:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351880667152-101</Id><Topic><Title>Real employment 11% and Obama just can't trick them into thinking they are employed</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351862748127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:25:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"LOL, well sh*t then get more ink and fire up the gov't money printing press, run up that debt and hire all the people who want jobs. Then what do we do about the millions who are happy coasting on the Obama giveaway plan? unemployment, disability, food stamps, cell phones, okay what else do you need from the muslim santa clause. does it snow in kenya?" Well, you can fire up the printing press and run up the debt if that is what you want. Some people don't want to do that. Your comment SUPPORTS MY COMMENT 100%. Thanks!! There are far fewer "happy coasters" than your propaganda would imply. A majority of them were created when GEORGIE destroyed the economy following your game plan. BUSH destroyed the revenue and ballooned the spending. The BUSH wars cost far more than all the food stamps, unemployment and disability expenditures combined. BUSH created the extra poor but like you, he did not care.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351880667152</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:24:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351880772789-102</Id><Topic><Title>Real employment 11% and Obama just can't trick them into thinking they are employed</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351862748127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:25:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or retired or moved to Mexico with their job.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351880772789</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:26:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351880986550-103</Id><Topic><Title>Medfield vs A6 vs A15 vs S4</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351873742090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>32nm Medfield at 1.6GHz is roughly at par with Apple's 45nm (ARM A9 based) A5 at 800MHz in the iPhone 4s. That's a known data point and Medfield's success in the market is a reflection of that fact. 22nm Silvermont will be roughly at par with today's Apple A6. That's a projection. In both cases, we assume we've normalized for battery life. Without doing that, comparisons are meaningless.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1351880986550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:29:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351881208559-104</Id><Topic><Title>Real employment 11% and Obama just can't trick them into thinking they are employed</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351862748127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 09:25:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice try. I already covered what I think of GWB's performance, prior to your flailing attempt to explain why Obama has no business sense. ----------------------------------------------- By aholewad . 6 minutes ago. There are far fewer "happy coasters" than your propaganda would imply. A majority of them were created when GEORGIE destroyed the economy following your game plan. BUSH destroyed the revenue and ballooned the spending. The BUSH wars cost far more than all the food stamps, unemployment and disability expenditures combined. BUSH created the extra poor but like you, he did not care. By tiglet2l . Nov 2, 2012 12:06 PM And yes, again I say GWB was awful, and yes I know the wars were expensive. I agree but we are headed down the wrong path</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351881208559</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351882001373-105</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for a bad jobs number tomorrow</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351825442336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:04:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If this is the case, that's 23 million votes for Romney as I'm sure they aren't thrilled to hear that everything is so honky dorry." [That would only be the case if those 23 million thought Romney could actually do anything. Given that he has been unable to state what he would do different from George Bush, this is a reach...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351882001373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:46:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351882160324-106</Id><Topic><Title>Short-Sellers of Europe Set to Be Unmasked</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351865719786</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:15:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today is just another example of Chump Street manipulation. Why these guys can't work for a living is beyond me. Skumbags...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351882160324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:49:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351882392745-107</Id><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Msg>They are buying the JAN $12.50 (27k contracts), $15 (130k contracts), $17.50 (55k contracts) so they can exercise today and steal the dividend. The Option market maker is shorting Intel to protect himself.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351882571735-108</Id><Topic><Title>Short-Sellers of Europe Set to Be Unmasked</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351865719786</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:15:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah waldo, they've been manipulating INTC down since 29.20 placing intc in a bear market where it will lanquish for quite some time as you wait again for the lofty heights of 24.00</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1351882571735</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:56:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351882580076-109</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&amp;41k JAN $10 contracts. Just these contracts amount to 250k contracts which translates to 25,000,000 shares.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882580076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:56:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351882731215-110</Id><Topic><Title>Otellini endorses Romney...duh Obama is pro-foodstamp and anti-business</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351869747312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:22:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is revealing when a president tells business owners that the entrepreneur who gave their sweat and blood to build that business, didn't really create it after all - the federal government actually did. Really? In what reality does the federal government replace the hard work, creativity and self initiative of entrepreneurs? Today we have a climate that belittles private initiative and reviles those whose hard work have brought value to the public and rewards to themselves and their employees. It's not surprising that the CEO's of many Silicon Valley firms believe their firms will be better off with new leadership.</Msg><Username>publicservice100</Username><Timestamp>1351882731215</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:58:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351882822861-111</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NOV 17th $21 78k contracts $20 35k $19 12k 125k contracts more covers another 12,500, shares for 40,000,000 shares total. Expect HUUUUUUUUUGE trades in Intel at the close.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882822861</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:00:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351883103142-112</Id><Topic><Title>Short-Sellers of Europe Set to Be Unmasked</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351865719786</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:15:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well, it's about time. Lets see the same happens here</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351883103142</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:05:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351883428534-113</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok, but are the buying Puts, Calls or something else? And Yes I don't understand how they "steal" the dividend by doing so...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351883428534</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351883454569-114</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not sure how shorting INTC will help to protect option MM - shorting will also expose the MM to more risk. As you said before the options (calls and puts) already priced in the divy, that being said the buying is in anticipation of pps appriciation.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351883454569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:10:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351883499336-115</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HUUUUUGE up swing, or down swing? Ya confused me...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351883499336</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:11:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351883627518-116</Id><Topic><Title>Medfield vs A6 vs A15 vs S4</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351873742090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'In both cases, we assume we've normalized for battery life. Without doing that, comparisons are meaningless.' You don't normalize performance which is measured in seconds over battery life which is measured over hours. You look at both and see what combination suits you best. The RAZRi beats the iPhone4S in one of those battery tests anyway. iPhones success is as much to do with the design and Apple ecosystem as it is due to the chips themselves. Medfield is a new chip in not many phones outside of the brand leaders, it will take time to acquire brand recognition and sales.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351883627518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:13:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351883639538-117</Id><Topic><Title>Acer expects 10 % PC growth in 2013</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1351874000978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:33:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's what the Yankees say, just wait till next year, unfortunately, the recession will quite possibly be underway.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1351883639538</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351883855067-118</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>calls since give you the option to purchase the shares and get the divy. puts - option to sale the intel shares - no shares = no divy</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351883855067</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:17:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351884049600-119</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They buy the deep calls for zero premium and sell a higher strike call that has a premium. The combined buy/sell is a neutral transaction on its face. The paired transaction is neutral so it it does not affect the trading price that much. How else could they take a 40,000,000 share position in one day without dramatically affecting share price. They will exercise the deep calls today and own shares for the dividend. They will have sold the call options and will be able to exit the share positions when they calls are assigned.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351884049600</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:20:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351884087576-120</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So we should see a huge UP swing near close then if I follow that right... I see that the option market maker, by shorting the stock protects him/her self by lowering the stock price to a level below where they will have to sell and can even make a profit on the stock... I think I followed that right...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351884087576</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:21:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351884142181-121</Id><Topic><Title>Medfield vs A6 vs A15 vs S4</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351873742090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember that a single core Medfield is able to beat the dual core A6/Krait in multithreaded benchmarks (Kraken, Octane). Further, it is able to hang with a dual core A15. Can't wait for the Z2580 in 1H 2013 :-)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1351884142181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:22:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351884268152-122</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok, I guess, hence when the little man (me) always loses when we up against someone who cheats right in front of the ref...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351884268152</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:24:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351884287725-123</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The Option market maker is shorting Intel to protect himself. " ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------- shorts are forced to pay the divy as far as i know. So it make no sense. the QQQ's are down, the market is down, it's not just Intel.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351884287725</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351884359321-124</Id><Title>INTC is DEAD - ARM Holdings is the next KING</Title><Msg>Intel will die - bye Intel</Msg><Username>aapl_crash_2012</Username><Timestamp>1351884359321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:25:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351884769157-125</Id><Topic><Title>It is falling</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351866934537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like you made money BIG time today... nice move... I should have followed that move...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351884769157</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:32:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351884792384-126</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They buy the deep calls for zero premium and sell a higher strike call that has a premium. The combined buy/sell is a neutral transaction on its face. The paired transaction is neutral so it it does not affect the trading price that much. How else could they take a 40,000,000 share position in one day without dramatically affecting share price. They will exercise the deep calls today and own shares for the dividend. They will have sold the call options and will be able to exit the share positions when they calls are assigned. ---------------------------------------------------- ok, selling the higher strike make sense. just the same the option MM by selling short is just lowering the price of the calls. The option MM care less about the stock pps, he/she makes money by arbitrage. the more ppl buy the better for MM.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351884792384</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:33:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351885080269-127</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The person who borrows shares and shorts them will be responsible for paying the dividend to the person he borrowed the shares from. Since the OMM will not be borrowing shares (nake shorting), he will not pay the dividend. I must confess that it might be some other than the OMM but someone will not pay the dividend on 10,000,000 to 40,000,000 shares of shorted Intel stock. Check out last NOV 4th and 5th on fails to deliver. You will see a delta spike on the nake short for Intel. failstodeliver DOT com</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351885080269</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:38:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351885815787-128</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good time to do WHAT? then... 22.03... makes me wonder why I didn't see all out at 22.50 and then sell short at 22.50... would have been a killer move, but who knew this was going to happen... except teaandtea of course...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351885815787</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:50:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351885950803-129</Id><Title>go intx</Title><Msg>far better dividend</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1351885950803</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:52:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351886459707-130</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>intc is prohibited from going up 2 days in a row, just like the qqq. lower low today on the qqq than the low yesterday, higher high, not a good sign, markets worked off short term oversold yesterday, and now no longer oversold</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1351886459707</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 16:00:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351886508026-131</Id><Title>SMELLTEL DOLES OUT A LITTLE MORE TOUGH LOVE</Title><Msg>I'm certain that the freaky longs on this message board view it as nothing more than "just shakin' out the weak hands."</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1351886508026</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 16:01:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351886659171-132</Id><Title>Slaughtering the DIP buying lambs today, WOW the sharks are feeding on AAPL</Title><Msg>Slaughtering the DIP buying lambs today, WOW the sharks are feeding on AAPL</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351886659171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 16:04:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351887225833-133</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"..They will exercise the deep calls today and own shares for the dividend. " --------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- in that case the open interest next week should stay around the same as today or it will not increased by much... will be interesting to see</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351887225833</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 16:13:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351887863273-134</Id><Topic><Title>Slaughtering the DIP buying lambs today, WOW the sharks are feeding on AAPL</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351886659171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 16:04:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some think the markets have one more rally in it to a spy over 1500, for a significant top, some believe the top of the bull market that began in March 2009 has already ended with the recent highs when INTC was way up there in the 27's. it is naive to believe that the bull market that began in March 2009 is never ending without another bear tossed in. chips are already in one. Intc stopped right at resistance, 22.50, rsi 50, which can be an overbght signal when a stock is clearly in a downtrend. on the plus side, it outperformed the qqq with less of a drop, the macd line is still pointing up, but those with visions of new highs are likely to be waiting a very, very, very long time.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1351887863273</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 16:24:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351889439086-135</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are many, many combinations of trades (options + stocks) that can be combined to execute an arbitrage strategy. The key elements are a combination that the entry position and exit are fixed so they are able to take shares early. The cost should be less than the dividend. If they bought the deep at 0 cents premium and sold the shallow as an exit path with they are called. The number of call contracts was high today. JAN2014 $15 84k JAN2013 $17.50 148k JAN2013 $15 208k JAN2013 $12.50 41k JAN2013 $10 65k DEC $19 20k NOV $21k 78k NOV $20 35k NOV $19 12k 691,000 contracts = 69,100,000 shares Early exercise could also be to cover short shares to avoid paying the dividend and exit the short position. Contract volume could be churn from same day buy sell early exercise for just capturing the dividend (arbitrage as I described it) early exercise for short covering (lots of shares acquired without moving price up) exit path for the arbitraging. retail investors buying the cheap calls retail investors selling covered calls sigh ....</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351889439086</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 16:50:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351890334418-136</Id><Topic><Title>OPTION ABITRAGING IN FULL SWING</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351882392745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry. Huge volumes. I saw only one 2,558,000 share trade. Large but smaller than I expected.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351890334418</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 17:05:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351892019835-137</Id><Topic><Title>Otellini endorses Romney...duh Obama is pro-foodstamp and anti-business</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351869747312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:22:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Monty agreed with Romney strapping his dog to the car for the brief 600 mile drive. 'The Simpsons'' Mr. Burns endorses Mitt Romney By Patrick Kevin Day November 1, 2012, 5:18 p.m. The 2012 presidential campaign is almost over and slowly but surely the celebrities have announced their endorsements. Though some are worth more than others. Joss Whedon has endorsed Mitt Romney (in a way) and now "The Simpsons'" Mr. Burns, owner of Springfield's nuclear power plant, titan of corporate capitalism and honcho in the Springfield Republican Party, has come out with his own backhanded endorsement of the Republican nominee. Backhanded in the sense that C. Montgomery Burns is positively Dickensian in his baseness. To show Americans who the best choice for president would be, Mr. Burns puts Shamus the dog to the test between "Broccoli" Obama and "Meat" Romney. When confronted with the choice, the dog does what any reasonable animal would do. TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYY</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351892019835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 17:33:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351892996657-138</Id><Topic><Title>Medfield vs A6 vs A15 vs S4</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351873742090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember that a single core Medfield is able to beat the dual core A6/Krait in multithreaded benchmarks (Kraken, Octane). Further, it is able to hang with a dual core A15. ------ Javascript for the most part is a single threaded environment. Both Kraken and Octane are single threaded (run them on your PC and see for yourself).</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351892996657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 17:49:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351893234923-139</Id><Topic><Title>Paul O proves he is an idiot.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1351872315385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It comes down to this really. There are MORE DEMD than REPUBS! If the idiots on the left come out and vote, they crush Romney. Thus we have the voter surpression efforts by the shrinking GOP. This will be the last Presidential election that the right has a chance to win. Soon, the demographics of the voting population will make the angry white rual voters a minority. Eight years from now, even a solid GOP state such as Texas will likely go Dem based upon the Hispanic vote. But this election? No one knows for sure but since the loser normally yells the loudest and the Republicans seem to be yelling a lot, they look to be the loser here. Romney is a terrible candidate but since he is willing to say anything and lie about everything, he has made it close. It will be comical watching the likely events on the election night. Obama wins Florida, Republicans start to cry. Obama wins Virginia, they upchuck and wet their pants. Of course Ohio goes Obama and then they start to yell and scream as the Dems laugh at them. Romney waits until the polls in California close and then concedes. Fuxed up news is already trying to hint to their delusional rightwing nutjob viewership that Obummer is going to win. thus, Fuxed up news, instead of spending most of its time pumping Romney, has switched to calling Obummer names and pushing for anojhter lame House impeachment, just like they did to Clinton. It is stupid and a waste of time but the GOPTards on the right are going to need a bone to keep them happy. Your favorite Rightwing Raspukkin poll has made the last minute swith calling it all even now in popular vote. By Monday, he will show Obummer up 1 or 2. Why is it rightwing trash are so so stupid?</Msg><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1351893234923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 17:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351893547743-140</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is DEAD - ARM Holdings is the next KING</Title><Username>aapl_crash_2012</Username><Timestamp>1351884359321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let me guess, your a short that got burned, right !</Msg><Username>joespada282</Username><Timestamp>1351893547743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 17:59:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351895368575-141</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is DEAD - ARM Holdings is the next KING</Title><Username>aapl_crash_2012</Username><Timestamp>1351884359321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>aapl_crash_2012 ? gee I wonder what your agenda could be? LOL!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1351895368575</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 18:29:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351901677194-142</Id><Topic><Title>Paul O proves he is an idiot.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1351872315385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Red States = Dumb_blank_istan. Fox News is about as fair, balanced, and reality based as The National Inquirer. No one can blame these 'news outlets' for trying to sell their fiction to make a buck,.... The really scary thing it's that there is a very large portion of this nation that actually believe them.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1351901677194</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 20:14:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351902581907-143</Id><Topic><Title>Paul O proves he is an idiot.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1351872315385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And by the way the latest polls in Massachusetts have the President up by between 15-30% over their former Gov. Could have something to do with his boasting about their fantastic schools, which he had absolutely nothing to do with, and in fact did his level best to dismember through teacher layoffs and other cuts during his administration. He is what Bill Clinton once used to characterized another fraud of the same ilk,.... 'the rooster who attempted to claim credit for the dawn. Hmmm maybe the good people of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts know a thing or two about Mr. Romney after having to deal with him during the 30% or so of the time he actually spent in Massachusetts during his term as Gov there. It's a pretty strong message for all you undecided voters.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1351902581907</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 20:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351905680759-144</Id><Title>AMD: Is Move Into ARM Chips Positioning It For Sale?</Title><Msg>Advanced Micro Devices this week announced a plan to begin developing ARM-based processors targeted at the server market, in an attempt to diversify away from the core battle with Intel for the x86 PC processor market. That’s an interesting move, but one which might have deeper implications than simply trying to evade its eternal tormentor. UBS analyst Steve Eliscu thinks the odds are against widespread success for AMD in ARM server chips. “AMD will be challenged to compete vs the existing ARM-based suppliers, especially those who have an architectural license and can best optimize for performance and power consumption,” he writes in a research note this morning. “However, we believe AMD’s shift towards ARM better positions it to be sold at some point in the future to a leading ARM processor vendor. While few would dare compete vs Intel in x86, AMD offers an existing ARM supplier thousands of engineers that could provide it a huge boost.” In a sense, he’s arguing that that AMD would be a good target for an “acqui-hire” deal for a company in the chip business that wanted a ready stable of experienced microprocessor engineers. And as it turns out, there are some additional goodies hidden in AMD as well. AMD Jumps Into The ARM Server Business Roger Kay Roger Kay Contributor AMD Cutting Staff 15% Eric Savitz Eric Savitz Forbes Staff AMD: Bernstein Gives Up, Cuts Rating And Target Price Eric Savitz Eric Savitz Forbes Staff Eliscu asserts that an AMD buyer would get some useful assets that could justify a “significant premium” to its current enterprise value: A big design team, including thousands of engineers. Broadcom picked up 250 engineers in paying $3.7 billion for NetLogic, he notes. “Possible buyers of AMD could include: a major Korean semiconductor maker to augment its processor development efforts; Apple, which in addition to processors could also vertically integrate in graphics; Qualcomm, which would have better capability to provide processors for PC clients and servers/communications infrastructure,” he writes. Graphics: He thinks the graphics unit could be worth $2 billion or more to Intel. “If Intel made AMD-designed discrete graphics chips in its most advanced manufacturing facilities, Intel would potentially be able to create a much more profitable discrete graphics business than AMD has,” he writes. “We would expect Intel to focus on the premium segment of the market, including the professional graphics business, which NVIDIA currently dominates.” Embedded processors, in particular for game consoles: “Market speculation suggests AMD has swept design wins in all of the three major console platforms – Microsoft, Nintendo and Sony, each of which would result in a either IP and/or silicon sales,” he writes. “ If we estimate the business will be sustained at $500 million/year, given the low-opex intensity of the business on a go forward basis, even a blended 30% gross margin business could yield operating margins in excess of 20% or $100 million/year. If we assume a 7-year product life-cycle, this would result in a pre-tax present value of $500 million. Patents: He notes that AMD has over 4,400 non-expired patents, which he thinks could be worth somewhere between $1 billion to $2.1 billion, depending on what comparable transaction you use. Net operating loss carryforwards of nearly $1 billion. “While the price highly depends on the buyer, we believe AMD offers enough value to justify a 100% premium to its current $2.2 billion enterprise value, an offer that we believe the board would need to strongly consider,” he writes. Eliscu keeps his Neutral rating and $2.75 price target on the stock. AMD is up a penny this morning to $2.15.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351905680759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 21:21:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351908751083-145</Id><Title>ARM, Microsoft Team up to Make 64-Bit ARM Windows</Title><Msg>New operating system(s) could target the consumer (mobile, traditional) and enterprise spaces In the wake of ARM Holdings Plc.'s (LON:ARM) announcement of the upcoming 2014 ARM Cortex-A50 cores, ARM's first 64-bit processors, the company had more big news to share. Ian Forsyth, program manager at ARM, announced this week that Microsoft Corp. (MSFT) was onboard and the two companies were working together closely to make sure one or more versions of Windows support the new iteration of the low-power architecture. Nandan Nayampally, head of ARM's processor marketing division, wrote to PC World in an email, "ARM works with all its OS and ecosystem partners to inform them on next generation technologies and enable their support." The current version of Windows 8 for ARM chips -- Windows RT -- only supports 32-bit chips. Likewise, Windows Server 2012 is expected to bring ARM server chip support -- but no 64-bit support. That's not much of a problem because, as mentioned, 64-bit ARM CPUs won't land for another two years. Samsung Ativ Tab Samsung's Ativ Tab is among a crop of initial Windows RT products. Early retail Windows RT products include Microsoft's Surface and ASUSTek Computer Inc. (TPE:2357) Vivo Tab RT, both of which use NVIDIA Corp.'s (NVDA) quad-core, 32-bit Tegra 3 system-on-a-chip (SoC). Dell, Inc.'s (DELL) XPS 10 and Samsung Electronics Comp., Ltd. (KSC:005930) P8510 Ativ Tab instead use the dual-core variety of Qualcomm, Inc.'s (QCOM) Snapdragon 4, also a 32-bit chip. x86 software does not run natively on ARM architecture chips, or vice versa. That means that any application you want to run will need to have been freshly recompiled for Windows on ARM (WOA). The grunt work is not limited to recompilation. Microsoft will have a lot of hard work ahead looking to port and optimize Windows 8 or its successor to work with the new ARMv8 64-bit instruction set extensions.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351908751083</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351909666453-146</Id><Title>ARM A57 core revealed</Title><Msg>SANTA CLARA, Calif. – ARM provided the first peak at its Cortex A57 high-end 64-bit core at ARM Tech Con here Wednesday (Oct. 31). The A57 aims to provide maximum performance in a mobile power envelope, extending ARM’s reach into networking and server systems. The out-of-order design will deliver performance measured at 1250 SpecInt2000 at 1.7 GHz, or about 25-30 percent more umph than today’s 32-bit A15 cores. It can be clocked at up to 2.5 GHz in a 20 nm process, said Mike Filippo, principal design architect for the part. Filippo declined to provide detailed performance and architecture figures such as performance per watt. However, in a series of slides reproduced below, he outlined the main features of the core. It will provide three times the performance of today’s high-end smartphones. In configurations with up to 16 cores on the new ARM CoreLink interconnect it will deliver a ten-fold performance increase over the current A15, ARM claimed. The A57 will also deliver slightly greater power efficiency than the A15, but it could require as much as 30 percent more die area, Filippo said. The core was designed for equally effective use on 32- and 64-bit code, he added. “It’s a straightforward translation of the A15 to 64-bits-- not a revolutionary microarchitecture but a new ISA with optimizations,” said David Kantor, an independent microprocessor analyst at Real World Technologies. “It’s a pretty cool part, though it will eat more power." In a separate talk, ARM outlined its little brother companion, the A53, an in-order, 64-bit part focused on minimizing power consumption. It’s expansion to a 16-way set associative L2 cache was one of the remarkable features of an otherwise straightforward architecture, said Tom Halfhill of the Microprocessor Report.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351909666453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:27:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351909749409-147</Id><Topic><Title>Medfield vs A6 vs A15 vs S4</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351873742090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't normalize performance which is measured in seconds over battery life which is measured over hours. You look at both and see what combination suits you best. The RAZRi beats the iPhone4S in one of those battery tests anyway. iPhones success is as much to do with the design and Apple ecosystem as it is due to the chips themselves. Medfield is a new chip in not many phones outside of the brand leaders, it will take time to acquire brand recognition and sales. Intel has a history of emphasizing performance while downplaying battery life. Why else would they clock their first version of Medfield at 1.6GHZ when Apple's A5 was at 800MHz. This when they were terrible battery hogs at that frequency. They are concertedly trying to make people think in terms of performance, even on battery operated smartphones. As you've correctly observed market success is based on several factors, not just performance for short bursts. You can trust Intel to continue to bump up the frequency of their future chips with utter disregard to power consumption because they think consumers will buy their performance message. Today, Medfield is a new chip. Tomorrow, Silvermont will be a new chip and then Airmont will be a new chip. I guess they'll start getting traction in the market when Paul Ottelini accelerates their fabrication technology faster than Moore's law with Airmont while the other foundrys stand still.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1351909749409</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:29:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351909822764-148</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is DEAD - ARM Holdings is the next KING</Title><Username>aapl_crash_2012</Username><Timestamp>1351884359321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>idiot.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351909822764</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:30:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351910954134-149</Id><Topic><Title>AMD: Is Move Into ARM Chips Positioning It For Sale?</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351905680759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 21:21:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>-------- Graphics: He thinks the graphics unit could be worth $2 billion or more to Intel. “If Intel made AMD-designed discrete graphics chips in its most advanced manufacturing facilities, Intel would potentially be able to create a much more profitable discrete graphics business than AMD has,” he writes. “We would expect Intel to focus on the premium segment of the market, including the professional graphics business, which NVIDIA currently dominates.” ----------- Okay I already posted about this. INTC could buy AMD for GPUs, but they don't even have to. All they have to do is become a foundry for AMD GPUs. In exchange, AMD could offer INTC a license to their GPU technology for INTC to use in SOCs. INTC gets graphics for their SOCs and CPUs and AMD gets the best GPUs on the planet using INTC processes to wipe out NVDA and corner the GPGPU market. INTC and AMD win. NVDA and ARMH and others lose big time. NO BUYOUT REQUIRED.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1351910954134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:49:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351911198144-150</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe INTC should be AMD's foundry and GPU licensee</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1351698372095</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumping this. Am I the only one who sees this as a great opportunity for INTC? #$%$.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1351911198144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:53:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351911430842-151</Id><Title>Guarantee that Jack-CHEESE zooms around in a smart car</Title><Msg>ROFL!!!!!!</Msg><Username>smartcarwallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351911430842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:57:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351911437023-152</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe INTC should spin off Processor Design and become a Foundry</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1351722680673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump this one too. Doesn't anyone think outta the box here? INTC needs to unlock the full value of their businesses. Shareholders deserve no less.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1351911437023</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:57:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351912057384-153</Id><Topic><Title>Guarantee that Jack-CHEESE zooms around in a smart car</Title><Username>smartcarwallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351911430842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:57:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rolls up to the Food Stamp office in his Smart Car convertible. OMG!</Msg><Username>smartcarwallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351912057384</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:07:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351912367083-154</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe INTC should spin off Processor Design and become a Foundry</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1351722680673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INtel will have to make more $$ per wafer from being an open foundry compared to the $$ they can make selling x86... and they got a lot invested in x86.. However, It was posted the other day that INtel is taking on Cisco in such a deal... It's a start...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351912367083</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351912509255-155</Id><Topic><Title>AMD: Is Move Into ARM Chips Positioning It For Sale?</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351905680759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 21:21:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's in INtel's best interest to keep AMD alive... otherwise INtel is sole source for x86... (assuming no one counts VIA)</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351912509255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:15:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351912613895-156</Id><Title>UMC to develop 14nm FinFET process</Title><Msg>United Microelectronics (UMC) will move to aggressively develop 14nm process technology featuring FinFET 3D transistors, according to company CEO Shih-Wei Sun. Deploying Finfet transistor technology is now a must for chipmakers in order to keep Moore's Law applicable, said Sun. Moore's Law sketches out the concept of shrinking semiconductor device dimensions, but the shrinking of technology nodes will have to overcome some challenges, particularly cost-related barriers. The transition to 20nm process technology shows that the pace of cost reduction for transistor production has been slowing, Sun pointed out. Transition to a newer process should enable a 25% improvement in performance, and the manufacturing cost per transistor should also fall at the same rate in order to be cost effective, Sun said. The current shift to 20nm process from 28nm has encountered problems associated with rising equipment costs for double patterning techniques, and performance is only able to see a 15% improvement, Sun indicated. "Based on our IBM FinFET licensing, UMC has decided to aggressively develop 14nm FinFET technology on 20nm metal. 14nm FinFET will deliver the most optimal low-power and high-performance solution to offset the cost impact from using double patterning lithography," Sun said. In addition, Sun revealed that UMC has taped out a mobile communications IC using 28nm HKMG (gate-last) process, with commercial production slated for early 2014. Sun did not provide updates on the foundry's targeted sales ratio for 28nm, and progress on 20nm. Sun previously remarked that 28nm process technology would account for about 5% of UMC's revenues by the end of 2012, and that the foundry expected to start making a small volume of chips using 20nm process sometime in the second half of 2013</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351912613895</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:16:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351914660373-157</Id><Topic><Title>AMD: Is Move Into ARM Chips Positioning It For Sale?</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351905680759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 21:21:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would INTC being the sole source of x86 be a problem for INTC?</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1351914660373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 23:51:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>