<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350100819322-1</Id><Topic><Title>Last thing Paul O. cares about is the whiney daytraders/gamblers on the YAYHOO board, LOL!</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350098617611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 23:23:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ooooooooooooooo! You are so knowledgeable. Ooooooooooooooooooooooo! You know it ALL!!!</Msg><Username>pumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1350100819322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 00:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350101301362-2</Id><Title>ALERT: INTC_inside outed by marco</Title><Msg>This just in. INTC_inside is a paid pumper for INTC IR. He gets $3.75 per pump and may get fired if INTC closes below $22 next week. He was let go at his last job, assistant hamburger flipper at MCD. They dismissed him because he kept forgetting to turn the grill on before he fried the burgers. They actually gave him three chances, but it didn't work out. I don't usually out #$%$ like him, but, I can't stand watching this guy pumping to innocent victims and feel it's my duty as a human being to stop it. Look, INTC will probably never see $22 again in our lifetime, so INTC_inside is probably history next Friday. Being a compassionate person, I'm offering this #$%$ a job after INTC IR fires his a_s next week. INTC_inside, after they dump your sorry anu_, please call me at 1-800-gogetf_cked.</Msg><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1350101301362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 00:08:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350106088988-3</Id><Topic><Title>China exports up 10% in Sept vs 5% forecast</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350097458150</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 23:04:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wall Street has priced Intel for a series of total and complete disasters. We're just not seeing them. US economic news has been pretty good lately and this China news is also very favorable. Anecdotal news about the channel is not reflecting anything close to the complete disaster that Wall Street has priced in. And I'm thinking Intel got in some shipments in Q3 in order for companies to build Windows 8 machines this month even though they hadn't gone on sale yet. So, Intel may have started to recover from the wait for Windows 8. Anything other than an announcement of the bottom falling out on Tuesday should send Intel much, much higher and the forces of doom and gloom back to the woodshed where they belong...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350106088988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 01:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350107192795-4</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT: INTC_inside outed by marco</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1350101301362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 00:08:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$3.75 per pump??? That is more than you charge for your personal services.</Msg><Username>pumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1350107192795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 01:46:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350119195793-5</Id><Title>Just A Weekend Thought</Title><Msg>Both the DJIA and the S&amp;P 500 barely held on to their 50-day moving averages Friday, while keeping their uptrend intact. However, the small cap Russell 2000 index broke down. So did the mid cap S&amp;P 400 index. The overall downside risk is high. Although the "don't fight the central bankers" mentality has kept selling pressure contained, the lack of buying interest could lead to a further down drift of stock prices. There is no leadership in the market to excite the buyers. First, the large cap momentum techs, such as AAPL, fell hard. Now the financials, which had been outperforming until today, became a cause of concern on long term profit growth. Stocks are oversold. As earnings start to pour in next week, expect a bounce along the way. The QE effect should continue to keep downside limited but without leadership, there isn't likely to be much upside. have a nice weekend.</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1350119195793</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 05:06:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350120004766-6</Id><Title>If U Dont Want Socialism In USA</Title><Msg>then you know whom to vote for. This is the USA NOT Venezuela. Here people strive to be successful and creative. We just cant have a nation of people who are just dependent on handouts and Obamacare. Its just sad we dont have the right candidates to run for the office. On the other hand we have an incumbant who sends jobs overseas, cuts into seniors retirement entitlement and all this to fix the defecit which the friggin govt has created by borrowing to create bloated government and social spending. I am personally sick and tired of hearing negative TV Campaign ads and neither of the candidates have any specific topics or any spice or material specific to resolving the unemployment or deficit crisis. It seems both candidates just like to hear themselves talk and give Bullcrap and you have a bunch of Adult-kindergarners waving the flags and clapping for the talking clown. What a sight, what a joke these candidates have turned this country and its citizens into. What a shame, we have become the laughing stock of the globe. We are headed in the same path as Greece and will be there by 2016 if there is no serious resolve.</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1350120004766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 05:20:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350120533603-7</Id><Title>If U Have a 4-5 Year Horizon</Title><Msg>I would be doubling down on INTC at anything under 20. In the next 3-5 years Intel will have the edge and advantage and would have wiped out any and every competetion out there. All the Qualcoms, ARM's, Nvidia's, AMD, Samsung and more will all be history of the past which yall can read to yr kids "There was once upon a time when a company like ARM existed that went to fight a good heroic company called intel and it got nearly killed but survived to be moving around in a wheelchair......." Buy every single intel stock under 20 and hold it for yr retirement glory days which is just over the horizon. goodluck.</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1350120533603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 05:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350126865267-8</Id><Title>Maybe that's why Hathaway sold his millions of shares:</Title><Msg>Did he know something before hand?</Msg><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1350126865267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 07:14:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350130192925-9</Id><Topic><Title>If U Have a 4-5 Year Horizon</Title><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1350120533603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 05:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree that the stock is approaching extremely attractive valuations. I've started buying and will average down slowly to however far it may drop. I'm not knowledgeable about all the finer technical details about their products chips but from a 10,000 foot level I believe they will be fine going forward. I don't believe the PC is dead and it's exaggerated. Is it a mature market? Yes. Will it grow like it use to? Probably not but that doesn't mean it's going extinct as some think. They are complementary items but not substitutes for each other, specifically not in enterprise. It's also not as if Intel isn't trying to break in to mobile. They were late to recognize the trend but I think that means they will be late in getting in not that they will completely be shut out. With a company with size and R&amp;D of Intel I think it's just a matter of time before they find their way. IMO, they'll either develop their way in or buy their way in. Secondly, they are well established and growing on the other side of the coin of mobile. Their server/data center business is doing very well and that's a booming market just like mobile devices and will probably be more so in the future. This isn't a company that doesn't recognize the problems it has. It's a company that has the resources and R&amp;D to fix them over time. I''ll use the analogy of another company I've followed which to me had much greater problems but suddenly has become a darling to some degree. PFE sells the worlds biggest drug, Lipitor. For the last few years everyone was panning the stock saying they have nothing in the pipeline to replace Lipitor. Also that there was nothing there to move the needle for a company of Pfizer's size. They really still haven't replaced Lipitor and they had to cut the dividend, like some others, during the height of the financial crisis. Their divy coverage wasn't not even close to as strong as Intel's. I started adding in the low 20's all the way down to the mid-low teens. There was definitely pain there to manage. The stock is now at 25 and whenever I see an analyst on tv discussing the pharma sector it's a darling when just a few years ago it was ridiculed every chance anyone got. Frankly, I don't think anything has fundamentally changed either as they still haven't replaced Lipitor, yet suddenly that doesn't matter to the street. A couple other pharma companies faced similar crises, but I didn't invest in them at those times. BMY with Plavix. They had a threat from a Canadian generic maker (Apotex) thanks to poor management and had a severe threat of a divy cut. In the end they managed, never cut the divy, although never raised it either until recently, but they recovered. MRK with Vioxx also had a huge litigation threat but they too recovered. I don't think they ever cut the divy either. Point being is that when everyone is bad mouthing the stock, is the time to start buying. Tread carefully no doubt but start buying slowly. I don't think any of the companies I mentioned has as strong a fundamental profile as Intel but they all have recovered from their issues and made very nice gains. It's not something that happens overnight and could take some years though. Now that's not the case with every company. I just don't see Intel going the way of Kodak like others do, especially when they are doing so well on one side of the mobile coin and actively trying to fix the other side of it. Not to mention that PCs aren't dead. To me this has a much greater chance to be a recovery play like the others mentioned above rather than extinction play like Kodak.</Msg><Username>jwin125</Username><Timestamp>1350130192925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:09:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350132727913-10</Id><Title>i dunno...</Title><Msg>this thingis getting hammered every day. wow. earnings are going to be interesting. not gonna be good as we all know, just wondering how bad, and how much of a drop. hopefully, bad earnings are baked in.</Msg><Username>sharppolly</Username><Timestamp>1350132727913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:52:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350133130151-11</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT: INTC_inside outed by marco</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1350101301362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 00:08:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I lost so much money on FB By marcopubio.Jun 4, 2012 12:00 AM.Permalink I'm going to kill the wife before she gets a chance to see our brokerage statement. Any suggestions on how to make it look like an accident?</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350133130151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350133298476-12</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe that's why Hathaway sold his millions of shares:</Title><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1350126865267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 07:14:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, he just decided that making 25% in mere months on an investment in a sector he admittedly knows absolutely nothing about was too good to pass up. How many 80 year old do you know that are looking to buy and hold?</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350133298476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:01:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350133620847-13</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT: INTC_inside outed by marco</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1350101301362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 00:08:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Marco. Mad that his attempts to decieve others are just not going over on the Intel board. You poor guy. Sounds like life his kicked you squarely in the teeth........sounds like you deserve it, putz.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350133620847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350133809105-14</Id><Title>Marcopubio, a guy you should listen to.. a guy you should let handle your $$$ LOL!</Title><Msg>Re: BACK TO $20 By marcopubio.Jan 17, 2012 8:46 PM.PermalinkGo to topic satan, I've been to Vegas too many times. I dropped $800 one night at blackjack and spent $5,000 over past 2 years trying to get even. I have better luck with stocks. I only dropped around $500 on shorting BAC, but I was smart enough to get out before it was all gone. I figure if I just get 2 out of three right, I can make a nice living out of this. I've been out of work for over a year and there is absolutely nothing out there.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350133809105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:10:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350135773588-15</Id><Topic><Title>i dunno...</Title><Username>sharppolly</Username><Timestamp>1350132727913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:52:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the nail has no head left -after election might see a slight bounce.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1350135773588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:42:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350135956722-16</Id><Title>How are iPad sales bad for Intel?</Title><Msg>The headlines are saying it. But I don't see it. Using the success of the tablets (which only really means iPads alone), as a big reason for lack luster sales in PCs. These are the facts though. Apple had their first full quarter of iPad sales at 4.1 million units, when Intel delivered third quarter revenues of $11.1 Billion. Due to Intel's huge growth success during the quarters after the launch of the iPad, Intel most recently had to give guidance that is less than 2011 results for Q3. Again, this is due to 2011's huge success that was beyond what most analysts expected at that time. Yet still, with iPad sales that could top 15 million units, or maybe even 20 million units, Intel will still deliver between $13 Billion to $13.5 Billion in revenue for Q3. So as the iPad sales grew from 4.1 million quarterly unit sales to over 15 million units, Intel revenue grew from $11.1 Billion to over $13 Billion for Q3. That does not sound like cannibalization to me. In fact, it actually helps Intel's most lucrative business which is server sales. For every 120 iPads sold, a server is needed to serve them. And analysts still don't differentiate the success of the iPad from tablets in general as they should.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1350135956722</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:45:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350136116567-17</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is the best deal around....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350088240646</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 20:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel will be up 10% after the earnnings.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1350136116567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:48:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350136318188-18</Id><Title>INTC a buy rating story</Title><Msg>I am bullish Intel for several reasons. First, I like the 4+ % dividend. It has the potential to move higher from this base due to its cheap price at P/E=9. Second, I love what Intel is doing right now. With the exception of Apple (AAPL), it dictates the trajectory of the PC business to the PC makers and mobile manufacturers. Intel's investment in the ultrabook should pay off, as consumers look for lower-priced, but still credible Macbook alternatives. Look out for 3D Ivy mobile chipsets in 2nd qtr of 2013. We might see that decision start to pay off for Intel on this report. There's something, however, I love even more about Intel. It's not content with owning the present; the company has a keen eye on the future. Don't forget its better than expected earnings report coming, dividend boost and ex-devidend date coming on Nov 5, 2012.</Msg><Username>vette_999</Username><Timestamp>1350136318188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:51:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350137912962-19</Id><Topic><Title>INTC a buy rating story</Title><Username>vette_999</Username><Timestamp>1350136318188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:51:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ultrabook not going well!</Msg><Username>bylo19</Username><Timestamp>1350137912962</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350138466530-20</Id><Topic><Title>INTC a buy rating story</Title><Username>vette_999</Username><Timestamp>1350136318188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:51:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 ain't out yet. And, PC-chips are only 40% of INTC business...how are servers doing? Especially Google's servers? Did you think about that? And, INTC inside AAPL tablets. And INTC inside a number of snazzy cell phones. Did you think about that too? No you didn't....why not? Because, you have a hard time thinking about much of anything.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350138466530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:27:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350138553508-21</Id><Title>Saw a Samsung Galaxy smartphone last night</Title><Msg>A thing of beauty. AAPL is doomed.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350138553508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:29:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350139328099-22</Id><Topic><Title>INTC a buy rating story</Title><Username>vette_999</Username><Timestamp>1350136318188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:51:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whoa...you are the twilight zone, man.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350139328099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:42:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350139664769-23</Id><Title>I see a democratic win in November as an opportunity to buy beans and rice</Title><Msg>and head for the hills....</Msg><Username>dc10050</Username><Timestamp>1350139664769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:47:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350141058294-24</Id><Topic><Title>I see a democratic win in November as an opportunity to buy beans and rice</Title><Username>dc10050</Username><Timestamp>1350139664769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:47:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Might be the best place for you.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1350141058294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:10:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350143457048-25</Id><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Msg>Intel lowered the numbers based on the fact that customers delayed PC purchases till Windows 8 was launched; so Q3 numbers were adjusted downward as there was no visibilty on the launch date for Windows 8 at that time.... So with the announcement on Friday that DELL, HP, SONY et al are taking pre-orders for Windows 8 based PCs and Tablets, this is a strong signal that in the last month of Q3, Rev. thus Earnings exceeded Intel's lowered expectations as the PC makers need 4-6 weeks before they can "actually" ship their products.... And above all, Intel could have "encouraged" PC makers to take larger amount of chips just before the cut-off date end of September so the numbers will look good.... The idiots who have shorted Intel since the bogus downgrade on Monday, are in for a rude surprise as Intel and MSFT will be up by 20% plus this week so will be the PC makers.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350145545349-26</Id><Title>How will Intel react to the death of AMD?</Title><Msg>It's a two-edged sword. On the one hand, the niches that AMD now supplies with x86 product will be open for Intel to sell to. Which will actually create a production problem, since Intel schedules EOL on low-end products to free up resources for newer products. Old fab lines will have to keep running a little longer, causing minor managerial cost increases. On the other hand, AMD buys Intel chips for kitting into Sea Micro boxes, and it'll be a shame to lose those sales. But Sea Micro could and probably will be spun off preperatory to any AMD chapter filing, so this may not be a concern. And then there will be the sudden independence of ATI. This should concern nVidia, as Intel could acquire ATI and make it the core of its APU business. Which would be a winner, ironically, since buying ATI is what killed AMD in the first place. Intel can do right what AMD does wrong (that should be the slogan for the chip business for the past 40 years).</Msg><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1350145545349</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:25:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350145711055-27</Id><Title>What We know Now</Title><Msg>1.) The doom and gloom has been substantially oversold. Even Jack Welch got it wrong and was unaware of significant improvements in the economy: "If former General Electric Co. Chief Executive Officer Jack Welch’s charges of a political fix to manipulate economic data ahead of the presidential election are true, there must be a vast econometric conspiracy embracing auto dealers, real estate agents, the Federal Reserve and corporate America’s 96-year-old Conference Board. The economy is improving more than professional forecasters anticipated, particularly in data on employment and housing, according to the Bloomberg Economic Surprise Index, which compares 38 indicators with analysts’ predictions. The index, based on gauges compiled by private businesses and trade groups in addition to government, confirms U.S. growth is generating jobs in the face of a global slowdown and looming federal spending cuts and tax increases known as the fiscal cliff." 2.) Wall Street hasn't just gotten the Intel story wrong, they have gone stark raving mad pricing in the same news again and again and again. Wall Street has priced in an $8 billion revenue miss. Intel's revenues would half to decline by half to justify the reduction in the stock price Wall Street has now baked in. Does anyone really think Intel's revenues will decline by half??? This is what happens when you price in the same thing over and over and over. Revenue miss announced. Chump Street prices it in. General economic conditions decline (which is why the revenue miss is announced along with the Windows 8 wait). Chump Street prices it in. Report of chip sales decline. Same thing and Chump Street prices it in. News of AMD having problems. Chump Street prices this in even though it's a good thing for Intel. And on and on and on. The same exact thing. 3.) Employment is improving. Housing has really improved. Consumer sentiment has reached pre-recession levels. The news from China is improving. 4.) Intel's mobility strategy is gaining strength. The new Motorola smartphone demonstrates this. Intel now has Motorola, Karbonn, MegaFon, Lenovo, ZTE, Orange and Lava selling its smartphones. And a big LTE roll-out in the US planned for 2013. 5.) Intel's new tablet design is really good and will open up the tablet market, especially in the enterprise area. 6.) Intel's fabrication lead is huge and growing every day. Intel is ramping up while ARM is coasting to a stop and will pause after 20nm for an extended period of time. 7.) Intel's WiFi chip development is going to give them a significant advantage with the Internet of Things (IoT) as connectivity of devices (modems, routers, sensors, RF Tags, ATMs, vending machines, signs, coffee makers, etc.) generates a new network as large as the existing cellular network with a revenue stream just as large. 8.) 2013 will be the year after which there will never ever be the need to buy an ARM chip except at the low end of the market as ARM evolves into the next AMD due to lack of technology, fabrication and manufacturing. 9.) Intel will have five 22nm facilities running in 2013 and quickly moving to 14nm. ARM is struggling just to provide 28nm to its customers. Those wanting state-of-the-art technology will have to move to Intel. 10.) Intel will continue its every eight quarter fab cycle. No company on earth can match it. It will continue its tick-tock strategy to integrate design and fabrication improvements. I believe Marsavian said it best: "Medfield is just the starter but Silvermont will be the main course and will ask questions of Arm chips that they probably won't be able to answer. Haswell is such an awesome design that will be like the second coming of Conroe which struck down Athlon64 with a mighty blow that AMD never recovered from. Haswell will be a similar quantum jump in performance and there will be sub 10W versions. 14nm Broadwall though will get the power down to 5W which is tablet class. At 14nm Intel is going to squeeze ARM from above with Broadwell and below with Airmont, probably only Apple's bespoke processor will still look any good in comparison. Even well before then the 32nm Medfield/Clovertrail generation will spread far and wide in phones and tablets and Windows 8 will give PCs a buying boost. " Earnings on Tuesday...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350145711055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:28:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350146233565-28</Id><Topic><Title>I see a democratic win in November as an opportunity to buy beans and rice</Title><Username>dc10050</Username><Timestamp>1350139664769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:47:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol agreed. I will be loading up on tech and biotech. QE3 has done nothing to increase commodity prices. Gold alone has fallen 30 bucks per ounze in the last week.</Msg><Username>bbkenno</Username><Timestamp>1350146233565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:37:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350146272179-29</Id><Topic><Title>How will Intel react to the death of AMD?</Title><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1350145545349</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:25:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD will not go bankrupt, they may be low on the life meter but they will always be around.</Msg><Username>bbkenno</Username><Timestamp>1350146272179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:37:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350146359585-30</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe that's why Hathaway sold his millions of shares:</Title><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1350126865267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 07:14:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC will be the first at 14 NM node for mobile and dominate the space with power saving chips and speedy processors.</Msg><Username>bbkenno</Username><Timestamp>1350146359585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:39:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350146755768-31</Id><Topic><Title>Saw a Samsung Galaxy smartphone last night</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350138553508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:29:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Might be right. The only way I see AAPL with a lead is for them to have something the others don't. A faster and more powerful processor might be just what it takes. INTC &amp; AAPL comes to mind.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350146755768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:45:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350146814670-32</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe that's why Hathaway sold his millions of shares:</Title><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1350126865267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 07:14:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gordon Hathaway? "Hi, ho, Steverino!" TOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1350146814670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:46:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350147058851-33</Id><Topic><Title>How are iPad sales bad for Intel?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1350135956722</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The real problem is the facts don't agree with the spin they want you to believe. If more people were like you, the big boys wouldn't be able to scam the system!</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350147058851</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:50:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350147502967-34</Id><Topic><Title>What We know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350145711055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe Lucy said it best when he said "Intel has no presence in mobile. Intel missed the mobile boat!" Hi, ho, Weaverino!" TOOOO FUNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1350147502967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350148761069-35</Id><Title>Market pros are saying INTC will go to $16, buy then.</Title><Msg>Most likely the dividend will be cutin the next year.</Msg><Username>trading_pro_broker</Username><Timestamp>1350148761069</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:19:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350150364366-36</Id><Title>Buying opportunity of t perhe decade?</Title><Msg>I don't usually buy tech stocks. But INTC is at a 52-week low and has a dividend yield of 4.2 percent. Too good to pass up?</Msg><Username>d_fens_usa</Username><Timestamp>1350150364366</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350152967608-37</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So the rest of the noise is by crooks and felons who beat up the stock by 5% and are going to get killed on Tuesday of self-inflicted wounds. Stay tuned!</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350152967608</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350153975426-38</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That has usually been the case specially when people short a major DOW component at it's low.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1350153975426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:46:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350154344025-39</Id><Title>A Fresh look ar Romney's Tax Plan</Title><Msg>http://blogs.wsj.com/washwire/2012/10/12/fresh-debate-over-new-tax-study/</Msg><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1350154344025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:52:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350154449139-40</Id><Title>Is $21 the bottom?</Title><Msg>Or will INTC fall into the teens?</Msg><Username>d_fens_usa</Username><Timestamp>1350154449139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:54:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350154832680-41</Id><Topic><Title>Is $21 the bottom?</Title><Username>d_fens_usa</Username><Timestamp>1350154449139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:54:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good question guess everyone would be rich if they knew the exact answer,I only know you can only beat a good company down so far &amp; IMO it's plenty closer to bottom than it's top.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1350154832680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:00:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350156899699-42</Id><Title>What Romney Believes</Title><Msg>What Romney believes! 1 Reducing taxes and regulations will create jobs. This was the policy under Bush that took our country from a budget surplus to a budget deficit and failed to sustain a vital growing economy. 2. Only those individuals currently covered by medical insurance should be covered for pre-existing conditions. 3. Competition between the insurance companies will reduce medical costs. Isn’t this what we have today for everyone under the age of 65? Have you premiums gone up and health care improved? 4. The current Social Security system should be changed to allow individuals to invest their retirement funds in the stock market in hopes of getting a higher return. How much money would you have lost if you had sold the stocks in your retirement fund at the bottom of the recession? 5.You believe that higher income earners (those in the top 10%) should pay taxes at lower rate than Warren Buffet’s secretary or the average wage earner. 6. Taxes and regulations, not the lack of demand, were the major cause of the recession. 7. That the banking and financial industry does not need to be regulated. What do you think caused the housing industry to collapse and the banks to need financial aid from the government to survive? 8. Women should be paid less than men for the same job. 9. That the United States should increase its military spending even though the U.S. already spends more on defense than the next 13 countries with the highest defense budgets. 10 That companies are people and should be allowed to make unlimited political contributions without disclosure. It is your vote. This former Republican is voting for Obama</Msg><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1350156899699</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:34:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350157196301-43</Id><Topic><Title>What We know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350145711055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone, including the idiots, should print this message and post it on their refrigerator, on the picture of Aunt Mabel in the living room, on the wall facing their favorite toilet, and read it once, or twice, or thrice times a day. Thank you, Wallis.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350157196301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350157484498-44</Id><Topic><Title>Is $21 the bottom?</Title><Username>d_fens_usa</Username><Timestamp>1350154449139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:54:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, haven't you heard, INTC will be -$25 by end of the month..a negative price! Why, by next year it will be a complex number, like -$85 + i$67, with a negative definite norm!!... and then it will be a quaternion, an octonion....and soon it will suck anyone who owns it into a black hole in the quantum landscape of lost souls and depraved darkened hearts...haven't you heard? All the analysts, Cramer and CNBC are saying it...over and over and over and over.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350157484498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:44:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350157590476-45</Id><Title>INTC will never have another up day, ever....</Title><Msg>there..I said it...had to...it was the last Bingo square left that Cramer, CNBC, Vomit Shah, and all the other analanalysts haven't already taken.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350157590476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:46:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350157706822-46</Id><Topic><Title>What We know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350145711055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you, straw man, missed the opportunity to have a brain at birth because you were hanging by your prehensile toes from some neon sign at a bar in downtown Detroit at that moment.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350157706822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:48:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350157948250-47</Id><Topic><Title>What We know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350145711055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be nice as some of us also reside in Michigan. But i must admit if we got rid of Detroit, we would be even better</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350157948250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:52:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350159218031-48</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My analysis is based on facts and not the fictional crap advertised by crooks and felons predicting the death of the PC.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350159218031</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:13:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350159284599-49</Id><Topic><Title>Saw a Samsung Galaxy smartphone last night</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350138553508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:29:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now that Apple has adopted the "play it safe" model, one would think staying on the cutting edge of technology and performance would be extremely important to them. They can only do that with Intel. The most important decisions in technology are being made right now. Those are the decisions of whether to move to Intel's superior technology or to hope some miracle will occur with the ARM foundries. Companies must be deciding now in order to be in the queue for 2014 and 2015 when Intel will be dominant...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350159284599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:14:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350160056461-50</Id><Title>Article published 2 hours ago regarding "Saw a Samsung Galaxy last night"</Title><Msg>LOL.... Surprise! Apple Awarding 20nm Fab Requirements to TSMC, Samsung Out Saturday, October 13, 2012 - by Rob Williams It's been proven time and time again that Apple and Samsung are not on the best of terms, but despite that, Apple has still relied on Samsung for certain production up to this point. That Apple A6 under the hood of the latest iPhone (which we reviewed here)? It's built by Samsung, using its High-K Metal Gate process. As switching fabs isn't something that happens overnight, no one expected the shift to be quick, but it did seem to be inevitable. Hot on the heels of the news that Apple has snagged one of Samsung's prized designers comes a rumor initiated by the Chinese Economic News Service which claims Apple will soon be making the move to TSMC for its fab needs. Although Apple has worked with Samsung for quite a number of years, the company isn't taking much of a risk with the move. TSMC has been responsible for chips produced by Qualcomm, VIA, Marvell and even NVIDIA. In fact, the company currently plays a major role in the mobile market, and with Apple joining the fray, that fact is only cemented further. Apple A6 die shot, courtesy of iFixit and Chipworks It's being said that Apple's first order of business will be the production of 20nm quad-core chips - but as production is not set to start until at least Q4 2013, it's somewhat unlikely that these chips will make an appearence in the "iPad 4", given that there has been a new iPad every year since the release of the original. Things won't stop with the iPad, however. Other potential products include the iTV and possibly, even the MacBook. As Apple has a major focus on battery-life for its iPhone, it's unlikely that these quad-core chips will make an introduction there anytime soon. With this move, Apple also stands to save up to 10% per chip produced, which is attributed to Samsung's supposed inefficiency. Will that result in lower-cost iPhones? Not likely - 10% off of a $15 chip isn't ground-breaking, though when you consider that Apple can easily sell millions of units, its pockets do stand to benefit.</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1350160056461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:27:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350160234520-51</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beat or no beat, it's all the same. It will keep falling until l say buy. My analysis is based on facts. I told you so!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1350160234520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:30:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350163415498-52</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JMO, There is enough information on the other side to be very negative without being an "idiot" for deciding to short Intel. Intel will report and the clarity of the picture will become more clear. Even if Intel says they don't know, that will be information for the market. The "idiots" who shorted Intel are in the green by 50 cents a share or so. If they bought near term put options, they could be up by 100% with little chance of taking a loss. There is macroeconomic concern. There is the impact of smartphones and tablets which are changing the way things are done. Touch screen input and very low power consumption (enabling portability) are the key differences that will be integrated into higher levels of the compute continuum. There is the performance of tech companies in many sectors of the market. In addition the DELL and HPQ PC concern, there are other indicators. OCZ cannot even file their 10Q to the SEC. What does it mean for technology if one the big SSD companies is sinking? Eric Savitz, Forbes Staff "OCZ shares took a pounding earlier in the week after the company warned that results for its fiscal second quarter ended August 31 will be “materially lower” than it had previously expected. The company also said the reduced guidance reflects “the impact of customer incentive programs which were discovered subsequent to the preliminary announcement during the normal close process, and which the company will be reporting as a material weakness” in its 10-Q for the filing. OCZ also said it expects to report “negative gross margins and a significant net loss” for the quarter." --------------------------------------------- That said, Intel management is very good and I expect the results will come in close to their projections and not too much different. It would please me if they did beat. As for the market and the Intel trading pattern? I am watching options volumes related to the Nov ex-dividend day. I suspect that the group who traded over 1.6mil option contracts for the Intel ex-dividend are playing the same game.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350163415498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:23:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350163855861-53</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is all done by the PC death crowd who were pumping AAPL and now they have dumped that stock and are beating up the PC crowd just before the Windows 8 comes out so they can get in on the cheap. Intel is a diversified company with software and hardware solutions that goes way beyond the PC market waiting for the Windows 8 for 10 months.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350163855861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350164291338-54</Id><Topic><Title>How are iPad sales bad for Intel?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1350135956722</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The truth about cannibalization lies somewhere in between the analysts extreme view of "the PC is dead" and what as is actually happening. There are probably some users that had only very modest demands of a PC in the first place for light content consumption. In the past the desktop or laptop were the only options but for those users but today a tablet might satisfy their minimal requirements. So is there substitution happening? Perhaps at the low end of the market, but for anyone that needs to get real work done or run a business today's tablets are not an adequate substitute. Going forward the lines betwen the laptop, ultrabook and Ivy Bridge-based tablets will blur. The high-end of Microsoft's new tablet lineup are probably capable of substitution but those devices are full-fledged W8 systems in a thin form factor.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1350164291338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:38:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350164397046-55</Id><Topic><Title>Article published 2 hours ago regarding "Saw a Samsung Galaxy last night"</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1350160056461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:27:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple is very, very agressive about driving down costs. They will wring out every vendor for the lowest price possible. The TSMC rumors "may" be evidence of a real Apple decision. I think they are still rumors from what I can find. The TSMC rumors may also be circulated by Apple to encourage Samsung Semicondutor to lower their prices too. If their is a problem with TSMC meeting leading edge fab capacity for their current customers, it would be strange for them to offer aggressive prices to Apple on a process node that is constrained. IF TRUE, it will be pretty tough for others to squeeze out any 20nm parts and I think the deal would trash the TSMC margins. Apple does not have any problems dealing with Samsung Semi, even if they are having problems with Samsung Telecom and Consumer divisions. They are isolated profit centers. Samsung Electronics America (SEA) Samsung Consumer Business Division (CBD) Samsung Enterprise Business Division (EBD) Samsung Telecommunications America (STA) Samsung Semiconductor, Inc.(SSI) Samsung Information Systems America (SISA) Samsung Austin Semiconductor(SAS)</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350164397046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:39:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350164914909-56</Id><Topic><Title>What We know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350145711055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the most beautiful place in america is in michigan according to a recent poll. it's that sand dune park area in the northwest of the state. have you ever been there? does it live up to the title? just curious. thank you</Msg><Username>ramalamalongdong</Username><Timestamp>1350164914909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:48:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350165355608-57</Id><Title>What happen to CNBC's PETE the CON man who said buy INTC at 29.25 He should tell all you suckers that purchased shares that he is very very sorry and pay you money</Title><Msg>What happen to CNBC's PETE the CON man who said buy INTC at 29.25 He should tell all you suckers that purchased shares that he is very very sorry and CNBC should have to pay you money.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1350165355608</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:55:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350166231105-58</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is computing. 2/3 from notebooks and 1/3 from servers. Does this match your definition of diversified? Are they missing something? Intel gets 67% from notebook and desktop CPU/chipsets Intel gets 27% from servers Intel gets 5% from Atom and others (from trefis) 34% Notebook processors 23% Server processors 14% Desktop processors 13% Chipsets - notebook and desktop 5% Atom and other CPU 4% Chipsets - server 4% Cash</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350166231105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350166703224-59</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So sales were down 7% due to Windows 8 delays, this is not a 7% per quarter as is being advocated by the PC death crowd.... Q4 will bury the shorts, starting on Tuesday.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350166703224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:18:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350167569200-60</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As for the market and the Intel trading pattern? I am watching options volumes related to the Nov ex-dividend day. I suspect that the group who traded over 1.6mil option contracts for the Intel ex-dividend are playing the same game. ----------------------------------------------------- what are you seeing. do you think they will exetcize thier options in ordr to receive dividend?</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350167569200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:32:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350167888242-61</Id><Topic><Title>What happen to CNBC's PETE the CON man who said buy INTC at 29.25 He should tell all you suckers that purchased shares that he is very very sorry and pay you money</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1350165355608</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:55:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pete Najarian has owned Intel for a long time and is a perpetual bull on Intel. A quick search shows he recommended Intel when it was $15, in May 2009. I did not look farther back than May 2009. CON man "a person who swindles another by means of a confidence trick" I don't view Pete as a CON man for expressing his bullish opinion any more than I view you for expressing your bearish opinion. I personally give Pete a little more credit than you because there is a little more transparency in using a real name (Pete) than using an anonymous Yahoo ID (coinmaker77). ---------------------- What's the Trade on Intel? Wed 26 Sep 12 | 12:51 PM ET not so fast, pete. your call on intel this month has some viewers scratching their heads. take a listen. i would take intel right now because of the fact that where are they going to get growth? in mobile. they have made a huge push. they brought along a guy mike bell that was at palm. he helped get ty phone into the marketplace. this guy is leading the mobile division. that's where they get the growth. ouch, ouch. since your call september 7 intel is down almost 10%. are you still in the name? do you own any other ties? i have the same shirt and tie. i just show up here, throw them on. i continue to hold intel. they were late to mobile. we knew it. this is a name where i have held it for a long time. i will sell calls against it, collect the dividend yield. i like it. stephanie? we don't own it. you got two downgrades today and the stock is green. i think the yield gets interesting in the low 20s. clearly they missed the boat to get into the smartphone or mobile early, but they have a strategy in place. i think the risk-reward in the low 20s. steve? they have two things going they are tied to the pc market and the dividend play became out of favor. people were selling dividend plays and buying risk. they are still so attached to the pc market you have to wait for those dividend plays to come back in favor. i like the dividend close to 4%. do you see how nice your colleagues are? none of them made fun of you. grasso laughed about the shirt and tie. what's to laugh about? the guy is a gentleman. i love you, brother. you have questions, the traders have answers. seema has been tracking tweets and joins us now. let's talk about iphone carriers. mac tweets, do you hold or sells shares of verizon in the wake of the iphone 5 hype? oppenheimer noting carriers are entering a seasonally strong period. grasso? 4.5% yield on this one. -------------------- Your First Move For Thursday May 3rd Published: Wednesday, 2 May 2012 | 7:23 PM ET Pete Najarian thinks Intel [INTC 21.4803 -0.1997 (-0.92%) ] is a buy. “I think it’s going higher. I think its going through $30. Giddyup!” -------------------- July 17th, 2011 Jon Najarian recommends it too. "We heard this week that PC sales are not dead. That bodes well for Intel into earnings." -------------------- Fast Money Recap, Tuesday May 12, 2009 Intel (INTC), Cisco (CSCO), AMD (AMD), IBM (IBM), Intel may open higher on Wednesday's open after CEO Paul Otellini made bullish comments after hours; "Looking at order patterns, billings patterns, (outlook) is a little better than expected," he said. “This quarter is incredibly dependent on the month of June, but so far so good." Intel is a barometer for the entire tech sector; Karen Finerman's pick is Cisco. Tim Seymour would short AMD, but Pete Najarian disagrees, citing bullish action in the stock. Jared Levy of Peak6 Investments likes IBM.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350167888242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:38:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350169253004-62</Id><Title>400 Million Windows 8 devices to be sold by July 1, 2013....</Title><Msg>"Even though people have long lamented the dearth of apps in the Windows Store, a Microsoft executive recently made the proclamation that the company will be aggressively pursuing more than 100,000 apps in the first three months after launching Windows 8. “In order to reach our goal, a conservative estimate of 400 million units in marketplace by July 1, we know we have to have a healthy ecosystem of apps,” Keith Lorizio, Microsoft’s vice president of U.S. sales and marketing, in an interview with Beet.TV. “We’re putting millions of dollars against that effort and working with publishers to get their apps live as soon as possible.” How Many Intel Chips Would Be Inside! 75% or more....</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350169253004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:00:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350170851772-63</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[Beat or no beat, it's all the same. It will keep falling until l say buy. My analysis is based on facts. I told you so!] *** Another of Lucy's "Sybil" ID character creations. They get worse and worse. I like Agent Orange better...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350170851772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:27:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350171010486-64</Id><Topic><Title>What We know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350145711055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I had the best sex I ever had in Michigan. But it wasn't in Detroit.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350171010486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:30:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350171686426-65</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree if you notice its all the MM's who downgrade Intel at the same time so they can take it down and buy at cheaper prices. If Intel goes to $19 as everyone is saying it will I will load up the truck and wait. It will be back above $20 in no time.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350171686426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350171708251-66</Id><Topic><Title>400 Million Windows 8 devices to be sold by July 1, 2013....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350169253004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:00:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is a "Conservative Estimate" and represents 50 million units per months or 2.5 million units per business day.... That would give Intel 2 million units to power each day and that sounds very good.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350171708251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:41:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350171769386-67</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. Some of my thoughts .... The options market maker prices the dividend into the put and call options price. With Intel closing Friday at $21.48, you can look at the options that expire in OCT and NOV to see this discontinuity. IN THE MONEY OPTIONS ... and this works for all DEEP ITM options. If you take the options that are 50 cents into the money: $21 strike CALLS and $22 strike PUTS and look at the options market maker (OMM) pricing premium for just OCT and NOV. $21 CALL BID prices OCT $.72 NOV $.88 $22 PUT BID prices OCT $.76 NOV $1.11 OCT Now, there is only the 2 cents difference in premiums (since the price finished 2 cents below the $21.50 mid-point) add 2 cents to the CALL and subract 2 cents from the PUT and you get the mid-point of 74 cents. 50 cents intrinsic value PLUS 24 cents with one week life left. Volatility normally runs at 22 on Intel. These premium levels IMPLY a volatility of 35. Too high for INTC. The options have the 22.5 cent dividend partially price in already. 50% of the dividend in the call and 50% in the put option. NOV The CALL is too cheap. The PUT is too expensive. Why is the NOV call priced at 88 cents and the PUT priced at $1.11 ???? $1.11 - .88 = .23 the difference in the PUT and CALL premiums for NOV is because the stock price will be adjusted down 22.5 cents on ex-dividend morning 11/5. If someone has written a covered call on their shares and it is the call is in the money trading at near zero premium on 11/4 there shares will be at risk. Nov, Dec and Jan expiration months are targets.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350171769386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:42:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350171848902-68</Id><Topic><Title>What We know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350145711055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The mobile boat is not missed...maybe late but not missed that is why stupid traders like yourself make me money cause you have blinders on and do not understand how Intel can design and fab faster than you can blink with higher quality. When AMD came out with their first Quad core everyone was calling for Intel's doom...now look what has happened. Intel's duo core = AMD's quad core and AMD's quad Core = Intel's octo core etc.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350171848902</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:44:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350172137846-69</Id><Title>Intel has bottomed and death of PC overhyped</Title><Msg>Its all in cycles...there is no death of the PC. The PC may mutate but no death. The reason being people use tablets as toys (i.e. watch movies, surf web, play games etc). Professionals have no need for tablets since PC's can do it all. Have you ever tried an excel spreadsheet or word doc on a tablet or even better a mini tablet...what a joke. There is a PC cycle and it will be back mark my word. Tablets are for the kids you can't do work on them.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350172137846</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350172217340-70</Id><Topic><Title>Intel has bottomed and death of PC overhyped</Title><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350172137846</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:48:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agreed. My old company bought laptops and used docking stations for mobility. whether it's a desktop or laptop, it's still intel inside.</Msg><Username>chevymalibu1966</Username><Timestamp>1350172217340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:50:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350172426745-71</Id><Topic><Title>What We know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350145711055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great write up. INTC was 25's when they warned. Went to 24 on the news and paused. then dropped to the 23's. then the HPQ and AMD news and over and over again with barrons and other reporters. I bet we rise on intc's earnings if as expected. If they come out with 45 cents and 9B in 4Q, then we're toast but they shouldn't go that low. I hope Tues AH's sends INTC to 22.75 or higher.</Msg><Username>chevymalibu1966</Username><Timestamp>1350172426745</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:53:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350172584261-72</Id><Topic><Title>400 Million Windows 8 devices to be sold by July 1, 2013....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350169253004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:00:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ok, and at about $100/chip, that's $30 Billion in new revenue, a 50% bump up for a year. But, of course, INTC stock will NEVER have another up day and is going to be trading at a NEGATIVE PRICE by Xmas, have'nt you heard,? (via CNBC, Cramer, Vomi Shah, and a whole nest of analanalysts)?</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350172584261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:56:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350173910507-73</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Appreciate your informative posts. Do you have an opinion on what the fair price of Intel should be. Not going to hold you to it.</Msg><Username>jcjky</Username><Timestamp>1350173910507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:18:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350174549970-74</Id><Topic><Title>Article published 2 hours ago regarding "Saw a Samsung Galaxy last night"</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1350160056461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:27:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good response, Alex. IF Apple moved to TSMC, wouldn't that really hurt Qualcom which would in turn help Intel? Seems to me like Intel is going to cause alot of companies an awful lot of problems when it gets to 14nm, especially if Apple is taking up all the TSMC capacity.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1350174549970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:29:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350174918224-75</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see. Looking at the numbers I can see now that the call\put options already adjusted for the coming dividend. however, i'm not sure I understand what you mean that if someone wrote covered calls (meaning sold call options) his shares will be at risk if that premium on 11/4 is near zero? don't they just expire worthless? (my options understanding is limited). On a different note may i ask -- if someone has let's say 1000 shares and he sells calls options (covered calls strategy), how many contracts he has to sell to protect his 1000 shares? is it one to one, meaning he has to sell 10 call contracts to cover 1000 shares? (hope what i'm asking make sense at all. lol)</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350174918224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:35:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350177031952-76</Id><Topic><Title>400 Million Windows 8 devices to be sold by July 1, 2013....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350169253004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:00:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And with AMD out of the way and ARM/Qcom et al getting hit by Intel's Chips for Mobile communication, I can see Intel hitting $50.00 a share in 2013.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350177031952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350177071688-77</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The person who BUYS the option can EXERCISE the option ANY day, up to an including the option expiration day. If I sold NOV call options at $21 strike, they would have an INTRINSIC value today of 48 cents with Intel trading at $21. Any option price beyond the 48 cents is premium. I am only talking about the options with say 1 or more cents of intrinsic value. 10 option contracts for 1000 shares. ONE option contract USUALLY represents 100 shares of equity EXCEPT relatively special cases. those cases where the 1 to 100 ratio has been modified by some event .... usually some kind of spin off or merger where option already exist and have to be adjusted. Say, for example, you sell $23 strike options on your shares for say, 15 cents and get $150 extra on your shares. If the Intel price went to $24, I would not be surprised to see your shares get exercised early so someone could snatch the 22.5 cent dividend from you. Anyone who wrote call options that will be in the money with near zero premium on 11/4 near close, is a candidate for having there shares called away from them EARLY ON 11/4.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350177071688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:11:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350177171966-78</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is the best deal around....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350088240646</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 20:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We will have very strong guidance going forward with Windows 8 and AMD out of the way.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350177171966</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:12:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350177462363-79</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has great relationship with the PC makers so they will ship the goods in Q3 and book the sales and the PC makers will cost them in Q4 as they will "arrive" at the site in October.... So they will both win!</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350177462363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:17:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350178352826-80</Id><Topic><Title>Article published 2 hours ago regarding "Saw a Samsung Galaxy last night"</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1350160056461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:27:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>8-) BINGO. It is hard to say. Qualcom or one of these others might just buy a foundry. Many companies work happily with companies where they compete with other divisions. My opinion and does not predict the future ... it is more complex that a sound bite. Apple does NOT care who builds there parts for them. Apple just wants parts that satisfy their needs and at the best price. Apple will do what makes the most tactical (short term) and strategic (long term) sense. Using the lure of Apple business is one way to get better pricing from Samsung or TSMC or Intel. Samsung has capacity. They are proving performance to Apple daily. TSMC has capacity shortage but they could be used as a threat. Intel MIGHT have a spare 22nm fab since yields are good. Good yields would be a good sign for a customer IF Intel was looking to contract out fab capacity. Samsung they want to keep their fabs full and costs down. Under pricing pressure from Apple. TSMC they want to get some contract from Apple for the future when capacity frees up. Apple contract now would be tough. Intel wants to keep the Apple MAC business they have and win more .... but what kind of business?? Intel also wants to fill fabs. Qualcom, Nvidia, ..... want to keep Apple from going to TSMC and having TSMC give capacity contracts to Apple on advanced process. What will each company be saying publicly to ultimately get what they want. It is not simple to figure out NOR is it easy to know which company is leaking the "rumors" and for what reason. It is a chess game.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350178352826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350179105900-81</Id><Title>Intel Longs should consider DELL....</Title><Msg>AS Windows 8 will kill AAPL and that DELL is the only major PC company that can rocket up fast as HP is still struggling to find its footing.... We should be over $15.00 by Xmas.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350179105900</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350179115340-82</Id><Topic><Title>What happen to CNBC's PETE the CON man who said buy INTC at 29.25 He should tell all you suckers that purchased shares that he is very very sorry and pay you money</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1350165355608</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:55:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope it gets down to $20 then I'll back up the truck</Msg><Username>dishthedirt61</Username><Timestamp>1350179115340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350179227641-83</Id><Title>INTC short interest could be as high as 250-300 million shares....</Title><Msg>And on Tuesday it will be an ugly day in shortland.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350179227641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:47:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350179561527-84</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>".....Anyone who wrote call options that will be in the money with near zero premium on 11/4 near close, is a candidate for having there shares called away from them EARLY ON 11/4" --------------------------------------------- ok, I see now. options on stocks that pay divy has additional dimensin to how one plays it. Thanks a bunch Alex</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350179561527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:52:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350180756306-85</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IMO, ..... TSM is a good comparison with a forward PE of 14 JMO ... Today ... probably guess $28 to $32 if fully valued giving where everything stands. (My weasel way of saying $30) The markets Intel is in must be shown to be growing and they are growing along with them. If you use the 14x and a $2 to $3 earnings then the price of $28 to $42 could be expected. The two companies have a lot in common. NOW .... judge the impact yourself .... trefis will allow you to play with revenue streams and compute these number .... if you want to play. Potential negatives .... just some servers ..... if the 23% of Intel revenue and 50% of Intel profits is affected by dropping prices OR conversion to other architectures (SPARC, POWER, ARM, ATOM, ...) revenue and profits will be affected. same is true with desktops ... If Apple converted their whole line of MAC to their ARM, that is 16% of the PC market. Intel surprise product .... Haswell capabilty is better than expected .... early placements of systems are showing up so it appears on schedule Potential positives .... just some smartphone/tablet does better than expected. There are some signs of this. royalty payments agreement announced give Intel some revenue stream on their IP lower costs and higher margins that being modeled by analysts. I make 2 assumptions. 1. Intel can fill their fabs 2. Intel fabrication is as good or better than TSM TSM has 4.3bil shares float 5bil outstand ... INTC 5bill TSM sales per share $2.93 Intel $10.73 TSM profit margin 30% Intel 22% TSM operating profit margin 32% Intel 31% TSM return on assets 11% Intel 15% TSM return on equity 22% Intel 25% TSM trailing PE 16 Intel 9 TSM forward PE 14 Intel 10 TSM operating cash flow $8b Intel $20b</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350180756306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350180916793-86</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will beat the Rev/EPS numbers....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350143457048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Haswell comment should be a positive not a negative. I was also talking about things beyond Haswell. Intel surprise product .... Haswell capabilty is better than expected .... early placements of systems are showing up so it appears on schedule</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350180916793</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:15:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350186834205-87</Id><Title>$16 Billion to Intel</Title><Msg>10% smartphone penetration gives Intel $16 billion in revenue.This WILL happen by November 2014. Apples is only 6% of Intel's business.Guess who is going to abandon ARM first.</Msg><Username>sanjitkumar23</Username><Timestamp>1350186834205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 23:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350186864605-88</Id><Title>$21.48 - $3.48 = $19.00 = cover baby!</Title><Msg>Yep, I'm gonners at $19.00. You realize that after forward guidance all of you still in this stock will never see $20 again? A few months later the dividend will be lowered, and this stock will probably settle around $14 - $16. I hate to see any of you suffer, and after the CC on Tuesday, I'm offering my counseling services free of charge, just pay $100 shipping and handling. Oh my, what have I found here? It's the world's smallest viloin playing hearts and flowers for you.</Msg><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1350186864605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 23:54:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>