<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344745656000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be 10+ percent faster than Ivy Bridge</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344697458000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:04:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Haswell should end up at least 10 percent faster than Ivy Bridge based cores at the same clock" The Intel RD budget was $8.3b last year. I would hope that they spent "$Billions$" on Haswell. Probably more. It is pretty hard to quantify the man years of time invested but Intel is already working on Broadwell, Skylake and Skymont and beyond. There are a couple new features that should help specific application types. The redesign of the power distribution will also get the 10+ percent at a lower power consumption point. Confirmed new features AVX2 256-bit integer instructions gather, bit manipulation, and FMA3 instructions Transactional Synchronization Extensions (TSX) Direct3D 11.1 and OpenGL 3.2 implementations DDR4 on servers increase memory bandwidth</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1344745656000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:27:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344747463000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be 10+ percent faster than Ivy Bridge</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344697458000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:04:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Expect some Haswell "surprises" next month at IDF.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1344747463000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:57:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344748359000-3</Id><Title>The ghost of W....American Idiot</Title><Msg>The primary causes of today’s deficit and the largest contributor to the national debt continue to be Bush-era policies. Policies that Paul Ryan voted for. Paul Ryan voted for the Iraq war. He voted for Medicare Part D. He voted for TARP. He voted for the Bush Tax Cuts. Twice. He also voted for the Economic Stimulus Act of 2008, HR 5140. Paul Ryan is not a deficit hawk, and he’s not a “serious budget cutter.” He’s a fake. A reverse Robin Hood who takes advantage of the media’s malfeasance to push an austerity agenda, which includes austerity for “you people” and none for their betters, designed to funnel money to the top at the expense of the deficit and the national debt. Or as Charles Pierce put it earlier this week [E]very time he comes up with another “budget,” actual economists get a look at it and determine, yet again, that between “What We Should Do” and “Great Things That Will Happen When We Do” is a wilderness of dreamy nonsense, wishful thinking, and an asterisk the size of Lake Huron. At which point, Republicans who’d like to have careers in five years take to hiding behind the drapes when he comes down the hall. Then, a few months later, he’s at it again. And even some putatively liberal commentators shrug and tell themselves that, at least, Paul Ryan is a Serious Person. He gets credit for sincerely wanting to “reform” entitlements, when his entire career makes it quite plain that he doesn’t believe in the concept of entitlements, let alone the ones we actually have. The only real fiscal conservative in the race at this point, if the phrase still has any meaning, is President Obama. http://bobcesca.com/blog-archives/2012/08/paul-ryan-is-very-serious-about-ballooning-the-deficit.html</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1344748359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 01:12:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344749253000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be 10+ percent faster than Ivy Bridge</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344697458000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:04:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you expect it, how can it be a surprise? you just ruined the surprise! terrible! oh, the humanity!</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1344749253000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 01:27:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344752523000-5</Id><Topic><Title>The ghost of W....American Idiot</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1344748359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 01:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent post!</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1344752523000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 02:22:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344756066000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be 10+ percent faster than Ivy Bridge</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344697458000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:04:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>server can never be too fast. Not sure how arm can compete in this area with their lukewarm chips.</Msg><Username>starbauch</Username><Timestamp>1344756066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 03:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344776508000-7</Id><Title>Dems will CORNHOLE GOP this Nov...</Title><Msg>You heard it here first!</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1344776508000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:01:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344776651000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Dems will CORNHOLE GOP this Nov...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1344776508000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:01:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a wallisweaver alias. He's gay and he's absolutely insane.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1344776651000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:04:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344777740000-9</Id><Title>Dagger for GETANID61, wireless cell charging</Title><Msg>Who's gonna buy a Windows RT machine? LMAO. Get some Nads, you F-ing loser! http://www.complex.com/tech/2012/08/intel-is-working-on-ultrabooks-that-could-wirelessly-charge-your-smartphone</Msg><Username>getsome_nads</Username><Timestamp>1344777740000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:22:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344778119000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Dagger for GETANID61, wireless cell charging</Title><Username>getsome_nads</Username><Timestamp>1344777740000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:22:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know those Motorolla phones are gonna be synched up to charge wirelessly. You KNOW they are. Intel is the next Apple.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1344778119000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:28:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344779389000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Dems will CORNHOLE GOP this Nov...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1344776508000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:01:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wallis cornholed his sister</Msg><Username>dividiot</Username><Timestamp>1344779389000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:49:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344779580000-12</Id><Title>Apple's next six months</Title><Msg>I am very curious to see what happens in the next six months with Apple, the three things on my watch list. iPad 7"- The Google Nexus 7 is filtering into stores right now between $200 and $250 depending on memory configurations. It's a bit more than a poor man's iPad. It's powered by a Tegra3 and runs the latest version of Android (Jellybean). Apple didn't bother responding to the Kindle Fire but this version is a bit more of a threat to iPad sales. Android is currently growing at four times the rate of the iPhone and Android users may want an Android tablet that is practical and functional. The largest new feature of Jellybean is an enhanced Google Play store which is Android's version of the iTunes store. Risks: Not acting If Apple ignores this segment they could risk losing untold billions in tablet and iTunes sales. Tablets for the most part are consumption devices and a $200 device makes it easier for people to consume non-Apple content. The other risk is that by not acting a growing market develops for the competition and they can have an easier time moving up into the 10" market. For acting: Steve Jobs warned against this move. The problem with a $199 tablet is that it doesn't cost $300 less to make it. There's a lot of profit that is lost with this sale. Also there would be product cannibalization which means that the larger iPad sales would take a hit as some consumers opt for a cheaper iPad. iPhone5- It's not do or die time for iPhone. There are so many people locked into the ecosystem that nearly any upgrade will sell. But the once confident iPhone fan base has grown tired of watching Android phones take the lead with cool features they wished iPhone would have. Will Apple once again set the bar for the industry with a phone far ahead of Android? Or will it be a "me too" phone with most of the features already available from Samsung? If the iPhone5 doesn't satisfy you may find more iPhone users jumping ship over the next couple of years. iPad-My opinion of the iPad has changed recently. I think they were onto something great with iPad and perhaps hit a deadline without new features being ready. My view now is that iPad's objective is to go after Xbox. With the help of some inexpensive adapters and maybe even Thunderbolt iPad may plug into TVs and give the console gaming experience. Will it accept headsets and joysticks? We'll see. The risk XBox has is that you need to be hooked up to a TV to use it. An iPad doesn't need this. I have heard some rumors that XBox is moving toward X86 in it's next generation. Perhaps they see the risk of not going mobile as well. The normal console upgrade cycle has been five years and Xbox 360 has been out for seven years (March 30, 2005). They are running on borrowed time and an iPad gaming system can inflict some damage.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1344779580000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:53:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344782669000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be 10+ percent faster than Ivy Bridge</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344697458000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:04:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"server can never be too fast. Not sure how arm can compete in this area" We'll all find out next year with ARM-64...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344782669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:44:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344783604000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's next six months</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1344779580000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:53:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmm... Apple playing catch-up with 7" tablets... Oh My... "Android is currently growing at four times the rate of the iPhone and Android users may want an Android tablet that is practical and functional." Can any single company compete with the rest of the world's R&amp;D... What is the growth rate for x86 ? What is the growth rate for ARM ?</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344783604000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 11:00:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344787317000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's next six months</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1344779580000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:53:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>About the iPad going after xBox. I've been thinking for a while now that the iPad is much more of a gaming gadget rather than anything else. Definitely one of the weakest computing machines that cannot be taken seriously. So after seeing plenty of talk about how iPad will cannibalize the PC, I've been seeing the cold hard facts of Sony playstations and Nintendo Wi's losing lots of sales. With over 80% of Apple's apps being in gaming, I'm pretty sure that iPad has and may continue to cannibalize video games rather than anything else. It's just the cheapest was of playing as many different games as you want. If it was a replacement for the PC, then we would already see a major move towards ARM based laptops. AMD is the closest competition to Intel based computers, yet many still choose the more expensive Intel. Why? Because in many important computing tasks, performance matters a whole lot. So again, there is a market for iPads and maybe even Google tablets. But for mostly gaming purposes. It just does not make sense to consider them as a replacement for PC. Ultrabook hybrids on the other hand may give the iPad or tablets in general a run for their money. For example, an Ultrabook that can turn into a tablet but costs only a few hundred dollars more than an Ultrabook laptop version makes alot more sense. Having the function of an iPad or other tablet that is 11" or more in size with great performance but much cheaper would eliminate the need for a standalone tablet.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1344787317000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 12:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344791897000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's next six months</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1344779580000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:53:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Steve Jobs warned against this move. The problem with a $199 tablet is that it doesn't cost $300 less to make it. There's a lot of profit that is lost with this sale. Also there would be product cannibalization which means that the larger iPad sales would take a hit as some consumers opt for a cheaper iPad. " true, hoever they don't have a choice, not acting is far more costly. imo</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1344791897000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 13:18:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344793765000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Great Read</Title><Username>javierkdc521</Username><Timestamp>1344778503000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:35:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the site</Msg><Username>feneliadow578</Username><Timestamp>1344793765000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 13:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344795024000-18</Id><Title>Hey Wally, want me to post you saying......</Title><Msg>..........actually, it was you CRUSHING people for posting political stuff here. Then, being the complete liberal hypocrite that you are, you do what you condemn. Lying, hypocritical, Liberal Scumbag.</Msg><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1344795024000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>36</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344795481000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be 10+ percent faster than Ivy Bridge</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344697458000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:04:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Though still some years from “must have” status" From lead architect Oct 2011 ARM TechCon Presentation last year. Do you have any idea what features the lead guy was talking about "some years" away in his Oct 2011 presentation? http://www.arm.com/files/downloads/ARMv8_Architecture.pdf On page 19, "ARM architecture has a Weak memory model" because "Good for energy". Six months later, ARM figured out the problems with weak memory modeling in servers and addressed the problem. http://herbsutter.com/2012/08/02/strong-and-weak-hardware-memory-models/ Page 19: "load-acquire/store-release instructions" Check out the Intel Itanium instruction set. The more I read, the more familiar this looks. It will be very hard for ARMv8 to everything right the first time. If they do, they deserve a lot of credit.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1344795481000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:18:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344813083000-20</Id><Title>A Brief History of Semiconductor IP</Title><Msg>"ARM has done a similar transformation of the microprocessor market blindsiding even the mightiest of semiconductor companies Intel Corporation. ARM also enabled the SoC revolution with a more balanced business model of upfront license fees, royalty revenue from every chip sold by customers incorporating ARM IP, and revenues from related development tools and customer support. Today the resulting ARM ecosystem is second to none which makes the David and Goliath battle against Intel for mobile, laptop, and cloud SoCs a fair fight....." http://www.semiwiki.com/forum/content/1564-history-semiconductor-ip-brief.html</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1344813083000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:11:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344813572000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Dems will CORNHOLE GOP this Nov...</Title><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1344776508000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:01:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agreed................ This guy (jerry_cornholed_you) is a real freakshow. Liberal gay Dem. I'll bet Barney Frank is his idol!</Msg><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1344813572000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344814873000-22</Id><Topic><Title>A Brief History of Semiconductor IP</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1344813083000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:11:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD always was a flash company. One of AMD's founding technology leaders is back in the AMD fold, Jim Keller, a leading architect for K6-K9 series of advanced microprocessors.</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1344814873000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344815804000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcomm Acquires Intel's Playbook</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1344628056000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Qualcomm acquired a hack foreigner that couldn't cut it at Intel." as in knife play in the spirit of Crocadile Dundee exiting the hotel with girlfriend biographer, "That's not a knife - this is a knife," ??</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1344815804000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:56:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344816171000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Gap widening between INTC and AMD</Title><Username>v_shukla72</Username><Timestamp>1344510538000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 07:08:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uhh, don't fall in love with a stock ? http://finance.yahoo.com/q/ta?s=AMD&amp;t=5y&amp;l=on&amp;z=l&amp;q=l&amp;p=&amp;a=&amp;c=intc</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1344816171000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:02:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344816181000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Wally, want me to post you saying......</Title><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1344795024000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:10:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well I think his political posts are EXCELLENT, you deceitfull, disgusting, ignorant REPUBLISCUM!</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1344816181000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344818179000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be 10+ percent faster than Ivy Bridge</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344697458000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:04:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've always maintained ARMH is a rubber stamp...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344818179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:36:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344821354000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be 10+ percent faster than Ivy Bridge</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344697458000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:04:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel will always be a few steps ahead.</Msg><Username>starbauch</Username><Timestamp>1344821354000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344822275000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Buy or Sell</Title><Username>fedorapfh045</Username><Timestamp>1344791241000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 13:07:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Expecting more news</Msg><Username>petejpc897</Username><Timestamp>1344822275000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344824966000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Wally, want me to post you saying......</Title><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1344795024000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:10:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You think his posts are EXCELLENT.........because you're Wally. Wallisweaver = Gay Liberal = all the cornhole and amd monkeyroadkill aliases. Total freak.</Msg><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1344824966000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:29:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344826115000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Just A Weekend Thought</Title><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1344669977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 03:26:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"For now, it's probably not a good idea to make big bets in a thinly traded market." Juxtapose the phrases, "The trend is your friend," and "Its not over until the fat lady sings (volume?)."</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1344826115000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:48:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344826920000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Curiously, TSMC</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1344624943000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:55:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those chips are getting so big they may as well be the router when eventually the routers become the system.</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1344826920000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 23:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344827045000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be 10+ percent faster than Ivy Bridge</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344697458000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:04:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It will be very hard for ARMv8 to everything right the first time. If they do, they deserve a lot of credit." Agree... but they will have the rest of the world helping them with the definition of 64-ISA... Plus many companies, NVidia, AMCC, etc... will be designing their own ARM64 CPUs... and finally go beyond what ARMH ever could...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344827045000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 23:04:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344827789000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be 10+ percent faster than Ivy Bridge</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344697458000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:04:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Not sure how arm can compete in this area with their lukewarm chips." That dry sense of humor suggests low power results in lukewarm chips.</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1344827789000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 23:16:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344828354000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be 10+ percent faster than Ivy Bridge</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1344697458000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:04:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With a mere dongle the Hollerith IBM 80 column punchcards would be faster than Ivy Bridge.</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1344828354000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 23:25:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>